Sponsored by: Ministry of the Navy
The Battle of the Malay Sea
War Movies
Yokohama Cinema Works
RAW acquisition: Anonymoose
Translation: Perevodildo
Editing: Paul Geromini
Crush the Unsinkable Ship
December 8th
On December 8th, 1941,
the Rubicon was crossed.
We entered a state of war with our archenemies,
the Anglo-Saxon nations.
Early on this day, our elite troops landed in front of the enemy at Kota Bharu and Singora on the Malay Peninsula.
At this time, the main force of the enemy's British Oriental Fleet, stationed in Singapore,
urgently sailed north to attack our troops.
Upon receiving that intel, our fearless submarine fleet
was dispatched to intercept and destroy it.
Searching for the enemy ship
To the Malay Sea!
Waiting for good news...
Our soldiers were awaiting some good news.
With sleeves rolled up and hearts pounding,
they waited patiently for good news.
It was the calm before the storm.
They watched their chances
diminish by the minute.
No, their chances still hadn't peaked.
"Say it... Say it!"
Enemy ship!
Enemy ship! Enemy ship!
December 9th
Exactly at 15:15 on December 9th.
Enemy ship!
Enemy ship! They found it!
They've discovered the enemy Oriental Fleet.
Enemy ship!
Our archenemy has taken the bait and is coming.
That's right. That's what we trained for.
That's what we trained for!
Enemy ship!
Our front line soldiers have gained a foothold already.
Let's go!
And come back alive!
Impossible to see anything in this squall.
It's as though the sun had disappeared altogether.
There were low rain clouds on the sea,
and we couldn't see anything.
Unfortunately, we had to return to the base.
The squall has cleared up,
but there are no enemy ships in sight.
We missed our big catch.
The heroes of the sky and the heroes of the sea
drank from the cup of frustration that day.
At dawn on December 10th,
the enemy ships were discovered once more.
Oh, look! The gigantic ship advancing arrogantly.
The British Empire boasted it to the world as unsinkable.
35,000 long tons, Prince of Wales.
Bow armament: one quadruple and one twin 14-inch gun turret.
Stern armament: one quadruple 14-inch gun turret.
A total of 10 main caliber guns.
There are also 16 anti-aircraft batteries.
And four seaplane catapults.
Among them, the most vaunted QF 2-pounder "pom-pom" gun.
Combined, the ship can fire
60,000 rounds a minute.
An unsinkable battleship.
The Prince of Wales is a giant ship of the British Empire,
brandished to the world with arrogance.
And what is that other battleship?
You can tell by its special mast.
Weighing 32,000 long tons,
the second battleship is Repulse.
The main armament is a 15-inch gun.
4 forward, 2 aft.
6 in total.
With 12 triple barreled anti-aircraft guns,
and four seaplane catapults.
Its cruising speed ​​is 31 knots.
It's the fast battleship Repulse. Repulse!
Found the enemy ships!
As soon as we receive this news,
our strategy is immediately put into action.
Plane No. 3 of the long-range recon squadron finally reached the designated point,
but couldn't find the enemy fleet.
They were running low on fuel.
Oh! It's the enemy!
We found their fleet!
103°50′E
4°N
Found the enemy ships!
Plane No. 3 of the long-range recon squadron
was running low on fuel.
Found the enemy ships!
But they persisted.
They knew they had to hold out until our attack aircraft arrived.
Found the enemy ships!
Push on!
Don't give up, Plane No. 3!
Found the enemy ships!
Hey, it's our friends!
Friends!
Our planes are here!
More...
And more of them.
Loaded with bombs,
with the torpedoes underneath.
They're the angels of victory we've been waiting for!
They'll hammer the sea!
Can see the enemy fleet!
Oh, it's the enemy!
Looks like the Prince of Wales!
The British vaunt it as the unsinkable battleship,
but that's only because no one's sunk it yet.
That's right, let's sink it!
Let's sink it!
Now’s the time to show them
the Japanese spirit of achieving the impossible!
It's up to us to sink Repulse!
Sink Repulse!
It's a hit! We've hit Repulse!
Repulse caught fire!
The mast has fallen!
It's burning! Burning! It's on fire!
Repulse is on fire!
It's burning here too!
We've scored a hit on "Wales!"
Miserable and wretched,
trying to run away—
such is the fate of the pride of Britain's Oriental Fleet, with which she intended to "rule the waves" on the seven seas.
"Wales" is burning,
finish off Repulse!
Prince of Wales is sinking.
Repulse is sinking!
It's the end of Prince of Wales,
and the end of Repulse!
It submerged underwater!
It's going down!
No, it's still too early to rejoice.
The first ship is still afloat.
That's right, the first ship.
We still have the "Wales" to sink!
Don't let "Wales" escape!
It's got nowhere to escape now!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot at the "Wales!"
Shoot at the "Wales!"
It's over, both our engines caught fire.
They caught fire!
We haven't fired our torpedo yet.
Still haven't fired. Still haven't fired!
There, it's fired.
Yes, the machine marches forward.
It marches steadily forward!
Right on course.
Right on course. Right on course!
The smoking ships, the setting sun,
the torpedoes, fired by our heroic comrades...
Behold!
Another one scored!
The water column rose high!
We got "Wales!"
"Wales" is listing!
The man deck is underwater!
She' taking water!
We got her! We got her!
So much for the the "unsinkable battleship!"
But are you sure it will sink?
Yes, it's sinking!
It's sinking!
"Wales" finally opened fire from her 14-inch guns.
They opened fire with all the guns on board.
Okay, let's deal the final blow!
The final blow!
Fallen and devastated, the enemy's Oriental Fleet
Off of Kuantan, on the Malay Peninsula,
It is sinking
Prince of Wales sunk!
It was you, our fearless and glorious Sea Eagles,
who sunk the Repulse, who sunk the Prince of Wales
Britain's pride, with which she intended to rule the waves,
Prince of Wales is finally sunk!
No, we sunk it!
Let us remember, let us remember
this day for eternity
Who sank the unsinkable battleship?
It was us, the Imperial Navy!
That's right, it was our Naval Air Corps.
We wiped out the enemy warships
that came our way in one fell swoop
That's right, it was us—
the Sea Eagles—who sank her!
That's right, it was us—the Sea Eagles!
The Sea Eagles!
Three days into the war, and we're already victorious!
Sink, Repulse
Sink, Prince of Wales!
The End