Twilight of the Cockroaches
Good evening. I'm...
I'm looking for Hans...
My name is Naomi.
I'm nineteen months,
in cockroach years.
Until that day,
I had never experienced
such terror or bloodthirstiness.
Ichiro!
No... I guess I just can't do it.
You're doing a bit better than before.
The training at the Cockroach Center
must be paying off.
I quit that.
You did?
I felt like an idiot there.
What kind of cockroach goes on all six like...
...in this day and age?
Ichiro, stop it!
Right, listen, Naomi,
I hear tonight's dinner is Italian cuisine.
Saito's such a gourmand,
and I guess he knows our tastes too.
Chinese food yesterday,
steak the day before that...
I bet he feels like eating pasta tonight!
And maybe even...
Saito-san?
Good evening!
Let's go.
Yeah. Thanks for the meal!
By the way, I've finally found it.
Well, the smell of late night is here on my back again
Listen, Naomi.
The south wall in that room is all glass.
You knew we'd be going in circles, but it's all right!
And there's plants hanging from the ceiling.
It's incredibly chic.
You see the happy me and jump in when you see an opportunity
It's just right for a loving couple.
Right...
I think living in a bright place like that
is the most snobbish thing to do now.
We dance the night away, just dream of Rock & Roll
What's wrong?
Well, you've decided to be an innocent woman
If you don't want to hear about it...
But you're already showing that you want to throw out and leave
No... Not at all.
It sounds nice.
Hi, my cockroach friend!
Baby, good luck!
You're so unbelievable
You groom me into the kind of man you like, and then you run away
But really, you're on the fast track, Ichiro!
A job at the national intelligence center,
and you're Leader's second assistant!
Just Dream of Rock & Roll.
The world's your oyster, huh?
My dad's got connections.
At dawn, twisted and left behind, I see right through
You didn't have to remind me.
This tomato sauce is marvelous! It's perfect!
Wouldn't it be nice to eat this
every day, eh, Parsley-chan?
to the depths of my heart, Crazy Dance
Yeah, I like it too.
Isn't it just ordinary ketchup?
Let me keep dreaming like this a little more
Come on, Takashi.
This is what makes you a cockroach.
You should try training at the Cockroach Center.
Maybe you'll learn a thing or two.
Let me ride on without waking up for a while
Maybe you should.
Oh... Evening, Saito-sama.
Suddenly remembering something, I started laughing at you
We'll be closing up soon.
Sorry for the inconvenience...
Do you want to show me your own world, Crazy Cat?
And yet...
Wasn't that tasty?
Just look at yourselves!
Watch where you're going!
You call yourselves cockroaches?
Cavorting in the middle of the road...
Right, right. You're absolutely right, Nakai-san.
It's late, isn't it?
Hey kids, don't take offense, okay?
Well then, take care.
And go straight home!
Stay with me tonight.
Ready.
Do you want to meet Naomi?
It will happen.
You'll see her before long.
What can we do, Kan-san? Right?
These days, everyone's so "proud
to be a cockroach..." I just don't get it!
If you ask me... Huh?
Oh! If it isn't Gosuke-san...
Master...
Shouldn't you be in bed already?
Come on, let's get going.
Really, Master...
If something were to happen to you,
we'd all be in dire straits! Right...
Huh?
That's creepy...
You'd better get to bed soon.
Ichiro! Ichi...
Hey, um...
Excuse me?
Um...
If I may ask who you are...
Um... Hello?
Hello?
He's one of them.
From the distant land across the field
that I always gaze at from my window.
I'd never been there before, but my grandfather had told me stories about it ever since I was little.
About how it was so different from our country.
It was more dangerous.
The legendary land where brave
cockroach warriors fought in endless battle.
I'd never seen anyone like this mysterious man.
Ichiro, however, reported it
to the information center.
Ichiro, what happened to that man?
Did they arrest him?
Ah, don't worry. The sub-leader said
they'd give him a warm welcome.
It's not often that we get refugees here, after all.
What do you think happened to him?
A war, they said.
A war?
With cats?
With humans.
Huh?
Humans, like Saito-san?
I wouldn't know.
Maybe they messed up big time to earn that.
By the way, Naomi, have you picked out
your costume for the ceremony?
It's already around the corner!
Ah, I was going to choose one today with Parsley.
You're making the clothier wait.
May I interrupt?
L-Leader!
Kiichiro, was it?
I-Ichiro, sir.
Ah, right, you're Ichiro.
Greetings, Ichiro!
Greetings, sir.
Greetings, miss.
Now then...
Regarding that man from last night, Hans...
Y-Yes?
He's very impressed with our reception.
You did great work.
Great work, sir?
Yeah. Especially since today
is Armistice Commemoration Day.
Going live!
Let's roll!
Standby... 4... 3... 2... 1...
Cue!
Good morning, everyone.
There's blue skies above, and it's time
for our monthly Armistice Commemoration Day.
It's been 36 months since that terrible war ended.
In today's peaceful and prosperous times,
it is easy to forget the valuable experiences of our people,
but we'd like to look back on them together with you all.
Our great Leader has come to the studio
to join us today.
Greetings, fair citizens.
I'm such a fan of yours, Professor.
Do you mind if I call you Professor?
Sadly, we don't have much time.
So without further ado,
we'd like Leader to tell us the story.
Please, sir.
It was a terrible time
that overthrew the natural order.
Bitter hatred divided Cockroach and Man.
And it was we, the roaches, who were to blame.
The residents of this space before Saito-san,
the Hosono family, lived in peace,
until we, the roaches, invaded.
Eventually, leaving behind the corpses
of many of our fallen,
the Hosono family moved away.
Still a young man then,
standing in this town of death,
I vowed in my heart to uphold peace forever.
And that is when the new resident,
Saito-san, appeared.
He sympathized with cockroaches.
He became our benefactor.
Saito-san,
the cockroach people swear a grave oath.
We will live quietly and discreetly,
only helping ourselves to human leftovers.
My friends.
We must never repeat the mistakes of the past.
As long as we are devoted to peace,
humans will reciprocate our feelings.
Today, as you all can see,
we enjoy lives of peace in our beautiful country.
But I want to remind all of you...
Not all cockroaches on this earth
enjoy this kind of happy and carefree life.
I'd like you to meet one young man.
He came to us from a sorrowful,
dark country very far away.
Hans-san, you say you were almost killed,
and just barely made it to safety?
Yes.
How many of our own
do you think are dying every single day?
Hundreds, maybe?
Oh my! That many!
Are they also mostly getting crushed underfoot?
Yes.
Crushed in bloodlust, burned without mercy,
and savagely torn apart! Hundreds fall every day!
Hans-san, could you please
show the audience your scars?
Goodness! That must have hurt.
Cameraman, can we get a close-up?
How awful!
How heartless must one be
to do something like that?
Now, back to you, Professor!
Once again, many thanks to Saito-san.
Many thanks to Saito-san...
Ready! Go!
Number 1, ready! Go!
Failed! Next!
Number 2, ready!
Go!
He did it!
Passed!
Incredible!
You love Ichiro, don't you?
Well, he's not bad...
We've been together for long.
He's so nice and loving!
Ah!
The toilet roaches are here again!
Every so often, they come here looking for girls,
covered in shit from head to toe.
I think...
I'm going to the Birth Center next month.
Huh? Again?
It's my first litter from Yasuo!
Having all those children will kill you, Parsley.
I haven't...
even once...
Grandpa?
It's me, Naomi.
I'm coming in.
Hans?
Hans!
Why are you here?
I mean...
Not so loud.
Um...
Go into the kitchen.
Goodbye.
Hans... Hans!
He's going back...
Back to that awful place?
Just as he had escaped it?
Naomi.
This man is risking his life.
His life?
That night, Grandpa told me a very long story.
It was about my grandma,
who died a long time ago.
One day, after the war had ended,
when she was about my age,
grandma came to this country all by herself.
When she met my grandpa,
she already had a litter inside her.
And...
the place she had come from...
That was...
the country across the field
that Hans was now returning to.
You seen Naomi today?
Yeah. Not long ago.
It seems she wanted to be left alone.
Whoa there!
Let's go check it out!
We'll be married real soon.
What's wrong?
You don't like this room?
You decide.
Naomi!
Hey!
What're you doing way out here?
A turd!
How disgustingly prejudiced!
I'm sorry.
Huh? Say, don’t suppose you have any connection
with that young man I saw here not long ago?
Yes.
I see.
Well, he went that way. That way.
Wh-What? She left?
Where'd she go?
I don't know.
That answer won't do!
We're all having kittens
with the wedding ceremony coming up.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
Naomi...
Naomi!
Tsk. Did you get a look at who it was?
Some fool who doesn't know when to run
and hides in a place like that.
Did you sound the alarm?
Hurry!
Prepare to move out!
Yes, sir!
Jochen!
Sir!
Target #1.
Dieter!
Sir!
Target #2.
Hans!
Sir!
Target #3.
Troops...
move out!
Hans!
Hans... Hans!
Keep quiet, you!
Hans!
After me.
Go!
Now!
Charge!
Okay, go in!
Come on! Hurry!
Faster!
Go! Go!
Keep going!
Come on, Fritz!
C'mon... Let the others have some too!
At ease.
Commander...
Let me go after target #1 next time, please.
You were chosen by the chief.
Don't be in a hurry to die.
You're taking too long!
Hurry it up!
Hans!
Today, we face a cataclysmic crisis.
Greedy humans are trying to snatch the riches
that belonged to us for millions of years.
They ejected us from Eden
and now they want to destroy us down to the last roach.
Meanwhile, we cockroaches
have never killed a single human.
Why, then?
Why is that?
Why is man so devoted to our destruction?
It is because he fears us cockroaches!
God chose us roaches
to be the true rulers of this earth.
We can live where the humans can't.
We can eat what they can't stomach.
Unlike man, we're in tune with nature.
And above all, we take pride in being cockroaches ourselves and in defending our race.
Let them kill us if they wish!
For every 100 killed, we'll breed 10,000 more!
If they kill 10,000, we'll breed a million!
In the end, we cockroaches will always prevail!
Hey, time to change the watch.
Okay. Where's the commander?
Who knows?
I'm scared...
I'm with you, and yet...
I'm...
scared.
scared too.
Ever since then, Hans went into battle every day.
Many of his comrades died.
But Hans always returned.
He'd done that
hundreds of times since he was a child.
"I'm still alive...
I'm still alive!"
He'd whisper it to me every night.
2.35 meters! Next!
Number eight, ready!
He can't do it.
Ready!
Next! What's the hold up?
I know that Naomi will come back!
Let's still hold the ceremony tomorrow.
I know Naomi, so...
Look, Ichiro...
All the Center's top brass are going to be
at your wedding ceremony tomorrow.
What are you going to do
if she doesn't show up after all, huh?
I'll quit working at the Center.
Oh, come on.
Ichiro, say that again.
Look into your father's eyes
and say it again.
We'll do it.
Not you too...
Don't be late!
W-Wait a minute.
What's going on? You want me to stand there
in the middle of everything, embarrassing myself?
We're friends, aren't we?
B-But I am the Leader of this country.
Fool.
Have you really never been embarrassed before?
Hm?
Oh, so you haven't?
Reporting for duty—two of us, sir.
If I may...
Please leave him alone.
You'll jinx the captain.
Let's go, Fritz.
COCKROACH
HOUSE
Hans! Han...
N-Naomi!
Naomi...
I knew it!
Naomi!
It's going to be a lovely ceremony.
Still... Something's wrong with her, I can tell.
Did you talk to Ichiro?
Yeah.
He says she doesn't remember anything.
Maybe she's been through some trauma?
D-Don't you tell her what happened to Parsley!
I wouldn't. Today's a happy day.
Smile! C'mon, smile!
She's been missing for three weeks!
That's a secret, got it?
We've not heard from her grandfather either...
She's so reckless!
Oh, by the way, you heard
what happened this morning?
Three of our own were found dead!
Ah, must be those nasty delinquents again.
Probably fighting amongst themselves.
Not at all!
They were found smashed
by some immense force,
tangled in strange cloth,
and thrown into the trash.
He still isn't here?
The Professor?
His meeting is running late, it seems.
What a fool.
Almighty God,
Prophet Tora...
souls of our ancestors, harken...
Before us today stand Ichiro and Naomi,
who have willingly chosen to be joined
in matrimony for the sake of their offspring...
You two can touch feelers now.
"I hereby take you..."
I...
hereby take you
a-as my wedded wife.
I hereby take you as...
What is it?
It's her!
What's going on?
Run!
Quick! This way! This way!
We'll be crushed!
Hey, please hurry!
Today, I offer condolences
to the victims and their families.
From what we know so far,
it seems the human responsible for this attack
has already left our country.
Presently, Saito-san is out as well.
We believe he's gone in pursuit of her.
Who will take responsibility for this?!
The fact that he did not consult with us
about the entrance
of such a dangerous entity
into our country is a major issue.
I intend to meet with Saito-san
tomorrow already,
and make sure he knows
that this must never happen again!
Ichiro!
Yasuo, Takashi?
Naomi.
Grandpa...
A curfew is in effect.
Please return home at once!
But... I'm telling you, we're in a state of emergency...
I'm not going to stand for this
"state of emergency" excuse!
You're violating our civil rights.
But it's dangerous out there!
It's that kind of thinking that's the real danger!
Hey!
How are things looking?
Business as usual, it seems.
Good. Don't be so tense, then!
Now, let's go!
Look, guys...
Come on, let's go!
Yes, don't be shy!
It's a good workout!
Maybe some other time?
Come on, show more confidence!
You're in good health!
Careful down there!
Let's go!
Wow!
So cool!
What's going on?
What are they doing?!
What is he doing?
COCKROACH
HOUSE
When we were little, we always had to do it like this, in the middle of the night.
Doesn't scare me one bit.
Me neither!
That's just what cockroaches are.
Yes, that's how it should be.
B-But we have a right to a life of comfort!
Don't be stupid!
B-But humans used to love cockroaches.
Who is the idiot who told you that?
Th-The Professor!
He was only leading you by the nose. Right?
All lies.
Well, I don't like to speak ill of the dead,
but then again, I couldn't
say anything while he was still alive.
Wh-What do you mean?
Listen up.
Since long before our grandparents' time,
we've always been
slaughtered without restraint. Right?
That's right!
Even though cockroaches
never did anything wrong,
they just didn't like how we looked.
More than anything, the biggest lie of all
was about the Hosono Family
that lived here before.
Professor made the whole thing up!
Saito-san was the head of the Hosono family
before his wife left him.
Back when he had a woman in his life,
he was already killing us in droves.
But when she left him,
he suddenly became very slack.
That's when he started being nice to us.
But why did Professor lie to us?
He never knew the truth.
That's right.
He spent the whole war hiding above the ceiling.
He only met Saito-san after his wife had left.
I couldn't...
find Yasuo-san.
Just this evening, when I was dozing off,
I had a dream.
I saw us in the moonlit field...
And everyone was dead.
Only you and I were standing there.
Parsley and Yasuo were dead.
Parsley's children too...
Parsley...
It's straight ahead, about 2.5m away.
I could do it with my eyes shut.
Now, watch a real cockroach in action.
All set, Kan-san?
Here I go.
Sh-She's seen him!
No, she hasn't.
Focus on the dropped food.
That's roachcraft 101—
move along the black things.
Yes. Make no sound.
What's that?
That's him showing off.
They've found the entrance!
Ichiro! To the plaza!
Okay!
Please calm down!
You're safe here!
Don't go home until it's all over!
We're on the trail.
We'll be there tomorrow at dawn.
We arrive at sunrise.
Heed the words of our chief!
Men!
Never again will we have
to starve and writhe in hunger.
From tomorrow on, it's full bellies for all!
To victory!
Captain.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Grandpa...
I'm...
I'm pregnant.
But...
I don't think the litter is Ichiro's.
More likely it's both.
Ichiro's honest.
Hans is strong.
Listen, Naomi...
Tomorrow night,
when the waning moon rises in the sky,
come here alone.
What will you do?
Come alone.
Okay.
Steady your soul.
Slow down and feel at peace.
Then talk to Tora.
Say, "I am Naomi,
your namesake."
Takashi...
Takashi!
Time to change the watch.
Oh, right...
Fall in line!
Squad 1 lined up!
Good!
Squad 2 lined up!
Strike up the marching song!
We are the cockroaches!
We are the cockroaches...
If one is crushed...
If one is crushed!
Ten will arise...
Ten will arise!
If ten are poisoned...
If ten are poisoned!
A hundred will take flight...
A hundred will take flight!
We are the cockroaches...
We are the cockroaches!
Halt the singing!
Wh-What's this?
Is this... Na-Naomi? Hm?
Naomi? Naomi!
Naomi!
Is that true?
We don't have anything.
Just look at how we live!
You probably thought we still had all that delicious stuff
back from when we saved you...
Fine.
We'll join forces to attack
the humans together and drive them out!
Long live the chief!
Hans!
Yes, Chief?
Long live the chief!
It's been a long time, Master.
You've grown so big, Alois.
I've come to bid farewell.
My job is done.
Tora's prophecy is fulfilled.
Many will die.
You taught me never to be sentimental.
Your hope lies with that young man, Hans.
So you knew already?
Hans will be the last man standing
on the mountain of the dead.
Alois.
You raised Hans,
but you didn't love him.
That's why you overlooked one thing.
Halt!
I have an urgent matter here!
Let me through!
Th-The chief is meeting someone there.
This is urgent!
W-Wait...
Naomi!
Hey, Naomi!
So that's...
what it was?
Hans,
I'm going to survive this.
I...
don't know.
If we meet again,
we can settle things then.
Squad 4, go!
Squad 5, go!
We're coming along.
Don't.
Keep it up!
Wait! Not so fast!
Wait!
Wait, you hear?!
Charge!
Dive down!
Under the fumes!
We're landing, Fritz!
Stay here awhile, you two.
Hans, where are you?
Here, Chief!
Escape now.
You must survive.
Yes, Chief.
All these deaths have been for your sake.
Go!
Oh! Captain!
This way, Fritz!
Naomi!
Naomi.
Close your eyes and count to 100.
You too.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Six...
Seven.
Seven...
Eight.
Nine...
Naomi!
I am Naomi.
I am your namesake.
Naomi...
Naomi.
Who's there?
Naomi!
N-Naomi!
C'mon, get up. You're safe now.
Come on, hurry! Hurry!
Naomi...
Naomi.
Who's there?
I am Naomi.
I am your grandmother.
Listen to me.
It was to refine our breed,
to shape us into the ultimate survivors,
that God bestowed deadly poisons upon those bloodthirsty humans.
Cockroaches are always being slaughtered,
and only the strongest,
who can endure the poison, survive.
Humans tried many different poisons
to wipe out those survivors as well.
I, who could not be killed by any poison,
and two strong males were the only survivors.
Now you also know about the ruthless methods
with which God chooses
his "last survivor."
Naomi,
you're the last hope for all the fallen cockroaches.
Like I did, you must test your own strength.
Ichiro,
meet me at Tora's feet.
Tora's?
Run!
Naomi!
I... I flew!
I'm flying!
The soap bubbles reach my tiny hands
How far do the clouds go?
My mother answers kindly
The soap bubbles reach my tiny hands
Eventually, with the passage of time, my thoughts close away
The slippery memories are so far away now,
I can never go back
WOWmd
Batty
R1 DVD
Perevodildo
Marty Mcflies (LonelyChaser fansubs)
Paul Geromini
Encoding
LD provider
Original translation
Translation check
Quality check