This work is a doujin anime, an attempt at new forms of expression.
Additionally, this work is fiction and has no relation to any real people, groups, or existing works.
Furthermore, this work was created for private viewing purposes only.
Reproduction or public screening without the author's permission is prohibited by law.
Those under 18 are forbidden from purchasing or viewing.
Witch Girl Knights
The Movie
For Adults
Encoding
CLAP-Raws
Translation
Quality check
Perevodildo
Anonymous
Ah... Who'd think they'd take us to Tsutenkaku
for a modern social studies field trip?
It is a bit unusual, isn't it?
Right! Seriously, our school is so annoying.
Whoa! Hey, check this out!
It's amazing!
You look happy...
Just look already!
Oh, please, what can it be?
Yes! That's good!
GREENGROCER
Ma'am...
Deeper, push it in deeper!
GREENGROCER
Right? Right? It's amazing, isn't it?
Help!
Please help us.
Save our world...
P-Please!
The legendary Witch Knights
save our wo—
H-Hey, wait... save you from what?
What should we do?
Where are we?
What is this place?
Where on earth is this?
And so, the three of us were summoned
to the magical world by the princess's power.
We became the legendary Witch Girl Knights
and fought against the demons.
To rescue the princess captured by the Demon King
and to save this magical world.
We've finally made it this far.
The princess is being held there, right?
We can't turn back now.
Alright, let's go!
Princess!
You've come, Witch Girl Knights...
Oh, so you are the legendary Witch Girl Knights?
You're still just kids.
Poor things.
If only you hadn't stuck your noses in.
Well, well, what's wrong, Witch Girl Knights?
Is this the first time you've seen a man's cock?
Perfect timing.
I'm gonna let you taste it plenty now!
Let go, you...
W-Wait... No! I don't want it! Stop!
Here, savor this properly.
This is horrible!
They're still just children!
Once they've been violated by us,
they lose their qualifications as Witch Girl Knights.
If you want us to stop,
you'll have to try harder.
No... Let's stop for a minute, okay?
Wait...
Hey... At least put on a condom, you idiot!
This mouth looks bored.
Instead of screaming, get to sucking this.
What the hell is with these guys?
Stop! What are you doing?!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Here, now taste this.
Please... forgive us...
Don't be stupid, the real fun is just starting.
That's right.
We're gonna enjoy you girls thoroughly.
No...
Really, you're already this wet?
Guess you gotta serve us even more then.
No!
Please forgive them, I beg you!
Not enough yet. Next is your ass.
Come on, put it in yourself.
Y-Yes...
Something this big could never fit...
I've pumped a huge load inside.
Take a look, Witch Girl Knights!
Even the princess you came to rescue
at such great risk
is now being violated by demons
and moaning like a whore.
You should just give up
and enjoy the pleasure too.
Please... You're gonna break me!
P-Princess...
No way...
Look, she's covered in cum from head to toe!
At this point, I've made up my mind.
I'll jerk you off as much as you want.
You can come inside!
Now... give me even more!
Wh-What the...
Give me more!
Ridiculous... So the Witch Girl Knights
were his trigger?!
Thank you, Witch Girl Knights.
Thanks to you releasing this little one's power,
this world has been saved!
Farewell, legendary Witch Girl Knights.
Wh-Where are we?
It seems we've returned to where we were.
We made it back to our world!
Thank goodness!
No way...
No!
This is terrible!
THE END
How did you like it?
Since doujin anime is still an unestablished genre, there were all sorts of challenges, but we somehow managed to complete it.
In the making of this work, we received tremendous cooperation from everyone involved.
Thank you so much.
From now on, we want to continue our activities believing in the bright future of doujins.
-Morally Dubious Gang