EDO, Retklaad Disasmount has completed
his mission and safely returned from Fedvar.
Well done, Retklaad.
Of course. I'm glad I was able to be of service.
This has been a blessing in disguise.
Thanks to this accident, we can now definitely prevent
the destruction of Fedvar's environment.
EDO should be pleased with that.
EDO, in light of recent events, we'd like
to appoint a new administrator to Fedvar.
I understand. We shall select
the most fitting candidate by tomorrow.
Of course!
Really though, that was excellent work, Retklaad.
No. All I did was fulfill my duty, that's all.
Sure, but that duty wasn't for the faint of heart.
But you did it for the good of the world
and its people. I hope you know that.
I do.
Still, Retklaad, are you sure this
won't be discovered later?
Please don't worry about that.
There's no evidence to use against me.
EDO's system is safe, for now.
Let's hurry up and forget about Fedvar.
Oh, look at that.
The cherry trees are in full bloom.
Throughout the ages, the cherry blossoms
have retained their beauty.
Speaking of cherry blossoms,
how is your oh-so-beloved son Gold doing, Retklaad?
Your sarcasm is obvious.
I disowned him five years ago.
By now, he's probably dying a dog's death
by the roadside somewhere.
This era is ruled by a massive
computer named EDO.
Constructed through international cooperation,
it connects Japan's cities and space colonies.
EDO's job is to decide on the best policy
for a given situation.
Its work is overseen by five consuls.
What's going on?!
Wh-Who are you?!
Retklaad Disasmount...
The graveyard of the cosmos brought me
back to life as a vengeful spirit.
Y-You... It can't be!
Die!
Toyama Sakura Space Chronicles
His Name is Gold
My first and last confession
Didn't go as I had hoped
I can't just say that I love you
Getting on my bike, parked in the shade
I need to cool my head off
Girls who don't cry
Here we go. I'm going all in.
Are always the first to lose in love
Hey, now! Haven't you had enough tonight?
Cool guys in TV dramas always hit the jackpot at
the last moment, turning the tables for a happy ending.
Being strong-willed is a minus
Yeah, but real life isn't so forgiving.
It's not cute at all
I'm starting to hate myself a bit
Are you sure about this?
I'm sure.
I'll get the last laugh.
In this twilight of dreams
I wonder about that.
You're on!
I should act more grown up
See, what did I tell you about real life, Gold?
But I'm so sentimental
Th-That's not fair!
I'm honored.
This brought me to my senses.
I'll never gamble again.
That's what you said yesterday.
Oh shut up, you old bastard!
Gimme a drink!
Don't worry about it. I've still got enough
to buy myself a drink. See?
Are you new here?
Yes.
I see. They call me Gold. What do they call you?
Gold!
Hey, Midi. That was a lovely song.
Thanks. Did you lose all your money again?
Yeah. I can only buy one drink tonight.
Ah, this is the new bartender.
He's a nice guy, even if he doesn't say much.
Better than a guy like me
who never shuts up.
Anyway, the bar is about to close,
so how about a date with a stunning beauty?
Huh? A stunning beauty?!
Where? Where? Where? Where's this beauty?
Midi, you've got to tell me! Please!
Where is this stunning beauty? This beauty...
Hey, Midi... I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
I didn't mean it like that!
I don't care.
Yo! Gold!
Doing good?
Far from it!
Why's that? You lost big at gambling?
Like you even care!
Women and games don't mix well!
Idiot, what are y—
Did you say something?
Gold never changes.
Cheer up and try again!
Try not to get dumped this time!
Thanks, guys.
Don't work too hard now!
Come on, Midi.
Isn't it time to forgive me already?
Maybe I will!
But you owe me a proper date tonight. Deal?
Y-Yeah...
Finally, it's just the two of us...
Hey, Midi, what were you doing in Downtown?
What were you doing there?
Me?
That face tattoo is just makeup, isn't it?
You shouldn't ask about people's pasts
like that in this town.
We all carry scars we don't want to be asked about.
I'm sorry, Midi.
Looks like I brought the mood down.
Thank you.
Huh?
I'm glad you were here...
to hear me out.
H-Hey! Someone might see us here.
Nobody ever comes here anymore.
But I see someone coming our way right now.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
You bastards have been following us like stink on shit!
If you're after money, I'm broke!
You're not average thieves, are you?
Midi, I need you to step back for a moment.
No, I'm scared!
Oh, no!
Y-You idiot!
I can't move if you do that!
It's my turn now!
Ouch!
So you're all androids?
Then I don't need to hold back.
You're not even human!
I'll cut you to pieces!
All right, your turn.
Here's a good-looking man.
I love the way you fight.
My boys here suddenly went haywire.
Forgive them, will you?
S-Sure...
But y'know...
When I see a good-looking man,
I can't help but want to cut him into pieces!
That's the first time anyone's dodged my scythe attack.
I'm getting aroused!
Who the hell are you?
That's none of your business, now is it?
We're done here!
Anyway, let's hurry up and have some more fun!
I'll dance with you,
but do you promise to leave the girl out of it?
I'm not interested in women.
Glad to hear that.
Midi, I need you to watch from a distance this time.
Okay.
I'm so happy!
I'm positively shivering!
You've defiled me.
Now take responsibility!
Does that mean I was your first?
What an honor.
I'm gonna have to say goodbye for now.
We're leaving!
Gold!
Are you okay?
Yeah, kind of.
Whew...
Gold!
Damn! Uncle?
I got a report of a fight in No Man's Land,
and it's because you're at it again!
Peace comes at a price.
They had to send all of you because of one little fight?
Huh? What was that?!
Wait a minute!
I'm telling you, I'm the victim here.
Right, Midi?
See? I even have a witness.
But I've got cold hard evidence too.
Cold hard evidence?
Yeah, yeah. Take a look at this.
My cold hard evidence.
Hm? Huh?
This cold hard evidence seems to be ticking.
It's a time bomb! Throw it away!
Huh?
Gold?
Th-That's not fair.
I had no idea about any of that!
Your father's in critical condition,
and that's all you can say?
Gold, please tell us.
Thankfully, the ambulance got to him quickly,
so they were able to save him.
When did Dad get back from Fedvar?
You didn't even know my brother had come back?
I don't remember saying you could come in
and call me "Dad" like nothing ever happened.
Brother...
He's just pretending to be asleep!
What was that?!
Ah, no! You can't get up yet!
So, Uncle, who attacked that old man in the bed?
Well, he was...
There's no use looking for the culprit.
I was... I was attacked by a ghost.
A ghost?
Hey, Uncle, you think this old man lost his mind
a little after being at death's door?
Gold!
Don't worry. I still remember how you ran away from home,
and how you got those marks on your back.
Marks on Gold's back?
Gold! My brother is very sick!
Relax, Uncle. He won't be dying anytime soon
if he can still talk to me like that.
Gold!
Do you hate my brother that much?
I know he can be stubborn and headstrong.
He's the epitome of honesty and sincerity.
I understand why a lively young man like you couldn't stand such a strict upbringing and left home.
But I know, deep down,
my brother cares about you more than anyone else.
That's why he's so hard on you.
It's obvious to me how he feels.
Ebota, you've said enough.
Don't let me see you ever again!
Brother...
That's fine by me.
Gold!
So, Uncle, what was all that stuff about a ghost?
He insists he was attacked by a ghost,
no matter how many times I ask.
I don't know if it's connected,
but ever since he came back from Fedvar,
my brother's been a little depressed.
Depressed?
Yes... There must be something wrong.
Something's tormenting him.
It seems the key to this ghost mystery lies on Fedvar.
Are you going there?
Might as well. I've been dying of boredom lately.
Ghost hunting sounds like a good change of pace.
So you are going there? That's excellent.
My son is studying abroad on Fedvar.
I'll get in touch with him. He might be able to help you.
Huh? You mean Ritt?
That little pest...
Huh? Did you say something?
The ship Discovery, bound for Jupiter,
has been delayed due to a computer malfunction.
The ship Enterprise, from Venus, was...
Gold! Gold!
Mi-Midi?
Sorry to make you wait!
Make me wait? I don't remember
inviting you to come with me, though.
Oh, you don't?
How did you know I was here?
Never mind, never mind.
Never mind, you say?
Here! Let's go!
Space Colony Fedvar
Ladies and gentlemen,
Fedvar is a space colony designed for tourism.
It stands above all the other
tourist destinations in the world.
Here you can enjoy ocean swimming, hiking,
hot springs, and cave exploring.
Hey, Gold, do you think
we look like newlyweds too?
In addition, its wonderful nature has become a center of attraction for visitors from all over the solar system.
Did you say something?
You're so delicate.
You're not worthy of the name Gold.
Where am I? Who am I?
Ah, butterfly!
I don't care!
Don't you know I hate carrots, green peppers, and getting motion sick?
What are you, a child?
Midi...
What's wrong?
But the thing I hate most are homos!
Ah, it's that homo.
I know what to do!
Midi, all my life I've wanted to do this.
Come on already.
My, what a good-looking man...
U-Uh, lady?
Huh? Is something wrong?
Do you want something from me?
U-Um... your back zipper is open.
Oh my, you're such a kind man!
Can you fix it real quick?
Oh, oh no! Don't touch me down there!
Ah, yeah! Yeah!
A little to the right!
All right...
Really, I'm so sorry I had to trouble you like this.
It's nothing...
No, you pervert!
Thank you very much.
Will you come to dinner with me
tonight so I can thank you?
N-No, that's quite all right.
Anyone would've done the same.
This is why I hate women.
A brilliant tactic that strikes directly
at that homo's weakness.
You're buying me a new dress now.
Huh?
So you finally came out, huh?
R-Ritt!
I always thought you'd do it someday.
Guess I was right.
I can't believe he saw me.
Who's this kid?
I'm Ritt, this cross-dresser's cousin.
Nice to meet you, pretty lady.
Wow, he's so straightforward!
Just leave this idiot behind and come with me!
You're right, let's go!
Ah... Will I be this unlucky for the rest of my life?
Is that a five-story pagoda over there?
It is. Is this your first time visiting Fedvar?
That's right.
Ritt.
Here, I looked into it.
Did you find anything out?
Just that Uncle Retklaad
is involved somehow.
"The latest cruiser, Obconia,
was brought over from Japan
by Consul Retklaad Disasmount, currently on Fedvar for a routine inspection.
It passed all of today's inspections and is scheduled for a test run tomorrow.
The test run will be attended by the King of Fedvar,
Tonomono Plenmatz, his wife, and their son, Prince Ion.
Prince Ion, who will pilot the Obconia tomorrow,
has been visiting the airport nearly every day."
What's wrong with that?
Well, just keep reading, okay?
"While on its maiden flight today,
the latest cruiser, Obconia, carrying the King of Fedvar,
Tonomono Plenmatz, his wife, and their son, Prince Ion,
suddenly went into a steep dive,
crashed on the coast, and burst into flames.
Everyone on board is believed to have died instantly.
The tragedy is being attributed
to pilot error by Prince Ion."
The authorities also treated it like an accident.
But they didn't know that the incident
had a surprising sequel.
Sequel?
Yeah.
Is that the beach over there?
Hey, Gold, did you bring your swimsuit?
What's so funny?
Girl, my home is on the coast,
so we can go swimming anytime.
Wow, that sounds amazing!
So let's just head back to my place.
Hey, Missy, I'm leaving you a towel here.
Thanks.
Well then, Mr. Gold,
would you mind explaining all this to me?
Shut up. She decided to tag along on her own.
Really? On her own?
You're still weak when it comes to women.
Yeah, spare me the lecture.
Maybe you accidentally let
something slip in front of her?
I wouldn't do that.
She thinks this is just a leisure trip.
So what's the plan?
Hell if I know.
But I gotta do something.
Instead, tell me about the sequel to that incident.
There's no need to rush things like that.
Stop wasting my time and tell me!
Shortly after the accident,
two more men were found dead.
Dead?
Yeah, one was the Plenmatz family
driver and bodyguard.
He left a note saying he would follow his master
and threw himself into the sea.
Seems like the body was never recovered.
The other was a worker responsible
for maintaining the Obconia.
He'd been cut in half with a sword.
With a sword? My dad was also...
This is no simple accident, is it?
The newspapers really made a fuss when the authorities
suddenly began insisting that the two dead guys
were unrelated to the Obconia incident.
What?
They're covering things up.
Covering things up?
Seems the authorities want everyone to forget about the Obconia as soon as possible.
Why's that?
I-I don't know. It's just that...
Just what?
I know that Tonomono Plenmatz
opposed EDO's interference on Fedvar.
Yeah, they wanted the government
to be "for humans, by humans."
But EDO's great.
It helped eliminate war from our world.
All I know for sure is this accident has been
a godsend for EDO and the consuls.
Things are starting to get interesting.
Wow, that felt good!
Huh? What's wrong?
No, don't mind me.
I'm just appreciating how lovely you are.
What are you looking at, you little brat?
Let's go to the beach, okay?
Hey, why won't you take your shirt off?
I have sensitive skin and don't want to burn.
He's just getting old.
That's boring. I'm going for a swim.
Gold!
She has a nice body.
Yeah.
You didn't tell her about your back?
Nope.
Is that the Plenmatz Palace?
Yeah.
Who lives there now?
No one. It's just gathering dust now.
No one except the security robot.
Wanna go sightseeing?
Think they'll let us in for free?
Did the palace inhabitants
have to come and go like this?
Of course they didn't!
Looks like a ghost could jump out any minute now.
Hey, Ritt, got a light?
Of course, I came prepared.
A-A ghost!
Just a portrait?
Ah, that's Tonomono Plenmatz!
Oh? That old guy?
I wonder if there are other portraits here.
This place seems like a hall.
Ritt, turn off the light!
We should split up.
You're right.
Here's a flashlight.
"What's on the menu tonight?"
Something like that.
A living room?
Looks like it.
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
A doll?
Don't startle me like that, c'mon!
So the ghost is finally here?
But no one told me the ghosts
on Fedvar were homos!
That's none of your business!
So we meet again!
And this time we'll finish it!
Now why don't you tell me?
Why are you after me?
I would say it's because I'm in love with you,
but I don't think you'd buy that one.
It's because of the blood flowing in your body!
The blood in my body?
Exactly!
Th-This melody...
Oh? So you're the driver-bodyguard
who supposedly committed suicide?
Turns out there's even homos among the ghosts.
You figured it out!
I became a vengeful spirit to avenge my master,
who was murdered at the hands of your father!
My father killed Plenmatz?
That's right!
A wonderful husband and his gentle wife...
And even Prince Ion!
Retklaad is a demon! Evil incarnate!
My father... assassinated them?
It's time to say goodbye!
I guess it is.
Die!
Gold!
What was that sound?
The sound of a ghost dying.
What's that supposed to mean?
What were you doing out so late?
And you came back hurt too.
I was really worried, you know?
I'm sorry.
It's no laughing matter!
Hurry up and take off your jacket.
Huh?!
What's so shocking about that?
I can't treat your wounds
if you're dressed, can I?
I suppose.
What's wrong?
Huh? O-Oh... When I got back from the beach,
you had both gone somewhere.
Where'd you two go, this late at night?
Bear with it.
It's just a scratch.
Really, you two are so selfish.
There, I'm finished.
Thanks, Midi.
I'm sure you're both tired.
Hurry up and get to sleep.
What a kind little lady you are!
Shut up! Hurry up and go to bed already.
Okay...
Who goes there?
It's me.
Did you see the marks on Gold's back?
Answer me!
The marks weren't there.
They weren't there?
You're the one who told us
that he had them on his back.
You'd better not be wrong about this.
If you are, the whole plan will fall apart.
Let's just forget about taking revenge.
What did you say?
Even if we take revenge,
it won't bring the dead back to life.
Leave.
But...
I said leave!
Gold?
I couldn't fall asleep for some reason.
I went for a walk and ended up here.
You can drop the act, Princess Beryl Plenmatz.
It was really careless of me.
I didn't investigate the fate of the Plenmatz family princess,
who was adopted at a very young age.
I see.
So I don't have to keep it up anymore?
It's a relief, y'know.
How did you find out?
There'd been too many
strange coincidences so far.
Starting with what happened
on our date in No Man's Land.
The reason you clung to me
wasn't because you were scared.
You were trying to hinder my movements.
What else?
Then you somehow found out I was going to Fedvar.
Back at the hospital, you must have overheard
the talk about the ghost and the marks on my back.
Then you took us to the beach
to get me interested in the Plenmatz Palace.
And this is the melody
you always hum to yourself.
That music box is my mother's memento.
You left it in the living room on purpose, didn't you?
You wanted me to recognize your true identity.
Everything seems to suggest that
my dad murdered your parents.
But I'm sure you know
revenge won't make you happy.
I'm sorry, Gold.
I...
You don't owe me an apology for anything.
Gold, I...
You only did this because he made you do it.
Huh?
Only one person could order you
to do such a thing.
And that's you, Ion Plenmatz!
Brother!
Long time no see, Mr. Quiet Bartender.
Brother, stop this!
Gold didn't do anything to us!
You weren't in the cruiser, so you can't understand the hell we went through.
I knew the consuls were annoyed with my father and me
because we opposed the policies EDO had introduced.
So Retklaad was the only consul we trusted completely.
Still...
Retklaad decided to eliminate me and my father,
and he killed my innocent mother too!
Retklaad proved to be just another man who'd do anything,
even murder, for the sake of such immense power.
So it really was like that.
Unforgivable.
I'm going to kill the consuls, those cowards who'd let a computer take control!
I see.
Now I understand why you didn't
kill my dad right away.
You wanted to kill me first.
Huh? What do you mean?
What does he mean, brother?
Accept your fate, then!
Brother, stop this!
If you're going to kill Gold,
you're going to have to kill me as well!
Beryl! Get away from him!
I refuse!
Beryl!
Thank you, Midi.
G-Gold...
Beryl!
Kill him!
Take that!
Shit, I knew a stone wouldn't do it!
How about this?
Did they get him?
Brother!
Brother, stop it!
Don't kill Gold!
Gold, your life has come to an end!
Farewell.
Gold...
Gold's been missing for three days already.
He's got some nerve just to leave like that!
Am I right, Missy?
Huh? Yeah, I guess.
We'll punish him once he gets back
for making you worry so much.
Yes, this is Keane reporting live.
Well, it seems the press conference is about to start.
For the first time in 20 years,
we're seeing a consulate succession.
A consulate succession?
As you can see,
Gold Disasmount just arrived.
Huh?
I-Is that Gold?!
That bastard went back to Earth
without saying anything!
I've got to go back to Earth too.
As of today, I, Gold Disasmount,
will assume my father's position as consul.
Are you going to reverse your father's policies?
It's said that you ran away from the Disasmount family,
but now you've suddenly become a consul yourself?
My father was recently attacked.
I think you all know
he's currently in the hospital.
While searching for the culprit,
I stumbled upon a massive conspiracy.
Conspiracy?
Did you say conspiracy?
The person who attacked my father
was Ion Plenmatz.
What?
Ion Plenmatz?
But didn't Ion Plenmatz die in the Obconia accident?
That's right.
So what do you mean?
Ion Plenmatz miraculously survived the accident
and tried to take revenge on my father.
He's alive?!
C-Can you explain in more detail?
The Obconia incident in Fedvar
was a transparent plot by my father
to assassinate the Plenmatz family.
Assassinate?!
While on Fedvar, I found compelling evidence for this claim.
But where's Ion Plenmatz now?
Unfortunately, he passed away.
But I heard his first-hand testimony.
He used the last of his strength to tell me.
What do you plan to do now?
Now that I know the truth, I cannot simply allow
this incident to fade into obscurity, not while I'm a consul... No, not while I'm a human being!
I intend to bring my father,
Retklaad, to justice.
This really has become a problem.
In such an extraordinary situation, using conventional methods
will only result in the public losing faith in EDO.
We have no choice but to hold a public trial.
Gentlemen, what do you think?
But will Gold really be able
to prosecute his case?
If he does, he'll have to put his own father on trial.
No matter what Gold wants,
he can't be allowed to do that.
Still, just in case, we must tell Retklaad.
I suspected you might say that.
That's why I called Retklaad here.
Retklaad.
I certainly can't accuse you of cowardice.
Your statement reveals the cracks not only within the consul system,
but also within EDO itself. You know this.
I am well aware.
We now commence proceedings on the case concerning the attack on former Consul Retklaad Disasmount,
the murder of a Fedvar Station worker, and the conspiracy to assassinate the King of Fedvar, Plenmatz, and his wife.
Under normal circumstances, Ion Plenmatz, perpetrator of the crimes, would've been summoned here as a defendant,
but he died during the investigation of this case.
Therefore, I summon
Retklaad Disasmount here as a witness.
Furthermore, I personally interviewed Ion Plenmatz.
I confirmed his testimony just before his death,
which I intend to present as evidence.
Retklaad Disasmount, show yourself!
Y-You're...
Wh-Who are you?
The ghost of Ion Plenmatz.
What did you say?
I have arrived at your request.
Take off that mask!
It's me! Your old friend Gold!
Behold, Ion Plenmatz!
There are two Golds!
What's going on?
Gold!
You villain who impersonates me,
you dare mock this sacred court with your games?!
If it's come to this,
then I shall punish you with my own hands!
So you survived?
Somehow.
I'm on a great mission to kill all the consuls
and crush the EDO system!
And I'm here on an even greater
mission to restore justice!
Out of my way!
Why? You knew what I was planning,
so why did you let me get this far with it?
I've been thinking.
About what?
Which of us would do worse in this situation!
But which one is real?
I-I don't know.
Do you suppose one of them
could be Ion Plenmatz in disguise?
If Ion survived, we're in trouble.
Gold, do you even realize
you're at a disadvantage here?
What are you talking about, Mr. Fake Gold?
How do you intend to prove to everyone
that you're the real Gold?
Oh, I see. That'll be a bit annoying.
I've already been recognized as the new consul.
Unless you intend to show everyone the marks on your back to prove that you're the real one?
Oh, I see. I guess I could do that.
What?
Didn't I say I'd show you?!
You tried so hard to find the marks
on my back, but you couldn't!
So now, feast your eyes!
And watch closely!
What?
Your delicate skin is rather womanish,
but where's these so-called mark—
Th-That's...
Aren't these the marks on my back
you wanted to see?
The real Gold Disasmount has cherry blossoms
in full bloom carved on his back!
You can't see them normally, but when the blood rushes to my head, they appear and start to bloom.
It's a white-powder engraving!
The wind and dust blow away
Downtown stands there
Without a cloud in the sky!
The crowning achievement of a man's life!
It's too bright for your eyes,
so bright you can't even see the heavens.
Take a good look!
And come and get me!
We've been waiting!
I've had enough of this!
Time to conclude the play, Ion Plenmatz!
Dammit...
I am Gold Disasmount. I bring before you Ion Plenmatz,
who tried to assume my identity.
Well done, Gold!
Don't wait for our approval!
Just kill him here and now!
That doesn't sound like something
a consul would say.
What?
Even though he was a fake Gold Disasmount,
he was nominally appointed as a new consul.
Therefore, I intend to fulfill my duties as consul.
Ion Plenmatz, son of the former King of Fedvar, Tonomono Plenmatz.
Do you admit to attacking the former consul Retklaad Disasmount
and murdering the worker at Fedvar Station?
It is as you say.
You claim that Retklaad Disasmount orchestrated
the crash of the Obconia on its maiden flight
with the intent to kill your parents,
the rulers of Fedvar.
Are you sure it wasn't just a coincidence?
It was clearly a premeditated crime.
What evidence do you have
to prove these claims?
The technician at Fedvar Station told me Retklaad ordered him to tamper with the Obconia and hide the evidence.
And you killed that technician
with your own hands?
With your only witness dead,
it's obviously somewhat hard to believe you.
Then let me say this.
Since, as you say, my only witness is dead,
why not summon Retklaad Disasmount, who knows more about this incident than anyone else, to testify?
I demand that he be summoned
immediately to confront me.
And what if we summon Retklaad here,
but he claims to have no memory of the events?
Then that would be interesting.
If this means you'll have the chance to try
and see through his lies when I confront him,
I insist you summon him!
Let us summon him, then.
Retklaad Disasmount, show yourself!
Dad...
Former Consul Retklaad Disasmount,
did you orchestrate this assassination,
as Ion Plenmatz claims,
or is he merely trying to shift the blame?
You must answer with absolute sincerity.
Indeed, I did orchestrate the assassination.
Did you carry it out using the Obconia
and the crash that killed the Plenmatzes?
That is correct.
Nothing is certain about this case.
Depending upon your testimony, I may not hold you accountable for this crime.
What do you say, Retklaad?
I confirm this was carried out under my direction.
In that case, I must ask if you acted alone in planning this assassination.
Or perhaps this plan was devised
by all of the consuls?
Answer with full integrity of your soul.
I alone was behind it all.
I shall ask once again.
Did you answer with full integrity?
I did.
I shall now render a verdict.
Ion Plenmatz and Retklaad Disasmount,
I sentence you both to capital punishment.
This should settle things.
Gold, that was a brilliant start
to your consul career!
I'm sure EDO will be pleased with this verdict!
Let's go report it at once.
Yes, let's get going.
Wait!
What was that?
Hey! You can't leave the party before it's over.
The clock hasn't even struck midnight!
What the hell was all of that?
How is this matter "settled"?
How was this a "brilliant start"?!
Ion, who was presumed dead,
and my honest yet foolish father,
have been made to shoulder full responsibility,
while everyone else who caused this
pretends they didn't do it and walks away!
That's not how it works!
I'll never accept that!
G-Gold!
Are you out of your mind?!
This is a sacred court!
Shut it!
Hey, consul bigshots!
You would've loved it if this all ended here, right?
Your reputation is saved, and your problems are gone.
Would've been real nice, right?
Are your noble consul bodies somehow immune to the scars of shame?
Is this what you call politics?
Do you really think you were given the prestigious title
of consul just so you could sit silently at meetings?
All you care about is shifting the blame
and pretending like you didn't know!
Don't you have a shred of empathy
for those people below you?
Who is actually to blame in this case?!
Was it my stupid father who assassinated Tonomono?
Or was it you, who ordered him to?
Or was it perhaps Tonomono Plenmatz,
who opposed EDO's policies?
I'm sure Tonomono expected something like this
to happen one day, as long as EDO was there.
So? Who's going to take responsibility for all of that?!
There's no one who can take it.
If one person was responsible for all of this,
it never would have happened in the first place!
Because all of you are fools, because each and every one of you is so foolish, it came to this!
That goes for you guys too!
You've became so engrossed
in what these idiots were doing
that even when something bad happens, not a single voice of conscience rises to shout that it's wrong!
Now, with that said,
I have no more regrets left.
Since cherry blossoms bloom all at once,
it's natural that they all scatter all at once!
These were some sharp words I just said...
Now that I think about it, Toyama Sakura was also born into a consul's family,
bound every day by rules, and in the end,
marked his skin in a desperate attempt to escape.
But it only just dawned upon me
how stupid he was.
Well, whatever, it's all in the past now.
The cherry blossoms are most beautiful
when they are scattered.
And a man is at his manliest when he is scattered in front of so many onlookers!
Wait, Gold! I will take responsibility!
Wait a moment!
Wait a moment, Gold!
Gold, put your sword away.
EDO?
This was all my fault.
I was the one who instructed the consuls
to remove Tonomono Plenmatz from Fedvar.
I am the one responsible for all of this.
Thank you. Thank you, EDO.
If you apologize, everything will be resolved.
But you're not entirely at fault either.
You had to do something to save Fedvar from ruin.
That's right. But hear me say this!
The fault lies with the stupid people
who listened to your commands.
Even your perfect predictions and judgments
can drive stupid people crazy.
Please tell me, Gold.
What can I do to help humanity?
Is there a way for us to reach an understanding?
You don't get it. You don't!
That's something we have to figure out on our own!
Something we've forgotten about!
I shall pass down a new verdict.
Retklaad Disasmount was acting on orders
and is found not guilty.
Ion Plenmatz is no longer alive.
There is no record of his survival in my data.
Therefore, he could not have committed these crimes.
EDO...
With this, everything is reset to how it was initially, before we all met.
Come on, Midi, cheer up!
That's right!
Yeah!
But...
Gold is a renowned consul now.
He couldn't come to a secret bar
like this now, even if he wanted to.
I suppose.
Who says I can't come?
Gold!
Hey. Long time no see.
Heh! Look who's back.
I ain't losing to you today, you old bastard!
Lovely.
But I need a drink first.
Gold!
Here you go.
You didn't return to Fedvar?
I think you're mistaking me for someone else.
I've always been a quiet bartender from Earth.
He's a nice guy, even if he's a little quiet.
I see. Good to know.
Anyway, the bar is about to close,
so how about going on a date with a stunning beauty?
Huh? A stunning beauty?
Where? Where? Where?
Where's this babe?
Midi, you've got to tell me! Please!
Where is this pretty girl?
Did someone call me?
Long time no see.
You're not getting away from me this time!
Gold is mine!
Oh no, he's mine!
All right, we'll settle this right now!
With pleasure!
Th-That's not fair!
I don't want a boy who thinks about past love like it's a criminal record
A playboy keeps trying to get with me
But you know he's a liar when you touch him
If you hold me, the devil will come out
You're scared of the cherry blossom storm, aren't you?
Tattooed lady wants a heart
Tattooed lady hates men
Tattooed lady is a risky woman
Tattooed lady hurting a lot
Wouldn't that be nice?
If you hold me, the devil will come out
You're scared of the cherry blossom storm, aren't you?
Tattooed lady wants memories
Tattooed lady hates men
Tattooed lady is a risky woman
Tattooed lady hurting a lot
Wouldn't that be nice?
THE
END
Translation
& Timing
Perevodildo
Translation
Check
TougeWolf
Editing
darkcart
Collectr
Translation
& Timing
Perevodildo
Translation
Check
TougeWolf
Editing
darkcart
Collectr
Typesetting
QC
Collectr
Muzussawa
QC
RC
tim-x
WasteOfHair
TougeWolf
LD ripping
Encoding
WOWmd
Rezo
Typesetting
QC
Collectr
Muzussawa
QC
RC
tim-x
WasteOfHair
TougeWolf
LD ripping
Encoding
WOWmd
Rezo
Presented by
Inka-Subs and Orphan Fansubs