Selected by the Ministry of Education,
Science, and Culture
Suitable for young children and families
-
Recommended by the Eirin Youth Film Deliberation Council
Huh?
What's wrong, Dear?
I can hear a baby crying.
Think somebody left a baby
in front of the orphanage?
There it is!
There, there.
Dear, we have to let the principal know about this.
Right, I'll go get her now!
And be quick about it!
Then, we'll leave it all to you.
There we go. There, there.
Isn't she a beautiful
baby, Principal?
Now we just need
to give her a name.
Since she's the first baby we've had since I became principal,
we'll start with the letter 'A'.
And you're using the phone book to pick a name?
Yes, is something the matter?
N-No, of course not.
Abbott.
That will do nicely.
Let's call her that.
Abbott?
Oh my. I don't think she likes that name very much.
Principal, what do you think of the name Judy?
Judy?
Yes, it was the name
of my late sister.
Judy, you say?
Well, why not?
You'll be called Judy.
We've decided on Judy Abbott.
She laughed!
She really likes the name Judy!
There, good girl.
Daddy-Long-Legs
Somewhere beneath this sky...
I'm sure we'll meet someday.
Clouds, you're my friends.
What lies beyond
that deep red sunset?
Please tell me, please tell me.
From inside this small cage...
I've always longed for
the world I've never seen.
Somewhere beneath this sky...
I'm sure we'll meet someday.
To my happiness, to my happiness.
There we go.
What are you all doing?!
A-A frog!
Freddy, catch it!
R-Right!
Hey, get back here!
Come on!
Save me!
Someone, save me!
Where is Judy?!
Where is Judy when
you need her?!
The children brought yet another frog into their room.
I'm sorry about that.
You're the oldest one here.
If you can't look after the children properly, then what will I do with you?
I'm sorry.
Tomorrow is the first Wednesday of the month!
I understand.
Surely you know what would happen if the guests saw the children acting like that?!
I do.
The guests donate
to the orphanage,
so we all have to be on our best behavior when they're here.
That's right.
And that goes double for you. You've been here for 17 years, after all.
When most people finish middle school,
they go to high school and then start working.
But you are being allowed to attend the village high school as a special exception.
You'd best remember that.
I appreciate it, I really do.
That matter aside, the principal has something important to discuss with you.
Three months from now, you'll graduate high school.
We will discuss your future with the rest of the benefactors tomorrow.
My future?
In my opinion, you are free to work here, should you wish to do so.
But we must ask our benefactors.
Um...
What is it?
If I'm to work, I'd like to do it somewhere else.
You want to work
somewhere else?!
That's right.
I want to try working
in the outside world.
What are you saying?!
A child raised in an orphanage knows nothing of the troubles of the real world!
I intend to know of them.
I don't think you understand!
Don't you know how hard life will be outside of the orphanage?!
Does she, Principal?
Either way, we'll come to a decision with our benefactors tomorrow.
But I will let them know what you want to do.
Judy!
I'm sorry, Judy.
- I'm sorry, Judy.
Sorry about what?
Y'know, about the frog.
Oh, about that.
I only got told off a little,
so we're okay.
But remember, tomorrow is
the first Wednesday of the month,
so the benefactors
will be coming over.
Wait, really?
Oh, not this again!
Freddy.
I want you on
your best behavior.
If you don't behave,
I'll be given another earful!
You got it, Judy.
Now then, everyone,
back to their rooms.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
blue Wednesday.
Today is the first
Wednesday of the month.
The members of the board come riding in carriages and cars.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
blue Wednesday.
Everyone has to
be good all day long.
From morning till night,
it's such hard work.
Floors glisten, windows sparkle, every chair and desk wiped clean.
Beds made, showered and shampooed, clothes starched, gingham checks.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
blue Wednesday.
If not for this day
that comes once a month,
life here wouldn't
be so bad at all.
Ah, ah, how I hate Wednesdays.
I wish Wednesdays
would never come.
Today is the first
Wednesday of the month.
The members of the board pay us their monthly visit.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
blue Wednesday.
Everyone has to mind their manners all day long.
And on top of that,
we must serve the meals.
Answer promptly. "Yes, sir."
Stand up straight. "No, sir."
Buttons fastened tight, no crying,
no squabbling, and no chattering.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
blue Wednesday.
Be brave and just endure it.
When tomorrow comes,
we'll forget it all anyway.
Ah, ah, how I hate Wednesdays.
I wish Wednesdays
would never come.
There are a number of things I wish to discuss with you all today.
First on the agenda...
is our oldest orphan,
Judy Abbott.
Judy!
Why are you so spaced out?
The principal
wants to see you.
Again?
Did I make a mess
of something again?
I thought we were all well-behaved in front of our guests.
You were, weren't you?
But you should really
hurry up and see her.
Right, I'll go and see her.
Come in.
You wanted to see me?
I did indeed.
Well then, take a seat.
Okay.
Did you see the
man who just left?
I only saw him from behind.
That man is the richest
among our guests,
and has donated a lot of
money to the orphanage.
I see.
But his name is kept secret.
And that's how he
wants to keep it.
Is that so?
Charles Penton and Henry Fritz, who used to live here,
only went to university
because of him.
He wanted to offer a scholarship to
a promising young boy this year as well.
Isn't that nice?
However, the matter of your
future came up during our meeting.
Right.
So that the benefactors could get to know what kind of person you are,
Mrs. Pritchard read aloud a poem you had written, one called "Wednesday."
What kind of poem was that?
I'm terribly sorry.
Making fun of the very people
who had been so good to us.
And it's nothing
to be proud of.
I'm sorry.
However...
The man who just left seems to take quite
an interest in that rude writing of yours.
And has offered to
send you to university.
T-To university?
Sit down, Judy.
Yes, ma'am.
But he really wants to send me to university?
I'm as surprised as you are.
But he's a very
idiosyncratic man.
He said that your very 'unique' manner of writing showed talent.
And set up a plan for you to become a writer in the future.
A writer?
Like a novelist?
So it seems.
Me, a writer?
I don't know if I could...
So, shall I cancel
the university plans?
No!
I'll go!
Please let me go!
But there is one condition for
him to put you through university.
That is for you to write a letter to him once per month.
A letter?
Is that all he wants in
place of the money?
No, not quite.
Had your parents been alive, you'd tell
them of how your school life was faring.
Like how your studies were going, what
you did with your friends, that kind of thing.
Then, would you be able
to tell me his name?
If I'm to send them a letter,
it has to be addressed to someone.
Griggs' Law Office will suffice.
Griggs?
He happens to be a legal advisor to our benefactor.
Mr. Griggs will be coming
to town before you leave,
and he'll take care of
the arrangements for you.
You should be thankful for having
run into such good fortune.
Is that clear?
Farewell!
- Farewell!
- Take care!
- Judy, you forgot this!
- Bye-bye!
- Oh my.
- See you later, Judy!
Take care!
- See you later!
- Take care!
My heart is a clear blue sky.
I'm in high spirits.
I want anyone at all to hear this flutter in my chest.
I was just a freckled girl in a gingham checked dress.
I never dreamed I'd
get to go to university.
An unfamiliar world, rosy with promise, spreads before me.
I'm so dazzlingly happy,
I can't help but smile!
But wait just a moment.
Somewhere deep
inside my heart,
there's something that's
weighing me down.
I, Judy, who knows
nothing of the world,
will I really be all
right on my own?
Come on now, Judy!
Worrying won't
get you anywhere.
Throw yourself in and
break through anything.
Cheer up now,
come on, Judy.
This is the journey
of a brand new me.
Go for it, go for it, Judy.
Don't you worry.
Go for it, Judy. Don't give up, Judy.
Keep your spirits high!
Go for it, go for it, Judy.
Think only of good things.
Go for it, Judy. Don't give up, Judy.
Believe in yourself!
My dear benefactor,
I've been thinking about you a lot.
But there are only two
things I know about you.
Even blessed with imagination,
there isn't much for me to go off.
Number one, you're wealthy.
Number two, you're tall.
And I did think of calling you Mr. Moneybags,
but I'd feel bad if your
fortune ever changed.
So I've decided to call you
Daddy-Long-Legs instead.
Please don't take it personally.
Whoa there.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Um, which way
is the university?
Oh, are you a
new student as well?
That's right.
So am I!
Why don't we go together?
Are we close by?
It would be better
to go by carriage.
By carriage?
I've heard it's traditional for new students at Walston to arrive by carriage.
Let's see...
Over here!
Come on, get in.
I'm Judy Abbott.
I'm Sally McBride. A pleasure.
The pleasure is all mine.
Ever since I got into university, I thought
about what kind of person I'd meet first.
Don't you know
anybody here?
No, what about you?
Me neither.
How about we be friends?
Of course!
"And by some coincidence, we even
ended up sharing the same room."
"It's three people to a room, so we're
with someone called Susan Pendleton."
"Susan comes from a well-to-do family in New York...
and has a very prim and proper air about her."
"I don't think I'll be friends with her as quickly as I was with Sally."
Come in.
Wow, all of your
clothes are so pretty!
Oh, these old things?
Did you pick these yourself?
That's right.
Hey, can I borrow this one?
Of course.
I wish I could buy
clothes like these.
I bet your parents dote
on you all the time, huh?
I don't have any parents.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Even if they were around, they wouldn't
have the money for things like this.
But a very kind person got me
them so I could attend university.
I see!
Yes?
Would you like to come downstairs
to the tearoom with me?
We can get acquainted
over a cup of tea.
Of course!
I couldn't bring myself to tell them
that I was raised in an orphanage.
I've heard the cake
here is wonderful!
Welcome, everyone!
- Congratulations!
This is a lovely garden of maidens,
a courtyard of learning that grants us wisdom.
But for you brand new students, it feels like you're in Hell.
From waking up to going to bed, bells mark off every moment, no time even to breathe.
You’re made to read piles of books, and then the library is waiting.
Dead tired from the schedule.
The moment you finish it, it's...
Lights out!
There's no time to fall in love,
and the upperclassmen pick on you.
Teachers yell at you and your classmates are no help there.
Ah, ah, how pitiful we are.
You and I alike,
university students.
But, everyone, don't panic.
Once you get the hang of things,
there's nowhere more comfortable and there are no lectures from your father.
You're never forced to go shopping with your mother.
Even if books turn into coffee,
who's going to care anyway?
Ah, ah, happy university students.
"Home is where you make it" really says it all.
Welcome, Mrs. Pritchard.
I'm sorry, I know
you must be busy.
Please, take a seat.
I take it you're worried
about Judy Abbott?
That's right.
I was wondering how she
was getting on at university.
While I haven't seen her in person,
she seems to be enjoying herself.
At least, that's how
I interpret her letters.
Is that so?
I must say, that girl's letters
are quite the interesting read.
Daddy-Long-Legs of all things.
Daddy-Long-Legs.
Daddy-Long-Legs?
What's that about?
Well, I don't know how it came about,
but ever since she left for university,
she's given him the name of Daddy-Long-Legs in her letters.
My, what a rude
thing to call someone!
No, no.
He found it rather amusing.
Um... is it always to
Daddy-Long-Legs?
Yes, she was supposed to
send one letter per month,
but she's been sending about one per week so far.
Well, she always did have
a thing for literature.
So, has he been
reading her letters?
Oh, indeed. Of course he's been reading them.
Ever since he went to France,
they've been waiting here for him.
So, would you like to hear one?
Yes, if you wouldn't mind.
I don't mind in the slightest.
Truth be told, I also look forward to getting her letters.
"These letters are a little one-sided, so I was wondering if you could answer a few things."
So, I would appreciate it if you could answer these questions.
Are you an older gentleman?
Or are you younger perhaps?
Are you bald?
Or do you have a
little bit of hair left?
I look forward to
hearing back from you.
My, what do
you think of that?
Well, aren't they rather
interesting to read?
Yes, this is Griggs' Law Office. Yes, that's me.
It's from Daddy-Long-Legs.
That's right.
The only thing I have is that
letter for your eyes only.
Yes, the letter?
Yes, there are two more
letters from Judy Abbott.
If you could just
wait a moment.
And another one
has just arrived.
Shall I read it to you?
Very well, just a moment.
"Dear, Daddy-Long-Legs."
It looks like you really are Daddy-Long-Legs now.
Yes, yes, I'll read it now.
"I'm currently in hospital."
"I've got both tonsillitis, influenza, and probably a few other things too."
Oh Lord...
How are you
feeling now, Judy?
Thank you,
I feel much better now.
A present came for you.
Wow, I wonder who it's from.
There's a letter attached.
"How are you feeling?"
"I hope you get better, Judy. I look forward to many more letters - Daddy-Long-Legs."
I wonder what it is.
My, it's beautiful!
Judy, are you
feeling better now?
Ah, Sally, Susan!
You look a lot better!
Oh my!
What beautiful roses!
I bet these cost a fortune!
Hey, who sent you these?
R-Remember that
man I told you about?
"I look forward to many more letters - Daddy-Long-Legs."
What's that mean?
That's not for you!
"Daddy-Long-Legs, this is the first time I've been given a present in hospital."
"I was so happy,
I could've cried."
"Thank you so very much."
"And, now that I know you read my letters,
I hope you look forward
to even more of them!"
Judy!
Can you help me?
With what?
You have got a gap
between classes, don't you?
That's right.
But I was going to
practice basketball.
Could you skip
practice for me?
I'm as surprised as you are.
I never thought Uncle Jervis would come and visit me.
What did he do that for?
He said he had a meeting
to attend in town.
And then it reminded
him I go to school here.
Are you sure you want
me to meet him?
It'll be fine.
It's only for an hour.
And an hour will fly by when you're
giving him a tour of the university.
But...
Then, there we have it.
Come on, this way!
Sorry to keep
you waiting, Uncle.
Oh, it's nothing.
Allow me to introduce you.
This is Judy Abbott, my roommate.
I'm Jervis Pendleton.
A pleasure.
Uncle, Judy will show you around the university. I've got classes to attend.
Thank you, Susan.
Well, I'll meet up with
you both later, okay?
Right.
Well, Ms. Abbott, would
you care to show me around?
O-Oh, I'm sorry.
Is something the matter?
When Susan mentioned her uncle,
I assumed he'd be much older.
I'm already 33 years old.
So I am old compared to you.
Of course not. You're
not old in the slightest.
"Daddy-Long-Legs... would you
like to visit one day as well?"
"I'm very good at
showing people around."
"I used to do it all the time
at the orphanage, after all."
"I think it would be wonderful
to show you around."
"I showed Susan's
uncle around today."
"He's from the esteemed Pendleton family, but he was very easy to talk to."
"I keep thinking if this is what you would've been like 20 years ago."
This is the university hospital.
I was here not too long ago.
Oh, are you unwell?
No, not anymore!
So I see.
You seem rather lively.
I'm starting to
get a little tired.
Is there anywhere we can
get a cup of tea around here?
There is, but Susan's class
should be ending soon.
Shouldn't we go
and meet her?
No, it doesn't bother me.
There are other things
I want to talk to you about.
So, how about that cup of tea?
Since it's the end
of the month,
most people have used up their
pocket money, so it's really quiet here.
Have you used all
of yours up too?
I don't usually, but I
bought a book this month.
So, I don't have a
penny to my name.
If you wouldn't mind telling me,
what kind of book is it?
It's the works of Shakespeare.
Surely they have
Shakespeare in the library?
They do.
But I just had to have
a copy of my own.
I see.
Oh, it's almost
time for my train.
Oh no.
Miss Abbott, please
give Susan my regards.
I'll have to head home.
I knew we shouldn't
have gone for tea.
No, you made this whole
ordeal rather enjoyable.
Judy, where did
Uncle Jervis go?
U-Um...
I know that Uncle Jervis is considered a
bit of an oddball in the Pendleton family,
but he came all the way here to see me,
and didn't even speak to me.
Instead, he spent all
day talking to you.
I'm sorry.
I should've paid more
attention to the time.
Uncle Jervis is a rather
difficult man, isn't he?
No, I didn't feel that way. I mean,
we talked about all sorts of things.
Time went by so fast!
I see.
I've only spoken with
my uncle a handful of times.
There are rumors in my family that he hates
women, and that's why he hasn't married.
Is that so?
Hey, hey, hey!
These were delivered to us!
What is it?
They look like chocolates.
They came from
the chocolate shop in town.
Oh, who are they from?
Let's see... they're
from Jervis Pendleton.
Oh my.
"To my beloved niece, Susan,
and her two delightful roommates."
"To Judy and Sally McBride, a little thank
you for today's visit - Jervis Pendleton."
Oh, Uncle, that's so like you.
It's even addressed to me too!
Did you talk to
my uncle about Sally?
Not at all.
Then how did he
know about you?
I'm sure someone
else must've told him.
Alright, let's eat some.
- They look delicious!
"Susan said Mr. Pendleton
was a little odd,
but I didn't think
anything of the sort."
"If I'm being honest with you, that was
the first time I'd ever spoken with a man."
"That's not to say that speaking to
the visitors at the orphanage was easy,
but this was the first time I'd had
a proper conversation with a young man."
"To Daddy-Long-Legs, from Judy."
"P.S. You're more than welcome to come to the university as well."
"I would love to show you around."
I returned to the orphanage over the summer break for the first time in a year.
Ms. Ann is unwell, so Ms. Rivette has asked me to come tend to the children.
- It's Judy!
- She's back!
You've grown so much, Freddy.
- Freddy!
- What a relief!
When you see a rainbow, you wish you
could cross that seven-colored bridge.
That's what you think, right?
With white wings, soaring high in the open sky, you want to be a bird in flight.
That's imagination, with just that,
invisible worlds come into view.
As long as you have imagination,
there's no time to ever be bored.
Imagination. (Imagination.)
Any time at all, imagination.
What matters most
is imagination.
For you and I as well.
I-I-Imagination.
If you're feeling gloomy,
try dreaming of a wonderful tomorrow.
That's fun, right?
If tears should start to fall,
remember something happy.
It's funny, right?
That's imagination, with just that,
you can turn the impossible into possible.
So imagination, with just that,
you don't need to be a rich king.
Imagination. (Imagination.)
Whoever you meet,
imagination.
Imagination. (Imagination.)
With a heart full of love,
imagination.
For you and I as well.
I-I-Imagination.
Come in.
You okay?
Hey, Judy, you want to come
to my house over Christmas?
To your house?
You had to stay here last
Christmas, didn't you?
So, wanna come over?
You really don't mind?
Of course not!
As it happens,
I've already asked my parents.
I said I might be bringing
a friend over for Christmas.
What's wrong?
Susan, what happened?!
It's a centipede.
I-It fell from the roof
onto my desk!
Not again...
But there's...
nothing on her desk.
Yes, there is!
Look, there it is!
It's huge!
Why'd a centipede have
to show up now of all times?
That's my slipper!
Sally!
Throw that slipper away!
I won't wear that ever again!
It's okay, it'll only
be on the bottom.
No way, those things
give me the creeps.
Then, I'll head back to my room.
I hope there isn't
another one of them.
It's gone now.
Judy's writing a novel,
isn't she?
It sure looks that way.
The school magazine is accepting
admissions for stories, isn't it?
And she'll be aiming
for first place.
You never know,
Judy might just do it.
You're right,
she is a rather good writer.
"Dear, Daddy-Long-Legs,
I've finally finished my novel."
"If I remember correctly,
you did say I'd end up being a writer."
"Daddy-Long-Legs, I've been invited to Sally's house over Christmas."
"Sally's home reminded me of the orphanage."
"I was so curious about how it would look on the inside."
"And it was just how
I imagined it."
Judy, would you
like another?
Please.
Hey, Sally, I'm home!
Brother!
Brother, I've brought
Judy with me.
Hello.
This is my brother, Tommy.
He's a fourth-year
student at Princeton.
I'm Judy Abbott.
My sister has told
me all about you.
She says you're
quite the writer.
I wouldn't say that.
Judy... is writing a novel.
Now that I'd like to read.
I'm sure it will be in the school
magazine, so I'll send you a copy.
Sally, that's not happening.
There's no way my
novel will get picked.
You need to be more
confident in yourself, Judy.
Oh, by the way, Father, I've prepared
all the presents for the children.
Good work.
On Christmas Eve,
we go to give presents to the children of the people who work in my father's factory.
You should come see
the Christmas tree as well.
Hey, can Judy
give us a hand too?
Now that's a good idea.
...the sleigh glides on by...
Cutting through the wind, cutting through the snow...
Singing merry songs,
bells ringing all around!
Hey! Jingle bells, jingle bells,
the sleigh glides on by.
Tonight the sound of hooves rings out with cheer!
Hey! Jingle bells, jingle bells,
the sleigh glides on by.
When we sing a song,
our hearts take flight!
Merry Christmas!
- Wow!
- It's Santa!
Now then, we've got
presents for all of you.
All in a line now!
The smallest kids first!
Hey, no pushing!
Judy, give me a hand here! Judy!
R-Right!
All in a line now!
Here's a dolly.
- Don't forget me!
- Thank you, miss.
Oh, but this present
is from Santa.
Here, this book
looks interesting.
Thank you!
"It was a very
strange feeling."
"Was this what it felt like to be a benefactor at John Grier's Orphanage?"
"They used to give us presents
while looking at us with pity."
"But what I hated most of
all was them rubbing our hair."
"It really is a strange feeling."
"For Judy the orphan to be giving presents to children of all things."
Silent night, holy night.
The stars are shining.
The child of salvation...
rests within his mother's arms.
- Goodbye! Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
- Goodbye!
Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
See you later!
Come on now.
- Goodbye!
- Bye-bye!
So, Brother, how about we
throw a dance party for Judy?
Yeah, I was planning
on that already.
As it happens, I've already spoken
to Mother and Father about it.
That's wonderful!
Judy, we're hosting a party for
you the day after tomorrow.
What? All for me?
Of course.
She's even brought her very
own white evening dress.
Judy's a pretty girl,
so I'm sure white will suit you.
"I wore the white evening
dress you sent me...
the white gloves...
the white shoes and
danced with Tommy."
"They all said I looked beautiful."
"Deep down, I thought the same thing, so it made me feel happy."
"I'm so terribly vain, aren't I?"
"I even invited Tommy
to the university festival."
I'm sorry!
What's wrong, Sally?
You seem in a hurry.
Yeah, I need to find Judy.
If you're looking for her, she should
be in the teahouse with a guest.
Ah, right! Thank you!
And Susan's with her too!
Now that was delicious.
Oh, Judy!
Welcome.
Sally. This is my uncle,
Jervis Pendleton.
This is Sally McBride,
my roommate.
Th-Thank you
for the chocolates.
Oh, no, think nothing of it.
Hey, hey, hey, Judy!
I've got big news!
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong at all!
You won first place!
Your novel! It's going to be published in the school magazine!
I knew yours
would get first place!
I overheard Ms. Morris,
the editor, talking about it.
Though, it won't be
official until tomorrow.
Isn't that great, Judy?
I-I got first place?
I can hardly believe it!
They said that you'll be
the first ever second-year to win.
Congratulations.
If you'll allow me to congratulate
you too, Miss Abbott.
Thank you, Mr. Pendleton.
Oh, no.
Please, call me Jervis.
And may I call
you Judy in return?
Very well, Jervis.
Now that's much better.
Anyway, congratulations.
Uncle, will you make
it in time for the train?
Oh, you're right.
Well, if I am talking with three pretty young
ladies, there's no way I could hurry home.
Naturally, Uncle,
you should stay a little longer.
If I may say something.
I hope I'm not being
a nuisance, ladies.
Oh, not at all.
Of course you aren't.
Thank you.
Then, I suppose I'll help
myself to another sandwich.
Ah, that reminds me, Judy.
You said you bought a copy of
the works of Shakespeare, didn't you?
That's right.
Hamlet is being shown at
the Strong Theater in New York.
I've heard it's rather good.
Is that so?
It sounds lovely.
Do you two like
Shakespeare too?
I do.
I suppose.
Then, it's decided.
"Dear, Daddy-Long-Legs,
last Friday, Sally, Susan,
and myself went to New York."
"Jervis took us all to see Hamlet."
"Susan stayed at her own home, but Sally and I stayed at the Sheraton Hotel."
"It's my first time seeing a play,
my first time staying in a hotel."
"I can hardly describe it!"
"The play of Hamlet was much more interesting than the book."
What's wrong, Judy?
I never knew they
served food on trains.
Where on earth
were you raised?
A village, but there weren't too many people there.
If you didn't know trains served food,
did you not go on holiday?
My first time was
going to university.
"Susan always thought I was a bit strange because I sometimes say such odd things."
"I was so overwhelmed by everything in New York...
that I blurted out it was my first time seeing a dining car."
"Having spent 17
years in an orphanage,
experiences like these would
make anyone's head spin."
Are you okay?
My uncle seems to have
taken an interest in you.
Don't you think so, Sally?
Yes, he was talking to Judy a lot.
I guess the rumors about him hating women aren't true after all.
"Honestly, even without Susan saying anything,
I already knew that Jervis
felt this way about me."
"Some things don't need to be said to be understood, do they?"
"P.S. I'm amazed you've spent the last year living in the hustle and bustle of New York."
"But I'd recommend going out into the country once in a while."
"Given your age and all."
Over the summer, she's to go to
the Rock Willow Farm in Connecticut.
Ah, yes, I understand.
No, it hasn't come yet.
Yes, very well.
Hey, Judy, would you like to
spend summer at our family villa?
Your family's villa?
Yeah.
It's a real rustic place surrounded by lakes and forests.
My mother thinks
you'll love it.
So she'd love for you to come.
My, that sounds lovely!
I'd love to go!
And Tommy said he's coming
with all his friends from university.
It's your chance
to get a boyfriend!
Oh, Sally.
Then, it's decided!
I'll let my mother
know right away!
I'm sure Tommy will
be pleased as well.
My...
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
Well, it says here that she's been
invited to the McBride's villa.
Yes, very well,
the Rock Willow Farm it is then.
Yes, I understand.
I'll see to it personally.
"Dear, Daddy-Long-Legs,
I'll be staying at the Rock Willow Farm over the summer, just like you asked."
"But... why? Why couldn't I spend time with Sally?"
Hey, Judy, why can't you?
Thank you.
My!
Judy, you already know
Young Master Jervis?
Young master?
No matter how old he is,
he's still the young master to me.
I nursed him when
he was a child.
I never would've guessed.
What a coincidence.
So, is Young Master
Jervis doing well?
Yes. He seemed well when we met
two months ago in New York.
Is that so?
I'd say it was when he
was about 11 years old.
He caught pneumonia and ended
up staying here over the summer.
Young Master Jervis really is the most
dashing man in the Pendleton family.
"Daddy-Long-Legs,
could this really be a coincidence?"
"Or do you happen to know Jervis?"
"Did you hear of this
place because of Jervis?"
There!
Whoa, almost.
Jeez!
"This is a wonderful place."
"It's good for the soul."
"And I also got a letter from Sally."
"For Tommy's
graduation present,
they're going to go on a car trip, and they said they're going to come to the farm!"
"I can't wait!"
"To Daddy-Long-Legs, from Judy."
Here.
Up you go.
There I go.
- Wait, I've never done this before.
- It'll be fine, this one's well-behaved.
W-Wait, hey.
O-On second thoughts,
get me down.
Away you go!
Help me!
Young lady!
Judy!
A-Are you okay?!
She doesn't seem in
a bad way, does she?
Y-Yes, she's just sleeping.
But didn't she
fall off a horse?
It wasn't anything serious,
Young Master.
Could you stop with the "young master" thing, Laura?
What's wrong with calling you
"young master," Young Master?
Hey, I hear you
fell off a horse?
Jervis...
I thought I'd come and pay
Laura a visit, and look who I find.
Judy.
What is it?
You're in your second year
of university, aren't you?
That's right.
The same year as Susan.
But we'll be in our
third year soon.
Will you stay
on at university?
Of course.
Don't you want
to see Europe?
Paris, Rome, Vienna.
Well, that's...
But that would
be impossible for me.
What if someone paid
for you to do that?
Someone is already paying
for my university fees.
I couldn't possibly ask them
to pay for me to go to Europe.
Don't you ever think of leaving
university and traveling around Europe?
I don't.
There's still a lot for me
to learn at university.
I want to make
many more friends.
There's so much
more I want to learn.
But couldn't you
do that in Europe?
That looks like Tommy!
Look, it's Sally's brother!
There can't be many people
with a car around here.
He said he'd pay
me a visit on his trip!
Tommy!
Judy!
I'm going to Europe!
Will you come with me?!
Jervis...
Will you come to
Europe with me?
No, I will continue
my studies at university.
Judy!
Tommy!
You look well, Judy!
Of course!
Lately, something strange has been happening.
I'm in an oddly sweet mood.
I feel like talking to the blowing wind and the stream's clear water.
What on earth could be going on?
Is this all Judy's doing?
It really does feel a
lot like being in love.
A sweet, sweet mood,
such a mysterious feeling.
When I look at Judy,
it comes flooding back.
That nostalgic,
mysterious feeling of youth.
Judy!
My brother says he'll come to our graduation.
What a relief.
So, who did Susan call?
Her favourite uncle,
who else?
Mr. Jervis Pendleton.
Who are you inviting, Judy?
Well...
"The graduation ceremony is three weeks from next Wednesday."
"I'd love for you to come."
"If you don't end up coming,
I'll have to hold a grudge against you."
Very well, I'll begin reading the names of those who have graduated.
Grace Hudson.
"Daddy-Long-Legs."
"I didn't think you'd turn up."
Mary Stewart.
Hold still now.
Are you ready?
One, two, and...
Three!
"I graduated university."
"Tommy came to
the graduation ceremony,
but Mr. Jervis, invited by Susan,
was too sick to attend."
Number 532 to
New York please.
Ah, is this the
Pendleton household?
"I'm on my way back
to Rock Willow Farm."
"I'd planned on writing a novel here over the summer."
"But my heart isn't in it and I can't seem to focus."
"I've wanted to talk to you for a long time now."
"About Mr. Jervis."
"When Susan told me he was unwell,
I knew I had to visit him."
"If only I could see his face."
"I don't know why I
feel this way about him."
"Daddy-Long-Legs."
"Please, would you give me permission to visit Jervis Pendleton?"
"To Daddy-Long-Legs,
from Judy, a girl lost in love."
Judy! Judy!
A letter's come for you!
Okay!
Here.
Thank you.
It's from Daddy-Long-Legs!
"I'll meet you next Wednesday at 4:30 pm - Daddy-Long-Legs."
Hooray!
I finally get to meet him!
Be careful, okay?
Okay, but it's okay, I've been
to New York three times now.
Good morning, Henry.
Good morning, Judy.
You seem in
good spirits, Judy.
Giddy-up!
I'll be back soon!
Your boyfriend waiting
for you in New York?
My boyfriend?
Oh, but of course.
That's right. I finally get to meet the man I've been thinking of for the past four years.
Judy.
Mr. Griggs!
Here, your carriage awaits.
Thank you.
I-Is Daddy-Long-Legs
an older gentleman?
Is he older than you?
Or perhaps younger?
Is he bald?
Or does he have gray hair?
You'll see when you meet him.
Surely, he must have children?
Or maybe even
grandchildren?
You can ask him yourself.
Does he know Mr. Pendleton?
Does he know
Jervis Pendleton?
Now, I wouldn't know.
They're both wealthy and live in New York,
so they must know one another.
Well, who is to say?
Miss Abbott, I assume?
That's right.
I'll show you to the master. Right this way, Young Lady.
The master hasn't been well of late,
so he has been confined to his bed.
My...
Is that so?
He's through here.
Miss Abbott is here to see you.
I am Judy Abbott,
Daddy-Long-Legs.
I've... I've wanted to
meet you for so long!
Daddy-Long-Legs?
Judy, didn't you realize
I was Daddy-Long-Legs?
Jervis...
You were Jervis?
You were Daddy-Long-Legs?!
Jervis!
Judy!
I'm sorry.
Daddy, Daddy-Long-Legs.
It was you all along,
Daddy-Long-Legs.
Daddy, Daddy-Long-Legs.
Yes, it's me, I'm Daddy-Long-Legs.
The one I was
searching for was you.
(Daddy-Long-Legs. Daddy-Long-Legs.)
This meeting means everything to me.
If this is a dream,
don't let me wake up.
Now I know being by your side is my only wish.
Daddy-Long-Legs. Daddy-Long-Legs.
Daddy, Daddy-Long-Legs.
It was you all along,
Daddy-Long-Legs.
Daddy, Daddy-Long-Legs.
Yes, it's me,
I'm Daddy-Long-Legs.
Hold in your warm arms...
(Daddy-Long-Legs. Daddy-Long-Legs.)
I always dreamed of dancing with you.
We could only meet like this because our hearts longed for each other.
Daddy-Long-Legs. Daddy-Long-Legs.
The sparkle of love.
The joy of love, forevermore.
@InkaSubs