This spring, Atlus brings you
a slightly naughty jigsaw game recommended for ages 18 and above.
"My Best Friends: St. Andrew Girls' School", Sega Saturn edition.
St. Andrew Girls' School
In "My Best Friends" you can assemble
a 7 x 10-piece jigsaw puzzle.
Depending on how fast you complete it, you'll be able to watch some erotic animations.
Make your pick
Configuration
Make a
phone call!
Girls'
introductions
Start the
puzzle
Let's explain the game in practice.
Yayoi Nishizaki
Ayano Yutenji
Hiromi Aoki
Megumi Hagiwara
Reiju Ikegami
First, you choose one out of five girls.
Then the self-introduction begins.
Hello, my name is Ayano.
I am 17 years old, Gemini.
I'm the head of the photography club.
And today I'm supposed to be a model myself,
but I'm not sure what kind of poses to do.
Huh? Take off my glasses?
Okay.
One of the stills during her introduction
becomes the base for the puzzle.
This is where the puzzle starts.
Use the C button to pick up the piece
or to place it if you've found where it fits.
If you pick up a piece that you don't know where to place, you can discard it with the B button.
If you own a Sega Saturn Shuttle Mouse™️,
playing becomes even more comfortable.
So? Isn't it easy?
Once it's finished, you'll see another anime scene.
The less time it took you to assemble the puzzle, the more perverted it becomes.
There are a total of eight girls in this game.
It uses 2750 animation cells for smooth movement.
Make your pick
Configuration
Make a
phone call!
Girls'
introductions
Start the
puzzle
If you pick "Girls' introduction" in the mode selector,
you'll be able to view the full profile of that character.
At first, you'll only be able to choose from five girls, so pay attention.
As for the other three...
You'll get a chance to enjoy your time with them once you've beaten the main game.
And that was a puzzle game for Sega Saturn—
"My Best Friends: St. Andrew Girls' School."
Get it starting on March 22nd for a recommended price of 6,800 yen, from Atlus!
My Best Friends:
St. Andrew Girls' School
Saturn compatible CD-ROM software
Recommended for ages 18 and over
Shuttle Mouse™️ compatible
Release date: March 22nd
Recommended price: 6,800 yen
RAW by John
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by JmePenseBon