It's so beautiful...
The longer you look,
the more it seems to draw you in...
It's showing us those beautiful stars
because our hearts are beautiful.
Yeah...
Can we really get the Rido with this, Liot?
Yeah. It's an ancient lens called the Eye of Zalem.
That lens is the key to the Rido lying in Zalem.
Then let's hurry to Zalem, Liot!
Not so fast...
First, we go to Zygoa.
Zygoa?
Yes.
That's where the owner
of the other Eye of Zalem lives.
Le Deus
Demon Realm Side Story
Motsureru jaggy beat sono te o hodoite
(I untangled the jaggy beats that were holding me down)
Kodoku na yoru eranda no ne hajimete jibun de
(For the first time, I chose a lonely night)
Anata no step midareteru
(Your steps are growing fainter)
Nagareru seaside breeze kokoro o shizumete
(As the softly blowing seaside breeze calms my heart)
Omoide-iro ni somerarete yuku nagisa no balcony
(This balcony overlooking the sea attains the hue of my memories)
Anata no kage tooku naru
(And your shadow gradually fades)
Hitomi tojireba baby kata o karite nemuritai yo
(When I close my eyes, baby,)
(I want to fall asleep leaning on your shoulder)
Dakishimetai kedo ima koso say good bye
(I want to hug you tight, but it's time to say good bye)
Midnight shout! I'm a Star dust
Mayonaka no challenger
(A midnight challenger)
Kinou yori tashika na ashita o tataku
(I knock on the gate of tomorrow that's more certain than yesterday)
Midnight shout! Mystery dash!
Hashiru koto yametara
(As soon as I stop running)
Ah... yume wa yume no mama de owari sa
(Ah, my dreams will fizzle out unfulfilled)
Midnight shout! Mystery dash!
Hashiru koto yametara
(As soon as I stop running)
Ah... yume wa yume no mama de owari sa
(Ah, my dreams will fizzle out unfulfilled)
Tell me! Out with it!
Where is the Eye of Zalem?
We found out that you're a descendant of Zalem!
No! I don't know what you're talking about!
I'll break your fingers next, one by one...
This one looks more cooperative.
The old man can't hear us very well. So...
Would you tell me what
I want to hear, my young friend?
He gave the l-lens to some guy called L-Liot.
What? To Liot?
Y-You idiot!
Well then...
You'd better tell me where he is now.
L-Liot...! Z-Zalem...!
Come one, come all!
Go ahead and take a closer
look at my wares, dear customer!
We have lots of fine goods!
My wares are the only reason to come to Zygoa!
Wear this and you'll conquer
the heart of any man you want!
Come on!
I'm bored...
You must be Yuta la Caradeen.
Old Randall from the
Shirale Valley told me to see you.
Randall? Oh, that Randall!
This is his message.
The Eye of Zalem invites misfortune.
I'd like you to give it to Liot.
And there you have it.
Now give me the lens
that looks just like this one.
Liot! Do you have to
flirt with every girl you meet?
He isn't flirting with me!
Do you always treat your customers like this?
Only the rude ones.
I feel sorry for your boyfriend.
I don't have one!
Figures.
D-Damn you!
What's going on?
What are you waiting for?!
Go and do something about this mess!
I helped you already, didn't I?
If you want to fight, do it somewhere else!
Oh, fine.
Geez!
Kaiser, give me the status report.
Sir, the Rido excavation
project in Zalem is going well.
I hope you won't repeat your past mistakes.
Don't let Liot overtake you again.
Sir!
You must not fail me this time.
If you do, you'll answer for it with your life.
Yes, sir! I'll live up to your expectations!
Spica! Seneca! Keep back!
-Okay!
-Are you sure?
I can handle them by myself.
Now, give me your Eye of Zalem.
Unfortunately for you,
the only eyes I have are my own.
The sheer nerve of you...
Ordinary humans like
you can't hope to defeat me!
Get him!
What do you think you're doing?!
Take him out already!
Hurray!
One against three.
The odds aren't in his favor.
Shall we help out?
How? They look so formidable...
Look no further.
-There!
-Hold on!
Whoa! Y-You idiot!
Dammit!
Let's retreat for now.
You shall pay for this, Liot!
I'll send you a postcard!
Bye-bye! See you again!
You stupid girls! The situation
wasn't dangerous enough to use those!
Really? We thought you were losing.
So what? That's no reason
to throw the Hiss Candy at me!
I tried to stop her.
That's not fair! It seemed
like the best move at the moment!
Listen here!
This is the bill for
the damages to my shop.
Ouch!
Don't even think about dodging the bill!
Erm... We're poor,
so how about a monthly payment?
No!
-There's only one way I could pay it off.
-How?
If you give me the Eye of Zalem,
I'll use it to find a treasure.
What's the secret of the Eye of Zalem?
Well...
Look! The lens!
I'll give this to you on one condition.
One condition?
Moron!
I'm sorry, sir...
Liot has thwarted our plans again!
Have you located the other descendant?
Not yet, sir.
You were fixated on Liot to
the detriment of everything else....
Why do you think Liot went to Zygoa?
He went there to get the other lens!
T-That means...?
The other descendant of Zalem lives in Zygoa,
and yet you allowed Liot to get there first!
Do you speak of the
girl who works in that store?
Exactly. Bring that girl to me,
along with the Eye of Zalem.
Why did you decide to tag along?
You'd simply run away
unless I kept an eye on you.
Our journey is full of grave dangers.
A perfect way to stave off boredom.
You never run out of retorts, do you?
Have a Jigu fruit. You should eat something.
A Jigu fruit? What's this?
Those fruits are very nutritious.
One will last you a whole day.
They're our favorite food.
I'll try it, then.
Yuck! It tastes terrible!
Hmph!
What was that for?!
Get back here!
Are you finished yet?
Yeah.
You ate a Jigu fruit?
That's the Planas' food!
It doesn't taste good for us.
Planas?
Oh, didn't I tell you about Seneca and Spica?
They belong to another species.
They aren't exactly human beings.
What? They're not human?
No, they're Planas. In other words,
artificial life-forms grown from polytron artificial cells.
Artificial life-forms?
Yeah.
Those two were born to be my partners.
Just who are you three?
-Ordinary treasure hunters, looking for the treasure of Rido.
-Rido?
Do you know the legend
of the ancient Quall civilization?
I've heard of it.
It was destroyed several centuries ago.
The ancient Quall people had a treasure of sorts...
A type of mineral that can provide infinite energy—Rido.
As the legacy of their civilization, the Quall people hid a
few small deposits of that mineral somewhere on this planet.
The ruins of Zalem are one such place.
Zalem...
Where did they wander off to?
They must be flirting
with each other as we speak.
What do you think about it?
We gotta stop them!
You know Liot.
He has a thing for girls like her.
Puru, come closer to the surface!
Puru, let's play again some other day!
Liot...
What'll you do after you find Rido, the treasure of Zalem?
Will you live the rest of your days in luxury?
Regrettably, that lifestyle doesn't interest me.
I'm not the type to stay
in one place for long, you know.
Then, why...?
I don't want it to fall into the
hands of Demster and his gang.
Rido has the power to
save people if it's used correctly.
There's someone I want to help.
Who?
My sister was injured in an accident.
Now she's suspended in stasis.
I need the Rido to bring her back to life.
Let's go to sleep.
We have to get up early tomorrow.
Damn it... The entrance to Zalem
is supposed to be around here...
Liot!
Yeah?
Look! There are towers around the lake!
Around the lake?
Not you again!
It's time you paid for your impudence, Liot!
If you want to save her life,
you'd better give me the lens.
L-Liot!
Alright.
Good. Put it on the ground and step back.
I've got the lens.
Here's your change!
Hey! Are you all right?
-Yeah!
-Oh, I'm covered in soot!
What do we do now?
We go after Yuta, of course.
But how?
Which way did they go?
Back into the lake they came from.
But where exactly?
Could there be an underwater passage?
Can you find the tunnel entrance underwater?
I'm trying to!
What if we can't find it?
We keep searching. It's a slow process.
No arguing with that.
If only you could detect each other
over long distances, like we can...
Detect each other...? Wait a moment!
You made her eat a Jigu fruit, right?
Yeah, but she spat it out straight away.
What a waste of food...
That's it!
Welcome, Yuta la Caradeen.
Or should I say, Kladinova Rei?
How do you know my name?
I made detailed inquiries about you.
I discovered you were
a descendant of the Priests of Zalem.
T-That's...
It was easy to find the other four
Zalem descendants. They were all old men.
I couldn't imagine that the owner of the other lens,
the fifth Zalem descendant, would be a young girl.
Those old men were all tight-mouthed...
They could have lived longer,
had they been more obliging.
You murderer!
Bad temper is in your blood, I see...
Well then, will you hand
over the last Eye of Zalem?
If you want me to spare your life, that is...
Mabuta wo tojitara
(Once you close your eyes,)
Kimi no festa ga hajimaru
(Your festa will begin)
Maketemo suteki na yuuki kitto wasurenai
(Even if you lose, I won't forget your wonderful courage)
Senakagoshi ni ryoute ippai no smile for you
(Look back, and you'll see a handful of smiles for you)
Koe ni naranai ai ga hajiketeru
(My love surges out, though I can't put it into words)
Fortunately, the juice of the Jigu fruit which Yuta ate contains polytrons.
Detectable traces will remain in her
body for the next three or four days.
Asa ga kuru made soba ni iteageru smile again
(I will stay by your side until the dawn, so smile again)
I found her, Liot!
There's a chasm dead ahead!
Alright!
Hoshizora mo kimi no tame ni dake oritekita...
(The starry cloak of night descended just for you...)
At last, the Rido will be ours!
The ancient Quall writing...
"If the one who serves me touches the crystal
embedded in my forehead, the door of life will be opened."
Damn it!
"The one who serves me..."
So only the descendants of
Zalem Priests can open the way?!
Bring the girl to me!
Yes, sir!
Might as well be a maze, dammit!
Turn right, Liot!
Okay!
Now turn left!
Whoa!
Who could've guessed the
exit would be through a waterfall?
Liot, over there!
Excellent. Come on up here.
Now, touch the crystal before you.
Yuta!
You didn't make it in time.
The lock to the treasure is open!
I'm grabbing the Rido.
My gang will keep you occupied in the meantime.
Where am I?
Yuta!
Liot!
I had no idea the dungeon
under the temple was full of traps.
No!
Let me go!
You don't need me anymore!
Not so fast. You're staying
with me until I get the Rido.
Spica!
On it!
Spica, Seneca—handle the rest!
The flow of the water's too fast. In that case...!
At last, it's mine!
Rido, the source of infinite energy
that powered the ancient Quall civilization...
Now that I have it,
I can easily conquer the world!
From now on, I am the ruler of the world!
You aren't going anywhere.
I'll use you to entrap and kill Liot.
What?!
Yuta!
Liot!
Yuta?
Idiot! You shouldn't have
removed the Rido from sacred water!
What?
The moment you take the Rido from
the sacred water, it begins to release its energy!
In other words—you made a
mistake at the last possible moment!
Where's the Rido, Liot? What happened to it?
It's gone for good!
What?! But we came all the way here!
We could always look for another one!
Anyhow, pick up the pace.
The underground realm's collapsing.
But why?
The ancient Quall people used
the Rido as the core of this realm.
When the Rido disappears...
...this realm collapses likewise.
-Liot!
-Are you okay?
Of course! More importantly,
let's get out of here—this realm is collapsing!
Seneca, summon Puru!
I did so long ago!
He must be in the sea nearby.
I bet he's just messing around!
Liot! You won't get out of here alive!
Oh, really? I wonder about that.
Le Deus!
That's Le Deus.
Le Deus?
Yeah.
Seneca, Spica—take Yuta and get away!
Yes, sir!
We've suffered enough at your hands!
Now the tables have turned!
Bring him down!
Die!
Liot!
Over here!
I see you got out safely.
Of course we did!
Liot!
Liot! Time and again you thwarted
my plans! Today, I'll return the favor!
Tch! So you haven't
died with the city of Zalem, huh?
I'll have to personally finish you off!
Enough talking!
Not so fast!
Liot...
Huh?
He's more powerful than I am!
Come on! Aren't you tired of running yet?
You wish! The real fight's just beginning!
The angels of victory are on my side!
Angels, you say? Well, I don't see any!
Die!
Le Deus!
Synchroid Twin!
I'm counting on you, ladies!
Yes, sir!
Say your prayers!
Weapons selection: Hypersword!
Yes, sir!
I owe you one, girls!
The target is on the move!
Thirty degrees to the left!
Roger!
Weapons selection: Spin Cracker!
Shoot!
The target is moving again!
What?!
Seneca, Spica! It's time to finish him off!
Yes, sir!
Deploying the ultimate weapon!
Shadow Flare!
The likes of you couldn't defeat me...
I won't accept this...!
Done and dusted at last.
Nicely done!
Having said that,
the Rido was almost within my grasp...
Such is life.
We'll get another chance someday.
That's right.
I wonder—where's Yuta?
Liot!
You aren't going to leave me behind, are you?
Don't forget about this!
T-The bill...!
And here I hoped she'd forget about it...
She's so damn pushy!
Seems like I'm stuck
with another piece of baggage...
What did you mean by that, Liot?
Er, well, see, in other words...
I won't be getting bored any time soon.
Kazoekirenai ai wo kono sora ni kazarou
(I'll decorate the sky with countless displays of my love)
Itsuka kimi ni todoku you ni
(I hope one day it reaches you)
Sore ga boku no aurora sa
(That's what my aurora is)
Hyakuoku nen tatte mo
(Though ten billion years may pass,)
Kawaranai hikari de
(its light will never fade)
Itsumo kimi wo mimamoru kara
(I will always keep watching over you)
Mayowanaide ikiteite
(So live out your life without doubts)
Haruka na sora ni
(In the faraway sky)
Ah, kirameku aurora dream
(Ah, a shining aurora dream)
Itoshii hito yo, sono hitomi de uketomete
(My dearest, I hope you will notice and accept it)
Miageru sora ni
(Whenever you look at the sky,)
Ah, mabushii aurora dream
(You'll see a dazzling aurora dream)
Hitori janai sa
(You are not alone)
Donna toki mo kono ai wa shine on you
(My love will always shine on you)
Haruka na sora ni
(In the faraway sky)
Ah, kirameku aurora dream
(Ah, a shining aurora dream)
Itoshii hito yo, sono hitomi de uketomete
(My dearest, I hope you will notice and accept it)
Miageru sora ni
(Whenever you look at the sky,)
Ah, mabushii aurora dream
(You'll see a dazzling aurora dream)
Hitori janai sa
(You are not alone)
Donna toki mo kono ai wa shine on you
(My love will always shine on you)
Tabitatsu sora ni
(Whenever you go on a journey,)
Subbed by:
LonelyDildo
(LonelyChaser & perevodildo)
Project Manager:
MartyMcflies
Raw Encoding:
tanks404
Raw Acquisition:
Noodles
Timing & Translation:
Yume
TLC & Typesetting:
perevodildo
QC:
Muzussawa
Thanks for
watching!
Ah, kirameku aurora dream...
(A shining aurora dream will be seen in the sky...)