We Are Mangaka
The Story of Tokiwa-sou
009, Doraemon, Tensai Bakabon, and so on.
The authors of these manga, now so familiar
to you, spent their youths honing their craft.
Our wonderful animation will
showcase those days, full of tears and laughter.
Coming up — NISSAY Family Special:
"We Are Mangaka—The Story of Tokiwa-sou"
Please look forward to it!
We Are Mangaka
The Story of Tokiwa-sou
I bet you remember them, too
The hallways and rooms of that dormitory
And the rain puddles you saw from the window
Though the rain has already let up,
The rain puddles in that town never went away
That's what...
That's what our youth was all about
With a squint, you too could also see it
Here's a volume of manga.
Can you imagine the shock this tattered
book had on the young minds of bygone days?
It was released on April 1st, 1947.
Written by...
"Written by Osamu Tezuka"
Osamushi Tezuka?
Isn't that read as Jimushi?
Jichuu?
Or perhaps not?
Written by Harumushi Tezuka, huh?
Those comics might as
well have been written by a god.
With their own eyes,
the boys saw cars rushing forward.
With their own ears,
they heard the roar of the engine.
What gave this manga such an exciting effect?
The boys had no idea whatsoever.
Stop drawing cartoons
all the time! Focus on your studies!
Alright then...
Crap...!
Relax, Sho.
That you, sis?
"Manga Shounen"
This came in the mail.
Whoa! "Manga Shounen"—
I made sure to keep it hidden.
Congratulations, Sho.
You've been published again.
Hurray!
Though, you're the only
one to ever congratulate me...
I'm sure everyone will appreciate it now.
You're on a publishing streak, after all.
You have what it takes to become a pro.
Do you really think so?
A pro...
I'd sure like to become one.
That's why I'll have to move to Tokyo.
Let's dig in!
Thanks for the food!
Ow!
I messed it up again.
Here we go.
This will do. Let's begin!
Ouch!
That hurt!
I'm almost done.
Coming through!
What gives?!
Will it arrive, or not?
Of course it will.
He said so, but...
I've waited for long enough!
I give up!
You have mail.
C-C-Coming!
Ouch...
Nothing inside?
I thought I heard it...
"To: Hiroshi Fujimoto"
"From: Osamu Tezuka"
It's here! At last, it arrived!
I knew it'd arrive!
Wow, it really is from Mr. Tezuka.
Told you so, didn't I?
I knew he'd answer!
That's my line.
Whatever. It doesn't really matter.
He thinks our manga's very fun,
and even wants us to come visit!
Visit him? All the way to Tokyo?
That's out of the question, Abiko!
Exactly, Fujimoto. The two of us...
...are going to Tokyo...
...in order...
...to draw manga!
That's right!
Hup!
This is the Tokiwa-sou dormitory.
"Tokiwa-sou"
Police box
Stationery
store
Tokiwa-sou
Food market
Telephone exchange
Hup!
Ah, here they come!
Goodbye, then.
-Thank you!
-Thanks a lot!
Welcome, Hachigo.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Please take care of us.
No need for that.
Leave the formalities at the door.
Just call me Mr. Tera.
Shall I help you with your luggage?
Life's going to be
livelier with you guys here.
Mr. Tezuka's old room is surely
too small for the two of you, eh?
Nope, it's way too big for us.
And... here.
Mr. Tezuka's deposit really helped us out.
What's more, we get to use his old desk!
The two of us, Fujiko Fujio,
get to live here from today on.
"Beware of fires"
So this is the kitchen?
You're cooking by yourselves, too?
Do you have any utensils?
Well, the thing is...
We've got no proper pot to steam the rice in.
This pot right here is good enough.
See?
For real?
So we put the rice in. What next?
How would I know when you don't?
Shall we go ask Mr. Tera again?
I don't feel like bothering
him about every little thing.
That's right.
Hang in there.
"Encyclopedia"
An encyclopedia?
It was pretty pricey for a second-hand book.
I bet it’s got a section on cooking rice.
So far, so good...
Fujimoto! What's wrong? What happened?!
Hey, what happened to you?
Look!
The rice cooked nicely!
It's a miracle!
We might be the first people to ever
use an encyclopedia as a rice-cooking guide.
"Encyclopedia"
Hey!
Do you need anything?
Excuse me, are you Fujiko Fujio?
And you are...?
Suzuki Shin'ichi.
"Manga Shounen"
The Rookie of the Year from Manga Shounen!
Yeah.
My pen name's Kazetarou.
That's right, Mr. Tera told us about you.
You live in Tokiwa-sou too, right?
The more, the merrier! Pleased to meet you.
The pleasure is ours.
Excuse me, which way to Tokiwa-sou?
Tokiwa-sou?
That's how you get there!
001!
Here's Tokiwa-sou.
Mr. Terada!
Hey.
Come in.
Welcome, Onodera.
Name's Ishimori.
Ah, I see.
Your pen name's
Kuni no Ishimori-Chou, is it?
I'm Fujio Akatsuka. Nice to meet you.
Hey, so you came already.
Together with Mr. Akatsuka, I see.
It's going to become
even livelier around here.
So Mr. Tezuka used to live in this room?
Did he leave these marks with his thumbtacks?
I'm so glad to breathe the same air as him!
Stop that!
Don't waste all the precious air!
See the moldy spot over there?
That's where the drunken editor used to urinate.
-He could reach pretty far, I see.
-Yeah.
Can I reach that far...?
Hey! Anything but that, okay?
Huh? What's up with this hole?
Mr. Tezuka must've kicked through in his sleep.
Oh? That was one impressive kick.
We're ready to celebrate your moving. Come to Mr. Tera's place.
-About time!
-Coming!
Hey, don't leave me behind!
Ow!
What is it?
Shush. An editor is here.
What manga would you like me to draw?
W-Well...
Well, that's simple...
Something that sells, something popular.
Are popularity and sales all that matters to you?
Such a thought has never crossed my mind.
A manga should speak to the
children's hearts, and grasp their imagination.
That's what a proper manga should be.
Y-You put it like that, but...
A manga which grasps the children's imagination.
One that connects with the children's hearts.
Listen, did we ever consider any of this?
Nope...
I've been drawing what I wanted.
Nothing else to it.
This is hopeless!
Hey. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Come right in, don't be shy.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Alright, cheers!
Let's draw manga that can
keep the children truly entertained.
Exciting...
...and fun manga.
Manga offers unlimited freedom of expression!
Let's bring manga to a whole new level,
with adventures and experiments!
As for my manga...
What kind of manga would I like to draw...?
We can do this!
More and more of those slackers living up there...
Hey! Keep it down, will you?!
A sorry lot of adults obsessed with cartoons!
Well, nothing wrong about that.
For your information, I'm worried
about the future of Japanese literature!
I'm feeling it for real!
Right here in m-muh heart!
-Pokkun pokkun!
-That's right!
So that's where you were...
Sho.
Take care of it.
I will. Thanks.
I hope it's not too
embarrassing as a farewell gift.
O-Of course not!
You made it for me, after all.
I'll treasure it.
You were the very first
person to praise my manga, after all.
Achoo! Kemunpas-choo! Achoo!
Here we go.
H-Hey, what are you doing?
Whoa...!
On cold days, stay in your bedroll to keep warm!
Topsy-turvy!
Hey, Fuu. Huh?
What are you doing?
Up we go...
Isn't it obvious?
This way, even a single futon can keep you warm.
I see...
Well then, good night.
There...
It's like you're an apprentice to
some wise hermit! So philosophical!
Fuu's the real weird one.
He's obsessed with animation.
Animation?
Yeah. You know,
the movies with moving drawings.
Making those is a very painstaking job.
One day, I'd like to make some, too...
But I'm nowhere near as good as Fuu is.
We poke each other with
a pen if we doze off, remember?
You're right...
Remember the promise, man?
Oh well.
-Wanna fight?!
-Bring it on!
The editor's coming!
What now?
We'll need one more day to wrap this up.
Hey, man...
We surrender!
Our deepest apologies! It isn't ready yet!
If at all p-possible, please give us one more day!
"Bread"
It's just me, guys.
Mr. Tera!
I brought snacks.
Starving won't do your health any good!
Here.
You can eat this with just one hand.
Thank you.
Let's dig in!
I appreciate Mr. Tera's gesture.
But after surviving on nothing but bread
for days, even the sight of it makes me uneasy.
"Year-End Big Sale"
Hey, Mr. Akatsuka.
Found it...
Good morning.
I'm going home. I'll be back in a week.
A lot of luggage you've got there.
Souvenirs?
Something like that.
Well, have a happy New Year.
Oh, wow!
So you're going home to do laundry?
Yeah, that's about right.
Wow! Nice one!
No! I can do better!
You can win this! Hurry up!
Don't rush me!
Just like I thought.
I dropped five yen down there.
Now, what should I buy with these?
This is all I have to my name.
And it has to last me for a week,
until Mr. Ishimori returns.
What can I buy with 28 yen?
This calls for careful consideration.
Yep, let's go with that.
I'm going to cook some soup!
"Soy sauce"
If I slice it super thin,
it'll look like there's more of it.
Was that a tad too thin?
Looks yummy.
I can stretch this until Mr. Ishimori comes back.
Hey.
Happy New Year.
Same to you.
Turns out you're the only tenant
who stayed here for the holidays.
Yeah.
Aren't you going home too, sir?
Nope. My wife and
children did, but I have unfinished work.
Is that so?
Life isn't easy for you.
Indeed. I can't even
get a break during the holidays.
Now then...
What a nice smell!
No... It's nothing special.
Would you like some?
W-Well, don't concern yourself with me...
Having said that, I wouldn't
mind some to warm up my bones.
Smells yummy!
I feel warmer already.
And the taste isn't half bad either! This soup is something else!
Really?
How about another serving?
Who could've guessed
you were this great of a cook?
I'll help myself, then.
Yum!
I ended up staying for dinner.
Sorry for imposing.
I'll be going now.
-I look forward to working with you next year.
-Sure. See ya.
It could as well have been licked clean...
Oh, I almost forgot.
You have what it takes to draw a real
masterpiece one day. I can't wait to see it.
Glad to be working with you.
The Little World of Don Camillo.
The Caine Mutiny.
Yep, this will keep the drafts away.
And done.
This feels no different from a bedroll.
How am I supposed to
get by starting tomorrow?
Do I give up on cooking
and survive on mochi alone?
I can't stand winters.
Summer can't come any sooner.
Summer has come! It's here!
Be it plains or mountains,
the summer rolls on through!
"Ice"
I'm stumped.
This is no good.
I need a desk, after all.
I need one, yet I can't afford it.
That's it!
I have a sheet of plywood stashed.
Yes, this is perfect!
Like this...
And done!
An Akatsuka-style budget desk!
Now I just gotta wait for a new client.
Gotta hurry...!
You here, Mr. Ishimori?
Mr. Fujiko, what about you?
Mr. Terada! Mr. Tsuzuki!
Anyone will do...!
Say, could you draw a
panel for me? This is urgent!
Okay, I've been waiting
for it. It'll be done in a jiffy.
Go all out. I'm counting on you.
Alright.
At last, my chance has come!
If I manage to capitalize on it,
I'll be hired as a monthly author!
Mr. Akatsuka? What's on your mind,
Mr. Akatsuka? Keep drawing.
O-Okay. I'll make it quick.
Pick up the pace.
I'm almost done. Full steam ahead!
Er...
This won't do. Sorry,
but I'll have to find someone else.
Gotta hurry!
Damn it all! If only I had a proper desk...
You little...!
Nyarome!
How refreshing.
Huh? What are you doing?
Trying to cool off, is it?
I'm too broke to go to a bathhouse.
Well then, count me in.
This can't replace a real bath, though.
No, it'll do just fine. This is more
relaxing than a trip to a bathhouse.
See? Pure bliss, right?
You can say that again.
There! Take this!
You can't just catch a
cold and leave me hanging!
I've reserved the pages for your chapter...
Don't worry, I'll have it done in time.
It'll be okay.
Our dorm is full of people who could help.
I'll hold you to your word, Mr. Ishimori.
He'd better hurry up...
My head...
Was last night's makeshift bath a bad idea?
Mr. Akatsuka, help me!
SOS!
What happened?
I wonder...
In times of need,
persevere and support each other!
Also, be nice to animals!
Mr. Nagatani is here! The cavalry has arrived!
Did you catch a cold, Mr. Ishimori?
Yeah. Sorry for bothering you.
How bad is it?
Don't worry, I'll manage.
Let's begin.
Mr. Akatsuka, the outlines are all yours.
As for the finishing touches...
Leave them to me.
Okay. I appreciate it.
You're working so fast, despite the fever.
Watch out.
For what?
It'd be bad if you got sick, too.
If that happens,
I'll simply ask you to lend a hand.
What are you working
on these days, Mr. Akatsuka?
Well...
A volume of a shoujo manga.
I've managed to land an order at last.
And it's so fun!
Having been bullied by her
stepmother, a girl runs away from home.
She's being chased by a gang, enters a
circus troupe, and breaks her legs in an accident.
Who am I kidding?
Such a stale, cliched story would never...
Did I really catch a cold?
All of this is wrong...
This isn't the story I want to write.
It should be something...
something much more extravagant!
"Chawanmushi"
That's a great one.
That plot twist at the end was so sudden!
Right, Mr. Akatsuka?
Huh? You watched it, too?
Mr. Ishimori invited me.
Twists are fine and all, but the
punchlines to the gags could've been better.
Hang on there.
We've gathered to talk about new manga, right?
Wouldn't it be better to research
manga instead of discussing movies?
I believe movies make
important research material, too.
You won't become a proper mangaka
if you limit yourself to reading manga alone.
It's not like you can't stomach movies, right?
Of course I like them.
But we'd benefit more from studying drawing!
Now, now.
We can continue this discussion over dinner.
What would you like?
Mr. Akatsuka, do you have any money
for food? I've spent mine on movie tickets.
Come on, you know the answer already.
What about you?
I spent mine on books.
Same here.
Are you for real?
So you spent all of your
food money on movies and books?
Yeah, that's about right.
You need to spend money more consciously!
Oh well. I'll treat you to dinner today.
We appreciate it, Mr. Tera.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
These guys are so intense.
While I have a home in Tokyo,
they've got no backup options.
And yet, they readily spend
their food money on books and movies.
"Now showing: Swan Lake"
"Coming next week"
It seems as if they're fooling around, but really,
they're just spending their savings on study materials.
Gotta hurry... Gotta hurry!
Gotta hurry!
And now, a national weather forecast.
Excuse me!
Tonight, a warm front will roll in, bringing cloudy weather.
In areas here and there, prolonged rain is likely at around one.
So you bought a TV, Mr. Fujiko?
In some places, it may change into a snowfall.
Er, I urgently need you to draw 16 pages...
As such, Boss Kokoro recommends
you to prepare the appropriate rain gear.
This wraps up the weather forecast.
I have a commission for you!
Shh!
I gotta hurry up, or else I won't make it...
That's it! What about Mr. Ishimori?
Excuse me!
Unlocked? How careless of him...
Hey. Did you want anything?
"Standalone TV set"
He bought a TV, too?!
Mr. Tera! Mr. Ishimori bought a huge one!
A big TV is so much more impressive.
And it was cheaper than I expected.
So, when's the deadline?
Huh? Er...
Well, take your sweet time.
It's gotten quiet all of a sudden.
Now we can finally watch TV in peace.
I can hear the violin from this speaker.
This stereo player is a great
achievement of our civilization.
What's that?!
While I don't have a player, I get to work while listening
to famous classical and jazz tunes. This is what I call luxury.
Oh! I'm not done reading this one yet.
Right... Sci-fi is so great, I must say.
The universe stretches on endlessly!
No, I prefer him masked.
What am I going to do
about their faces, though?
Try sketching them in various poses first.
I have to flesh out
the supporting roles as well...
I laughed just now.
This story might've been short, but I enjoyed it.
The children who read manga are no different.
I want to draw manga that makes people laugh.
Whoa there, time to put up a curtain.
Hey! Do you realize how late it is?!
Good heavens...
They've fallen asleep at last.
So they've been sneakily wasting electricity!
Nine servings of ramen, please.
Quickly, please.
Nine servings of ramen, right?
One serving of ramen for me, please.
Aye! Ten servings, coming right up!
Can't waste any time!
And done!
Thanks for the food.
And now, time to continue.
Do your best!
A popular one. Something that sells well.
That's one depressive outlook on the world of manga.
Consider the readers' impressions instead,
and how you can express yourself through manga.
That's what you should focus on.
I know this much, but...
So, what do you think?
I've decided to take a fresh start
and write a manga centered on comedy.
In other words—
"Akakka-kun"
I won't accept this.
So it's no good?
Well, let's just say it's mediocre.
Hurry up and draw the
new manga we already agreed on.
With that, I'll be going.
You there, Mr. Akatsuka?
Hey, wanna see a movie?
The deadlines are nearing.
I see.
Some other time, then.
Mr. Ishimori has it great.
Adventures and experiments...
Ah, I nearly forgot.
Wh-What is it?
Your share for helping
with my manga the other day.
Ah, thanks.
Should I simply
become Mr. Ishimori's assistant?
Also, the shoujo manga you've lent me...
It wasn't half bad.
Thanks.
Being praised feels nice,
but that isn't the type of manga I want to draw.
The water's so cold!
Good morning.
Morning.
You're up so early... Another all-nighter?
Yeah. You too?
Nope. My sister's coming to visit.
I'm off to Ueno to pick her up.
Oh?
Your sister?
Hello.
I saw a stunning beauty in the kitchen just now.
That's what you call a jewel in a dunghill.
Such a pretty girl in our humble dorm?
It's hard to believe.
Let me introduce you.
This is my sister, Yoshie.
Thanks for watching over my brother.
Huh?! So it's her?
Why are you so surprised?
W-Well, you see...
What?! S-So this is y-your sister?!
Don't be this shocked.
My bad. Nice to meet you.
I-Is she...?!
I've had enough of you all!
Do you have enough soy sauce?
If you need a pot, here's one.
You can also use our bowls.
I could light a fire for you!
Keep your hands off my sis!
Mr. Akatsuka?
Are you done with your work?
Nope.
He seems to be having a hard time...
Welcome.
That's it...
Even I can hold a job like that.
I've lost all desire to draw manga...
Are you here, Mr. Tera?
I see, I see.
This is the perfect time to call it quits.
I'm still young enough
to reconsider my perspectives.
Can I take a look?
Huh?
Show me the manga you've just finished.
Here.
I can't continue, no matter how hard I try.
I'd separate this manuscript into five different manga.
It begins as shoujo, then branches
into sports, comedy, and even action.
Isn't it overloaded?
You jump from one topic to the next,
which is why overall consistency suffers.
Now that you mention it—that's how I feel, too.
And then I start to panic.
No need to rush.
You can focus on
each of these topics separately.
Didn't you come to live with us
in order to become a mangaka?
Keep trying until your dream comes true.
Alright, I'll try again.
Take this, Akatsuka.
You're short on money, right?
You can use this for now.
Thanks for the loan, Mr. Tera.
This can last me for a whole year!
He can't be serious...!
Mr. Tera...
Mr. Tera, I'll become a
proper mangaka against all odds!
Mr. Akatsuka, you're looking at it the wrong way.
Am I?
You are.
Girls are the most
knowledgeable about shoujo manga.
Girls?
What are you looking around for?
Well...
A girl...
Look no further.
This isn't funny!
This is Mr. Sonoyama.
He writes absurdist manga.
Nice to meet you.
There are many different people
invested in the world of manga.
And they kept gathering in
this dorm, as if drawn by a magnet.
The seeds sown by Osamu Tezuka
are steadily sprouting one by one.
That's how it all started.
Ugh!
They're obsessed with
comics day in and day out!
What of Japanese literature?
Stop grumbling already.
If you give it a chance,
it's a fun read in its own right.
Your standards have plummeted, too!
Whoops...
Not again!
Squeak!
Though people may cross paths,
inevitably there comes the time to say goodbye.
Ishimori's frail older sister
passed away at the tender age of 24.
A separation so untimely and unbelievable,
he felt like the pain would never end.
It's a naturalistic tale
told solely through imagery.
I decided to name it Fantasy World.
What do you think?
Is it a bit too radical?
Nope, it's great. I like it a lot.
The panel layout is so inventive!
And your sister came out so beautiful!
This is the embodiment of the "adventures
and experiments" you're always talking about.
Mr. Ishimori's style is something else, alright.
Let's do our best, too. Can't let him outdo us.
Mr. Akatsuka...
Are you working on something fun?
Yeah. I've noted down heaps of ideas.
I'll expand on them whenever an opportunity arises.
Sis...
Please read it.
I'm coming in.
Hey, welcome.
My deadline is still a ways off, right?
Well, I'm in a tight spot myself.
There's a hole in the next issue.
What happened?
The planned eight-page gag
manga oneshot fell through...
I wonder if anyone could pull an
all-nighter and write a replacement...
That's a tall order, isn't it?
Ah, I know the perfect author for you.
That's right. Of course you don't...
What?! You know one?!
Just ask Mr. Akatsuka to draw it.
Huh? Who, me?!
His comedic timing is second to none. Right?
Y-Yeah, second to none.
Thank goodness. Please do your best.
I'll come to pick it up tomorrow morning.
Roger that.
I'll have it done by tomorrow morning.
Until then.
I'm looking forward to it.
Will he manage to
deliver on his promise, though?
What if...?
No, I've got to trust him.
Wh-What do I do now, Mr. Ishimori?
What if it turns out to be unfunny?
Just write a fun one.
You have lots of ideas
and characters noted down, don't you?
That's right!
Hey, stop that. It's too early to sleep.
Oh well.
Let's see...
This is it! Let's go with this!
"Terada"
Mr. Tera, I'll go all out.
This is my first ever commission
for the kind of manga I want to write!
I won't hold back, mark my words!
So, Mr. Ishimori,
would you listen to my ideas?
Sure, go on.
I'll make the protagonist a real brat!
And then, such-and-such, this and that!
What about this way? It'd be even more fun!
Of course! It's settled then.
Now, how should I name it?
The protagonist is bratty, so...
How does Nama-chan sound?
Good enough.
Can you wrap it up overnight?
You bet! I'll begin right away!
This gag is growing stale.
True...
Alright, here goes nothing.
And done.
Wait, is this actually fun?
Finding my own manga
funny isn't a good metric.
Take a look!
You're done already?
"I Am Nama-chan"
Seems good enough.
I'll show it to
Mr. Fujimoto and Mr. Abiko next!
This is a laugh riot!
Yeah, these gags are on a whole other level.
F-For real? Do you really mean it?
No, my friends may be
simply trying to cheer me up.
It's way too early to relax.
Yeah, this is a masterpiece.
Mr. Akatsuka, you've struck gold at long last!
Seems like they're honestly praising me.
So... do you like it?
I'm taking the manuscript as is.
I'm in a hurry.
Goodbye.
He didn't like it all that much.
"Good fortune comes to those who smile"
"Post"
Time went by. The magazine with Mr. Akatsuka's
painstakingly-created gag manga was published.
Mr. Akatsuka, your magazine has come!
"Manga King"
"New manga series"
"Nama-chan"
Wasn't it just a oneshot?
They've decided to serialize it?!
Hurray!
Congratulations, Akatsuka. It's been picked
for serialization right away. That's awesome!
All thanks to you, Mr. Tera.
If I had given up on manga that day...
This only proves how talented you are.
And that's one groundbreaking kind of a talent!
My own manga might be
getting dated in comparison to yours.
Don't say that, Mr. Tera.
I'm not giving up just yet, Akatsuka.
I'll keep drawing manga according to my own values.
And you should follow your personal way of gags.
Let's do our best!
Okay!
Faith and effort will definitely pave a way!
I've been able to come
this far thanks to everyone's support.
What's more, living in
Tokiwa-sou helped me follow my dreams.
I should extend my
thanks to the dormitory itself, too.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Huh...?!
Thank you!
I'm Hatabou!
Sheeh!
Pokkun! Pokkun! Pokkun!
I'm Hatabou!
That's right!
You dummy!
Are you going out? Rerere-no-re!
Accelerate!
Rider Kick!
Here it comes!
There!
H-Hold up! What are you doing?
Whoa there.
These dreams are far from over.
They offer infinite possibilities.
And so, life in Tokiwa-sou went on,
with youthful dreams crowding the windowsills.
That's what the early 1960s were like.
Back then, Tokiwa-sou fulfilled
its purpose as the bastion of dreams.
Now, it's quietly fading away.
The monument to the mangakas'
youth is vanishing before our eyes.
But still, are their dreams truly over?
About now, a new generation of authors follows
in their footsteps, carrying new dreams in tow.
Dreams never truly end.
My friend, my good old friend
Back then, we lived in this dormitory
It's about to disappear once and for all
But our memories will never fade
Next time we meet, why don't we go on a trip
somewhere far away, just the two of us?
Even my wife doesn't mind me leaving
her alone if she knows I'm meeting with you
My friend, my good old friend
I am fine
I am doing just fine
My friend, my good old friend
Subbed by:
LonelyDildo
Timing & Translation:
Yume
Encoding:
R
TLC:
perevodildo /
Anonymous
QC:
MartyMcflies /
imatu /
Anonymous
Special thanks to "edo999" for providing the DVD ISO
which was used to make the encode for this release.
Thanks for watching!