Feels like the sky's about to suck me right in.
They call this a sky full of falling stars.
Oh! A shooting star!
See?
Beyond that one, there's another star.
Space just goes on forever.
Kinda makes you realize
how small people really are.
Quit acting so modest.
You're the great Batsu, aren't you?
Young aspirations swell up
where it counts, huh?
Wh—
The hell, man?!
I told you to keep your jokes to yourself, dammit!
Damn, that's something else...
What if it becomes a habit?
Ah! Dammit...
Looking at all these stars makes
the daily grind feel devastatingly pointless.
I feel devastated as hell right now!
Oh, another shooting star.
Huh?
Make a wish before it burns out!
Too late, it's gone.
Ah, another one!
I want a woman! I want a woman! I want a woman!
Huh?
Kunio!
You okay?!
D-Dammit, Koshien's on the line...
C'mon, fight!
Hanasaki! Where are Batsu and Terry?!
What do they think this game is?
Koshien's at stake!
They'll come. I believe in them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yo, thanks for waiting!
Heroes show up fashionably late...
Told you so.
ustaB
Batsu
yrreT
Terry
Batsu
Yoo-hoo, Kunio!
Anne!
Yoo-hoo!
You okay, Anne?!
Clumsy me...
Anne...
I just love riding the bike.
Ta-daa!
No way!
Y-You okay?
Which one of us are you asking?!
Kunio! You're pushing it too hard!
Goodbye, Kunio...
That's bold.
What a waste!
She could've just given it away.
Ow!
Later.
Wait a sec! What do you mean by that?
She needs me.
Give it up. She'll just turn you down.
It's not about whether she dumps me or not!
You piss me off, you know that?
Why don't you go die in a ditch?
You're asking for it!
You bastard! You think you're funny?!
And you think you're a hit with the ladies?
Exactly!
She needs someone kind and sensitive right now.
Yo, girl, what're you doing out here?
How about going out with us?
It's a brand-new ride. Let's go for a spin.
C'mon, don't play hard to get.
At least talk to us a little.
Where you headed?
We'll give you a lift.
No, thanks.
Aw, come on, hang out with us, why don't you!
Relax, it's just for a sec. C'mon.
What're you doing?! Let go!
Let me go!
Hey, hold it right there—whoa!
W-What the hell?!
Y-You prick!
Ow...
Long time no see, sunshine.
Tacchan!
B-Battery...
Crooked Tacchan,
Snap-in-Half-Tacchan is here!
Kyaa! Gross!
Still crooked as ever, huh?
Crooked, crooked!
Shut it! You bastards ruined a perfect moment!
Snap-in-Half-Tacchan, Snap-in-Half-Tacchan!
Tatsuo-san, who the hell are these guys?
Ah, Snapped-in-Half! I'm so Snapped-in-Half!
I'll kill you!
Wanna hear Tatsuo's little secret?
What the hell do you want?!
See, this real important thing of his is—
Ugh! Shut your mouth, you rat bastard!
Aw, poor guy.
Hey, Yoshio, you okay?
That was slick back there.
Huh?
Yoshio...
Though maybe you jumped the gun a little.
It's a long hike to the station from here.
You punks!
And that heap of a car won't get you far.
I'm not the same guy I used to be.
I'll give you a taste of hell!
Well, no worries as long as we're around.
Hey, Bachan!
Watch out, this guy's dangerous.
Look who's talking—
your dirty little motives are showing!
Y-You lookin' down on me?! You pricks...
You punks! Quit standin' around—waste 'em!
Sorry, but hang tight a sec.
Whoa! You swine!
What if you'd hit a lady?!
Hey! Hey, hey!
What the hell are you savages doing?!
What's this, Tatsuo—
ditching baseball to go pro in boxing?
Jackass...
Shut up!
Phew... Not again!
Feel good pounding on your cute little lackeys?
You brats are dead meat!
So, how's that? Straightened you out a little?
I kinda feel sorry for your lackeys—
letting such a wimp boss them around.
That's right.
Hey! W-Whatcha doing?!
H-Hey, hey, hey! Cut it out! Stop! Stop, dammit!
Oopsie-daisy...
On a dry street corner in the afternoon,
Hop on?
Huh? Who are you?
Got a special seat reserved for you!
The two who just decided to break up
I'm Batsu!
And I'm Terry!
Didn't catch your name last time—what is it?
Anne.
As if continuing to believe in their path,
What was that? Couldn't hear ya!
Anne. My name's Anne.
they gazed into each other's sad eyes
The pounding in their hearts can no longer be stopped
Yoshio, Kazu—how long you gonna lie there?
What the hell's going on?
Don't get off, you idiots!
Follow Wind
What are we supposed to do?!
We can love each other again, with all our hearts, innocently
Wait! Hold on!
All the ways we pass each other by
Hold still! Don't move a muscle!
One wrong move and I'm finished!
Follow Wind
Man, the heavens sure got it in for us.
We face our sadness together, and, driven by the tailwind,
we return to this town and this dream
Right when we're about to start our youth, too.
Guess they're jealous of us.
Damn sky, screw you!
Stop here a sec.
Eh? Huh?
I've got things to do. Thanks for the ride.
Don't say that so coldly.
Let us take you home!
Hey, you two!
Sorry, we came for our lost piece of youth.
Come watch us play baseball tomorrow.
Baseball?
Yeah, believe it or not,
we're high school ballplayers.
You two?
What, is that weird?
I'm the star pitcher!
And he's the catcher who squats like he's shitting.
Man, your mouth is filthy.
Then squat properly, will ya?
I don't really like baseball.
What?
If you lost something last week,
you'll need to go to the Enoshima head office.
Not last week—youth!
You don't have to get all dramatic about it.
A lost piece of youth...
Our promise tomorrow.
Oh crap!
Tomorrow, one o'clock!
At Hodogaya Baseball Stadium!
Stick with us and every day'll be brighter.
We'll clear away the rain
and the clouds in your heart too!
So? Let's have some fun!
Alright, next!
Okay!
Put your back into it!
Sorry!
Next!
Honestly, everyone's out there covered in
mud practicing, and those two are slacking off again.
As their homeroom teacher, it's embarrassing.
Always late, always sneaking out early,
disrespecting teachers, no charm at all...
What do they even think school is? Ugh, my stomach...
What's the matter?
I-It's those two! Just thinking
about them lately makes my gut hurt.
Stop whining.
Our school might make it to Koshien for the first time since its founding.
And that's thanks to Batto Gun and Ichimonji Teru.
Your stomachache doesn't amount to squat.
D-Doesn't amount to squat?
Still, Chairman, if our school's star battery
is always acting like a pair of delinquents...
Principal, surely you've got something to say.
Now, now, Vice Principal, Kito—let it be.
When you're young, you stray off the rails a little.
Isn't that right, Chairman?
Exactly.
Kito-sensei! Kito-sensei!
We love you!
Smooch, smooch!
Bye!
This is the fall of education!
Love Dream
That was mighty brave of her—
how that girl tossed her bike.
Yeah.
But I bet deep down she's really hurting.
I got that feeling.
So even you can read a girl's feelings sometimes?
Well, I'm the only one who can get her back on her feet. She looked at me that way.
What way?
Like she fell for me at first sight
and was begging me to do whatever I wanted.
You've lost it. Here—pick one.
Huh? What the hell's this?
What's there?
X
Oh, you drew "X."
That settles it—Anne's my girl.
What "X"?! Don't hand me that crap.
You made this stupid thing up!
Don't let it get you down.
Hold up, let me see the other one.
Hmm? What?
You cheated as usual!
I've hated that about you since forever.
Don't lose your cool over some dumb crap.
You two keep fighting like that
and you won't make it to Koshien.
"You two?"
Hey, look, it's "You Two" Onishima.
Not "Onishima," it's Kirishima!
That thing looks good on you.
And where's Megumi-san?
Too bad for you, my sis is out shopping.
So your target's Batsu's sister, huh?
Man, this guy's been grinding it out chasing her.
And she hasn't dumped him yet?
Sis is running a business here,
so she has no choice but to serve him coffee.
Figures. A grumpy middle-aged biker
like him isn't exactly a chick magnet.
No shit—he dresses like he pulled
his clothes out of a chest at random!
You guys got some nerve.
You realize what'll happen if you mess with Traffic Officer Kirishima, right?
Oh my, uncle Onishima...
Kirishima-san is manly,
lame, and dazzling all at once.
Look here!
Quit goofing around with that "Oni" stuff!
Oh! Onishima-san, welcome.
Megumi-san?
O-Oh, please, you know it's Kirishima.
Please remember for when we marry: "Kiri" as in "chest,"
and "shima" as in "island nation."
Ah, I'm so sorry!
I said that without thinking...
It's because these kids are always goofing off.
Uh? Oh, not at all—when you're young,
you're always full of energy.
Listen up, if you mess with me once more,
I'll slap you with a mountain of tickets.
It's about time you start acting like adults!
Really, aren't they cute little rascals?
Huff, huff...
Dammit, getting double-teamed in this game—what the hell?!
Shit-for-brains!
T-Tatsuo-san!
Huh?
What's your problem?
You think it's funny I'm crooked?
Huh? Crooked, what do you mean?
Assholes!
Y-You okay?
Just trying to help, huh?
W-What's up with you, Tatsuo-san?
Those two sure have a real fighting spirit within them.
What do you think, Kashino-san?
Yep, they really have fight...
Who the hell's watching this crap?
Sorry, I'll turn it off.
Who said to turn it off?! Answer me, you punk!
Why do you think you can do whatever you want?!
Tokai University Sumo!
Tokai University Sumo
Kaiho
Are they really gonna do that every time?
It's not the Kokugikan Sumo Arena, you know.
Anyway...
I can't see her.
Yeah.
She said she hates baseball.
She said she hates you, actually.
Are your ears broken?
Is your face broken?
You've got your hands all over her breasts
‘cause of your obvious intentions.
Who's ever touched her breasts?!
You've got a sharp eye!
Battery!
Are we done talking?
The other batter's already in the ring.
Alright, Batsu, focus!
Yeah! Let's knock them all out of the ring!
Dead ball!
Don't stick that huge belly over the base!
Batto-kun must be really frustrated,
he's thrashing around on the mound.
I think that girl's planning to go to the cliff again today.
Since when do you understand a girl's mind so well?
You've gotta be kidding me!
It's because I'm from Edo... or not?
He runs!
Batsu!
Safe!
Stop running so noisily!
You're distracting me! Jeez...
Crud...!
It's outta here.
Nice one.
Ah! Hey, grab it!
That one in the middle.
Gotcha! Oh! Still warm from Yoko's boobs!
Hey!
Here, Miko!
Thanks.
Anne!
Yoo-hoo!
Feeling good?
Look, look! I finally bought it!
The brand new GSX400X Impulse!
I worked part-time like mad for six months to get it.
But I kept messing up,
so I was shy to show my face.
Yeah! Next, we're touring to Izu!
You should come too, Anne!
Why? Come on!
Yeah, let's go!
I... gave up my bike.
What? Really? That's a waste!
Is it because of what happened to Kunio?
Sacchi!
S-Sorry.
No, it's fine. Maybe I acted on impulse, though...
Anne...
You feeling down?
No, I'm okay. Thanks.
We'll ride again sometime.
Right! And next time, you lead the pack!
I've gotta go now. Everyone ride safe!
The game's moving surprisingly slowly.
Tokai University Sumo
Kaiho
She wouldn't do something crazy, would she?
Just because her boyfriend flew off a cliff,
doesn't mean she's the type to go flying too.
Anyway, let's kick things into gear.
Yep. I'm gonna hit one out of the park.
Strike!
What?
Terry swung and missed!
A screwball?
Was that a fastball?
What's going on with them today?
It's really strange.
That's just their real level.
Expecting more was a mistake.
We've spoiled them way too much...
You're not aiming at us, are you?
T-Those two would totally do it!
Not a straight pitch...
It's curving right at the edge of the base.
Hit it in front of the base!
Dammit!
Tch, no good?
What the...?!
Go for it, Terry!
Out!
So I didn't make it.
Unbelievable.
I can't believe he didn't even flinch at Terry's slide.
These guys really throw you off your game.
What now?
A shame to waste this game...
Don't tell me you're thinking...
Yeah, that's exactly what I think. Let's go.
Okay.
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
We've got important business.
We're heading out.
No way, we're in the middle of a game!
Handle it yourself.
No way! We're losing by two points!
This is for Koshien! Koshien!
We've got something
way more important than Koshien.
"More important," huh?
You're just off to hit on girls!
If you insist on leaving with your back to the enemy,
you'll need to go through me first.
You mean that?
Don't mess with the main characters' pace.
Here you go, thank you very much.
Thanks.
Hope the weather's nice tomorrow.
Still here, huh?
Alright, let's do this.
Tokai University Sumo
Kaiho
Greetings!
Try to stay back as much as possible.
Hey, Hanasaki-kun, do you have the data
on these fatsos' relief pitching?
Let's see... Tokai Sumo Team,
no relief pitchers.
What?
There's no pitcher?
Strike!
I see.
What's he planning?
Deadly Repeated Balls-Crushing Syndrome!
Deadly Repeated Balls-Crushing Syndrome?
Bye now!
This is it! Back in middle school,
he pulled this off on me too and made it snap in half!
You okay?
Yeah, I'll live...
Terry, gimme one big hit!
That stubborn pitcher
won't go down with just one.
Play ball!
Did he... die?
Hanasaki, you're up!
Okay!
Are you okay? Can you do it?
What? He's still got the guts?
Umpire! Pinch-hitter Hanasaki, taking the field!
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Those two already made it to base,
so I gotta help too!
Hanasaki! Strike the pitcher!
Right back at him!
I hope he's alive...
Good job, Hanasaki!
You did great! Keep running!
Sera! Back home, back home!
The ball's stuck! I can't get it out!
What?
Okay, one point!
Forgive me, Sera!
I got this!
Safe!
Hey, I need a favor, Kacchan!
Gonna throw your own body off there next?
Of course not.
You didn't come to the game.
I really wanted to show it to you.
Today was quite funny.
I don't care about baseball.
Our baseball isn't ordinary.
They call it "feel-good baseball."
Well, baseball aside, let's ride.
Let's feel the wind!
Lonely, if we could meet, Story
Can't get enough of this feeling!
I'm buzzing too!
I'm always waiting for a chance to fall in love
Buzzing?
Yeah, buzzing!
I've been buzzing forever!
Buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz.
Lonely, the story of how we met
Love now becomes a wonderful story
Whoa!
Uh oh, think we'll fall?
The fickle moon casts long shadows,
bringing back memories I'd almost forgotten
Sorry!
Whoa! That's one sturdy roof,
as expected of a British car!
With tears in my eyes, I gazed through the blinds into the silence of the night
I'm feeling the buzz,
so how about another go?
Anne! Hold on tight!
Batsu!
Let's go!
Buzzing...
Shuttle Loop!
Lonely, if we could meet, story
There!
Yeah!
Awesome!
I'm always waiting for a chance to fall in love
Lonely, the story of how we met
Take it slow. Check your surroundings.
Okay!
Ah, sorry, we actually needed to go that way! My bad!
Huh? Whoa.
Love now becomes a wonderful story
It's fine, just make a U-turn!
No problem!
Sorry, I shouldn't push you like this.
It's okay.
So? How was it riding in the back for the first time?
Huh?
Pretty solid, right? My driving.
I'd say it's passable.
Why you...
Wake up, Batsu!
What's wrong?
It's Onishima! Get off!
Onishima
That was close.
Bye-bye.
That's dirty! Wait!
It's your fault!
What did you say, punk?!
What the—
Hey! Stop it! Stop it! Hey!
Told you we should've stopped!
Huh? Is that you, kid? Running a marathon in this heat to aim for Koshien?
You idiot!
You being here is why this happened!
I hate you!
I'm never letting you into Love Dream again!
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
It's hot today, are you okay?
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I hate you, you swine!
Hey! Stop!
Dammit! That's obstruction of the law!
I'm never letting you into Love Dream!
The sea reflecting the city
is so quiet it's sad
Every time I think of you, I come to this pier
My heart was secretly burning,
but for some reason I couldn't put it into words
As I turned around, I realized my love, and my lips trembled
As I turned around, I searched for you, but that smile is gone
I'm going now.
Terry! If you're there, prepare yourself!
Achoo! Batsu must be cursing me again.
Look, Anne, you should know that
even if you try to forget, it's impossible.
Dwelling on it forever is a waste.
I know that.
Take it easy, take it easy
Escape from the empty time
If you waste your days on nonsense,
before you know it, you'll be an old lady...
Take it easy, each of our smiles is not wasted
Could it be...
You!
You bastard... Terry!
Take it easy, take it easy
Gazing at the sunlight of the coming day
How dare you do me dirty!
Bye now.
Take it easy, someday
We'll be able to laugh together, hey lover
Eh? Wait, w-wait a second!
You...! You did something to her!
She hates you, you know.
Don't make stuff up.
You're noisy, and that's that.
What now?!
This thing's blasting shit, for starters!
What the hell, you bastard...
Shut up, you whiny bitch!
You think you can beat me?!
Eat my dust!
Dammit! You shithead!
Anne, I'm the only one who can heal your heart!
Cretin!
Oh!
Kya! What are you doing out there, Mister?!
Not sure!
Hey!
Yes?
You're causing trouble!
Please return to your seat!
Seriously, stop it already! Please!
Whoa!
Get lost!
You punk!
Stop being such a nuisance!
W-Wait! Wait! Wait! Hey! Wait for me!
Hey!
Anne, even if you try to forget,
it's impossible. We both know that.
But dwelling on it forever is a waste.
Huh?
And...
And also...
If you waste your youth on nonsense,
you'll turn into an old lady in no time!
You guys are weird.
She laughed!
No way!
Well, maybe it was closer to just a smile, but still...
She was exasperated, wasn't she?
Rather than being alone, let's hop on the bus
and head downtown on a lonely afternoon
The coins in my pocket are bouncing
Even dreams can be bought on this pavement
A premonition blowing through the brick-colored sidewalk,
even my feet feel lighter downtown
Something good seems like it's going to happen
Is it thanks to your kindness?
Don't let anyone stop you in your precious youth,
keep your heart racing downtown
Let's get the party started
with a lively bunch of like-minded people!
The bazaars decorating
the street corners
are always inviting you downtown
Her boyfriend
Have more fun,
laugh more
You're the best, dazzling
I know that the fun we have now isn't everything
You two!
Back off!
Are you okay?
My true self is reflected in your eyes,
and my arm is wrapped around yours downtown
Let's start a lively party with like-minded people
HOMERUN
Let's dance
like lovers, with synchronized steps
Hey! What's gotten into you today?
You bastards don't normally show your true colors,
but you're a complete mess today, aren't you?
Well, even though I was impartial to you sometimes,
you've totally crossed every line today.
Actually, here, take this too,
I found it in my ice cream.
Only one stick, though, so you can fight over it, or gift it to a girl—whatever.
Bye then.
Bye-bye!
Alright, let's go.
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
To Anne
It looks like I'm working
tonight as well
From mom with love
69th National High School Baseball Championship: Kanagawa Qualifiers
Sponsored by Kanagawa Prefectural High School Baseball Federation and Asahi Shimbun
How'd it go?
No luck.
Oh! She's here!
What now?
Hey!
What are you two doing?!
The game's about to start!
Idiot, we don't have time for that!
Hey! Let go!
No! I'm taking you to Koshien no matter what!
I'll drag you onto the field even if it costs me my life!
Anne, you made it!
I didn't think you'd come.
Yes! It's the semifinals!
What's wrong?
Let's hurry inside.
Let's go!
If you insist on going,
you'll need to go through me first!
Stop with the same old trick.
Hey, Hanasaki, who's our opponent today?
Seiran.
Seiran?
Alright everyone, remember!
This game is do-or-die!
Understood.
W-What's with this vibe?
What's with these gloomy faces?
Something wrong?
It's that.
Who's that?
Seiran's third baseman.
Died in a motorcycle accident, apparently.
Strike!
Strike two!
Strike, batter out!
I'm feeling fired up all of a sudden.
Can't be any good if you're not fired up.
Strike! Batter out!
Sorry, but I'm on fire today,
and I don't intend on stopping!
Anne's in the stands, too.
Time to show off as a man to the fullest!
Dammit!
Safe!
I'm going all out—don't get hurt, everyone.
Catcher, Ichimonji-kun at bat.
Anne, you saw that? That was Batsu.
Alright, let's do this, Terry.
Of course!
Here we go!
That wasn't a pitch for a cleanup batter.
Already out of steam in the semifinals?
Show me what you're made of!
Yeah!
Fifth batter—Hanasaki, the third baseman.
Yeah! Anne, this home run is a gift for you!
H-Hey!
I know.
Ichimonji-kun's magnificent, daring home run!
Such incredible power. But am I the only one
who feels it's a little over-the-top?
Plus, their reckless energy is off the charts...
Those kids are always like that.
Isn't it disrespectful, with that portrait there?
They're fired up.
Huh?
Whether the other team's holding a mourning photo or not—actually,
because they're holding it—
the two of them are on fire.
Honestly, what are those two?
That's their "on fire?"
Here we go!
Whoa!
Like I'd ever let you!
Seriously, where are you throwing?
Safe!
He's giving it his all.
Yeah...
Andre-san?
Kacchan!
Tacchan!
They're really fired up now.
Today's getting interesting.
Don't worry about it.
He just hit it by chance off a lucky swing.
What are you, trying to comfort me?
You're ten years too young for that!
What's going on? Why did Batto Gun suddenly start chasing Hanasaki-kun?
Kacchan, can you believe it?
They're playing baseball too!
High school baseball, and doing all this nonsense!
If it were just delinquents, I wouldn't even get this worked up. But it's high school baseball!
Safe! Safe!
Damn, they'll send the runner no matter what.
Yeah.
Right, let's make it work!
Bunted it!
Second!
Out!
A bunt? That cheap tactic won't work on us!
If you want points,
play seriously like a man, dammit!
Three outs!
Third out, change!
That hurt surprisingly bad.
What is it? Lemme see.
Come on, catch it with your glove!
Ouch!
No good, it hit me squarely
and hurts like hell. No way I can wear it.
Just force it on.
No, I'm not driving anywhere today.
Huh? So a clumsy guy can't afford a single error?
Then just quit baseball already!
Left-field single to second? Shit!
A mere single won't cut it!
Safe!
That's embarrassingly bad.
Time to aim for a home run!
Ball!
Ball two!
Show me your grit!
Walking him is lame as hell!
You were already riding the waves,
but let it slip away!
Well, I'll be... He nailed it!
Three homers in a row!
Stealing all the attention...
You guys are still not even trying!
Hey, what are you doing here?
What's going on? Batto and Ichimonji
approached the Seiran stands near the third base...
Unforgivable!
They're defiling the sacred field!
H-Hey, what's wrong?
W-What are they doing?
Well done!
What happened, Hanasaki?
Huh? Nothing.
I got it.
Kaiho Team, what about the next batter?
Y-Yes, sorry!
Dumbass!
Still got eyes on us, huh?
Well, we'll give ‘em one more round.
Try and get me! Jump!
Dammit! Like I'll let you keep making a fool of me!
What an over-the-top dramatic play.
It's hard to believe we're up by three runs.
This is the last one! Let's settle this!
I'm pumped!
I really hit it...
I ended up giving Batsu his moment.
Touch up! Send it back home!
Flying Cross Attack!
Nailed it!
Safe!
Dammit... this isn't pro wrestling,
it's high school baseball!
Right? Kacchan, I know you'd get it too.
They're prepared to turn anything into a dirty brawl!
We gotta crush them or they won't stop.
Let's screw them up so bad they can never play baseball again! Right, Kacchan?
The ninth inning's drawing to a close. Will this be Seiran's final attack?
They want to win for Haraguchi Kunio, the third baseman.
Seiran Team has two outs, no runners.
Seems like Kaiho's Batto-kun and Ichimonji-kun completely disrupted them. Is it just a skill difference?
Here we go!
Alright!
Are you okay?
Out!
Pardon the intrusion.
Game set!
That was a good match.
Thanks!
Where you headed?
For now, up the Yamanote line.
Then I'm off to Chinatown.
Later!
Idiot! If she's around here,
she's gotta be at Yamashita Park!
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
Yokohama Port Festival
Fireworks Display
Yokohama City
"Hey, did you see my big plays?"
Big plays? Chinatown's that way!
This isn't Yamanote either!
Come on, Anne, let's forget about him
and go catch goldfishes or something.
Hands off, you idiot!
Go catch some pond fish on your own!
Anne doesn't need someone like you
following her around!
Yeah, leave me alone.
See?
And you too!
Hey, wait!
Don't follow me.
Why are you pushing me away?
I'm not pushing anyone!
You're planning to keep
running away like this forever, huh?
Running away?
You really should've watched the game to the end.
Kunio looked so relieved and clear-headed there.
Yeah! He was smiling right in that photo,
like he was toasting us.
If you two wanna celebrate, suit yourselves.
But I don't want to be near you!
See?
Anne! Why did you ditch that bike anyway?
Wasn't it to get over it?
Did you think throwing away that bike
would make you forget everything?
See?
Wanna go picking up girls?
Anne!
Sachi?
Yeah?
Can I borrow your bike?
Huh? Sure.
Where?
I parked it by the sidewalk over there.
Thanks.
Anne! Are you sure you should
ride it dressed like that?
Anne!
Yoohoo!
Are you okay, Anne?
I slipped up.
Anne, maybe you shouldn't ride this bike?
Huh? Why?
Because it's dangerous, after all.
I'm fine.
That was just a little mistake.
I'm actually good at this.
I'm fine, really!
I love riding!
I'll never quit biking.
You might as well quit baseball.
Anne, I've decided to get my motorcycle license.
What? Really?
But I'll keep it a secret from the baseball club.
Ta-da!
Anne!
Anne...
Kunio!
Look at that—she actually jumped in herself...
Well, it helps to cool your head off
after getting worked up,
and it's much cheaper than ditching the bike.
I always thought something like this might happen.
You think you're walking straight ahead,
but your footing's shaky.
This bike is shot...
I really have to pity this bike.
You've gotta treat it better.
My poor, poor thing!
Well, at least she's alive.
I suppose.
Luck was on her side.
But if you don't take care
of yourself, luck won't last.
People who take care of themselves
also take care of their bikes.
No way, really?
You're so smart, bud!
People who take care of themselves
also take care of their bikes.
Forget it or not, that's not the point.
Once you understand what it means
to take care of yourself, we'll meet again.
See you, Anne.
Be well.
Coming!
A package for Shiraki-san.
Fireworks leave this emptiness inside you when they stop.
Yeah, they really let you feel both the joy
of meeting someone and the sadness of parting.
Hey.
What's up, isn't that Tacchan's lackey?
If you wanna watch fireworks,
go somewhere else.
I'm alone!
What are you acting tough for all by yourself?
Shut up! We've got your woman, you get that?
What?!
W-Wait! I only came here
to deliver a message from Tatsuo-san...
I had to do it to you, but I bear you no grudge.
If you want someone to hate, save it for those two.
What are you saying? This is useless. There's no way those two will come for me.
They will come.
I don't know what you want to do with them,
but they have nothing to do with me.
You don't get it. Whether they're involved or not,
they're coming. That's just how they are.
And once they show up, I'll make sure they can never play baseball again.
Huh? What?
I just can't stand the way those guys
are playing sports. I simply can't take it!
What on Earth are you saying?
It's you who's not normal!
Shut up! They've strayed from the path of men.
You're the one who doesn't get it. They—
Batsu and Terry are...
The messengers of justice have arrived!
There they are—the Battery!
Batsu, Terry, stay away!
An off-season Santa Claus has arrived!
Anne, we're gonna save ya!
Sorry for dragging you into this mess.
No! Go back!
Oh, this seems intense.
Please, go home!
You jerks! Since you've embarrassed me so much in the past, now have a taste of your own medicine!
Go ahead, start stripping where you stand!
Show your manly treasures to this girl!
You're confident, right?
Stop! There's no need for something that stupid!
Shut up!
Tatsuo! If you want to see a man strip that badly, we'll show you anytime.
You can start some music,
Snap-in-Half Tacchan!
You idiots!
Why would I need that?!
Sorry ours aren't crooked, Tatsuo.
They've done it...
Look! Serves them right!
Anne! Don't hold back! Look!
This is everything we've got.
No hiding or holding back—Ichimonji Teru...
And Batto Gun!
Dammit... Kacchan!
Stop!
You stay quiet!
He's just playing with us like rag dolls...
Stop it!
Do more, come on!
What is wrong with you?!
You talk about the way of men,
yet you can't do anything yourself!
What did you say?
Coward! You're nothing but trash!
Shut up! Do you even care what happens?!
Go ahead! If it makes you feel better!
Coward!
Shut up!
Tatsuo!
What the hell?!
Put on your pants at least,
it's the least a man should do.
He's shooting at us!
Tatsuo!
You did something you shouldn't have.
Don't pretend you didn't hear me!
Die, Tatsuo!
Jump, Anne!
Kacchan!
Let go!
Tacchan!
Now, let's get Anne back.
What the hell do you think—
You're in my way!
I'm left-handed, anyways!
He's serious!
He's seriously trying to kill us!
Are you okay?
Y-You...
I'm gonna run you over!
The Rescue Squad's here!
Kacchan! Get it together! They're escaping!
Oops, my bad.
Here, Anne, a gift from Batsu.
Asshole!
Tatsuo...
You really dumped
a hell of a lot of extra work on us...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'll live.
Get back!
That... King Kong of a bastard is something...
Damn... I don't have any more strength left.
Me neither...
Batsu! Terry!
That was a spectacular jump.
You didn't even fall into the sea this time.
You idiots...
I guess we should call an ambulance after all.
Wait.
Let's just stay like this a little longer.
Yeah... I want to stay here too.
The stars are beautiful, and the wind feels good.
Okay?
Ah! Tomorrow's the final...
or, well, it's today already.
No way! In that shape...
I'm joking.
Youth is precious;
you can't just gamble it all on baseball.
Kunio's youth was all about baseball.
He worked hard aiming for Koshien.
I wasn't interested in baseball.
He was willing to adjust to me...
Because I liked bikes, he went through a lot of trouble to get his license.
He was clumsy...
But despite being bad,
he always pressed forward, leading the pack...
And so, he died.
What a fool.
He should've just stuck to baseball.
I'm looking for any witnesses to the massive brawl
that occurred around here last night...
Do you know anything?
Ah, I see.
Well, it can't be helped. I'll head back.
And if they're to be believed,
I ought to let you ride my bike too.
Foul ball!
Shit...
Just one more...
One more out, then a change.
With a two-point deficit, there's still a chance.
If they score even one decisive point here, it'll be a disaster!
And then Batto and Ichimonji will come up
to bat in the bottom of the inning...
You can't rely on those two for anything.
H-How can they can even play baseball?!
They've been beaten up so badly...
I-It's so infuriating. I swear!
Batsu, Terry...
Kanagawa
Foul ball!
T-The bases are loaded!
Koshien's slipping away!
Those two are getting expelled!
Yes, that's the best plan.
Right, Vice Principal?
I did judo in high school and college.
I like people who never give up.
Just one more out.
You said the same thing earlier.
Kanagawa
Look above the Kanagawa sign.
Huh?
Kanagawa
A mirage... my eyes are getting blurry.
That's better. I'm ready to pitch!
Batsu, Terry, do your best!
I don't know what happened,
but let's go to Koshien together!
Out!
Three outs, change!
That was thrilling...
These two are something else.
They can be a handful,
but they know exactly what's truly important.
It's finally the last inning.
Yeah!
Say, Kazu, can they overcome a two-point deficit?
W-Who knows...
No way they can, ain't that right?!
What's with you?
You're like a feeble old man.
And you're like a rotten mummy.
Hey, you okay?
Who do you think you're talking to?!
I told you, you're ten years too young.
S-Sorry... Batsu, it's your turn at bat.
Two outs, runners on first and second.
Cleanup batter—Batto Gun, the pitcher.
Batsu, let me have a turn too.
Don't state the obvious. I'll make it to base
no matter what, so let me do it.
Don't state the obvious...
Please, guys...
Strike!
Strike two!
Batsu!
H-Hey! D-Dead ball!
Go to first.
Got it!
Bases loaded, vice principal!
Damn...
I can't afford to mess this up.
Idiot! Get it together, Terry!
Was my twist too weak, maybe...?
Terry! Give me back my turn!
Two people who are bad at loving will melt away in the city lights
Terry, hold it together!
Terry! You're sloppy!
Don't mess around—show me baseball!
Terry! Terry! Terry!
If you wet your fingertips to tell where the wind blows,
you will never lose sight of kindness
Yes! Right-center field!
When you realize it, gently take it into your arms
He did it! He made it through!
and never let it go
One more! One more and it's Koshien!
Follow Wind, across the waves of memories,
I confess all my love honestly from my heart
Batsu! Third base is right in front!
Yeah...
Batsu! One more step!
Follow Wind, as time passes by,
I want to embrace it and never let go, pushed by the tailwind
Take care of the rest, Batsu...
Batsu! Fight!
Please!
C-Can he even run?
Batsu! Run!
Run, Batsu! Run, you bastard!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Safe!
He did it! He really did it!
Terry!
They've done it!
Lonely, the story of our meeting
I'll get them someday.
Love now becomes a wonderful story
The fickle moon casts long shadows, bringing back memories I'd almost forgotten
Don't worry. Even if you kill him,
he won't die, you know. Right?
You heartless bastard.
Like hell I'll kick it before you do!
With tears in my eyes, I gazed through the blinds
into the silence of the night
Just like I said, youth is always extreme!
Yeah!
Seriously!
If I feel a faint premonition in the wind of tomorrow,
the dark clouds hanging over my heart tonight
will drift away and disappear.
Lonely, sadness is also a story
So I drift along, letting myself be carried away by the wind
Lonely, until I'm satisfied, story
I'll keep dreaming like this until I wake up someday
Love is mischievous
The more my heart flutters, the more painful it becomes
The illusion of you, so close I can reach out, keeps bringing me sleepless nights
The flow of time whispers to my heart that's beginning to wander
A slight misunderstanding has even taken away my kindness
Lonely, if we could meet, story
I'm always waiting for my chance at love
Lonely, until we meet, story
Raw Capturing
Encoding
Audio Restoration
Translation & Typesetting
Editing
Raw Provider & QC
Additional QC
Additional Typesetting
Brought to you by
FatGooGooBabies
Anonymous
Krycek7o2
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Marty Mcflies
imatu
Windii
LonelyDildo
Love will now become a wonderful story