I haven't had such a good dinner in a long while!
Yeah!
Same here.
I'm surprised you have this kind of money, Wolf.
Huh? I'm not the one paying
tonight. Tatakku, was this your idea?
Nope.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
Ah, Slikichi, so you're paying!
Some guys from the casino
bought us dinner in exchange for the helmet.
Hey! Another serving!
You sold the Hero's Helmet?!
Wolf, I'm not done with my soup yet!
Who cares about that?!
We're taking the helmet back!
Slime's Adventures
Yay! Yay!
I'm the first!
Two cards.
-Don't you mess with—
-Bonk.
Here's your drink.
Bye-bye!
H-Huh...?
-I messed up!
-Get back here!
Catch me if you can!
Straight flush!
How d'ya like that?
Royal straight flush.
Damn it!
So pricey...!
They put a whopping one million coin price tag on it!
This is all I have.
Same here.
That's not enough...
Huh? Wh-What's that?
R-Raizou!
The winner of the next round
will receive exactly one million coins.
The Hero's Helmet will be mine!
Curses! At this rate, it'll fall into Raizou's hands!
Yay! There! There!
Slikichi!
Where did you get this much?
My winnings from the race! The race!
I entered it!
Great job!
Alright, let's proceed to the final round.
Not so fast!
Let's do it! Count us in!
Yay! Yay!
Alley-oop!
I'm not gonna waste
all of Slikichi's hard-earned coins!
Let's gamble! I'm betting on red 7.
I'll bet on black 20, then.
Hurray! Hurray!
We did it! We did it!
That's a million coins for me.
Hey, Gramps!
-Bring me the item.
-O-Okay!
The victory is mine.
I'll be taking the Hero's Helmet.
Slikichi, I'm so sorry...
This can't be happening...
Look.
Cheaters!
They fooled us.
Curses! Damn that Raizou!
Geezer, can you locate the helmet?
Sure.
A volcano?
How dare that bastard cheat?!
Wolf's ticked off for real.
Don't you think he's blaming himself for the loss?
Hey! I can hear you!
Come on down.
Hey, is this the right place...?
Yeah, definitely.
It's pitch black inside, though.
This is the perfect opportunity
for Slikichi to show off his skills!
Would you kindly?
Listen, Slikichi...
You're overdoing it...
This is so...
Is something the matter?
Don't scare me like that!
My torch went out!
Slikichi, could you...?
My bad! Did I wake you up?
They're totally mad.
Yup.
-Hey, guys!
-Slikichi!
Have you seen Raizou?
Huh?
Their foreheads!
Right here! See?
You're right, there's "Ra" written on their foreheads.
It seems Raizou is controlling the monsters.
Aku!
I'll handle the rest.
Oku, what about that thing?
Yes. It's ready, sir.
It's so warm here!
You don't say. It's so hot!
Huh? Is this a dead end?
This place will become your grave!
Fun! This is so fun!
They keep coming!
You're so stupid!
Huh?
So many of them?!
There!
Heave-ho! Up we go!
Wait! You aren't getting away!
It burns!
Get down!
Geezer, if you will.
Okay.
There.
It burns!
It burns! It burns! It burns, boss!
So that's where the exit was!
It hurts! Ow! Ouch!
B-Boss!
You're totally useless.
Where are we?
Raizou!
Raizou, you scumbag!
Damned cheater! Give back the helmet!
If you want the helmet,
come and take it by force!
Found the Hero's Helmet! Yay! Got it!
-I found it!
-Awesome!
Great job!
Hey!
Stop sneaking around when I'm trying to show off!
Whatever.
Feel free to celebrate, as long as
you think you can escape this place.
Oh no!
-Damn it...!
-Yay!
-New friends! So many new friends!
-Don't you mess with me!
Are you okay, Slikichi?
Raizou, fight me!
Charge!
Out of my way!
Eliminator Cut!
Thank you.
There!
Works like a charm.
Leave them to me!
Okay.
Raizou, say your prayers!
Eat this! Zapple!
Have mercy!
Wolf!
You're all bark and no bite.
Slikichi.
You're going down, too!
Drop dead!
A dead end.
You're cornered.
Slikichi, I have a special item
to obliterate you once and for all.
"Kaneko"
This Kaneko-brand balanced mix
contains the seeds of strength, life and magic...
...wisdom, resilience, and agility. It's called...
Special Nuts!
He turned into Super Raizou!
This is payback for all the
humiliation you've caused me in V-Jump!
I'll get rid of you along with the Rockbombs.
Whoa! Raizou, you're so cool!
S-Slikichi!
Hurry up and escape!
Damn it! If only we could
get rid of the Rockbombs...
Rockbombs...?
Slikichi, devour them!
If you devour those Rockbombs, you'll become cool, too!
Devour them?
Awesome!
You're doing me a favor.
I'm full...
Die!
I can't hold it in...
It burns!
Die!
What's going on?
It's scalding hot!
Yay!
Slikichi's blast shook the ground,
and caused a hot spring to form.
Ah, I see.
Either way, let's get out of here.
Slikichi, hurry up.
Ouch! It's boiling hot!
W-What the hell?!
Ow! Ouch! It burns!
My head!
Slikichi, I'll get you next time!
Yay! Yay!
We did it! We did it!
And we managed to take back the helmet.
All's well that ends well, right?
Wolf, you were totally awesome!
Fo' real?
That wasn't a big deal at all!
I thought I was a goner...
Subbed by:
LonelyChaser Fansubs
Project Manager:
MartyMcflies
Raw Encoding:
Kineko Video
Timing & TL:
Yume
TLC:
perevodildo
QC:
imatu
Thanks for watching!