I know this is sudden,
but our company is going bankrupt.
Huh?
What?
Seriously?
Yeah, that's it, period.
Thank you all for your work up till now!
You're kidding, right?
It can't be true!
Time is running out.
In the Kitchenette
Worrisome Feelings
So what do you have to say...
at a time like this?
Actually, this is the perfect time to tell you this.
U-Um, I've...
been in love with you, manager,
since I joined this company.
But I couldn't bring myself
to tell you until now.
As my final memento of working here...
I was wondering if I could kiss you?
Nishizaki-kun!
Yes?
I love you too.
Manager...
W-We can't! No more than this...
Since this is our last day here...
I'll tell you that it's been my dream to bang
you from behind in this kitchenette!
Nishizaki-kun.
Wait...
You're not a child anymore,
so I bet you want more than just kisses.
W-Well...
I'll take that as a "yes."
What's this, huh?
You're wet already.
How cute, Nishizaki-kun.
How lewd, Nishizaki-kun.
Listen to the sounds you're making!
You're already soaking wet, Nishizaki-kun.
I'm going in.
Nishizaki-kun...
Great.
This is awesome, Nishizaki-kun!
I can't hold back!
You're amazing!
Your pussy is swallowing me all the way!
So cute.
Here we go!
Nishizaki-kun, you've got
such a nice body. I mean it!
I like the size and shape of your boobs.
They're magnets for a man's eyes!
I-I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum inside you, Nishizaki-kun.
No, don't! Please cum outside!
I-I can't hold it any longer.
I-I'm cumming!
That was amazing.
That's not fair, manager.
You don't suppose you were the only one fantasizing
about doing Nishizaki-san in the kitchenette like this.
Let me join in too, please.
As you wish.
Let me have fun as well, okay?
I guess you've never had sex
with two guys at the same time, right?
Banging Nishizaki's pussy...
I feel like I'm dreaming.
But man... it's pretty tight.
Sensitive, isn't she?
I can feel tons of creases.
Her pussy is totally wrapping around me!
I'm at my limit, manager...
M-Me too.
The company's going bankrupt anyway.
We might as well have our fun too.
Let us join in, won't you?
What, you guys are here too?
Hey now. You'll have to take turns, then.
W-Wait a second.
Please... stop.
Why are you doing this to me...
No!
Let me go!
Nishizaki-san, suck me as well, won't you?
I'm cumming!
Hey, Nishizaki-san is letting
anyone bang her as a parting gift!
For real?
I can't believe I'm having sex with our secret idol.
This is like a dream come true.
Let's not forget this other hole here.
I'm in, but it's really tight.
You're good, Nishizaki-san...
I'm cumming!
Me too.
Cumming!
It's too soon to take a break, Nishizaki-san.
You can drink our cum as much as you want.
I'm cumming!
Nishizaki-kun, can I do it too?
N-No...
I didn't want this...
Staff Kitchen
The night is still young.
Come on, m-move your hips too!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah!
Good! More. Use them more! Your hips!
No more. You're thrusting too hard!
I'm going crazy!
Both your boobs and pussy are amazing.
Your boobs are so soft.
They're heavenly.
Yes...
I've never felt this good.
I give up. Do whatever you want now.
Yes...
Translation
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Raw Provider
Presented by
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
Collectr
CP, Paul Geromini
ProxyMan
Okizari Fansubs