TOEI COMPANY LTD.
Arabian Nights
Sinbad's Adventures
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Sinbad!
What happened, Ali?!
An old man washed up on the seashore!
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Translation Check
Yume
Editing & Typsetting
Collectr
QC
Nemesis
Paul Geromini
Encoding
Ioroid
How does it look?
Yes, he'll live.
Help me, Ali.
Where am I?
What is this place?
You're in Rasaar, a port city.
You're lucky to be alive, grandpa.
I must have caused a great deal of trouble for you.
You'll get better. Just hang in there.
No...
For me, there's no hope anymore.
I see you kids are fond of ships, aren't you?
That's right. We wish we had a ship to sail on.
I want to become a first-rate sailor.
Like my late father before me.
I see.
I became a sailor at about the same age as you are now.
My journey was perilous,
but it was also blissful in a way
only sailors can appreciate.
The sea beckoned me...
with the promise of making every man's dreams come true.
Oh... I know.
I'll tell you kids the strangest tale out there.
A long time ago,
in the sky above a southern island...
something miraculous happened.
No one had ever seen anything like it.
A star fell onto that island,
forcing the island to erupt in a bizarre explosion.
Afterwards, the island's coastline became unrecognizable,
and a certain valley on the island was strewn
with a multitude of dazzling gemstones.
What's more, they were guarded by terrifying monsters.
Even now, those gemstones remain there...
Mister!
Grandpa!
Hey, look at that bum!
Why do you come here every single day?
He said he wanted to get on the ship.
Oh, really?
Forget it! You're too scrawny for that!
Take that!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
All right.
Hey! What are you doing?
Come on, Ali. Cheer up.
Our ship's hold is full
Of heavy goods
Hey, misters! G'day.
Um, can we talk to the captain?
He's over there.
Captain.
What is it, you two?
Captain, please let us work on this ship.
No, you kids aren't ready yet.
And we don't have room for you anyway.
Is there nothing we can do?
That's right.
Better give up now.
Prepare to set sail!
Raise the anchor, reel in the mooring lines
Good bye, harbors and capes of my homeland
As our ship departs, it leaves a foamy wake
Good bye, my dear mountains and shores
Depart!
Raise the anchor, reel in the mooring lines
Good bye, harbors and capes of my homeland
As our ship departs, it leaves a foamy wake
Good bye, my dear mountains and shores
Farewell, my beloved port.
It's not like you have any girl here worth pining over.
I'll find one soon enough.
Allah be praised.
I swear to worship none but Allah.
May our voyage be peaceful.
This one's empty already.
Fine.
Gimme dat. I'll go get us some more.
What's that? A cat?
Don't you mess with me!
Y-Yasim! Come with me!
What's your problem?
Has the drink gone to your head?
Over here, Yasim!
Hey...
Aren't you that brat from before?
I'm sorry, mister!
This punk scared me half to death!
I oughta throw him overboard!
Ah, w-wait! Hold on.
What, there's more of you?
Captain!
What is it, at such a late hour?
Captain, these punks were hiding in the cargo hold.
What should we do?
Captain, we could toss them overboard
to teach them a lesson!
Wait!
Tell me, how'd you even get on board?
We hid inside a carpet.
Oh? Resorted to desperate measures, huh?
Yes. We're sorry, Captain.
You two got me this time.
You're gonna train those boys well.
Make sure to show them the ropes.
Yes, sir!
Leave it to us, Captain.
That one got you, Peppi.
Hey! No slacking off!
What a useless kid you are!
Watch carefully how I do things.
Ouch!
Make sure you don't end up like this too!
Yes, Boatswain Abdullah.
Sinbad!
Tense your abs while climbing! Got it?
Hey! Don't look down!
Hey, Sinbad! Calm down!
You'll be fine!
Deep beneath this sea
Mysteries await
Under these waves
Our dreams are hiding
So let's go, everyone
Enveloped by moonlight
Into the shadows of the stars
Sinbad!
What is it, Ali?!
It's coming this way!
It's a baby whale!
What's going on?!
A sawshark!
Abdullah, fetch the harpoons!
All right!
Sinbad, that whale's in danger!
Move aside!
Watch how it's done!
Okay.
Why, you little...
Damn show-off...
All right.
All right! Nailed it!
Great job, Sinbad!
That was a real smooth move.
My training finally paid off, huh?
Glad you're okay, little whale!
Captain!
We've arrived at the port of call!
All right!
Turn to starboard!
I am lonely, all on my own
My five-colored castle and lovely gardens
Are enveloped in deep darkness
My heart
Is lost in thick fog...
Your Majesty, you called?
Apparently the princess sneaked out again.
Yes, sire.
The princess is becoming quite a handful.
You can't handle her anymore, can you?
Yes, sire. Quite so.
Yet you still wish to marry her?
Well, that's another matter...
Long ago, a Turkish king played his flute and said
I'm sick of women, tired of feasts
What I want is a splendid robe no one else has
And then he invited his servant girls to come closer
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no!
You may come closer!
Hey, Sinbad, hand it over.
I'll sing you a much livelier tune!
Hey, everyone!
Clean out your ears and listen!
Now then, this guitar is so wondrous, and I'm a sailor!
One day I was rowing my little boat,
rowing and rowing across the sea
And look! An island up ahead!
I dropped anchor with a clank, but surprise!
It wasn't an island at all, but a giant whale!
It tossed me way up high, then swallowed me whole
But I managed to come back alive!
And from that whale's insides, I brought out this guitar
The very instant you pluck a string,
gold, silver, and diamonds appear
What a wondrous guitar this is!
Such a lovely guitar!
Your Majesty.
What is it, Vizier?
We've found yet another mysterious treasure.
Oh? What is it?
Show me!
Vizier.
So that's the magic guitar?
Yes, sire.
No, it's nothing like that!
If you're lying...
Ah, wait, wait!
They say when you strum it,
it conjures gold and jewels.
Go on, play it.
Hey, Vizier, nothing's coming out.
Your Majesty,
he must be distorting the melody!
No! No matter what melody you play, it won't...
R-Right, it's just an ordinary guitar!
Silence! If you're lying, you'll have to pay dearly!
This is bad, really bad.
Vizier!
You mustn't mess with those innocent men.
With respect, Princess,
your advice isn't welcome at this time.
Enough, Vizier.
No, sire!
We'll interrogate them at a later time.
Get moving!
Hey! No gawping!
What are you going to do with us?!
Your Excellency!
We can't find the boy anywhere!
You fools! Search every inch!
Kuppi!
Where have you been?
What's wrong, Kuppi?
My!
Where'd you come from?
I see. How amusing.
And they're all good people, you know?
I'm jealous.
I wish I could sail the high seas with you.
Princess!
Your Highness.
Have you by chance seen a boy here?
No.
I haven't seen anything.
If it turns out that you're hiding him...
I figured as much.
Kiddo, come on out!
Get your hands off me!
Spit it out already, will you?!
All right, I'll talk!
See...
Here's the thing.
Way down south...
There's this strange island.
Yes, yes?
Insolent brat! Get back here!
He's running away! After him!
Stop, you punk!
Stop!
You won't get away!
Hold up!
What now?
That's weird. Where'd he go?
That way? Or over here?
Which one?
Here you are!
Hey! Hold up!
Catch me if you can!
Get back here, you little...
Phew, here we go.
Ah! What could this be?
Whoa!
That's incredible!
What, is that all?
Ouch!
Money?
I don't have any money!
Thank you, Kuppi.
What? Ali?
We'll use that to help Ali.
Got it?
Damn it! Let us out already!
Shut up! Quiet in there.
This is all your fault, shooting your mouth off.
I wonder what happened to Ali.
A slippery little fella like him will be just fine.
Good work.
Nice to see you, Princess.
I thought I'd give you a reward.
Much obliged, Princess.
Go, quick!
Thank you!
There are horses in the courtyard.
All right, let's go!
Okay...
Don't leave me behind!
Stop!
Hey! Stop!
I'm telling you to stop!
Hold up!
Get back here!
It's already time for us to depart.
Hurry up!
Hey! Sinbad! Sinbad! Help, Sinbad...
Thanks! Good bye!
It's that brat!
He's flying overhead!
On a magic feather!
What an insufferable brat.
And they're all good people, you know?
Princess, I heard you let those sailors escape.
But, Father...
The vizier was furious.
Father, honestly, how can you trust a man like him?
She seems to be in a particularly bad mood.
Hey!
Oh? It's Ali!
He's back. Had us all worrying, that kid.
See? That's how good my training is!
All right!
Prepare to set sail!
Your Majesty, urgent news!
The princess is missing.
What? She's gone?
Wh-What should we do, Vizier?
Sire, please accept my apologies!
Sinbad!
Princess Samir!
What are you doing out here?
Pretty please, take me with you!
You won't send me back, will you?
What are you?
Greetings.
You won't be enough.
Oh my, Vizier, what's wrong?
You look irritated.
How do you like my style? Lovely, isn't it?
Ugh! I have no use for you!
Each and every last one of them...
Oh! You're the one I need.
You're my servant from now on.
Your name shall be... Hell Bat!
Come here.
You'll follow the Princess and
keep an eye on her. Understood?
Go!
Allah is great.
In the name of Allah the eternal,
may today's voyage be safe and peaceful.
What is it?
Now, man your stations!
They say if you depart from this sea
and sail all the way south,
there's a beautiful five-colored island.
Delicious fruit, cool springs...
Strange flowers and birds, and giant diamonds.
No, we can't make detours.
We can't?
No way.
Prepare to change course!
Captain, where are we going?
To Treasure Island.
Hard to starboard!
We'll be jolly on our journey!
We'll be tipsy when we set sail!
Ali, go have fun with them too.
I like it better here.
Hey, may I join you guys?
We'll be jolly on our journey!
We'll be tipsy when we set sail!
See, I'm not used to speaking with royals.
Why does everyone seem to shun me?
We'll be jolly on our journey!
Because you're so different.
We'll be tipsy when we set sail!
I see, I see.
Oh, you're back, Hell Bat?
What? The Princess in on the Boldar?
A Treasure Island to the south?
All right, got it.
Your Majesty, we've picked up the Princess's trail.
Have you, really? So, where is she?
Your Majesty, I regret to inform you...
She's on a ship.
Then what are you waiting for?
Go and bring her back right now!
Ali! Hurry and get down!
Furl the sails!
What's going on?
The rope is stuck!
Damn it...
Help me with this one!
We won't make it in time!
All right, now's our chance!
A wave is coming!
Furl the sails already!
There's nothing more we can do!
Captain!
Captain, please take over!
Okay!
Hand it over!
Princess Samir!
Hey!
Hurry!
The ship's gonna capsize!
Ali! Give me your sword!
Here!
Sinbad!
Hold on tight, Sinbad!
My!
Sinbad!
Don't look down!
Hang in there!
Clear out!
Hey, can you see the Boldar yet?
No, sir! Nothing yet!
It's that little whale again!
You doing good?
Peppi.
Aren't you glad to have a souvenir?
Little Whale, it's time for you to go home.
Your mom's waiting.
Oh, my! Kuppi!
I'm so glad to see you here!
Ali, look at the sky ahead.
O blue memories, O distant dreams!
How beautiful...
The fog that enveloped my heart is slowly clearing
Mother, I'm sorry for worrying you.
But I'm really happy now!
Traveling by ship is wonderful,
and I've made such lovely friends.
Oh, I can't believe that girl.
But you know, we got caught
in a terrible storm the other day!
What? A storm?!
But it's fine. Sinbad saved us all.
Sinbad did?
But I have to admit...
I'm beginning to miss Father by now.
Beneath that sky lies happiness abounding
Boundless hope can be found beyond those clouds
So let's go, everyone! Let's go, everyone!
Beneath that sky, past those clouds
So damn hot out here, Yasim.
Such is life, man.
We're low on water too.
Hope we get a squall soon, right, Captain?
No kidding.
Here, Sinbad, have some water.
Oh, thanks.
It's from Princess Samir.
My! What's wrong, Peppi?
Your Excellency! Hell Bat's back!
Oh! Hell Bat, I've been waiting.
Good. Don't slack on the surveillance.
Just you wait, Sinbad.
Your Excellency, at last we'll get
both the princess and the treasure!
Captain, the sky looks strange.
Captain, the color of the sea is changing!
Okay...
Oh? That's odd. It's stuck.
Captain, this is bad!
Something huge is down there!
We're in trouble, Captain.
Where did we veer off course?
The sea is so strange here, right, Sinbad?
This is the "Sea of Demons" I've heard about.
Looks like...
we aren't getting out of here alive!
Is that true?
L-Look!
C-Captain, that's a ghost...
A ghost ship!
Man, this is bad.
The ship's moving!
All right!
Everyone, man your positions!
Little Whale! You came to help us?
Thanks!
Thank you!
Your Excellency!
I see a small boat dead ahead of us!
Okay! Keep it in sight at all times!
Yes, sir!
Captain, fog's rolling in.
This is some thick fog.
A very unusual fog, Captain.
Yeah. Keep your eyes open.
I can't see a thing anymore.
Okay, come on down.
Yes, sir.
Watch out, Sinbad!
This is the island, right, Captain?
Yeah... probably.
Wow, what an island!
My, how wonderful!
Drop the anchor!
All right, I'm counting on you people.
Yes, sir!
We'll come back with some rare souvenirs, Captain.
Take me with you!
Nope. You're staying with me.
So this is Treasure Island?
We finally made it, Sinbad!
We'll find something incredible on this island.
What a creepy bird!
Yeah.
Samir!
Ali!
Sinbad!
Samir!
Ali!
How refreshing!
Hey, let me drink some too!
Yasim! Help me!
Treasure Island, my foot.
I've had enough of this!
I can't go on...
Come on, Ali, hang in there!
Listen well.
As soon as you find them,
kill them on the spot.
Yes, sir!
Samir!
Ali!
Sinbad!
Leave them be! We need to hurry!
What a nuisance!
Sinbad!
Oh!
It's the five-colored gemstones
the old man talked about!
Ali, more importantly,
we have to find Sinbad now.
Yeah.
Sinbad!
Sinbad...
Princess! We've crossed paths again
in such a mysterious place.
What do you want from the princess?!
Sinbad!
Let go!
You little brat!
Stop!
Sinbad!
Ali, take the princess and get out of here!
After them, men!
Move it!
Oh! That's the princess!
Stop!
Stop struggling, you wench!
What are you doing?!
S-Sinbad!
Caught you, kiddo!
Come on, Sinbad! We're h—
Ali!
Shut up!
Let me go!
You lot, stuff the gems in the bags, now!
Samir!
Ali!
This is magnificent.
Let's hurry back to the ship!
Samir! Ali!
Princess!
Sinbad! Sinbad!
Samir! Ali!
Sinbad!
Merciful God of Allah,
I pray that you may save their lives.
I know I've found a treasure
far greater than any jewel.
Oh? And what's that?
Princess Samir... it's you.
The End