Good.
With this, the family won't have
anything to worry about.
Shout! It's almost time.
10, 9, 8, 7,
Shut up, won't you?
6, 5...
When it's time go, I'll start on my own cue.
All right then, whatever you say.
Here we go.
Who's there?!
I'm sorry to interrupt your deal.
I'm just a garbage collector!
Asshole!
What gang are you from?!
They stole our goods!
Now!
We're not thieves!
We're just throwing useless things away.
Floor it, Crunch!
Roger that!
Who are they?
Don't tell me it's them, the Midnight Trash Throw Away-ers, who can throw anything away?!
The grimoire is in place.
Tension, max!
One pull on this rope
will get rid of magic for good!
I'll become just an ordinary girl!
Seriously...
I thought I'd shatter the grimoire
to pieces for sure this time!
Is it really resistant to conventional methods?
Doesn't matter. I won't resort to magic!
N-No, don't come!
Don't come after me! Please!
I so wish I could throw this grimoire away.
Yeah, I know. I won't forget it.
Another one of our sisters sets out tonight.
She'll be schooled in the ways of a bride
while sharpening her witchcraft.
Now then... To throw it away!
Show me all the info about how to throw it away.
It's gonna take ages
if I don't narrow my search down!
I just want to throw it away.
Why is it so hard?
What's this?
We're not thieves!
We're just throwing useless things away.
They throw things away?
Makina, what are you doing?
It's almost time for your ritual.
Y-Yes! I was just making sure
I didn't forget anything, Madam Bishop!
Makina, by tradition, on the night
of the first full moon after you turn 16,
you will be sent to the human world
to train in magic.
Under the guidance of a senior witch
waiting for you there,
collect all the passing marks
in your grimoire before returning.
Maybe I shouldn't go, after all-
Out of the question!
But I don't need magic.
Don't be childish!
This is human money. You're supposed
to know how to use it by now.
Study well and don't waste any.
Got it.
I don't care about magical training.
I wanna go into the human world,
but only to be a normal girl!
Magic be damned.
Magic be damned!
Greetings, fellow humans!
Ah, yikes! I'm supposed
to keep it a secret that I'm a witch.
Oh, don't worry! I have money, see?
Wow! So stylish, so cute!
Swell! It's more exciting
than flying on a broom!
Amazing!
Hey! Isn't it great?
Looks delicious!
Ah! I'm full!
But I sure wonder why humans
want to use money so much.
It'd be so much easier with magic!
No! I made up my mind!
There are billions of humans on this earth,
and not even a thousand witches.
But I'll try my best to become
a normal human girl!
Nice to meet you, brand new world
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
I'm sure I can change too
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
To be as colorful as everyone else
QC
Nemesis, Uchuu
Where are you?
Raw
Ioroid
If I can see your smile
I don't need anything else
Say goodbye to the magic of the dreamy world
I won't look back at my old memories
I'll go beyond my memories and move on to a new me
I know there's a future for me
I'm sure we'll meet somewhere
Far away from here
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
An ice cream truck!
Then I'll have twenty tea-flavored ones.
I'll have chocolate and pineapple, also orange, milk, strawberry, and chocolate mint... Three of each!
Here you go.
Madam! Ice cream!
I'm sorry, young lady. These last customers just bought up the rest of my stock.
Huh? No way...
Hey!
You, humans #1 and #2!
Why would you buy it like that?
Why so much?!
Don't you have any restraint?!
Ice cream! Ice cream! Ice cream!
Don't eat it just for show!
And it looked really delicious!
We bought it and paid for it.
Got any problem with...
Ice cream...
I've always wanted to eat it,
the stuff of my dreams, ice cream.
I burned through my money
and only have three pounds left.
I only wanted to eat some ice cream,
and then you...
They're gone! Where'd you go?! There you are!
Go!
Wait, you! If it comes to this...
W-Wait, what?
You tried to run, so my magic...
I mean, karma caught up with you!
All right, our bad. So, what now?
It's you...
Trash Throw Away-ers?
We are the Trash Throw Away-ers, all right,
but we're different from ordinary garbage collectors.
What are you throwing away, then?
In this world, there are quite a few things
that you want to throw away, but can't.
From your ex-lover's past secrets,
to large companies' confidential files, to state secrets.
Can you throw this away, then?
If you throw it away,
I'll forgive you for the ice cream.
See you!
Hey, wait!
What the...
That's it. That's why I can't throw it away myself!
But maybe if you flung it into
your machine with the teeth...
How did you know?
I guess I just knew, somehow.
Give it here!
How about this?
It's hot!
Cut it out, you idiot.
The children will copy you.
Yeah, sorry.
If we drop it from this height,
it'll shatter for sure.
There.
What the hell?!
So?
We've got no choice. Show it to her.
It's gonna cost you, though.
If you really need to throw it away,
come here at this time. It's our job.
Then we'll get rid of it for good.
I feel like that escalated rather quickly.
That's a nice pendant you have.
I've been waiting.
Where have you been, Makina?
Wh-Who are you?
I heard about you from Madam Bishop.
I'm Dorothy.
I've been living among humans
for who-knows-how-many years.
Did you get married?
Yes, to a very handsome man.
That's so nice!
A normal marriage, and a normal life...
It's not normal, though.
I was also sent to train in witchcraft
in the human world when I was young.
It was hard to live hiding magic.
Speaking of that, do you happen to know
of any good work for me?
I spent so much money in the human world,
I'm in a bit of a pickle now.
Yes. I'll show you a job that'll help
with your witchcraft training.
Um...
I don't really care about that training!
I just want to work normally
and live a normal life!
Out of the question.
You don't have to be so blunt.
But that's the witches' laws.
Laws?
At the height of the witch trials 500 years ago,
the great witch cursed those
who fail to master witchcraft fully.
You'll be turned into a frog.
A f-frog?!
Yes.
Witches are destined to learn witchcraft
and marry only demons.
Those who rebel against it get turned
into tree frogs, toads, bullfrogs, and so on.
You wanna be turned?
Anything... but a frog... Anything...
By the way, who were the two men
I saw you with?
Ah, just some friends I met by chance.
Or should I say, "My ice cream rivals"?
Did you realize it too?
What?
That girl's pendant was a magical item.
Which means that girl...
She's a witch, right?
Hey, what the hell, you knew?
Witches are so dangerous that the government
even keeps top-secret files on them!
Even the police has been on the move lately!
So what?
Look, I don't mean to sound rude,
but if we get involved with that girl-
She's still our customer,
even though she wants to throw away her grimoire.
Does she even have any money?
Doesn't matter. We'll get our due.
Training, training! Training!
Ouch...
Clairvoyance is my magic specialty!
It lets you avoid danger and keep one step ahead by reading people's mind!
So I'm unbeatable at rock-paper-scissors!
The trick to predicting the future is to use your nose.
You can read the air around you by smelling it.
We start with the nostril-stretching machine.
This is also part of your training.
Bear with it!
Come on, your nostrils! We need to widen them!
Okay, okay.
How about it?
Does it suit me, Madam Dorothy?
It's my debut as a human girl!
Yay!
You'll have to pay for the clothes
with your part-time job earnings.
Yeah, I know...
Ouch...
Come on, let's show you some applied witchcraft.
Witches shine in areas
that humans have no idea about.
Resurrection magic can help a flower shop.
There will be rain tomorrow. I guarantee it!
Making it rain at will can help a weather forecaster.
You can ride your broom to do delivery work.
Witches go to great lengths
to keep magic hidden from humans.
I see...
Magic that helps people?
How are you using your magic to help, Madam Dorothy?
You'll know when the time comes.
Now, as for your part-time job...
Yes?
It's this restaurant.
What? Seriously?!
But I'm not really good at serving customers...
More confidence!
Welcome!
There are six of you, right? This way, please.
Huh? No, there's only two...
We're late! Sorry!
Huh?! 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. How...
What would you like?
Let's see. What do you want?
Customers need more time for that.
Fish and chips, and a hamburger.
And you'll have a mellow-flavored hamburger
without pickles, and Stroganoff.
And for you, traditional chicken and green onion salt pasta without green onions, right?
Wow, amazing! She guessed it!
Start taking the order, manager.
Right... Sorry.
Okay, you'll have...
Clairvoyance can be useful, actually!
I'm back, Madam Dorothy!
Welcome back, Makina.
N-Nice to meet you... I'm back.
No, it's all right.
Dorothy said she'd be working late tonight.
Don't you want anything?
D-Don't mind me. I'm on a diet.
Dorothy's husband is so gentlemanly.
If only I could also find a normal man like that...
Huh? Giggle?
Oh, I can't pretend any longer!
Dorothy didn't say it at first,
but our eating habits are rather vulgar.
A-A demon!
Ah... Ah, excuse me, I gotta run now!
No way!
I don't wanna marry a demon.
And I don't wanna turn into a frog either!
No! No! Absolutely no!
No, no, no, no!
I wanna throw it away.
I wanna throw magic away!
I don't wanna be a witch!
If only I could throw the grimoire away,
I'd be free to do whatever I want!
That's true!
This way. No, this way!
Come on, right here!
Welcome to bus line O53 at 0:53!
'Sup! We'll make sure to throw it away tonight.
Don't scare me like that!
I thought it was magic.
Magic?
You mean our camouflage?
Hey, throw it away already! You promised!
The special vehicle we're towing has a 2.05 million horsepower press
and a 2,000-degree incineration capacity.
To be precise, it operates at 2,085 degrees Celsius.
We'll give you a demo
of how professionals do it.
Speaking of that, the fee for using our machine,
including fuel costs and tax...
I don't have any money.
Forget the money.
You said you'd do anything to get rid of it, right?
We thought you could help us out
with our work a bit.
Are you the two special agents
who can read minds?
Yes, we came as promised.
Have you deployed the guards
according to my instructions?
Yes, two armed droid policemen
are already waiting.
The arrangement is perfect!
Very well.
Launch a special capture team on two targets.
Isn't this stealing?
Just garbage collecting.
Why are we sneaking around, then?
Because we're sneaky Throw Away-ers.
And we're counting on your one special power.
M-My special power? What is that?
It's right below us.
There doesn't seem to be any security, though.
Keep it down!
Sorry!
Is this it?
We're stealing this?
We're not thieves!
Still, that's one distasteful painting.
"A Demon's Night Feast"?
You wanna steal this?
Throw it away!
I imagine the owner wouldn't take kindly
to you throwing it away.
Our client is the artist
who painted this picture.
It's just a plagiarized work
he drew when he was younger.
He came to regret it and wants to get rid of it,
but it's out of his reach now.
So now... You're going to throw it away?
Everyone has a piece of their past
they want to throw away.
A past they want to throw away...
Makina!
Even I have something like that...
Oh! They're aiming at you!
What?
A Special Capture Team!
Police Speed Droids on special assignment!
What?!
It looks like they're reading our minds!
That shouldn't be possible!
We're the clairvoyance squad here!
Hold up, how did it come to this?!
Doesn't matter, just run!
What about the picture, about your job?!
Don't worry. They saved us the effort
of getting rid of it.
We need to worry about ourselves now!
Turn right at that corner!
Got it!
But the exit is straight ahead!
Just listen to what I say!
We've been read again!
Hey, lady, why not use some magic?
Just blow them up!
No! I want to throw it away!
So you are a witch, after all?
Oops!
I've got it!
Send the droids to the eastern service entrance.
Roger that! All droids
to the eastern service entrance!
Hurry up!
Crunch!
What's the safest exit?
Eastern service entrance.
No!
Why?
It doesn't smell right!
Then use your magic...
Out of the question!
Why did we with bring you along, then?!
What was that?
Enough, Crunch.
If she wants to throw it away,
we can't use it.
Everyone should be allowed
to throw something away.
That's what we,
the Throw Away-ers, take pride in.
Guess you're right. So be it.
Come on, Crazy Trail!
What happened there?
This is bad! It seems they've read us
at the eastern service entrance too!
You won't be riding it with us!
Come on! Let me in!
They're only after us.
Take care, young lady.
Why are you trying to look cool?
You're riding a garbage truck!
Don't throw your life away
along with your magic.
Wha...
Are you serious?!
Not a target. Not a target.
I've gotta save them!
We gotta shake them off!
If only we had magic on our side...
Forget about it!
You've got to turn back now!
Back? Why?!
This is a dead end!
Hey, look after yourself!
Switch all droids
from capture mode to attack mode.
Attacking is against regulations!
Our job is only to gather data-
Doesn't matter! Just do what I say!
When even my magic doesn't help...
Attack mode. Attack mode. Attack mode.
Wait, what?
Attack mode. Attack mode.
Whoa! This is bad!
What?!
A dead end!
Please! Stop... Stop!
Stop!
Makina!
No!
Makina?
Hey, are you okay? Hey!
All the droids disappeared
from the search screen.
What should we do now?
Let the processing team deal with it later.
Let's return to headquarters.
Okay!
Stop!
That mole was Makina's familiar.
Is it possible that Makina was reading us?
Where am I?
You're up, Madam Witch?
Shout?
You saved us.
Isn't it a waste, throwing away such power?
No! I'm throwing it away!
You promised to crush my grimoire
with your truck, remember?
Destroying that grimoire is beyond our power.
Sorry, but you'll have to give up.
What?! No way...
What are you going to do now, Makina?
What should I do?
I guess I'll look for some other place
to throw it away.
Take me with you!
No, you must take me with you!
Yes! You promised to rid me of it!
What, you're still going on about that?
Yeah!
Are you sure we should just let her go like that?
Yeah.
I guess that's also part of her training.
After all, she's already better
at clairvoyance than me.
Huh? I already got one passing mark in witchcraft!
Look at that. You wanted to throw it away,
but you leveled-up instead.
Are you kidding me?!
I'll throw it away! I absolutely will!
Sure, sure.
What a fussy customer.
Well, let's go for now!
Floor it!
Crazily...
With a spring!
In other news,
the artist of the damaged painting, "A Demon's Night Feast," has released a statement.
"My sadness and indignation are immeasurable.
However, my dissatisfaction over this incident
will allow me to put my soul into my new work."
Apparently, the museum has offered compensation.
I forgot about my familiar!
What a broad-minded person!
Just bring him back with your magic.
Right, lady.
Stay tuned for further details.
I don't feel so good...