Please stop.
You are violating the traffic laws.
Yes, it's the best!
Yeah!
If you need to carry something...
You can send your luggage by cargobot.
I want to carry it myself.
This weight feels perfect too.
I see...
Well then, thanks.
Hello, Rabiri.
I want to go to the Secret Market on Avenue 5.
Leave it to me!
It's been 100 years since humanity
last needed to walk.
We have developed new medical devices and shoes
to ensure comfortable lives for all people.
We strive to pursue further evolution
and keep pushing the limits daily.
Fractal Walter Co.
Make way! Let me pass!
Huh?
Please stop.
You are violating the traffic laws.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Please stop.
You are violating the traffic laws.
Sorry, I'm not stopping!
Show me the Dynamelos announcement website!
Yes, this is it! Dynamelos sneakers!
The phantom year 81 Ulysses model!
Can't believe they went ahead
with this limited edition reprint!
It hits the Secret Market tomorrow,
which means I have to get them today!
I have no time for your crap!
Please stop.
You are violating the traffic laws.
No way!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Stop!
M-Miss Shelly Walter?
Daughter of the president of Fractal Walter?
This kid is my staff member.
This was our meeting spot,
so I'll handle things from here.
Yes, sir!
Thanks.
But wait... Daughter
of the Fractal Walter president?!
Those shoes...
and that car!
And this... and that... Everything!
"We strive to pursue further evolution
and keep pushing the limits daily.
Fractal Walter Co." That one?!
Why did you memorize the slogan?
I'm Shelley. What about you?
I'm Nike.
And I've got no time to talk! I gotta run—
We can fix that.
But those sneakers... Isn't that a reprint of Dynamelos year 94 summer model?
Wow, amazing! Spot on!
How come you know these by name?
Because I like them.
I'm a sneaker maniac.
No way! For real? Hey, let's be friends!
Won't you come to my hideout?
Definitely come!
I've got so much stuff to show you!
The year 81 Ulysses model?
But that only gets released tomorrow.
And that's why I had to get them today.
It's a limited release!
You just have to snag it under the counter.
I mean... To think I've met another true sneaker enthusiast who even knows about that!
This is the first time I've met someone other than me who likes sneakers.
Are you sure?
You won't be able to buy them ahead this way.
I've met you, and that's all that matters!
There used to be a lot of different sports
where people pushed their bodies to the limit.
Those people, who only exist in legends nowadays,
always had sneakers on their feet.
That's why I feel a great power
in the shape of sneakers themselves.
I think that's beautiful.
Didn't think I'd hear that from the daughter
of Fractal Walter's president,
the very company that made sneakers obsolete.
Isn't that amusing?
Come on in. This is it.
This smell...
Incredible! They're all Dynamelos vintage models!
But this... this Hazing model...
Don't tell me it's the original
and not a reprint?
Of course not!
They're all reprints.
After all, I use my collection sometimes.
It's a whole lot of fun!
Shelly! Hey, look!
Ta-da!
Shelly, climb up here too.
Let's dance together!
Ah, but...
It's fine, it's fine!
C'mon, let's dance together!
Hey, Nike, how did you come
to love sneakers so much?
I'm sure it's a phrase from some other country,
but it goes like this: "Wear good shoes.
Good shoes take the wearer to a good place."
I heard it somewhere once, and ever since then,
I loved just walking in my normal shoes.
Then I learned about sneakers,
and I loved walking in sneakers even more!
But I'm sure that proverb was true.
After all, it let me meet you!
Did we really dance the night away?
I have a gift for you.
Will you please accept it?
What? You're giving it to me?
I'm super happy!
Can I look inside?
Sure.
What? A sneaker box?
What? No way!
It's the year 81 Ulysses model of Dynamelos!
Were you buying it ahead of time too?!
I'm sorry, Nike.
I lied to you.
Actually, I'm the CEO of Dynamelos myself.
What? No way!
I practically begged the rights holders for Dynamelos and threw my whole heart into the negotiations.
Eventually, everyone was happy
to entrust the license to me.
When humanity sets out to push
the limits of the human body again,
I know they'll be wearing Dynamelos on their feet.
So I'm just happy to be a part of those reprints.
Then did you make all of the Dynamelos reprint sneakers here yourself?
I only planned and sold them.
They're made by craftsmen
who inherited the techniques of the time.
This is one of humanity's treasures, so I thought it was important to reproduce them properly and preserve it.
But when I saw your worn-out sneakers,
I really felt like they were laughing proudly.
So...
So I want you to wear these too.
I want you to let them join everyone else in here.
Thank you, Shelly.
I will totally treasure them!
We'll have countless adventures
with these two!
Let's go!
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Nemesis, Uchuu
Encoding
jireh