Yes, that's it! Go, go, go!
Good! He's finished!
Come on, you old fart!
Don't you know what time it is?!
Quit making disgusting noises!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
I'll be more careful from now on.
What's going on, Pedro?
Are you still wandering the heavens?
But it's not about you.
The one in my dreams...
That man who shows up every time...
Who the hell might he be?
Orphan Fansubs presents
I don't know when I started having
that same dream over and over again.
Yes, it started back then.
Dr. Alex Gordon,
you've been diagnosed
with a malignant tumor.
Ever since then,
whenever I go to sleep, I'm afraid.
Not of death, of the dream.
It feels like someone is ordering me,
"Don't give up! Fight until the end!"
Not over the illness,
but for something more important.
Hey, wait for me!
Hey, kid!
What's all this fuss about?
There's a Champion Fight at Yonkers High School over there.
Champion Fight?
Yonkers High School and Carroll High School
have always been rivals.
Each time there's a problem, their representatives settle it in a Champion Fight.
Why are you dawdling there?!
We'll be late!
Coming!
Champion Fight?
Might as well take a look.
Hooray, hooray, Yonkers!
Go, go, Carroll!
We will now hold a Champion Fight.
For Carroll HS, Jack Redman.
Hey, handsome boy!
I'm gonna crush your jaw.
I hope you have insurance.
For Yonkers HS, Guy Hyuga!
If you keep wasting oxygen,
I'll change my mind about letting you live.
What?
He's the boy from my dream!
I'm certain of it.
I want to see a fair and honorable contest.
Fight!
It's hopeless! Redman is a heavyweight high school wrestling champion.
Guy's karate won't help him all that much.
Karate? Are you saying
that boy is a karate fighter?
Yeah. He and his dad
run a dojo in Harlem.
So it's karate versus wrestling?
Referee, stop the fight.
Back off, boy! You won, all right?
Stop, stop! You wanna kill him?
You're good!
Wonderful. He's a natural!
He has the makings of a first-rate boxer!
You've been tailing me. Who are you?
What do you want?
N-No...
I didn't mean to tail you. I just didn't know how to start a conversation.
You don't look like a mugger to me.
I'm Alex Gordon. I'm a doctor
specializing in sports physiology.
Look, Guy, I was wondering
if you'd let me look at your body.
I'm not interested in your perversions.
D-Don't get me wrong.
It's purely out of medical interest.
I can pay. No, I mean, I don't have all that much, but I could scrounge up some...
Pay up. You said you could.
R-Right...
Would this do?
Just your upper body is enough.
Take it off.
Incredible! Just as I thought!
It's not just your physique.
You have flexible and supple muscles.
That's enough. I'm leaving.
W-Wait, Guy!
Are you...
interested in boxing?
Your stance in the fight was perfect.
You're a natural fighter!
You're first-rate boxer material.
So you saw... tonight's Champion Fight?
Yeah, those hard punches of yours
are seared firmly into my eyes.
Sorry, I don't plan on becoming a boxer.
What are your plans, then?
I heard that you're paying for high school
at your elementary school tuition rate.
So the principal asked you to participate
in those Champion Fights to make up for it.
I'll be a public accountant.
You?
Don't make me laugh.
You, a public accountant?
You can laugh all you want, but it's my life,
and I'll do whatever I want with it.
H-Hey, hold on! I'm sorry if I came off as rude.
Can we talk a little more?
Let go! Stop! Help me!
Our agreement doesn't include
serving you for free!
No good. We gotta do something.
Forget it. That woman's been around.
And those guys are hardened criminals.
What do you hope to achieve
if you step in now?
But I can't just let this happen.
If you wanna stay alive in this city, you gotta learn what to do and what not to do.
No! Help me!
But I'm an American man.
I have cancer.
I've only got a year to live.
Guy, you can strive to live
a long and happy life here.
But American men will fight to the death
when a lady is in danger.
Good luck.
Give it up!
You know guys like them won't hold back just 'cause you're old!
Stubborn old fuck.
No! Stop! Stop it!
Stop!
Billy, go keep a lookout.
All right, but I want some of it too!
I'll buy you plenty of your favorite donuts later if you go last. Deal?
You've got it, bro.
Who the hell are you?!
I came to help that lady.
If you want money,
we can strike a deal.
Bro?
How much we talkin'?
Eighty dollars. It's all I have.
We'll be taking that.
Billy, show him out.
Okay.
W-Wait a minute,
that's not what we agreed!
C'mon, out with you, grandpa.
You schmuck!
No, let go!
I can't breathe!
I-I can't breathe!
Th-The hell you want?!
Guy?!
Good, you can connect moves so seamlessly!
Why are you still mumbling? Let's run!
Right... Yeah, he's right.
Run away, lady!
Right!
Now you've got me real mad.
Careful, Guy.
This guy knows some boxing.
Is he a monster or something?
I know my kick landed squarely on his face!
That's it! It's bedtime for all of you!
That's my line!
I'll put you to sleep with a single punch!
It's a cross-counter!
Such destructive power!
It hurts, bro!
He dislodged my eye!
This is our chance! Run!
R-Right, l-lady?
That woman escaped long ago! Hurry up!
R-Right...
That helpless geezer.
Incredible! He can run so fast
without missing a beat!
Okay, we should be safe here.
Go home! And never show your face
in this neighborhood again.
Oh no, now you interest me even more.
Guy, my boy.
Wouldn't you like to box with me?
I can make you a champion in a year!
Hey, geezer!
Would you want your own daughter
to become a hooker?
What do you mean?
To me, boxers and hookers
are two sides of the same coin,
using their bodies to make a buck.
But a hooker's dealing out pleasure instead of pain.
Maybe she's got a better deal, after all.
You don't have the slightest idea
of what boxing is!
Don't come close to me ever again!
You're an angel of death,
that's what you are!
Die if you want,
but don't take me with you!
Guy...
Ciao! If you're lucky, we'll meet again.
Don't make me laugh, Guy.
You think I'll give up?
I feel that making you a champion is what the final fight of my life should be about.
Wh-Who's there?
Oh, lady?
You should cut it out with "lady" and all.
I don't deserve that kind of title.
But you're safe,
and that's all that matters.
Thank you.
I just wanted to say that.
P-Put that back on!
You'll catch a cold.
That's the only way I can think of to thank you.
Don't be shy, Pops.
You can have me.
No, I appreciate the concern,
but I'll turn it down.
Won't you find out
where that young man lives instead?
You should know this area better than I do.
Really? That's all you want?
Yes, please.
You know, something tells me,
we'll hit it off just fine, Pops.
I love a man like you.
You're making me blush!
Where have you been, Dad?
Binge drinking again?
I found this in your jacket.
Th-That's...
That's mine!
Don't you let your guard down
just 'cause I've had a few.
You'd better step it up
if you ever wanna catch up to me.
Asshole! To hell with you,
you rotten old geezer!
It sure feels good to be revered by your son.
Hey, what's this? You need to tuck your belly in more, Ronny!
Dammit...
What's wrong, Ronny?
I just remembered something nasty.
The youngest of the Zolder brothers,
Billy, lost his eye in a fight.
So?
They say some ungodly strong karate man did it.
It wasn't you, was it?
Because if it was,
the brothers will kill you!
They swore a vendetta!
Don't worry. It was someone else.
For real?
Yeah. Relax, Ronny.
All right, 50 straight jabs next!
Are you Alex Gordon?
Ryuu... Ryuu Hyuga, isn't it?
Guy's father?
That street whore Lily told me
something about you.
Still, you'd better give up
on making a boxer out of Guy.
Why's that? You don't find talent like that
lying thick on the ground!
He could become a champion in just under a year!
He's a stubborn bastard who doesn't even bow when I, his dad, enter the dojo.
Once he's made up his mind,
he won't change it, no matter what.
Oh no... please! If you mention it too,
I'm sure he'll at least think it over.
Lady!
I'm sorry, Pops.
They caught me off guard!
So, geezer, where's that karate man from yesterday?
I-I don't know.
I was actually looking for him too.
Don't mess with me!
We can send you to a world of pain.
What are you planning
to do with my guest?
Shut up!
We're here to avenge our little brother,
so don't try my patience! See this?
I do, but you can't see my legs.
What? Your legs?
For this!
Wh-Who the hell are you...
You're looking for Guy, and he's my son.
If you got a problem with him,
you can take it up with me anytime.
Just be aware that you can end up like this—
As expected. Like father, like son.
Watch out! Behind you!
He's still alive!
Call an ambulance!
Who are you?
This is an operating room! Get out!
Dad... Dad, don't die!
Half a month has passed since then.
Ryuu Hyuga is hanging by a thread,
and no one knows when, or if, he'll wake up.
He's been in a coma ever since.
But at least that event cracked open
a new avenue for Guy and me.
Sorry for the wait.
You came, after all.
I was afraid you wouldn't.
They told me you paid for Dad's hospital bills.
I came to say thanks.
Don't mention it.
Stick with me, and one day,
that fight money's gonna make you rich.
Pops, you really are an angel of death.
I know, but I'm also the man who's going to make you the best boxer in the world.
If I don't even know when, or if,
my dad's gonna wake up...
maybe it'd be better if he just died.
You shouldn't say that.
Your father is fighting too!
Shut up!
What do you know?
It pains me to see him like that too,
but I won't let him die.
I'll make sure that my dad comes back,
with my own strength!
Yes, that's the spirit!
The only way left for you is to earn
your own living with your fists!
You can be a champ too!
You just have to believe in me.
I've never believed in God,
so why should I believe in you?
Right you are.
I'm also strapped for time.
So I have to make you
a champion in under a year.
You're a good friend, Alex Gordon.
That's right, Guy Hyuga.
And then we crossed the Brooklyn Bridge
into Manhattan.
Guy, do you see it? Manhattan Island?
That island, a mass of concrete and steel,
is our arena.
To me, Manhattan feels less like a boxing ring and more like a graveyard,
more headstones than anywhere else on Earth.
That's fine. You'll have to beat
many a strong man on that island,
sending their dreams to the graveyard.
New York. An enormous city,
also called the Big Apple.
It's only natural to find many hungry
and dream-driven apples in there.
Wrong, Guy.
If you thrust your hook more from underneath like an uppercut, it'll pack more of a punch.
Okay. I'll try again.
What do you say, Alex?
If you only ever train with the punching bag,
your punches will blunt.
Why don't you pit him
against my King Kong?
No, we're good for now.
Guy is still merely learning
the ropes of boxing.
Let me do it.
Guy?
He's right. This blind practice
will only blunt my fists.
Okay! Then it's settled.
Get up here!
Hold it.
Lucky?
Won't you let me spar with that child first?
So you came, Lucky?
Who's this guy? Your friend?
He's your trainer, Guy.
He's doing it as a favor for me.
I haven't agreed to it yet, Alex.
I just came to get a taste of this boy
who holds you so spellbound.
Yes, taste him you will.
Prepare to spar!
Hey, hold it! What about me?
You should stay out of this,
dimwit that you are.
What did you say?!
Hey, chill! You don't understand.
He was once a candidate for the light heavyweight championship: Lucky Roman.
"Once" my ass!
He's but a common pansy right now!
I'll never let him look down on me!
Don't fuck with me!
Oh, what a shame.
A boxer with an untrained body
is worse than a pig.
So what do you say, handsome boy?
Wanna repeat his fate?
I'm not a "boy."
I have a name.
Very well. If you can still stand after one round with me, I'll call you by name.
If New York is a gathering of hungry apples,
then Lucky refers to himself as a rotten apple.
I remember going to ask him
to become Guy's trainer.
Forget it, Alex.
I'm too old for that.
No matter how much of a golden egg that guy is, I can't be a trainer any more.
I'm sure you'll think of something.
I'm also too old to withstand his punches properly.
This is hopeless.
Why?
I have...
AIDS.
Even a slight illness will kill me.
L-Lucky...
That's why I'm closing the bar as well.
Everyone's turned their back on me,
too scared to come near.
Get the fuck out, Lucky!
Get your sick ass out of our city!
The owner of this bar hired those thugs.
Wherever I go, I'm treated like a plague.
I can't help it. My days are numbered.
I'm scared! I don't want to die yet.
Lucky!
My poor Lucky!
I'm sorry for trying to dump my problems onto you!
Please live the rest of your days
the way you want!
I understand how you feel.
I have cancer.
I'll go even before you.
After much deliberation,
he finally understood my predicament.
You have a wonderful physique.
It's like you never quit!
It's because I kept on training.
Well, boy, we can start now.
I am not a "boy."
Don't ever call me that!
If you want to shut me up, you'll have to let your fists do the speaking, boy.
Dancing lesson is over.
Shithead!
That's it. Go to sleep, boy.
Weird... I can't knock him down!
P-Please, Lucky!
Don't mess Guy up!
I can't blink.
I need to see his punches coming!
He dodged my jab!
He's dodging Lucky's punches, even though I haven't taught him defense yet!
Guy... You're a beast.
I've never seen a man like you.
You finally called me by name...
Guy, Lucky! Hang in there!
Help me out, someone!
All right...
Get up, Lucky.
Stop... Don't touch me!
No touching! No!
Well, I'll be.
That was downright impressive.
Lucky, let me shake your hand in friendship.
Even though I have AIDS...
What did you say?!
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have kept it a secret.
But don't worry.
I'll clean everything up myself and leave.
You'd damn better do!
That's it! Get out! Out with you!
Guy, that's how it goes.
And that's why I can't be your trainer. Sorry.
Alex, disinfect his wounds, won't you?
Lucky, I'm glad you came.
You'll always be my friend.
Thank you, Alex.
I really envy you, now that I've seen this beast
who'll fulfill your final dream.
Lucky...
I really love boxing still.
Alex.
Do I need him?
I asked you if I need that guy's help
to become a champion.
G-Guy...
Guy?
Lucky Roman,
you should become my trainer.
It's a dead end.
Completely hopeless!
Didn't you hear? I have AIDS.
Don't worry about that, Lucky.
I can promise you one thing.
If you become my trainer,
you'll go down in history as someone
who created a world champion.
It was the first time someone
who's not my dad had hit me so hard.
Please, be my trainer!
I need your expertise!
Jesus... You really mean it, Guy!
You really need me!
Nobody ever told me they needed me...
You were...
the first person ever...
who told me to keep on living.
You shouldn't cry anymore.
Until the day I become a champion,
let's keep tears out of it.
I promise.
I'll save those tears for the day
when you become a champ.
Then it's a deal, Lucky.
My training is tough, though.
Is that okay with you? Are you ready?
Of course.
Guy! Dash! Quick!
Guy Hyuga. Physical examination revealed no abnormalities.
Heavyweight... Oh?
You forgot to put in
his amateur career record.
He doesn't have any.
He started as a karateka.
You can't be serious!
How could we ever issue a pro-boxer license
for someone like that?
Then why don't you contact
the commissioner directly?
Tell him Alex Gordon brought in a fighter
that has his full confidence.
What's all this Alex Gordon crap?
Pops, you need a nurse, not a license!
Gordon?
Alex Gordon?
If it isn't Dr. Gordon!
Mr. Gaston! How are you?
Commissioner, do you know this old man?
Show some respect!
Kid, Dr. Gordon is a big player
in the world of sports medicine!
He was also known
as a famous boxing manager.
Easy now, Mr. Gaston.
How about you license this fighter
I've brought instead?
Guy Hyuga?
Oh, no previous record as an amateur?
That's why I said we can't license him!
Someone like that can't go
straight to pro!
No, it's all right. Only because the request
comes from this doctor.
The doctor must've struck gold with the man he picked.
We'll grant this fighter a license
on my personal request.
Thank you, Mr. Gaston.
I will never forget your kindness.
Is it true, Alex? They licensed him?
Not just that, I've also found him
an opponent for his debut match.
Don Bailey, from Harlem.
A hard puncher they call Snake Bailey.
He's won all his matches by KOs.
I thought he would make a near perfect opponent for your debut match.
Don Bailey?
Don Bailey... Your fate is to become
the first man I knock out!
Dad...
They've arranged my debut match.
Do you remember, Dad?
When, as a kid, I lost a fight
and came home, you hugged me and cried.
"Guy, you can't lose! If you lose
in this town, you're as good as dead!"
Every time I remember your tears from back then, it gives me strength and courage.
Don't die, Dad!
Don't you dare die!
You'll be getting the best treatment that they have from now on! Just wait!
Guy, do your best.
What does this mean, Alex?
Guy has one more enemy here?
We're in the middle of Harlem.
And Don Bailey is the hero of Harlem.
So who's this other enemy?
Well, the audience!
Guy needs to beat
both him and the audience.
Alex, what is wrong with you?
Aren't you Guy's manager? Then why are you talking about it with such glee?
Yeah, I know. It's just something you should remember at all times.
It's a gamble, so to speak, that you need to take for Guy to become a champion.
Guy, how are you?
Bad.
I can't wait another moment
to get out of this room.
That's what I feel.
I know how it is. I was like that
during my debut match too, you know.
Too scared to step into the ring,
knees shaking, ready to bolt.
No! That's not what I feel.
What I feel is an urge to go straight to the locker room next door
and beat Don Bailey to a pulp!
Guy...
It's time to start! Get ready!
Guy, let's go. It's our turn.
Okay!
Who the fuck just threw that bottle?
Bailey!
Show him, Snake!
Bailey! Bailey! Bailey!
Run, Guy!
Before Bailey eats you for breakfast!
Alex, you were right.
Looks like winning the fight
is only half the battle.
If push comes to shove,
I'll sacrifice myself to save Guy.
In that case, you take Guy
and get out of here.
Alex...
Guy, win. I'll be cheering you on.
Look... I've washed my dirty body
so that I can go and cheer you on.
Lily! If you're going to that boxing match,
it's about time.
Got it. Give me just a moment.
That's dirty, you hack!
Fucking fraud!
That's it! Keep it up, Guy!
That punch is bound to make Bailey serious.
It's looking to be an interesting match.
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
No need to rush so much, boy.
I'll show you why they call me Snake.
He got back up after my straight right.
He's got a pretty sturdy head.
Fight!
Why is his stance so low now?
He's head-hitting!
Referee, stop them!
Break! Break!
You dirty cheat.
So this is why they call you Snake, huh?
Fight!
He's thumbing now!
Referee, deduct his points!
Referee, we'll kill you if you stop them!
Finish him off, Snake!
Do you get it now, boy?
This is my boxing!
Looks like he's got a background
in street fighting.
Well, that's just my specialty!
We'll do it your way!
They've already started.
Good luck, Guy!
You can't say that, Lily.
We're in Harlem.
Supporting that guy
is a surefire way to lose your life.
Why should I care?
He's risking his life to win.
So I'll risk my life to support him.
Fight, Guy! Fight!
I was raised in Harlem my whole life!
So was I. But even while constantly hearing
"Yellow Japs," my old man and I
always kept going on our aimless journey.
You reminded me...
In Harlem, they called me a "Sandbag Kid."
I was always craven back then.
I needed to learn from hands-on experiences,
so I got used to the thrashings.
Every time I got beaten to a pulp,
all I could think about was dying.
Yet I could never muster
the courage to kill myself.
Quit drinking?
Are you kidding me?!
Is that a way to talk to your parent?!
And when I got home, my own father,
drunk out of his mind,
would beat my mom and me without mercy.
You're all dragging me down!
So I made up my mind one day.
I'd kill my father and die myself.
Wh-What'd I do to you, Billy?!
Don't do it! Stop!
But I hesitated for a moment,
and Father used it to escape.
And then...
Father!
I couldn't believe what I'd done.
It was the same as if I had killed him myself.
That's when something
inside me burst open.
It was a rage directed inward,
at something invisible inside me.
I became a monster.
That's how I became a street fighter.
That was a rabbit punch!
Penalize him. He hit behind the ears!
That's Harlem-style boxing for you!
Go for it, Don!
Just you wait, Mary, Tom, Sammy.
When I win this, we'll all get full
on your favorite chicken!
Referee! What are you doing?!
That was a foul!
Guy! Put up your guard!
Too late!
One!
Two!
Three!
Dad, I'm hungry...
Bear with it, Guy.
Bear with it until we get to Chicago.
Okay.
I'll be strong.
Look at those stray dogs!
They're just like us.
Wh-What the hell?!
Poor thing...
That dumbass truck driver!
Could we eat it?
Huh? No, we can't! Imagine how
heartbroken this puppy would be!
But if we don't, we'll die ourselves.
That's still too much!
I'm not gonna eat it, Dad!
Guy, it's cooked.
Looks tasty. You should try it.
Who'd ever...
Who'd ever eat that?!
I see. Then the pup can have it.
Puppy! Stop!
That drumstick is your mother's meat!
Stupid idiot!
Didn't you hear me, goddammit?!
Let go! Let me go!
Dad...
Guy, don't blame the puppy.
You could while it still smelled of his mother,
but after I grilled it, it's just meat.
If it helps to save the puppy, I'm sure
his mother would've been happy too!
It's the only way!
Please forgive me...
I'm a damn worthless father
if I can't even put food on the table for you.
But if I die in this wasteland,
you must also survive by eating my flesh.
Dad...
Never give up!
Never surrender!
If you get knocked down,
get back up as many times as it takes!
Keep fighting for as long as you live!
Stand up, Guy!
Six!
Seven!
Oh, Guy...
He got up! Guy's getting up!
Fight!
Stubborn motherfucker!
I-I'll kill you!
Bailey, you have the eyes
of that puppy I picked up.
What's this crap you're spouting?
That's right. He was always
hungry and terrified.
Back then, I felt sorry for the little guy stuffing himself on his mother's meat,
so I tried to pat him on the head.
Hey, boy...
He probably thought I was after his food,
so he immediately turned hostile and bit me.
At that moment, I understood.
That puppy and I were brothers.
And you, Don Bailey... In the end,
you're also like that puppy and me.
You've also lived your life
hungry and burning with anger.
And now I have to bury one of my brothers...
What? Why are you crying?
Quit messing with me!
Die!
Jolting Blow!
It's a strike that blows your opponent
up in the sky, like a tornado.
That's it! That's the punch
I was waiting for!
Don!
Incredible... He really sent Bailey flying!
Bailey, get up!
Bailey!
One!
It's over.
Two!
Three!
Bailey?
Just you wait, Mary, Tom, Sammy...
We'll all get full on our way home...
Fight!
Guy! His lights are on,
but no one's home!
Rush him!
Mary... Tom... Sammy...
Don won't fall...
I can't...
lose.
Referee! Stop me!
Stop it!
Stop!
That's enough! Stop!
You were one of a kind.
I'll never forget you.
We'll avenge Bailey!
Now you've done it, Jap!
You think we'll let you leave here alive?!
It's not looking good, Alex. The other enemy you warned us about is here.
Lucky, Alex, Run!
I'm not going anywhere.
If I'm going to die anyhow,
I might as well do it in the ring, Guy!
This is dangerous, Lily.
If we stay here,
we might get killed for real!
Run on your own if you want!
I'm staying.
Bah! Whatever!
Guy, I'll fight alongside you.
If you die, I'll die too.
I'll fucking kill him first!
Yeah! Get 'em!
Enough! There's a child in the ring!
I'll kill anyone who comes up!
Listen, everyone!
I have 3 dollars and 50 cents here!
The entire wealth of our family!
I'll bet all this money
on Don Bailey's next match!
I'm sure brother will win his next match!
She's right. We've also made bank
on Bailey over the years.
Even if he loses, he's our hero!
Okay, I'll bet mine too!
Me too!
I'll wager on Bailey's next match!
Mr. Guy.
What?
Brother used some dirty punches,
but please don't despise him.
Sure. Don Bailey was a true professional.
I can't despise him.
Thank you, Guy.
Brother won't have to shed blood
in the ring anymore, right?
She knows already.
My punch shattered both Don Bailey's jaw
and his boxing dreams.
Then, won't you please...
become a heavyweight world champion, on Don's behalf too?
That's what brother lived for.
Sure, I promise.
I'll become the champion
in your brother's stead.
Thank you.
If you do that, he'll be able to say
that he was the first man
to be beaten by the champion.
Guy's debut match is over.
But from now on, even more formidable enemies than Don Bailey
will stand in his way
to becoming a champion.
Don't let your guard down, Guy.
It only starts now!
At that time, I felt
like my dad was talking to me.
"Fight, Guy! Fight on for as long as you live!"
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
And three days later,
Guy Hyuga's debut
opponent, Don Bailey,
retired...
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing
Paul Geromini
Typesetting
Collectr
QC
VigorousJammer
Collectr
Encoding
WOWmd