Shogakukan
Kosaku, move sideways,
goddammit! Run!
I feel sick!
I'm gonna barf now.
What?! You're that nauseous?
Yeah. Something like that.
My guts feels really heavy.
You didn't p-pig out after
your weigh-in, did you?
No, of course not.
Actually, he did wander off alone after his weigh-in.
I just took a walk.
You sure?! You didn't grab
a bite somewhere?
I did not!
Lord, I pledge my service to you
for the rest of my earthly days.
Lord, please grant me your strength.
Grant me the strength to save
the lost lambs of your flock.
My stomach is an empty pit.
Why am I feeling so dizzy?
My!
What's the matter with you?
Try to hold on, please!
Hi!
SANTA MARIA KINDERGARTEN
I see.
Despite all this abundance,
we still have young men like you,
in the prime of youth,
with stomachs so empty
they collapse on the street.
Truly unbelievable things
transpire in this world of ours.
Please, don't rush and eat slowly.
Lord, I'm grateful.
You gave me the chance to save this lost sheep, collapsed on the street.
Oh, no! Sister Angela!
Y-You gave him something to eat?
Sister, though you can't know it yet
'cause you're new to this parish...
We can't do that! We mustn't provide this child with food.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Kosaku Hatanaka   19 years old
Featherweight     six-rounder
Pro boxer . . . . . more or less
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
Sister Angela   21 years old
A nun in the service of God
Recently assigned to this parish
However . . . . . still a novice
One-Pound Gospel
Orphan Fansubs presents
Kosaku! Kosaku!
Wanting to know freedom
I'm hurrying on my journey
Foul! Foul!
Kosaku!
Even at times like this,
your heart stays with me
Come on! Get up, Hatanaka!
I gave him a foul.
Yeah, I know.
I've got to be strong!
When I'm tired of walking
I'm gonna do it!
I entrust myself to my dreams
I still can't find that special place
Kosaku!
Hatanaka! Move away!
Keep moving!
The more you grow up
Dammit!
The lonelier you are
Kosaku!
That happens to all of us, unknowingly
Every moment, every day
Don't you cry no more
You're alone with your loneliness
Gramps, he's lost it!
So don't let it burden you that much
That moron!
Every moment, communicated tenderness
When we're together, our hearts feel so fine
So keep hugging me all night long
MUKODA BOXING GYM
Recruiting Trainees
No, it certainly wasn't your fault!
That idiot's to blame for everything.
Right? Right, Ishida? Ain't I right?
No, it's my fault.
Right before an important match,
I made the mistake
of treating him to a meal.
"Not knowing" is no excuse.
He struggled so hard to lose weight,
and I ruined his form for the match.
I am so guilty!
Don't worry about it.
It wasn't your fault. Absolutely!
It's all that guy.
He's a repeat offender!
An awful, wicked guy. It's unforgivable!
Such a guy deserves a trip straight to hell!
Even if you hadn't fed him,
he'd've found some street
vendor on his own.
But you know, I used to think of him as my golden boy.
He's a natural at boxing.
He charmed me back when
he was still in high school.
I convinced him to quit school
and dragged him to my gym.
Yes. Perhaps... I pinned the first and last dream of my life on him.
Back then, he had some incredible luck.
When he was only 17,
he passed the demanding B-Class pro test on the first try.
He debuted as a flyweight.
He KO'd his opponent in the first round with a lucky punch.
Those were our salad days.
SASHASITA DON SHOPPING STREET
He was the first pro boxer
my gym ever produced.
SASHASITA DON SHOPPING STREET
I was rightly elated by our success.
But then...
Then, he failed his weigh-in
for the next match!
Just like yesterday's match,
he threw up in the ring and lost by a KO.
After that, junior bantamweight, bantamweight, junior featherweight...
He went up the weight classes.
We've never had a single proper fight since then, Sister Angela!
Not one?
Not one!
Howdy!
H-Hey! You came too?
I should be ashamed.
Did you see my fight yesterday?
Yeah... I guess I wasn't in the best shape.
But I'll do better next time.
I've learned from my mistakes.
Next time?!
You moron!
You think anyone will allow
you to fight again?!
Professional boxers don't puke in the middle of the match!
What boxer in the world will wanna take you on now?
I could search the whole country
and not find a match!
Do you finally get it, Kosaku?!
You'll never enter the ring again!
Until yesterday,
I had several opponents lined up
over the next twelve months.
Every single one of them called to cancel the whole thing!
It's only natural.
I fought such an embarrassing match.
I really shamed my coach.
But... If only one more...
If only one more chance came around...
Everything...
Everything starts with an effort.
If you keep trying your hardest,
the Lord will be merciful to you
and will lend you a helping hand.
May the Lord's blessing be upon you.
S-Sister...
Make an effort, Kosaku.
I'll be praying for your success every day.
Now then, keep your chin up.
Tyson! Tyson! Tyson!
Angela... Angela... Angela... Angela!
Good! That's the spirit!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Are you okay?
Did I hurt you?!
I'm not ranked yet,
but I'm kinda a pro boxer!
U-Um, should I get a doctor?
U-Um?
H-Hey!
Are you okay?!
Pretty sure I hit him right in...
Tyson! Tyson! Tyson!
So, Kosaku, if you had another chance, what would you do with it?
I'd do my very best, obviously!
I won't make Coach cry ever again.
I'll lose weight.
If I develop good habits and stick to 'em,
I won't pig out right before a match
and ruin my condition.
Um... uh...
What's wrong? You done already? There's still some left.
Yes. I'm on a diet.
Great!
Everything starts with an effort.
If you keep trying, the Lord will extend a merciful helping hand to you.
Who told you that?
I'm not telling.
C-Coach!
We've scoured every hash house
we could think of, and here you are!
Kosaku! You've got a match!
I've arranged your next match!
Someone actually applied for it, in fact!
You'll enter the ring once more!
No eating.
Hey, Amakusa, I applied to that guy,
just like you asked.
KANITANI BOXING GYM
But it's Hatanaka Kosaku!
The guy who threw up in the ring.
KANITANI BOXING GYM
Are you sure?
Even if you're a former Olympic medalist,
this is your first match since turning pro.
Really. What's so interesting about beating that loser?
No reason.
I just thought it was a waste,
leaving him hanging like that.
A waste, huh?
A waste!
By some chance,
did you know him before?
No. Never had the pleasure. Ever.
By the way, Amakusa, that black eye!
Where'd you pick up
a shiner on your eye?
I told you! I fell down!
For God's sake, Coach! Don't make me say it a thousand times!
Think I'd let a man who hit me retire and get away with it?
I'll drag him into the ring
and slam him into hell myself!
Wh-Wh...
Come on! At least try
to show some speed!
Milady, may I join you?
That's how kindergartners do it!
You said you'd do your best, didn't you?
I am doing my best! It's just...
Just what?
Oh?
Don't give me "Oh."
I asked you a question!
Listen, Kosaku. I'll be clear just this once.
Screw up this match
like you usually do,
and I swear by the gods,
your boxing career will be truly over!
I know that!
So... does it hurt yet?!
It hurts!
That's because you're carrying so much extra weight!
Normally, we oughta be able to slim you down to junior bantamweight!
But I wanna be in the middle!
What was that?
Fight!
What's wrong, Kosaku?
I heard God's voice just now.
What the hell?
From that bridge...
Idiot! Don't daydream
while you're running!
Lord... I'm so hungry.
Coach, take a quick look at this.
We're still way above the limit,
but he is losing weight, slowly.
Good, good.
He's finally serious this time!
Watch out!
Kosaku! That's dangerous!
Don't go so hard on me!
Hey, Tabuchi, meet me later.
We need to talk.
Great, Kosaku! That's the spirit!
MUKODA BOXING GYM
Recruiting Trainees
Hey, Tabuchi, over here!
5... 500 yen?
MOUNTAIN TRANSPORT
Please!
I could live with the food restrictions,
but they also cut off my money.
Add to that the "dawn-to-dusk" training schedule.
I don't even have time to do laundry.
So it's for underwear.
I thought I'd buy some.
500 yen. I'll pay you back next month.
That's a no.
Why not?
You'll just go stuff yourself again.
L-Listen, you! I've bet everything on this next fight!
Do you think I'd ruin it by pigging out?!
I sure do. You have
too many prior offenses.
If you need underpants,
I'll lend you some.
How do you know if they're my size?
I get it, I get it! All right!
But I'm not gonna pull my punches during sparring anymore!
K-Kosaku!
Jeez! How could he be so judgmental?
I really wanted to buy underwear!
And what's this "prior offenses"?
Besides, how much food could
you buy with only ¥500?
Even a hamburger dinner plate is at least ¥650 these days.
Banner: Yakitori
Chicken kabobs are ¥100 each!
I could only get five sticks!
Hold on a second.
If I could have five sticks...
SANTA MARIA KINDERGARTEN
See you tomorrow. Bye-bye.
Ah, that won't do, Akira!
You have to wipe your face clean.
Now, Sister, should we take a break?
I brought strawberry sweet buns.
Okay.
Oh, Hatanaka?
You want to confess?
Yes. I have to talk to someone about this,
or it'll keep tormenting me.
Very well. Please trust in God's mercy
and confess your sins.
Well...
What is it?
How are you doing?
Give your confession!
Okay, okay.
I ate some chicken...
Speak up, I can't hear you!
I ate five chicken kabobs!
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit...
may your sins be forgiven. Amen.
Kosaku?
Yeah?
I'm doing fine.
I'm doing fine too!
I'm working really hard!
Want to see a movie on Sunday?!
I'll buy the tickets, somehow!
Kosaku! What's wrong with you?
That's it, Kosaku! Good job!
You can do it if you try, even you!
You may be a spineless,
inveterate glutton,
but you pack a punch,
and you always will!
Kosaku, you promised
to pull your punches!
Listen, Tabuchi.
Meet me in the parking lot.
What? Again?
I've suddenly seen a sweet dream
The future is an unfinished project
But my slight fever is still there
Faster! Let's see some speed!
Premonitions burn through my heart
Come on! Don't just stand there!
Take a peek into the recesses of your heart
And try to catch my timid love, whoa whoa
Love me like fire
Take me far away
I don't have to go back
Love me like fire
Take me far away
Just now, call my luck for me
SPIRIT
GUTS
Wasted memory, filled with sadness
SPIRIT
GUTS
But something must happen soon
Coach, are you sleeping already?
No, I'm awake. Barely.
Thing is, there's something I have to show you.
He seems serious about his training,
with a "you can do it if you try" attitude.
Yet at the same time, instead of losing weight, he's gaining it steadily.
Impossible!
It's the truth.
He's gone back to his old habit
of gobbling street food.
That can't be!
This time, I haven't
given him even ten yen,
so he can't buy anything from anyone!
Well, I got bad news for you.
Hey, come on in!
Evening.
It felt odd that Tabuchi looked so panicked in the gym,
so I asked him directly.
Hey! Let Coach see the whole caboodle.
Okay.
What's this? He does it
damn near daily, doesn't he?
Yes. It was only ¥500 at first.
It gradually went up to ¥1000 and ¥1500.
He said he'd pay me back as soon
as he got his fight money.
MUKODA BOXING GYM
Coach! Ishida!
How's it going?
Perfectly fine!
Kosaku.
Yes?
I hate to interrupt practice,
but get on the scale real quick
so I can check for myself.
Come on, hurry it up.
We don't have all day. I'm a busy man.
Oh? Perhaps I gained a little?
I've had enough.
Coach, where are you going?
Some place where I don't
have to look at you.
Um. Excuse me, but... Um.
Aren't you Coach Mukoda?
That moron.
He's such a moron.
Did something happen?
Sister!
Hatanaka, do you have
something to confess?
Coach was crying.
Don't you have something to confess,
besides five chicken kabobs?
I see. You only choose
to confess or not
based on your own convenience, huh?
No, I...
Then what was your intention,
when you came to seek
absolution the other day?
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you, Sister.
I love you!
It was because I love you!
This isn't the time to be talking...
Sh-Should I slap the left cheek too?!
You... You...
spineless glutton!
Hey, hey. As a former Olympic gold medalist,
what do you have to say after turning pro?
Well, I don't know what to say.
I hope fighting a match that doesn't embarrass me as a medalist will be enough.
What do you think of your opponent, Hatanaka?
Well, what should I think?
I don't know much about him.
Oh, I've heard a nasty rumor
about Hatanaka.
He's having trouble
making the weight limit.
He could end up forfeiting
the match to you.
By the way, sir. That's quite a shiner.
It won't go away easily, will it?
Yes. It's surprisingly stubborn.
I guess that's it.
Kosaku is only 19.
He can start over at something new, right?
IMADASO
HATANAKA
Yes?
It's me, open up!
C-Coach!
Yes, coming!
What is it, Coach?
Let's take a walk.
Barbecue Taihoraku
Retire? Me?
Hey, that one is done.
Yeah.
Great stuff!
See? If you retire,
you can eat stuff like that
or whatever you like every day.
But I'm already doing that right now.
Exactly!
That's exactly why you don't qualify to call yourself a pro.
I wonder...
Look at you, wolfing it down so calmly!
Do you really even wanna be a boxer?!
Oh? If it isn't our Mr. Boxer!
Hey, Angela! Sister!
Forget it. She's plastered.
Yes? Who is?
Uh, no, you are!
Who...
It seemed unusual when she said she wanted to eat barbecue.
But really, I guess
she just wanted to drink.
I wonder if something happened.
Beats me.
Come on in!
Well, you know, that Amakusa,
the former Olympic gold medalist.
He's turning pro.
And his debut opponent
is Hatanaka Kosaku.
Hatanaka Kosaku?
Never heard of him.
No wonder. That guy fails the weigh-in every time!
So it's that messy loser?
Amakusa's aiming for a spectacular first-round KO debut.
In that case, smashing a wimp like Hatanaka
into the gutter works well for him!
C-Coach!
Violence never solves anything!
Aren't you ticked off yourself?!
I don't care what they say!
Well, maybe you should care!
Anything but violence!
Please rest assured.
Hatanaka is going to win.
He's probably fighting a tough battle
against his appetite even as we speak.
Now, let us pray for Hatanaka.
Listen, Sister...
Let us pray!
Sister!
That won't do!
Violence never works!
What are you doing here?
Well, I...
Were you eating again?
You spineless...
Only one week left until the fight.
Well, about your trip
to the barbecue joint...
He's become strangely serious since then.
He's now losing weight properly
and training exactly
according to the schedule.
That may be,
but he's been weak-willed
as long as I've known him.
Still, if this continues,
he might pull something off.
I wonder if he can keep it up.
There's a whole week left.
The real show starts now.
Banner: Musashino Dumplings
But he's come so far already.
I gotta believe in him again.
Checkmate!
Ishida!
No do-overs!
Right, no do-overs!
We'll lock him in the gym
starting tonight!
We'll wring him out totally!
That's what it's come to?
One, two!
I-I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Are you okay?
Did I hurt you?
I'm not ranked yet,
but I'm kinda a pro boxer!
Should I get you a doctor...
Aren't you the guy
from the other day?!
Hey, wait!
I'm back!
Oh, Kosaku, you're just in time!
MUKODA BOXING GYM
Recruiting Trainees
Before afternoon practice,
go home and return with your things.
MUKODA BOXING GYM
We're locking you up! Special regimen!
I won't take my eyes off you even for a second!
MUKODA BOXING GYM
That bastard! I won't let you off with just a knockout.
I'll make you puke your guts out!
Come on, come on!
Put your back into it!
Listen, you gotta lose
four pounds in five days!
Wring it out! Wring out the sweat!
Well, from now on, this is your daily calorie intake, the bare minimum.
Take your time and enjoy it.
Thank you.
1235 sheep.
1236 sheep.
1200...
Ah, this is no good.
I'm so hungry I can't sleep.
1237 sheep.
1238 sheep.
1239 sheep.
1240...
You know, I've been having
strange dreams lately.
I keep dreaming about sheep.
Hey, these are ringside seats!
Tomorrow, at last.
EXCITING                                 GLOVES
What happened to our Mr. Boxer since then?
That's right, we haven't seen him lately.
Ah! Ask and you shall receive!
My! Seems like our Mr. Boxer
is doing his best!
He didn't even glance at us.
But say, isn't that a little cold?
He ran past without saying hello to his girlfriend.
I'm not anyone's girlfriend!
I've devoted my life to serving God!
You're still a novice, right?
Well, maybe I am, but still...
But Sister, you're dating him, aren't you?
It's not like that!
There he is again!
Hello, Sister. Well, you see...
Hey! Why are you slacking off here?
Don't stop running!
See you!
Jeez! I can't take my eyes off you for a second!
"See you," just like that!
So you are dating, after all.
We are not!
I'm so hungry.
I'm so thirsty.
Don't drink! Bear with it until the weigh-in tomorrow.
Gulp down a lot of water,
and your weight will go up in no time!
Look closely, everyone, and remember!
If you don't observe your daily diet,
you'll end up like this right before the match!
That said, you worked hard this time, Hatanaka. Well done!
Hey! Someone carry him to Coach's room and let him sleep.
Okay!
Good evening.
Yeah?
Well, hello there!
Hey! Someone go upstairs
and wake Kosaku.
Now, come in, come in.
Can I get you some tea?
Well, actually, I didn't come here for any particular reason. So if he's resting...
No, no, this is the perfect time.
He needs to practice anyhow.
Don't you worry.
Coach, he's not there!
He escaped to the outside.
Crap!
We gotta find him.
Everyone, stop practicing!
Comb through every
hash house in the area!
When you find him, make him throw up!
He mustn't digest anything!
Yes, sir!
Forget it, Ishida.
I've had enough. Don't go
after him. There's no need.
He knows better than anyone that if he eats now, it's all over.
Even so...
Even so, if he decides to eat,
then so be it.
If he decides to do it
after coming this far,
I'm more than willing
to give up on him.
I still believe in Hatanaka.
Everyone, please believe in him too.
I believe.
Good night, everyone.
And he calls himself my superior!
Hey, mister, how many?
I've got the next ones fried and ready.
Lord! Please!
Deliver your lost lamb
from the Devil's temptation.
Hatanaka! Hold out just for tonight!
What's wrong? Not buying?
Banner: Chinese Food
1275 kabobs.
1276 kabobs.
1277 kabobs.
Hey! Mister, mister!
Stop by our place! Hey!
You'll like it here!
Banner: Gourmet Sweet Buns
1280...
Hey! Wel-
Chinese Cuisine
Thanks for waiting. Here.
Banner: Taiyaki
Lord!
IMADASO
HATANAKA
Sister!
You... You are so...
You betrayed your coach!
You betrayed me!
Is this... Is this where
you want it all to end?
Thank you.
I nearly lost that battle against myself.
Please make a vow.
Promise that you won't
repeat this mistake.
The Lord, your gym colleagues...
They haven't given up on you yet.
And you?
My heart stands with the Lord.
Sister!
Thank you so much!
Hatanaka?
Lord, please don't throw in the towel.
Please watch over this
lost lamb until the end.
Fighter Hatanaka,
126 pounds.
You pass the weigh-in.
All right! You did it, Kosaku!
On the first try! It's God's miracle!
I-Incredible, all right!
Congratulations on passing the weigh-in.
Nice to meet you. I'm Amakusa Jiro.
Likewise, nice to meet you!
Well, see you in the ring tonight.
Haven't we met somewhere before?
Never!
And where'd you get that shiner?
Th-That's none of your business!
Lord, please bless this meager repast.
May your blood and flesh grant
this young man the strength to endure his trials.
Amen.
What's wrong, Kosaku?
You can finally eat now.
You passed the weigh-in.
What is the matter, Hatanaka?
Coach has given you permission.
This much won't help my stamina in the match.
Huh? What is it? Don't mumble.
You can say clearly
what's eating you!
Not enough.
Oh, really, really?
All right! Then eat this!
A jumbo triple-decker hamburger!
Coach! Are you sure it's okay to give him a meal like that?
And immediately before the match!
Even I can see it's wrong!
God may forgive him
for his good deeds,
but his stomach won't forgive him.
It's a result of losing weight.
No matter what he eats,
he'll vomit it back on the spot.
Coach? Can I have a second?
Ishida, take him to the bathroom
and make him throw up!
Okay!
Completely hopeless.
Not a piece...
What a cast-iron stomach
that guy has.
You could say it's custom-made.
Nothing short of a massive body blow
will get that burger out.
Oh no!
Go, Kosaku!
You got this, Mr. Boxer!
Good luck!
He punched me in the eye,
not once, but twice!
Now I'll pay him back, with interest!
I'll pay him back tenfold!
Good, Kosaku! That's the way!
You bastard!
One!
Two!
All right! All right!
Three!
This is great!
Four!
Five!
Amakusa! Get up!
Six!
Stay down!
Seven!
Eight!
Fight!
You little punk! Don't get cocky!
Do it!
Finish him off, Kosaku!
What's wrong with you, Amakusa?
It's not like you to struggle
against a guy like him.
Coach, what's Hatanaka's record?
Huh? Two wins, five losses, I think.
Wins and losses alike, always with a KO.
I don't get it! He's good!
Not the kind who'd go astray after just two wins!
His team sure looks taken aback!
They expected this to be easy.
They didn't lie. When Kosaku's great,
he really is great!
Yeah. If only they could cure his abnormal appetite.
One way or another,
the way it's going now,
it may be worth trying to push it further.
What's wrong?
No, I'm fine.
Maybe I'll use this round
to get a better look?
Huh? His legs are giving out.
What now, out of stamina already?
If so, here's a quick spurt from me!
Just as I promised, I'll make you puke your guts out right here, in this ring!
Oh no!
Hatanaka!
Kosaku, don't puke!
Hold it back! Hold it!
Break!
Hey, what's this?
What the hell's with him?
Disgusting! Disgusting!
He should quit already!
Is this a default?
Well, Kosaku?
Will you quit?
Will you quit boxing like that?!
The towel.
Please throw in the towel,
Coach Mukoda.
Sister!
The Lord will forgive you.
No one is going to blame you.
So please...
Your Bible, Sister.
Please swear with me:
"I will never, ever throw in the towel."
Kosaku.
Hey! Isn't it over yet?!
Get him out!
You made me happy, Hatanaka.
If you're not giving up on this fight,
I'll return the courtesy
and won't hold back!
It's over!
Finish!
This is not good...
Not good...
Hatanaka Kosaku!
Kosaku!
You did it! Now, barf as much as you want!
There's nothing left.
Oh, really?
Well, Sister?
Yes?
I guess I owe it all to God.
Somehow...
I don't think so.
jiyuu o shiritakute
Wanting to know freedom
tabiji o isoideru
I'm hurrying on my journey
sonna toki mo kokoro wa itsumo Stay with me
Even at times like this,
your heart stays with me
aruki tsukareta toki
When I'm tired of walking
yume o azukerareru
I entrust myself to my dreams
basho sae mada mitsukerarenai mama ja
I still can't find that special place
otona ni naru hodo
The more you grow up
sabishi sa no kazu wa
The lonelier you are
shirazu ni fueteyuku mono dakara
That happens to all of us, unknowingly
Every moment, every day
Don't you cry no more
kanashimi wa hitori kiri de
You're alone with your loneliness
sou seowanaide
So don't let it burden you that much
Every moment, communicated tenderness
futarinara kokoro wa Feel so fine
When we're together, our hearts feel so fine
dakishimete All night long
So keep hugging me all night long
ikutsu mo no kodoku o
No matter how many times
kamishime kasanete mo
I go through this loneliness
rikou ni nado kesshite narenai Stand by you
I never learn, that's why I stand by you
sabitsuita yume kara
If I let go of my rusty dreams
te o hanashite shimaeba
Let them wander freely
itami sae mou warai tobaseru
Even this pain can be laughed away
dare demo hitori ja
All of us feel sad
sabishi sukirukara
When we're alone
jibun no yasashi sa o migakeru no deshou
Maybe you can learn to be kinder
Every moment, every day
Don't you cry no more
kanashimi wa hitori kiri de
You're alone with your loneliness
sou seowanaide
So don't let it burden you that much
Every moment, communicated tenderness
futarinara kokoro wa Feel so fine
When we're together, our hearts feel so fine
dakishimete All night long
So keep hugging me all night long
otona ni naru hodo
The more you grow up
sabishi sa no kazu wa
The lonelier you are
shirazu ni fueteyuku mono dakara
That happens to all of us, unknowingly
Every moment, every day
Don't you cry no more
kanashimi wa hitori kiri de
You're alone with your loneliness
sou seowanaide
So don't let it burden you that much
The End
Every moment, communicated tenderness
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
VIZ via Melonsubs
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis, Rezo,
Topper3000
anonymous