...Be on your guard!
Love is a gypsy child.
It has never, never known a law.
If you don't love me, then I love you.
If I love you, be on your guard!
My name is Chocchan.
I was born in Takikawa, Hokkaido.
Be on your guard!
If you don't love me, if you don't love me, then I love you!
While attending the Tokyo Conservatory,
I sometimes take chorus gigs like this one.
Be on your guard!
But if I love you, if I love you, be on your guard!
Right now,
I'm facing the biggest turning point of my life.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Chocchan's Story
The bird you hoped to catch
Orphan Fansubs presents
Chocchan's Story
Beat its wings and flew away.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Chocchan's Story
Love is far, you can wait for it.
You no longer await it, there it is!
All around you, swift, swift,
It comes, it goes, then it returns.
You think to hold it fast, it dodges you.
You think to dodge it, it holds you!
All around you, swift, swift,
Love!
It comes, it goes, then it returns.
You think to hold it fast, it dodges you.
Love!
You think to dodge it, it holds you!
Love is a gypsy child.
It has never, never known a law.
If you don't love me, I love you.
If I love you, be on your guard!
Be on your guard!
If you don't love me, if you don't love me, then I love you!
But if I love you, if I love you, be on your guard!
An orchestra dropout?!
What on Earth are you thinking?
That's why I want to marry him...
You fool!
Come on, dear. Chocchan's finally come home, after so long.
Oh, and look, she brought your favorite, sweet bean jelly.
This is all your fault.
Going to music school
behind her father's back,
and now talking about marrying some no-name orchestra dropout.
It's because her mother raised her wrong!
It's not Mom's fault.
And he's not a nobody, either.
His name is Kuroyanagi Moritsuna!
You keep calling him a dropout,
but his violin playing is amazing!
Everyone says he's a genius!
Nonsense.
Nonsense?
Genius or not,
a man shouldn't spend
his whole life on music!
You'll only end up suffering
if you marry someone like that.
You should marry someone
respectable, like a doctor.
You're kidding me.
What?
If you think you can control your children's entire lives, you're dead wrong!
Wh-What did you say?!
My life is mine!
I won't live it the way you want me to!
Dear!
Get out! I can't consider someone like you my daughter anymore!
Fine! I don't consider you my father either!
Chocchan...
So there was no wedding ceremony.
But my life as a newlywed
with Moritsuna had begun.
H-Hey! I said don't flow away.
H-Hey! I said don't spill!
Ouch!
So how is it today? You like it?
It's good for when you have indigestion.
Did I overcook it today?
Hello! The greengrocer's here!
Coming!
Be there in a moment!
Overcooked miso soup isn't so bad
every now and then.
Here you go, daikon and spinach.
Thanks! No money today,
so just put it on our tab.
But despite the kind of wife I was,
I became a mother the very next year.
Tetsuko, Daddy's here.
How truly wonderful children are.
How deeply lovable they are.
They're my family now.
I've got to hang in there.
After all, I'm a mom now!
Sun is setting, light is dimming, it's end of day
By the time Meiji was born,
Moritsuna had become the concertmaster of the New Symphony Orchestra.
But a musician's income is never steady.
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
LENDING & BUYING
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
THIS WAY
TERADA
PAWNSHOP
Hello.
Welcome.
Ah, that again?
Is your husband okay
with you pawning this?
He won't need it until the concert,
so just hold onto it till then.
All right. Fifteen yen, like always.
What's your name, little lady?
Totto-chan!
Oh, Totto-chan, huh?
What do you do for a living?
Oh, that's a rather tough question.
H-He's the laundry man.
See, we brought Daddy's clothes, didn't we?
So laundries pay you money?
Okay, then I'll also bring lots of clothes
and buy myself caramels!
Sorry, no can do.
Kids aren't allowed.
That's right, not until you're tall enough
to reach this counter, okay?
Let's stop by the candy shop on the way home.
I'll buy you some caramels myself.
Yay! Caramels! Caramels!
At last, the day was drawing near
for Tetsuko to start elementary school.
Hold on a second!
Yes, that's it, that's the spirit.
Hey, this kid's got talent. He might turn into a big-shot musician someday.
Welcome back.
Thanks! But I'm heading right out again!
Where are you going?
To the bathroom!
Lately, she won't even
take off her backpack.
She must really be excited about school.
But it turns out school was the first real hurdle I faced as a mother.
We simply don't know
what to do with Tetsuko anymore.
What do you mean?
She just can't sit still.
For example...
Ueno-san.
Here!
Ogawa-san.
Kaneko-san.
Here!
Kuroyanagi-san!
Ah!
"Ah" isn't an answer.
Your proper response is...
Ah!
I-It's gonna fall! It's falling!
What's the matter?
Whew, that was close.
They almost fell out just now!
Don't worry. They don't fall out that easily.
Now take your seat.
But why?
Why? Well, birds can fly, right?
So just sit down.
Really? Even the little tiny ones?!
Yes, that's right!
Anyway, sit down already!
But I wanna watch!
And then during class as well...
Whoa! It's got this lid that opens! So cool!
That girl again.
Kuroyanagi-san! We're in
the middle of class. Be quiet!
Kuroyanagi-san,
stop that banging right now!
And then she even did that...
One, two, three, four...
Kuroyanagi-san, sit down!
Street band!
Come over and play for us here!
Everyone! Return to your seats!
Sit down at once!
After me! One, two, three, four...
Come on!
I can't take this anymore!
So... that's what I've been dealing with.
And what happened after that?
After wandering all around the schoolyard,
they marched right into the school building
and turned the whole place upside down!
I'm so glad.
What exactly do you mean,
"You're glad," ma'am?
Ah, n-no... I mean, the children must've been delighted, so...
There's nothing good about it!
I'm terribly sorry.
In any case, she's a nuisance
to the other children as well.
I'm going to have to ask you
to discipline Tetsuko more strictly.
Yes, but...
But?
I do agree it's important to follow the rules,
but I also wonder... Is it really right
to stifle a child's curiosity so tightly?
Ma'am!
Welcome home.
I'm back.
This can't go on.
There must be a school somewhere
that's right for Tetsuko.
The school I found with the right mindset was Tomoe Gakuen.
Mama, is this really a school?
That's right. Do you like it?
Yeah!
Tomoe Gakuen was a one-of-a-kind school that valued each student's individuality.
Each child received assignments matched
to their level and then studied at their own pace.
Here!
Let's see. Did you fix the mistakes?
The teacher would patiently explain everything they didn't understand until it made sense.
Amazing, full marks!
Banzai!
And once they finished studying,
they were free to go play outside anytime.
Teacher! How does it look?
Is this good enough?
Yes, excellently done.
There were also some rather unusual classes.
After she started going to Tomoe Gakuen,
Tetsuko became a whole new child,
always in motion.
Every child has something
truly special about them.
It's the role of teachers and parents
to discover that spark. However...
However?
You mustn't think of it
as educating the child.
We also have much to learn from children.
Maybe they're the ones
actually raising us.
Look! The sunset's so red!
It's huge!
You're right! So pretty!
Why is it so red?
Soon after, our second son, Noriaki, was born,
making our home even livelier.
The concert's been canceled?
Yeah. Apparently, playing foreign music is "unpatriotic."
Really?
But you've worked so hard
to prepare for it.
It's a terrible world we're living in now.
It's hot...
That's true.
Wanna take a dip?
Yeah!
Papa! The water's a bit cold!
No whining! Come on. Start swimming!
I don't wanna!
What are you doing, Mama?
Wow! You caught five of them!
Catching fish is second nature to me.
Back in Takikawa, Hokkaido,
we had lots of ponds and streams.
I wanna go there too.
Take me there sometime, Mama.
Sure. Someday.
Help!
Oh no! Papa's...
I... can't swim!
Papa!
Mei-chan, go get someone, quickly!
Okay!
Papa?
Ha! Fooled you!
You think I'd really drown
in a river this shallow?
Did you forget I used to be
on the swim team?
Ugh! I hate you!
I was really worried, you know!
Hey! Get back here!
Wait, Papa!
Wait, I said!
It's like there aren't any real
grown-ups in this household.
Seems that way...
It's so quiet.
It really is.
That's a pretty tune.
What's it called?
It's an improvisation.
Impro-what?
It's our own song.
Our family's song.
I believed this happiness would last forever.
But sadly, Japan was already marching
steadily on the path of war.
Father, you were strong
Bearing the scorching heat that burns-
All they play are military songs.
Mama, a letter came for you.
Thanks.
Oh, it's from my mother.
Please bring the children home for summer break.
We want to meet them at least once.
Don't worry about your father.
These days, even he is looking forward
to seeing his grandkids.
Just the thought of facing that man again
made my heart sink.
But even so, I decided to go,
because I wanted to show my children
the beauty of my hometown.
Oh my!
I'm so glad you came.
We're home.
It's been a long time.
Come on now. Say hello
to your grandpa and grandma.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Tetsuko.
I'm Meiji.
Oh, what a fine greeting.
Now, hurry on inside!
Okay!
Come on, in you go.
You come too, Chocchan.
What's wrong?
I don't think I've ever seen
Father smile before.
Don't be silly.
Come on, hurry up now.
From morning till night,
Father was with the children nonstop.
I don't remember him
ever carrying me in his arms.
Back in the Meiji Era, men thought picking up kids
would make them look weak.
But now that he's older,
it feels like he's finally able to express
his feelings a little more honestly.
Look, Grandpa. I gathered this much!
Oh, that's very pretty.
Summer break flew by in the blink of an eye.
Father, thank you for everything.
It's time for us to head back.
Um...
Don't go!
But...
Tetsuko's school is starting soon.
So what if an elementary schooler
misses a day or two?
Don't go!
We are going!
He hasn't changed a bit.
Dear, Chocchan and the kids already left.
I do hope they'll
come again next year.
Here's your tea.
And then, the war began,
on December 8, 1941.
We interrupt this program with a special bulletin. A special bulletin.
The Combined Army Headquarters have just issued a statement at 6:00 AM on December 8.
This morning, Imperial forces engaged with the US and the UK in the western Pacific.
So it's finally begun.
Why do we have to go to war?
This morning, Imperial forces engaged with the US and the UK in the western Pacific.
What'll happen to us now?
Nothing's going to happen.
Everything's the same as before.
So I can still go to school, right, Papa?
Of course you can.
Just...
stop calling us "Papa" and "Mama."
Those are enemy words now.
Then what should we call you?
Let's see now...
Maybe "Father" and "Mother," I suppose?
"Father, Mother?"
No way! That makes it sound
like you're different people!
Just bear with it a little.
The war'll probably be over soon.
But two years passed,
and not only did the war not end,
it grew more intense and bloody.
Little by little, food, clothes,
and just about everything else
was vanishing from our lives.
Everything was rationed now.
Here you go, enough for five people.
That's it?
You only need enough
to hold out until Japan wins!
Here, for four people.
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
Victory
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
Victory
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
Victory
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
the Enemy
Victory
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
Victory
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
Victory
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
Victory
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Victory
Luxury Is
the Enemy
No Grumbling until
Luxury Is
Even eating rice is a luxury now?
However, that was still the better part of it.
Before long, even rice was completely gone.
Wow! It's moving!
Banzai!
I made it!
I built this boat all by myself!
I see. Impressive, Meiji!
Mom, I'm hungry!
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry!
Okay, okay.
Here's your snack.
I'm sorry. The rations
are dwindling by the day.
We know.
Yeah.
Bear with it, okay?
I heard if you play at a military concert,
you can get all the food you want.
Those places must surely
have plenty, huh?
While we're struggling
to get even a spoonful of sugar.
I don't want to play my violin
for the military.
I understand.
In 1944, our second daughter, Yuri, was born.
Yamada Koichi-kun, banzai!
Banzai! Banzai!
By then, "red papers," that is, draft notices
were sending young men off
to the battlefields one after another.
Again, huh?
Yamada-san is sending her only son.
I feel sorry for her.
They're both alone now.
Dear, don't you ever go to war!
I don't want to go.
But if I don't, it'll cause trouble for all of you.
Not at all...
Don't worry.
They won't draft a man
who only knows how to play the violin.
What's wrong, Meiji?
I... feel kinda cold.
Cold, you say? But it's summer!
Me-chan!
Meiji!
What do you think?
Looks like a cold.
He has a bad fever,
so keep his head cool.
Several days passed,
but Meiji's fever only kept rising.
Me-chan?
My leg... hurts...
Your leg?
There's a small wound here.
When did he get it?
About three days ago,
just before his fever started, I think.
He fell during gymnastics class.
So that's what it was.
It was what?
The germs that entered through the wound
spread throughout his body,
causing sepsis.
Sepsis?
He'll get better, right?
Only with medicine.
Please get it.
We'll pay any money for it!
Doctor?
There is no medicine.
It's not about the price.
There's none, anywhere!
No way!
Are you telling us
to just sit back and watch?
Ice cream... Ice cream...
Listen, Totto,
go to the pawnshop
and borrow money with this.
And then go to the candy store
and ask for ice cream.
But...
There's no time!
Go, and be quick!
Another month in the red.
Well, well, if it isn't Totto-chan.
Please, take this.
Totto-chan, this isn't exactly a valuable item.
My little brother Meiji is very sick.
So I wanna give him his favorite ice cream!
I see. That's a pickle, for sure.
Father told me to bring you his violin,
but it's as precious to him as his life,
so I couldn't bear to.
So please, take this hat instead.
Look, there are so many beautiful flowers on it, right?
Mom once asked me
what kind of flowers I liked,
and I said "roses,"
so she spent days embroidering it.
Isn't it a lovely hat?
When I showed it to my friends, they said
the flowers on it look just like the real thing!
Even the hat shop said
they'd never seen anything this pretty.
No good?
Ugh, fine! Now that you can reach the counter, I'll accept it.
Really?!
It's a pretty gorgeous hat,
so how about 10 yen?
Ten whole yen?!
That's about as much
as ice cream costs, right?
Here's 10 yen.
Thank you.
There's a big candy shop in the next ward
where I know the owner. Go there.
Look, you get off at the next station...
Me-chan, are you in pain?
Meiji, hang in there!
Me-chan!
TRAIN TIMETABLE
TOKYO RAILWAYS
I can't wait a whole hour!
Ice cream!
Me-chan, here's some ice cream.
Eat this and get better!
Ice... cream...
That's right, real ice cream.
Here. Open your mouth, Me-chan.
Delicious...
The war took one precious
treasure away from me.
And less than three months later, another one.
One of the red papers found Moritsuna at last,
and he was forced into the army.
Look carefully.
I can't find him at all.
This might be the last time we see each other.
We have to find him, no matter what.
No! I can't find him!
Papa!
We're here! Papa, answer!
It's Dad!
I'll take this with me,
as a memory of you.
Hey, Totto, let's make this
the last time you say "Papa," all right?
My heart can't take it.
But... But!
Thank you. Be good kids, okay?
Yeah!
Take care of the kids.
This will also be the last time I cry.
Until you come back, I will protect these children with my life.
We had three dumplings in the broth today.
It's because it's my birthday, right?
Oh, but you sound too impressed
for something so simple.
Did you forget we also got you
a roast chicken and sushi?
I'll go first!
Me too!
You'll get the biggest one.
Thanks for the meal!
Yummy!
Mom, I want strawberries for dessert!
Me too!
With lots of sweet cream on top.
All right, help yourselves, don't hold back.
I wish they were real.
That's true.
March 10th, 1945.
It felt like everything we had
turned to ashes in that red blaze.
Our future, our freedom...
In two and a half hours,
100,000 people died.
My uncle who lived in Honjo, and his entire family of five, were gone in a flash.
We decided to leave Tokyo
and move to Suwanotaira in Aomori,
where some acquaintances lived.
Goodbye, my home.
We have to live on.
We'll survive and come back here
to live together again someday.
Finally made it.
The place our acquaintances
arranged for us to stay
was a small shed used
for packing apples into boxes.
We're gonna live here?
We can make it work if we clean up a bit!
We should be grateful
to have a roof over our heads.
At least here, we don't have to fear air raids every night.
Though I said it with a buoyant smile,
deep down I was overwhelmed with anxiety
about how we'd manage to live from now on.
We do need workers, but the city folks don't have the skills for most jobs here.
Please, I'll do anything!
Can you count with an abacus?
So I thought.
O-Of course I can!
I can't wait! Click-click-click...
All right, then come here tomorrow.
We'll have you do the accounting.
Thank you so much.
I had lied.
We will win this battle!
100 million with unbent fighting spirit......
But compared to the treacherous lies
the government told us daily...
We will win this battle!
100 million with unbent fighting spirit......
My job at the agricultural cooperative alone
wasn't enough to feed our family of four.
So I worked late into the night sewing work clothes to sell
or helping out at banquets.
At that same time in China,
Moritsuna was enduring a harsh life of his own.
Hey!
Fall out!
You again, Stumblinagi!
Kuroyanagi reporting!
Don't talk back, you violin fiddler!
Yes, sir! I am honored.
What's with that smirk?!
I'm going to beat some sense into your rotten spirit. Grit your teeth!
Yeah, good! Dip it lower!
Kuroyanagi, step forward!
Yes, sir!
I'll let you play this violin you love so much.
Play a military song!
It's an order from your superior! Play!
Yes, sir.
What's wrong, Kuroyanagi?
Keep playing, Stumblinagi!
Y-You! Are you defying
your superior's order?!
There's been a lot more planes
flying around lately.
What a noisy bunch!
Is this area in danger too?
Nah, the enemy wouldn't bother
coming to our boondocks.
Kuroyanagi-san?
A telegram...
It said... that my father had collapsed from a heart attack.
Hey, Mom, when can we
get on the ship?
It's been two days already!
We can only wait right now,
so be patient.
I hope Grandpa's okay.
Dad...
Air raid warning issued!
Please leave the station premises!
It's dangerous here. Hurry, hurry!
Enemy aircraft incoming!
Get out fast!
It's dangerous! Hurry!
They're here! The planes are here!
Over there!
Please let us in, I beg you!
No way! Can't you see we're packed?
At least let the children in!
We were here first!
Can't you understand? Seriously!
Let's go!
Let's go back. We still might
be able to leave by ship.
Look!
They all died... They died!
That lady from before, and that man!
There'll be no one left soon!
Nothing will be left at all!
When will this war ever end?!
Soon... It'll be over soon, for sure.
The ferries and trains weren't running,
so we had no choice but to walk back.
We never got a chance to see my father again
before he passed away.
After pondering deeply the actual conditions
obtaining in our empire today,
August 15th. Finally, the day had come.
we have decided to effect a settlement
by resorting to an extraordinary measure.
We have ordered our government
to communicate to the governments
Japan had lost the war.
of the United States, Great Britain, China, and the Soviet Union
that our empire accepts the provisions
of their joint declaration...
A dream?
Sushi...
Egg would be good too...
Many soldiers returned from China,
where Moritsuna was stationed.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
My, my, how you've both grown!
Does anyone know Kuroyanagi Moritsuna?
Have you seen Kuroyanagi?
Good to see you're all safe.
But Moritsuna was nowhere to be found,
and we never got any news from him.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I've decided to start going to school
earlier from tomorrow on.
I want to study in the library
before class.
I see. That's commendable! Keep it up.
I will. Good night!
Good night.
Plenty of sukiyaki...
Moritsuna was still considered missing in action.
Sister shouldn't be so late.
Her broth's going cold!
Agreed. I'll go look for her.
Tetsuko!
Where have you been?
What happened?
We can't understand
if you just keep silent!
Tell me, Tetsuko!
I was walking on the railroad tracks.
Railroad tracks?
I hung from the iron bridge and didn't even lose my sandals. Isn't that impressive?
You idiot!
Why did you do something so reckless?
You almost got yourself killed!
It's because I lost my commuter pass.
And walking on the tracks is the shortest way!
Why didn't you say anything?
If you'd just told me, we'd...
But we've no money to spare!
Which is more important, money or your life?
What were you thinking?!
I couldn't just come and ask for money!
I couldn't say something like that!
I know you're working hard to save every yen.
Noriaki and Yuri are starving
but are putting up with it!
I could never ask you for money! Never!
Tetsuko!
Tetsuko, where are you?
Tetsuko! Tetsuko!
As I searched for Tetsuko,
it reminded me of my dad.
About the time he hit me when I said
I was going to marry Moritsuna.
Dad didn't hit me out of hatred.
He was just so worried about me,
he couldn't hold back.
Tetsuko...
Now, I finally understand how he felt.
Don't go!
We are going!
Even though his own child
had defied him, isolating him,
he still truly loved me.
Tetsuko...
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
It's okay.
You were worried about Papa,
but you still forced yourself
to stay strong.
So I didn't want to cause you
any extra worry.
Thank you.
Here.
Try not to lose it again.
Yeah!
Go now, or you'll be late!
I'm off!
You mustn't think of it
as educating the child.
We also have much to learn from children.
Maybe they're the ones
actually raising us.
I thought I had to be strong,
to support the kids all on my own.
But in fact, they were supporting me as well.
Thanks to the kids,
I was able to keep going.
Mama!
You've gotten really good with it!
Not really.
Mama!
I found someone who knows about Papa!
I'm Noda. I was in the same unit
as Kuroyanagi-san.
I see.
As a matter of fact, I owe my life to him.
To Moritsuna?
Yes.
It happened when I had lost my will to live.
The battlefield was truly a horrific place.
The war was already lost, but our comrades
kept going to their deaths, one after another.
We were out bullets and food.
We couldn't care for our wounded,
so we just left them there,
bleeding to death, writhing in pain.
I knew for sure I didn't want to die like that.
"If I know I'm going to die suffering,
I'd rather just end it myself with one cut."
That's what I was thinking.
During one of the camp shows...
Kuroyanagi-san suddenly stopped playing.
What's wrong, Kuroyanagi?!
Keep playing, Stumblinagi!
Y-You! Are you defying
your superior's order?!
"He's done for."
That's what I thought, but then...
I found myself...
thinking about my parents back home.
That's right.
I can't die now.
Until I return home and see their faces again,
I won't be able to die in peace.
All right.
I'll survive and return home!
No matter what happens,
I'll survive and return to Japan!
That...
was the vow I made in my heart.
It was thanks to Kuroyanagi-san.
His violin reminded me
what it means to have the will to live.
Moritsuna did?
Papa...
Tetsuko, could you watch Yuri
for me for a while?
Okay!
So where is Moritsuna now?
Well...
Thank you for letting me know.
So when is Papa coming home?
Very soon. Very soon!
Moritsuna...
You can't be dead, can you?
I can't believe it.
Absolutely, absolutely not!
Wake up! It's a flood! A flood!
A flood?
Is that tasty?
Quick, get up! We have to run!
Mama!
Tetsuko, grab Nori-chan's hand.
Okay!
Don't let go no matter what!
Quick, we need to get higher!
Hang in there! Just a little more!
Mama!
No! Dive under!
Should we go back to Tokyo?
Yeah.
Tokyo had changed completely.
Kuroyanagi
The familiar town we once lived in was gone,
reduced to a pile of ashes
as far as the eye could see.
Nothing's left. Nothing at all.
True.
Is this where the living room was?
Oh! Our radio!
I wonder if it still works?
Maybe Papa can fix it
when he comes back?
Yeah, you're right!
Wow! It's moving!
Banzai!
I made it!
I built this boat all by myself!
I see. Impressive, Meiji!
Why?
Hey, look at this, Mama!
Mama?
I have something important to tell you.
This is the sheet music Papa wrote,
the tune he played by the river.
This is really important.
Noriaki was so little,
he probably doesn't remember, right?
This is the tune Papa wrote just for us.
It's about Papa...
It's such a wonderfully beautiful song.
Tetsuko!
When Papa comes back,
he'll play it for us!
Tetsuko...
Papa is...
Papa...
Papa is already...
Already on his way home!
Papa!
Papa! Papa!
Papa...
Papa! Papa! It's really you, isn't it, Papa?!
That's terrible. You forgot Papa's face in just a year?
But... But!
So you were alive? You were alive!
The bullet only grazed me,
but I got seriously hurt
falling down that cliff.
Still, I was lucky
to have a river right below.
I swam all night.
You're so lucky to have made it.
You do remember I'm good
at swimming, don't you?
Besides,
I couldn't die and leave you all behind.
Hey, are you done getting mushy?
We've only started!
We were just getting to the good part!
Then we'll have to interrupt you!
Here, Papa.
Is this...
How could I ever let go
of Papa's precious violin?
I see.
Play it, Papa!
All right!
Time to start from scratch.
That's right.
Let's all do our best, together.
My marriage turned out very differently
from what I had imagined.
The war changed our fate drastically.
We'd been through a lot.
And I learned that people live
by supporting and being supported.
That, in itself, is the greatest joy.
If a family is the simplest gathering
where everyone supports each other,
then now, more than ever,
I truly feel that we are a family.
If today exists for tomorrow
You can overcome any road if you try
If you stretch out your arms
There's always someone nearby to hold you in their arms
Why do we fight and hurt each other?
Humans are weak and sad creatures
But each and every one of us must surely have
The heart to love someone
If we hold hands, we can share our warmth with others
One day, that will connect the world in one big embrace
Somewhere, somewhere, tears are being shed now
I'm sure we can stop them too
If today exists for tomorrow
Every prayer will be answered someday
In your dreams, there is always someone
Right beside you to hold you in their arms
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
Perevodildo
Eternal_Blizzard
Collectr
QC
Encoding
bananadoyouwanna
Eternal_Blizzard
Paul Geromini
anonymous