Selected by
the Ministry of Education
Special Recommendation
Japan PTA National Council
Art and Culture Promotion Program
Grant Fund
Production
Cooperation
Distribution
Aoi Kioku Production Committee
Manchuria Reclamation Project
National Museum
Nagano Prefecture Association
Joint National Affiliated Film Conference
This movie is a dramatization,
based on the experiences of many people,
created to convey historical facts.
Look, above the eastern sea, clearly dawns the sky.
Spring, 1941
Glorious and bright, the sun rides on high.
Spirit pure of heaven and earth fills the hearts of all.
Hope abounding springs, O sweet Isles Imperial.
Yonder where the clouds of morn shed a radiant glow,
Grandpa, it's the Iriyama folk!
Fuji Mountain, Nippon's pride, rears its crown of snow.
Is someone going to Manchuria?
That's one hell of a send-off procession!
Without a blot, nobly does it stand,
a true symbol of our land.
He who reigns above in power and in virtue right,
sovereign of unbroken line, is our changeless light.
Hey! Kenji!
We will follow, one and all, loyal subjects, we
Kyota!
The Iriyama volunteers are leaving!
Let's go and send them off!
Really?
follow Him aright: fulfill our great destiny!
Dad, can I go?
Yeah.
East, west, north and south, over land and main!
I'm going too!
Okay. But hurry up, Ayako!
Let's go, Kyota!
Let us make the world our home and call our fellow men.
Yeah!
Everywhere on the four seas, let us build the tower
of just peace, let our ideal bloom forth like a flower!
He's going to cross the sea!
Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai!
The prolonged Sino-Japanese war,
Though again and yet again trials we may meet,
which began with the 1931 Mukden Incident, was still raging.
over us may tempests roar, storms upon us beat,
People from all over the country
volunteered to go to Manchuria
as part of the land reclamation team.
Resolute in heart and mind justice we defend,
Manchukuo was a country created
by the intervention of the Japanese military
but one road we know to gain triumph in the end.
in the northeastern part of mainland China,
Hark! Far from the hallowed past of the Age Divine
which wasn't yet unified
as the PRC we know today.
The development of that land became
a priority project for the Japanese nation.
sounds our fathers' measured tread. O come fall in line!
And in response to the government's call
to assist in the development
As we, sons and daughters, march, shines our path before.
of Manchuria and Inner Mongolia,
Glory be unto our land ever, evermore!
many people from rural areas and towns
all over Japan set out for the greener pastures.
Look, above the eastern sea, clearly dawns the sky.
Glorious and bright, the sun rides up on high.
Blue Memories
Boys, Colonizing Manchuria and Mongolia
Spirit pure of heaven and earth fills the hearts of all.
Blue Memories
Boys, Colonizing Manchuria and Mongolia
Begin marching in file!
Forward... march!
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two...
The Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere
is a commonwealth, led by our Empire of Japan.
Signs: Universal Brotherhood (horizontal),
Action Before Words (vertical)
Its core idea is that under the blessed rule
of His Majesty the Emperor,
the nations of Asia
will come together and prosper.
The key to realizing the Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere
is uniting the five races in harmony and creating a paradise for them under our just rule!
Yoshizaki! Tell us the meaning
of the Five Races' Union.
Yes, sir!
The "harmony of the five races"
means the five ethnic groups in Manchuria
helping each other
and living in mutual goodwill.
Yes, good.
As expected of the head of class.
So the promised land where the paradise
for the five races can be built is Manchuria.
Manchuria is a brother nation to Japan.
Countless people
in the land reclamation teams
and volunteer armies who went to Manchuria are working hard to develop the land,
serving their country and setting an example
for the entire Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere.
Kyota.
Kyota!
What is it, Yusuke?
Suzuki!
Imbecile!
Suzuki! Name the races included in the idea
of the "harmony of the five races"!
Let's see...
The Yamato, the Mongols, and also...
Um...
The bandits!
Imbecile!
Why are you even coming to school?!
But Sensei, I'll be going to Manchuria soon
and will run around that huge continent on my horse!
I see. So you're going to the continent?
Enemy spotted ahead to the right!
Observing three enemy vehicles
approaching our camp.
All right, ready the bombs!
Ready to go!
I'm ready too!
Okay, charge! Suzuki's Boy Fighter Squadron enters the fray!
Yoshizaki's Boy Fighter Squadron follows!
Yusuke's Boy Fighter Squadron takes off!
Tanaka's Boy Fighter Squadron follows!
Charge!
Hooray!
Success! A complete victory for our air force!
Banzai!
Kyota, you sleazebag!
With your brains, there's no way
you're ever becoming a pilot!
See ya!
Yeah!
Okay!
See you!
Sure!
As the evening sun sets over the fields of canola,
I look upon the mountain ridges, softly veiled in mist.
Has it gotten a little better now?
We're almost home. Stay strong.
Can you walk?
Get on!
Hurry up and get on!
Thank you, Kyo-chan.
Is your mom ill again?
Yeah...
So you don't have time
to come to school?
Yeah...
My sister said she's quitting school to be able to work.
Is that true, Setsuko?!
Yeah.
I'm back!
Hey, Kenji, brother Keichi has just come home.
Brother!
Kenji, you've grown so big.
Brother, your leg...
I fought on the China front.
But with just this leg, I won't be able to fight for my country any longer.
Keichi, you worked hard.
You deserve some rest now.
Chiyo, prepare the white rice today.
To think he'd come back
disfigured like that...
Why did it have to come to this?
I'll avenge him!
I'll enlist as a boy aviator,
find the enemies who did this to him,
and tear them to shreds!
You don't know what you're talking about!
You have no idea what real war is like.
What do you mean, Dad?!
Enough. Go to bed already.
We really are living in troubled times.
Dad's hands...
Dad's hands are big.
They're rough and hard,
with thick thumbs, like tree roots.
They're good for holding
a hoe in the hot summer.
They can weave the straw in the cold winter.
He can cultivate anything that grows
on the earth, like rice or wheat.
I can't wait for my hands
to become like Dad's.
Yes, that's very well written.
The imagery of farmers living off the land
is vivid and strong.
Idiot!
Why?
How is that a bad essay?
It conveys the boy's loftiest feelings
when he sees his parents work!
All I want is to instill that kind of unpretentious sensitivity in the children!
You ditched the textbooks too and just taught by instinct, completely off the rails, right?
You seem to view national policies as mere recommendations, Yoshizaki-sensei.
I'm just trying to cultivate the most noble of emotions in the children
and let them grow freely.
The way I see it, you're possessed
by the devil of free thought.
What are you saying?!
Yoshizaki, I'm sorry, but we can't let you work here any longer.
Y-You can't be serious!
Why did Dad snub me like that?
Spare me!
Spare me, please...
Brother, what's wrong?
Are you ill? Does it hurt?
Brother...
Brother! Are you sure
you should be working already?
He doesn't need to strain himself that much.
He could just take it easy
and have a rest for now.
Brother, you seemed to be having
a nightmare last night.
Did you dream of something that happened in China?
I wonder what Keichi has been through.
He's unrecognizable.
He must've seen plenty of things
he never wanted to see.
Try not to bring it up, Chiyo.
During the busy rice harvest season,
neighboring farmers
lend each other a helping hand.
This kind of collaboration is unique
to agricultural communities and is called yui.
Schools are closed too,
and even the children have no time to play,
as they help with the rice harvest
or babysit the little ones.
Hey, everyone!
Late-morning snacks for you!
With this, we should be done
with Risaku-san's field.
Thank for your help, everyone.
Don't mention it. It's a quid pro quo.
We'll move on to Otomatsu's field next.
But the landlords or the government take away
the rice we do manage to harvest
before we can even smell it.
What's worse, they keep shoving our youth into the army.
How are we supposed to-
Shh! You shouldn't say that out loud.
What if the special or military police overhear you?
They'll snatch you up like old Yamashita Ippei,
and you'll never be seen again.
What's up, Shinbo? Why are you here?
Aren't you gonna eat the snacks with everyone?
Something happened?
Sis said, when the rice harvest is finished,
she'll sell herself off to a spinning mill.
Are you serious?!
Why must you do it now, Secchan?
You've almost finished sixth grade!
Can't you wait until you
graduate from school?
I've already accepted an advance from the mill boss, three years' pay up front.
We'll use this money to treat Shinji's leg...
and buy plenty of medicine for Mom.
I want to pay it back as soon as I can.
I mean, what's the big deal?
Even if I graduate,
I can't go to a higher school.
Besides, I prefer work to studying.
Kyo-chan, you've always been kind to me.
Thank you!
Goodbye!
Ah, Secchan!
Kyota! Secchan is coming!
Let's go see her off from the station.
Kyota, what are you waiting for?
Are you coming or not?
I couldn't do anything.
There was nothing I could do...
Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
Kyota?
Crap! Crap! Crap. Crap...
Please listen to this news bulletin.
Today, on December 8th, at 6:00 AM,
the Imperial General Headquarters announced:
"As of early morning on the 8th, the Imperial Army and Navy entered into a state of war
with the American and British forces
in the Western Pacific Ocean."
I repeat...
On December 8th of that year,
Japan declared war on the US and the UK.
Spring, 1942
Before long, the heavy footsteps of war
drew ever closer to Kenji and the others.
New Year's Day, 1943
Our Imperial Ancestors have founded Our Empire on a basis broad
and everlasting and have implanted virtue deeply and firmly.
Our subjects, ever united in loyalty and filial piety,
have from generation to generation illustrated the beauty thereof.
January, 1944
As I'm sure you already know, this year,
our school will again send out several applicants to join the Youth Volunteer Army
of the Manchuria Reclamation Project.
The mission of this Volunteer Army
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
is to develop the land of rural Manchuria
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
and through agriculture, build the model
for the Greater East Asia Co-Prosperity Sphere,
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Army War College
Calling Young Men
The Youth Volunteer Army
of Manchuria needs you!
Expanded Recruitment for the
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Youth Volunteer Corps
the paradise in which the five races live in union and understanding.
Manchuria Reclamation Project
Youth Volunteer Corps
High school
..Class 2-1
Approximately 70,000 young people from all over Japan have already traveled to Manchuria
and are continuing their noble pioneering work.
If you are also strong at heart, I would definitely like you to apply to the Volunteer Army.
If you go to Manchuria,
you'll receive ten hectares of land there!
Manchuria Reclamation
..Youth Volunteer Corps
So what do you say?
Manchuria Reclamation
..Youth Volunteer Corps
If you burn with aspirations for prosperity,
the land of Manchuria is waiting for you!
Manchuria Reclamation
..Youth Volunteer Corps
Oh? Yusuke, they've come to your place too?
Yeah. Twice already!
Same for me.
Junpei, what about you?
They've been at my place three times.
Hey, Kenji, what about you?!
Uh? Yeah. They've been at my place too.
Sounds like Mori-sensei
is going door to door,
recruiting people for the Volunteer Army.
So, whatcha gonna do, guys?
Will anyone apply?
I've decided to go for it.
For real?!
I don't really wanna go, though.
But my uncle is working at the town hall
as a recruiter for the reclamation project.
If word gets out he couldn't collect
even a single volunteer, he'll lose face.
He convinced my parents
to send me there.
Why the hell are you sulking, then?!
You'll get to do some important job
on that huge continent!
It's like a dream come true!
But I've heard there are wolves in Manchuria.
And in winter, it's so cold
even your pee freezes!
Come on, are you really worried
about stuff like that?
By the way, Kyota,
what about you?
Me?
I will
apply to the Volunteer Army
and go to Manchuria!
For real?
Yeah! I'll go to the new land
to build a paradise for the five races!
I'll work for the good of my country
and become a big-shot landowner!
This is the spirit of a Japanese boy!
I've decided!
Okay, count me in as well!
I'll go to Manchuria!
All right!
Kenji, aren't you going with us?
Kenji?
Brother!
Can I come in?
Sure. Don't be shy.
What's up, Kenji?
Brother...
What's it like on the continent?
Japan is trying to build a paradise
for the five united races on the continent.
But if they're united,
why are they at war?
Why did you have to lose
your leg in China for it?!
Kenji, are you considering
going to Manchuria?
The Volunteer Army, right?
Kyota and the others are asking me
to go there with them.
But I have to help Dad...
Do you want to go?
Yeah, I suppose.
Why did you have to go
through so much suffering?
Why are we sending so many soldiers
to the continent to wage war?
Is Manchuria really the ideal land
for building that paradise?
I don't know that either.
Kenji, forget about Manchuria
and keep studying.
You're a smart boy.
If you continue studying,
you'll naturally grow to understand this.
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Name           Suzuki Kyota
Born July 3, 1929 (15 years old)
I would like to join the Volunteer Corps
Kyota, how could you...
Manchuria is a terrible place!
But Mom, I absolutely must go there.
In Manchuria, I'll be able to farm an enormous field, not a tiny paddy like ours!
You've got some nerve to say that.
Kyota, I understand how you feel,
but if you leave us, our family...
Grandpa! Are you okay?
That's right, Kyota.
Your brother is on the battlefield,
and your grandfather is too old
to work as hard as he used to.
If you leave for Manchuria,
what'll become of our family?
I know that,
but...
Once I have my own land, you and grandpa will never have to go without again!
Ma'am, please try to understand
how Kyota-kun feels.
But Manchuria is awfully dangerous,
with all the bandits around.
In that case, you have nothing to worry about.
Manchuria is under the firm protection
of the Japanese army, the strongest in the world.
Furthermore, Manchukuo is a paradise
for the five united races.
Kyota-kun and the others
will do some fine work there,
serving their nation.
There's nothing to worry about.
Mom, look... I've already decided.
I'm going there, no matter what anyone says!
Now, ma'am, please sign.
You've done some extraordinary work, Mori-sensei.
It's a great honor for our school
to be sending three new applicants
to the Volunteer Army!
Oh no, I'm only doing this out of concern
for the future of my country and its children.
Good. That's a commendable mindset!
I'd like to see them grow
into model land pioneers,
instilled with the spirit of brotherhood among the five united races.
Yes, sir. I share that aspiration with you!
Well, it also allowed us to fulfill the quota for our school, and that's a relief for sure.
Yes, sir. With this, I can also leave the school
without any lingering regrets.
Fiftieth Regiment from Matsumoto, isn't that right?
Yes!
Mori-sensei, please trade your teaching stick for a rifle
and fight honorably for your country!
Yes, sir!
Kyota!
Hey!
Did you enlist in the Volunteer Army?
Yeah.
Kenji, so it's true that you're not coming?
Yeah...
So what are you going to do
after you graduate?
W-Well, go to the teachers' college, I think.
College?
Not the Imperial Army?
No...
I think I want to keep studying.
I see.
So while we're out there
fighting with hoes in hand,
you're just gonna sit back
and study in safety?
And I...
Actually wanted you to go to Manchuria with us more than anyone else!
We've always done everything together,
ever since we were kids.
So I trusted you.
I'm sorry.
Come on, Kenji!
It's not too late yet!
Won't you go to Manchuria with me?!
Come on, come with me, Kenji.
I... I'm not sure!
Is Manchuria really that nice of a place?
Is it really a paradise for five races?!
Kenji, what the hell are you saying?!
If we really wanted the five races
to be united there, why start a war?!
You dumbass!
Do you even hear what you're saying?!
I had no idea you were
such a coward, Kenji!
Don't... Don't you ever call me a coward!
You're getting it!
Shit for brains!
So you're a traitor, huh?!
I trusted you, you scum!
How could you ever understand how I feel!
Asshole!
Why do I need to understand a coward?!
Hey... Are you really going to college?
I've decided. I've chosen studying.
Okay, I understand.
It's your life. Choose your own path.
Mine lies in Manchuria.
But our friendship stays the same.
Isn't that right, Kenji?
Yeah.
Kenji
Kyota
I'll never forget about you,
even when I go to Manchuria.
Kyota
Kenji
Yeah. I'll never forget you, either.
Kyota
Kenji
I'll be writing you letters from Manchuria.
I'll see for myself all the things
you say you don't get,
try to figure them out,
and tell you what I learn!
Okay.
It is a source of pride for our village
to see off these three young men
who are joining the Youth Volunteer Army
of the Manchuria Reclamation Project today.
We hope these three young men,
with their diligence and resolve,
will become the founding fathers of the new nation of Manchukuo,
will rise above all hardship,
and will show admirable courage and grit
in rebuilding it and shaping a new order
in Greater East Asia.
Take care of yourself, won't you?
No need to worry, Mom.
I'll bring all of you over in no time!
Kyota...
Don't do anything reckless, Kyota.
What's with you, Mom, Grandpa?
I'm starting a new life.
You should be smiling!
Kyota!
Tachigawa!
Here! It's from Setsuko!
She works during the day,
so she asked me to bring it instead.
Is she doing well?
Yeah. Sister's spinning mill
is a plane parts factory now, though.
I see.
Kyota. Kyota!
Kenji!
Don't forget to write to me!
I know!
Secchan...
Nagano Teachers' College, Men's Dormitory
Impressive, bro. You managed to bring all this stuff with you.
Don't mention it.
I have to carry this much to live normally.
That's right. I got a letter for you.
It's from Kyota!
Ibaraki Prefecture,
Uchihara Volunteer Army Training Center
How are you, Kenji?
Ibaraki Prefecture,
Uchihara Volunteer Army Training Center
Right now, they're training me for when I go to Manchuria
Ibaraki Prefecture,
Uchihara Volunteer Army Training Center
at the Volunteer Army Training Center in Uchihara, Ibaraki Prefecture.
Our morning begins with a ceremony of bowing to the Imperial Palace.
Prince!
Boys from all over Japan
who volunteered to join the Youth Volunteer Army of the Manchuria Reclamation Project
undergo about three months of training here at the Uchihara Training Center.
Then it's time to set out for the local training center in Manchuria.
And then they finally said they'd be sending
my unit to Manchuria.
By the time this letter reaches you,
we'll probably already be out at sea.
What's wrong, Kenji?
Kyota is finally going to Manchuria.
Kenji, Manchuria may not be safe anymore.
That year, about 8,000 boys who had completed their training at Uchihara
We are the Youth Volunteer Army.
were sent off to the training camp in Manchuria
with a grand pep rally, their hearts full of hope.
Come autumn, we go to Manchuria and Mongolia
After coming to Tokyo to worship the Imperial Palace in person,
to build a second homeland.
Militia
the boys finally boarded a ship
bound for the continent and left Japan.
Militia
We will strike the bright green sky.
We will strike the bright green sky!
Manchuria
Hey, Yusuke, wake up!
It's so big!
Kenji, we started our new life
as land reclaimers
at a training center up north in Manchuria,
near the Soviet border.
Here, they renamed us the "Manchuria Reclamation Youth Volunteer Corps."
After three more years of training,
we'll qualify as full-fledged members
and be granted our own land!
The summer is hot in Manchuria,
but our hearts are overflowing with hope!
We are the Youth Volunteer Army,
inheriting the mantle of our ancestors.
All right...
With courage and pluck, we lead the way.
In our swinging arms, rings a sound.
In our swinging arms, rings a sound!
We are the Youth Volunteer Army.
Come autumn, we go to Manchuria and Mongolia
to build a second homeland.
We will strike the bright green sky.
We will strike the bright green sky!
We are the Vouth Volunteer Army.
Righteous and just is our rule, through power and love.
But man, Manchuria sure is big!
I wish you could see how amazing this land is,
even just once, Kenji!
Wherever we go, wherever our flag flies,
It's just that when I stand guard at night,
I can sometimes hear the wolves howling,
and that gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Behold, there's the light of co-prosperity.
What the hell is wrong with you?!
This isn't a kindergarten!
Grow a pair, goddammit!
Behold, there's the light of co-prosperity!
Got nothing to say?
Sometimes, senior trainees
get under our skin,
but the three of us are working hard
to encourage each other.
Sheesh... Sure is a long way to the city.
I mean, really!
We left the training center before dawn,
but by the time we get back, it'll be dark already.
Just buying supplies
takes a whole day of work!
Quit complaining!
Aren't you just glad that we got
to see the big city at long last?
What's that?
Are they from this village?
But where are they going?
We can't drive through this, Kyota.
Ah! Watch out!
Are you okay?
Does it hurt somewhere?
What are you doing?!
Wh-Why'd he look at me that way?
What did I ever do to him?
Stop dawdling around!
Get the hell out!
Please! Don't drive me out!
Silence!
This land belongs to the Japanese now!
But I've lived here my whole life! My whole life!
If I leave, I won't be able to survive!
Why are you still jabbering here?!
Get out of my sight!
Mama! Mama...
No loitering around! Keep going!
Sir...
Are you guys from the Volunteer Corps?
Yes, sir!
Yeah, sorry about that.
We didn't mean to block the road.
No problem!
But sir, what's going on here?
They'll be building a hospital for the Japanese here.
We had to drive the locals out.
What's wrong, Kyota?
You're unusually silent today.
No, it's nothing.
What if the land they give us is the same land
they took away from the locals?
Nagano Station, Engine Shed
Kyota,
I was relieved to hear in your last letter
that you're doing well in Manchuria.
At the moment, I work at the station's engine shed as a mobilized student.
Others weren't as lucky. They were drafted into the army and sent to the front lines.
Looks like Japan's
on a fast track to rock bottom.
Kenji, it's winter in Manchuria.
It's a whole different beast from Japanese winters. Here, it can drop to -40°C.
We're doing our best
to take care of our livestock.
What are you doing, Junpei?
It's not me. It's him!
Cut it out! What the hell!
I'd say he's taken quite a liking to you.
What wore the boys in the Volunteer Corps down the most
were the endless drills in the snow.
Continuing day after day,
they caused the first casualties in the Corps.
Squad, stop!
Okay, that's all for today.
Another march in the snow
is planned for tomorrow.
Tanaka, what's wrong? Hang on!
Junpei! Stay strong, Junpei!
Don't fall asleep!
Junpei, are you okay?
I wanna go home...
I really... wanna go home!
Junpei...
Mom...
Mom!
Spring, 1945
Kenji, the Manchurian spring is beautiful.
It's like spring and summer
have come and struck all together,
painting the vast grasslands with flowers.
...and that's how it happened!
I didn't expect that!
Looking at all these flowers reminds me of our village, of playing with you and Secchan.
Hey, did you hear? Tokyo was reduced to ashes in the latest air raid.
You think it's true?
Do you think it means
Japan is losing the war?
Kyota, everything you write in your letters
sounds leisurely and carefree.
Is Manchuria really that peaceful?
Is it really that laid back?
Short break!
All right, at ease, everyone!
Hey, Kyota, what do you think?
We're barely doing any work
in the fields these days.
All we do is military training!
It's like we came here to fight in a war!
Yeah, that's true.
What's more, I hear the Japanese garrison
has already been reassigned to the south.
What's the meaning of this?!
August 9, 1945
Midnight
At midnight on August 9, 1945,
Soviet troops crossed the border
and attacked Manchuria.
Prior to that, Japan and the Soviet Union
had been bound by a mutual treaty of non-aggression.
However, the Soviet Union had unilaterally revoked the treaty several months before.
The Soviet army was expected to attack at any time.
However, that information was only disclosed to the military higher-ups.
The general public and the volunteers
were kept completely in the dark.
Listen, everyone!
Last night, Soviet forces crossed the border
into the province of Heilongjiang!
Our Volunteer Corps will now join the Japanese army in the city!
Staggered column, spread out. Double time!
Hurry up! Run as fast as you can!
Our barracks...
No falling behind! Keep running!
Hey, look, what's that?
It's burning!
Wh-What do we do now?
No... This can't be right!
Why is this happening?
We're going west now!
Everyone, stay strong until we join forces
with the Japanese army!
Hey, did you hear?
The Americans used a new type of bomb.
Yeah. Hiroshima and Nagasaki
were totally leveled!
They're not joking, that's for sure.
Air raid! To the shelter, everyone!
Kyota...
Are you... Are you safe, Kyota?
Japan sued for peace just two days later.
But at that time, the boys in the Volunteer Corps had no way of knowing about Japan's defeat.
They'd only just begun their march westward,
while avoiding contact with the Soviet army.
People from reclamation teams
all over Manchuria,
who had finally carved out a living through hardship,
were now abandoning their villages and flocking to the bigger towns.
However, what was now awaiting the reclamation teams
was a path of unimaginable hardships.
Not this city either?
Hey, what's that?
The enemy?
They're a reclamation team.
Where do you come from?
Well, we're the Nagano Prefecture reclamation team that was stationed far from here.
We've come all this way
in hopes of finding our army.
I see.
We, the Volunteer Corps, were also heading to another town in search of our troops.
Maybe you won't find any,
no matter where you go.
Rumor says that most Japanese troops
at the border have withdrawn.
And local riots are breaking out left and right.
Even our Japanese reclamation village came under attack!
The village close to us was also attacked
and almost completely wiped out!
We only had time to grab the bare essentials before bolting for the hills.
However, the military had previously rounded up and conscripted most of the boys in the village.
Only the women, children,
and the elderly were left there.
It wasn't easy for them to make it here.
I understand.
Please let us accompany you too.
I'm sure we can be of some help, at least.
Say, why are the locals attacking us?
How would I know?!
I feel that I'm starting to understand why.
Say, Yu, remember when we came across
some Japanese officials
kicking the locals out of their village?
And those eyes!
They were the eyes of someone
who hates us Japanese with passion!
We only came here to live off the land
we took away from those people!
Then what was all that bullshit
about the unity of five races?!
Kenji, you were right...
The World Turned Upside Down!
Sign: Reclamation Team
By then, the balance of power
between the Japanese and the Chinese
in Manchuria had been completely reversed.
The pent-up anger of the Chinese, who had thus far been
oppressed under Japanese military occupation, erupted.
And now that anger was directed
at any Japanese they could find.
Mitsuo, do your legs hurt?
Try to bear with it for a bit more.
Just a little more,
and we'll be able to rest.
Secchan...
Sumiko, what are you doing?
We're going to fall behind.
Mom, Mitsuo's legs hurt!
We must bear with it and keep walking.
Come on, stand up!
Watch out!
We're safe now.
Sumiko! Mitsuo!
We're so lucky to have met you soldiers!
I-I'm Suzuki Kyota!
We're not soldiers. We're volunteers.
I see...
I'm Kawamura Sumiko!
Thank you, mister!
It's nothing.
To escape from the Soviet army
and the enraged Chinese people,
they wandered through
the mountains at night.
The group continued their escape,
battling hunger and fatigue.
People had to abandon
their carriages and carts,
and even the few belongings they had been carrying
had to be thrown aside because of fatigue.
The bridge... The bridge is gone!
H-How did this happen?!
Sensei!
We found this.
It's a Japanese gunpowder bag.
Ah? So that means our army is close by?
Wow, what a relief!
No, it was probably just to stop
the Soviet advance.
The bridge was blown up.
But if our army blew it up...
Our troops have long since retreated from here.
We can't count on them.
I finally understand the meaning
of this sabotaged bridge.
S-So then, are you suggesting
the Japanese army abandoned us?
Is that so, Sensei?!
I-It can't be! We only came here because we were promised
that the Japanese army would protect us!
How could they blow the bridge and hightail it out of here,
leaving our corps and all the civilians
in the reclamation team stranded?!
You don't know what you're talking about.
Our army just chose not to fight here.
But they're surely fighting back elsewhere. I'm sure!
It's my fault for giving you false hope
and putting you through this.
Sensei?
Please, Father!
If we leave you behind now,
what was the whole journey even for?!
Grandma, please!
Grandma!
This is as far as we can go.
There's no way we can cross this river.
Grandma!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, let's go!
Please, let's go!
I promise to be a good boy!
You're already a good boy,
and a strong one too.
Do your best and return to Japan.
We've already decided to stay here.
But even if you stay here, there's nothing to eat. You won't be able to survive.
We'll carry you across on our backs!
Yeah, let's do that, okay?
We'll be all right
as long as we stick together.
Sorry.
We appreciate your feelings, but our legs and hands are just too weak to continue.
You should just leave us here and move on.
Yasubo, never let go of your mother.
Asako, surviving will be harder for you
than staying was for us.
Stay strong. That is our final wish.
Allow us some peace of mind.
Grandpa! Grandpa, no!
Yasubo, I'll keep watching over you,
as a spirit in the sky now.
Now... go.
Please, don't take long!
Grandpa!
Grandma!
Most who attempted that crossing
over the river without a bridge made it through, but one in three were lost along the way.
Mom!
For those still on the run, finding food
became a bigger and bigger problem.
It was especially tough on mothers
trying to feed their babies and little children.
Oh man... The refugees who passed through here before have already picked anything edible!
It's not gonna work. Let's split up
and try searching elsewhere!
Okay.
Mister!
Hey! Found anything edible?
No...
I see. Wanna search with me, then?
Yes!
Oh! Check this out!
Here too!
Look, we can get our fill
with all this stuff!
I gathered a lot too!
Good. Then here's some more for your mom and Mitsuo.
Thank you!
Tomiko! Tomiko!
Open your eyes, please!
I'm so sorry...
I'm sorry! Please forgive me, Tomiko!
Poor thing.
She hadn't had any milk for days.
Isn't it like that for everyone?
Once a baby stops crying,
it's already too late.
Mom...
Ugh! Disgusting!
Is it even edible?
Do you care if it's tasty or not
when your belly is groaning?
It's better than eating nothing at all!
Sumiko, lend me your bowl.
Takao, you need to swallow it.
Why won't you eat it, Takao? Takao!
Chop-chop! We need to keep going.
Please prepare to leave at once.
Um... I'm sorry, but could you please
leave without us?
My son's legs still hurt
and he can't walk much.
We'll follow you later.
I see. Don't take too long, though.
Kyota? You're not going?
Oh, I see. Then I guess we'll stick around.
For mothers with infants and young children,
the journey was especially harrowing.
As time went on, more and more mothers
and families with children fell behind
and were left along the route.
Mitsuo, can you go?
Here, this should make it a bit easier for you.
Yeah...
I'm sure you'll feel better if you rest for a bit.
And then you'll be able to walk!
Yeah.
As the evening sun sets over the fields of canola,
I look upon the mountain ridges, softly veiled in mist.
As the spring breeze whispers gently through the sky,
I wanna go home.
Mom...
the evening moon floats gracefully-
It's a gunshot!
Pretty far away.
Junpei, take Sumi to safety!
G-Got it!
Sensei?!
Kyota!
But what's this?
What happened?
The locals attacked us up the road.
We're the only survivors.
Sensei!
It's the locals' village.
What do we do?
We can only turn back now.
It's an ambush!
Please calm down, everyone.
It's all right.
Thank you so much!
Ah! Friends! Hey! Please don't push!
Actually, if we see any Japanese,
we're supposed to inform
either the Chinese or the Soviet armies.
But we couldn't bring ourselves to do that,
because you've gone through such hardships.
We have a very good idea of how painful it must be for you to lose your reclamation land.
We too were forced out before,
our land and homes taken by the Japanese.
Takao! Takao!
Watch him for me for a moment.
Takao... You can't die, Takao!
Mom! Takao is sucking on her!
Thank you so much. Thank you!
May I?
Look, look, he's smiling!
He's laughing now! He's cute!
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Grow big and strong. Big! You hear?
Sumi-chan?
Why are you out here alone?
Mom told me to wait here.
Your mom did?
Last night, she went to the woman
who fed Takao her breast milk.
She had made up her mind yesterday.
I only pretended to be asleep,
but in my heart, I was saying goodbye.
Sumi-chan...
Driven by exhaustion,
hunger, and the threat
of death, the mothers
entrusted their babies to the Chinese,
clinging to the desperate hope
that at least their children might live on.
The children left behind in China this way
came to be known
as the stranded Chinese orphans,
their numbers reportedly reaching
into the thousands, or even tens of thousands.
It's a village!
I can see a village!
What?
That's a Japanese village!
A reclamation settlement!
The original pioneers of this settlement
had long since retreated.
Those gathered here now were all refugees who came
from pioneer villages deeper inland.
This pioneer settlement had
ample reserves of water and food,
so Kyota's regiment was at last able
to enjoy some much-needed rest.
However, this village was already surrounded by Soviet troops,
and a full-scale attack was expected the next morning.
So, summing up your views,
we've ended up with three factions:
Team Escape, Team Suicide,
and Team Attack to Buy Time for the Others.
We must start acting on those plans
before the enemy attacks.
It is what it is.
Excuse me... May I?
It seems the enemy is treating us
as the regular army. What gives?
That's because we attacked a Soviet plane that had crash-landed and killed the crew.
If you want to know why, it's because the Soviet soldiers kept coming here for our women.
And since everyone else had already escaped,
we ended up killing them.
We've picked this pioneer settlement as our place to make a stand.
I'm sorry you guys got caught
between a rock and a hard place,
but I'm gonna have to ask you
for some men for the attack squad.
Of course, I have no right
to make such a request.
All right.
Please allow me to join the attack squad.
All that remains is for everyone to do his duty. Dismissed!
Team Suicide, gather at the stables!
Team Escape, gather at the west gates!
The Soviets are planning
an all-out attack tomorrow morning.
Our mission is to attack them first.
We're doing it to buy time
for Team Escape and Team Suicide.
Once Team Suicide starts chanting sutras,
we will sortie from the southern gate.
Sumiko? Sumiko!
I also wish I could keep traveling with you.
Listen. Just keep running until daybreak,
as far as your legs will take you.
Got it?
Kyota!
It was then that I realized,
odd as it sounds,
that joining this desperate attack
meant certain death for me.
Goodbye, Sumi-chan.
No way!
Okay, stop!
Listen, everyone.
I'm not a soldier, I'm a teacher!
But for this attack only,
I'm going to become a soldier for one night.
Before that, I have one final thing to do as a teacher.
What I am about to say
is my last will and my absolute order!
If you disobey it, I'll kill you.
You are to survive by any means necessary.
And when you make it back to our homeland, Japan,
you'll tell everyone what you saw and heard
here in Manchuria, and about us.
Make sure the story of how we,
the Volunteer Corps
and pioneers, lived and died
is etched into Japan's history.
With this, the squad is disbanded!
I lied when I said I'd protect us.
In the end, I became just another
Japanese soldier who fled first,
leaving my subordinates to pay for it!
Squad Commander!
Please allow me to die alongside you!
Imbecile!
Taking my life will be the Soviets' only victory today. The rest of you must live on!
Is that clear?!
You flee from here as far as you can.
And I have to go! Farewell!
Oh no... Oh my God!
The enemy attacks! Fire!
S-Sensei...
Kyota?
Hello.
Kenji-san?
My mother made some
rice cakes. Please try them.
Yes, thank you for looking
after us all this time.
I know your family is having it hard too.
It's nothing.
Um, you still haven't heard
anything from Kyota?
No, not a word from anyone.
The war is supposed to be over.
Do you think that in Manchuria...
It'll all be fine, ma'am.
Kyota's always been a tough leader.
He never threw in the towel,
no matter what happened,
ever since he was a kid.
He'll come back. I know he will!
Those who had been abandoned by the Japanese military, on whom they had depended so much,
made desperate escapes
and were gathered in internment camps
set up in and around various cities.
But the camps were hell on Earth,
with hunger, cold, typhus,
and other diseases so rampant
that the number who died from lack of treatment exceeded the number
who died during their escape attempt.
Only one this morning.
Few is better than many.
Kyota, I'll go to the shop now,
so take care of Junpei.
Sure, leave this to me.
Yusuke!
Sorry we're only sending you
to work these days.
Compared to what we had to do during our escape, work is nothing to complain about!
See you!
Come back before dark, you hear?
Junpei, only some hot water
this morning. Sorry.
Ah... Kyota.
Yusuke will bring you
something to eat in the evening.
Bear with it until then, won't you?
I'm sorry for giving you all this trouble.
But I'm feeling much better,
so I'll also start working soon.
Well, you don't have to push yourself.
Besides, I will soon...
bring you plenty of delicious stuff
from the food warehouse.
Yusuke?
What's wrong, Yusuke?!
Kyota... I think I've come down
with typhus too.
Come on, Yusuke! Stay strong!
You were so healthy just this morning!
Yusuke, don't give up, please!
Yusuke!
Why did you have to die before me?!
That rascal Yusuke.
He died without a word.
To think that Yusuke would die before me...
You'd better not die before me, Kyota!
Did you say his name is Kyota?
Are you Suzuki Kyota?
Yeah... I'm Suzuki Kyota.
Then you probably know
Kawamura Sumiko, right?
Uh?! Do you know Sumi-chan?!
Yeah, we worked together
at a cloak shop about a month ago.
That's when she told me
she was looking for you.
So is Sumi-chan still working
at that cloak shop?!
No, she soon stopped coming.
But I know what internment camp she's in.
Tell me! Which camp is it?!
S-Sumi-chan...
Sumi-chan!
Kyota!
Thank God...
Thank God you're alive!
Kyota!
I see. So that lady died?
That's a pity.
That means Sumi-chan is
all alone now, doesn't it?
And Sumi-chan herself
looks pretty bad too.
At this rate...
Kyota, let's strike that warehouse!
Wha...
We'll swipe enough food
for Sumi-chan to eat her fill!
Then she'll get better for sure!
I'll go with you instead of Yusuke.
I'm sure we can pull it off!
Junpei...
Junpei, if that sentry starts walking this way, howl twice like a dog.
Okay.
Off I go.
It worked like a charm!
You keep this.
It's rice, right?
Amazing!
It was too easy.
I'll make another trip.
I'm sure they have some better stuff!
Kyota! But that's...
Shh!
Howl if the sentry approaches,
remember? Two times!
Kyota, don't take long.
This much rice is more than enough!
What?
Who goes there?! Who?
Ah! He noticed me!
Stop right there! Stop!
Junpei! Did you manage to get away?!
Junpei!
Did they get you?
Kyota, here...
Let Sumi-chan eat it...
Junpei!
Don't you die!
Please! You can't die here!
Say something!
Shit!
Damn it all!
Damn it! Damn it to hell!
Is there really no God
or Buddha in this world?
What was all that "unity of five races" crap?!
What paradise?! This is pure hell here!
Everyone died!
Junpei too... Yusuke too... Everyone!
What...
What am I supposed to do next?
...back in Japan, you'll tell everyone what you saw and heard here in Manchuria, and about us.
Make sure the story of how we lived
and died is etched into Japan's history.
Sensei...
Sensei!
Kyota...
Sumi-chan, you'll eat this porridge
to survive and go back to Japan.
That's what Junpei would want.
Where's Junpei?
Junpei is dead.
So you must eat this rice and live on,
for yourself and for Junpei!
And then go back to Japan!
I can't go back.
After all, both Mitsuo and Takao
are still in this country.
I must stay here too.
Kyota, you go home on your own.
But you won't be able to survive here!
My dad too.
My dad might end up at this camp too.
I must wait for him.
I see.
Then accept this, at least.
It's a talisman that's been
protecting me all this time.
If you have it,
I'm sure you'll survive.
Then there's also this rice
Junpei got away with.
With this much,
you can make do for a while.
Well, I'll be going now.
Goodbye, Kyota.
Goodbye, Sumi-chan.
Kyota, live on.
For yourself and for me...
Live on!
Sumi-chan... Why?
Sumi-chan!
Let's go home together!
I'll definitely take you with me! I swear!
You can wait for him in Japan.
I'm sure your dad will come home too!
And then, together with your dad, you can go look for Mitsuo-chan and Takao-chan.
Until then, you can just live with us.
Thank you, Kyota...
Kyota! Come home already!
Kenji, I'm coming home.
I'll definitely return to Japan!
Just you wait, Kenji!
The shrike is crying in the dead tree
I'm beating the straw
Grandma's spinning the cotton wheel
And the waterwheel's turning
They're all the same as last year
But there's one thing missing
I don't hear my elder brother chopping wood
I don't hear him chopping wood sharply
He's gone to Manchuria
The guns glistened with tears
O shrike, cry that it's cold
My elder brother may be even colder
Kyota
Kenji
Translation &
Timing
Editing
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Collectr
True Noobow Gamer
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs