Excuse me, can we please go faster?
I'm late for the concert rehearsal!
Orphan Fansubs presents
Gauche the Cellist
Public Hall
What happened to Gauche?
He's still not here?
What am I going to do with him?
Our ensemble specializes in music.
How will it look if we lose
to the town's amateur orchestra?
I'm sorry!
Gauche!
Y-Yes?
Didn't you know we started rehearsing a while ago?
I'm sorry. I got held up looking after my garden.
Your garden?
Let's play the whole movement now.
The cello was behind!
That won't do. I don't have time to run through a scale with you!
Right...
Let's try once more, then.
And...
No, no! That won't do!
This is the heart of the piece.
We can't perform
with this mess of a sound!
Listen up! We only have ten days
until the concert!
Hey, Gauche.
Yes?
You have no musical expressiveness,
neither anger nor laughter.
You're always trailing behind everyone else,
like an undone shoelace!
We can't have that!
You need to get it together.
Okay...
That's all for today.
Gauche, you have no musical expressiveness whatsoever!
No, no!
We can't perform
with this mess of a sound!
Is that you, Hauche? Come in.
Good evening.
Man, I'm tired.
Carrying these is no joke.
What do you mean?
Here, they're for you.
Please help yourself.
Aren't those... tomatoes from my garden?!
Getting angry like that is
bad for your health, Sensei.
Why don't you play me
Schumann's Träumerei instead?
I'll be your audience.
Why should I?
You're just a cat.
Because I simply can't go to sleep
unless I listen to your music.
Don't be impertinent!
Now, please don't be shy and play.
I'll show you now.
Is this the Träumerei you asked for?!
What the hell?!
For goodness sake, please stop it!
Shut up! I'm about to catch a tiger!
That should teach you.
There's something wrong
with your performance tonight.
Shut up! And get out of my sight!
Never again!
Gauche, you're holding us back.
You need to take it more seriously.
You're always trailing behind everyone else,
like an undone shoelace.
Did that cat really come for more?
This time it's a bird?
I want to learn music.
Did you say music?
But isn't your song just,
"Cuckoo, cuckoo"?
That's how you see it!
However, if we take...
and compare it to...
you can clearly hear
that they're different notes!
But they aren't.
You're just too dense to hear it.
But for us cuckoos, each one...
is unlike any other "cuckoo" ever!
If that's so, why do you need
my help to learn music?
It's precisely because I want to sing a scale accurately.
Sensei, please teach me to sing a scale.
All right, all right.
I'll play it once,
but then you go home, got it?
Wrong, wrong!
What do you know?
It goes like this:
What d'ya know!
To you guys, a simple scale and
the Sixth Symphony sound the same.
That's not true!
The hard part is keeping those going continuously!
So, like this?
Yes, yes!
Why did you stop?
Please play for a while more.
You're already getting good at it,
but your intonation is a little off.
What was that?
Aren't I supposed to be teaching you?
Just a little more, please!
But no more than this.
Ugh! Enough!
If I keep up this nonsense,
I'll start sounding like a cuckoo myself.
How can you give up so soon?
We cuckoos keep practicing until our throats bleed, no matter what piece it is!
You're impertinent!
Get out of my sight!
Are you stupid? The window is closed.
Now you're probably injured.
All right, let me open it for you.
Who is it?
Good evening, Mr. Gauche.
A tanuki now?
What do you want?
My father sent me to learn from you.
Learn what?
I play the small drum, you see, and I came to learn to play along with your cello.
But I don't see a drum anywhere.
Please play this piece.
Okay... But that's one strange piece.
All right, let's try.
Oh? It's turning out quite well.
Is something wrong?
You're always strangely slow
when it's time to pull that second string.
It makes me stumble every time.
It's probably this lousy cello.
Won't you try playing it once more?
All right.
Ah, the sun is up!
I have to go home.
Thank you, Mr. Gauche.
Take care on your way home.
Bye now.
So it's my second string?
Hello. Hello?
Come in.
Oh? A field mouse tonight?
Sensei, my child is sick,
and I think he's dying.
Please, please, cure him if you can.
But I'm not a doctor.
Sensei, you don't mean that.
Every day you cure
everyone's illnesses so skillfully.
What do you mean?
Thanks to you, Madam Rabbit got better.
Papa Tanuki was reinvigorated too.
Even the ill-natured Horned Owl was cured.
Hey, that can't be right.
I don't remember helping an ailing owl.
Why should this misfortune befall my son?
If this was unavoidable,
why couldn't it have happened sooner?
Until mere minutes ago, you were
thundering away so marvelously...
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Are you saying that my cello playing somehow cured your illnesses?
Yes! It makes our blood circulate
through the body faster,
and we feel a great deal better.
Is that so? The sound of my cello
cures the illnesses of animals?
All right, I'll play.
Dear, did you fall the way I taught you,
with your legs together?
Yeah.
Please, Sensei.
That should be enough, Sensei.
Please let him out now.
What, already?
How was it?
Are you feeling any better?
Yeah.
He's better!
Thank you so much!
Come on, you thank Sensei too.
Thank you.
Literature                                    Museum
Venus Orchestra Concert
Maestro, they're asking for an encore.
Do you have a short piece to play?
That's out of the question.
Oh, Gauche, how about you
throw something together for them?
Sir... Y-You want me to go out there?
They're making a fool of me!
All right, you can have
my "Indian Tiger Hunt."
Gauche, that was wonderful.
You've come so far in just a week or so.
You could've done it anytime
if you'd put your mind to it, you rascal.
Ah, Cuckoo. Sorry about that night.
I wasn't really angry at you.
Translation & Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
Nemesis, Paul Geromini
Omar Hidan