Orphan Fansubs presents
Run, Melos
Hey, Melos! Wait, Melos!
What happened?
You dashed away so suddenly.
Yeah. It's because I could see the town of Liaon.
Our village is beyond that town and
the mountain behind it. Right, Friend?
Yeah.
If we walk two more days,
we'll be there.
I bet Nina is waiting for us eagerly.
Of course she is. The wedding can't start until you're back.
Thanks for everything.
I owe you one.
Come on, Friend.
Let me carry it now.
It's your precious little sister's bridal gown,
so take good care of it.
Sure. You really saved me
by tagging along.
Oh, come on, now.
It's not even worth mentioning.
Executions!
Five more today!
What was that about?
They kill the innocent!
Executions!
Poor girls...
What cruelty!
Ah, the gods save us all.
Mister, what did those women do?
They haven't done anything.
Yet they'll receive capital punishment for no crime.
So they haven't done anything?
Why execute them, then?
It's the king's order.
This king of the Liaon Empire
sees treason everywhere.
All who even dare to gossip about him
receive capital punishment.
How can he be that cruel?
I'll see the king and stop him!
Wait, Melos!
You go there, and then what?
Relax! Give it a rest, Melos!
Let me go!
I can't!
Mom!
Mom...
You can't do that!
Give Mom back!
Give me back my mom!
Now I definitely must stop them!
Melos, stop! Calm down, Melos!
Melos...
I'm the King of Liaon!
Did you interfere with the executions?!
I never forgive those who disobey me!
Why did you interfere?! Answer me!
King!
Why are you killing innocent people?
Why do you distrust everyone?
Why do I distrust them?
Because humans are a treacherous breed!
I distrust them because
I can't believe them! That's all!
And I kill those I can't trust!
Nothing is more embarrassing than distrusting the hearts of others!
Shut up! Shut up!
King... Why are you like that?
Shut up! Don't you know
what "shut up" means?!
Humans can't live
without trusting each other.
If the king believes in his people,
the people will believe in the king!
You can pay lip service
to those ideals all you want!
But deep down, everyone's heart is corrupt.
Yours too, just like those
in this morning's execution lineup!
I'm not like that, King!
And a liar too! At least try to come up
with something more plausible.
When you're on the cross,
a tearful apology will be of no use!
If you want to apologize,
now's the time!
I'm not going to apologize!
Interesting. Take him away!
Yes, sir!
Nina...
What are you waiting for?
Throw him into a cell!
Yes, sir!
Move it!
King...
King, if I may ask,
please give me just a day.
I implore you to stay my execution for just a day!
I absolutely need to see my sister first
and give her this wedding dress.
Not happening!
I beg you, King!
My sister is waiting for my return
beyond the nearest mountain.
I will see her once
and then come right back!
I beg you!
Like hell I'd allow that, you fraud!
I don't trust anyone!
Who'd be dumb enough to come back to die when given a chance to run for the hills?
I'll never let you play me!
King, please let him go.
King, I will be Melos's stand-in.
I will be your hostage
until Melos comes back.
Friend?
Should Melos fail to come back,
then I'll humbly accept the death penalty.
Please, King.
King, please.
I like it. You're willing to sacrifice yourself for your friend's sake?
Very well!
Is that true? Thank you, sir!
Friend, no! You can't stand in for me!
Melos, you just need to give this
to your sister, right?
You two are the only children in your family,
so you must go, Melos. Go now!
Friend...
All right! Be back by sunset
the day after tomorrow.
The belfry bells chime
five times at sunset.
If you're not back by the time the bells stop chiming, Friend will lose his life!
Melos...
Nina!
Thank you, Melos.
You're beautiful, Nina.
Very well.
If you're not back by the time the belfry bells chime five times, Friend will die!
Friend, wait for me.
I will surely come back!
What's the matter, Melos?
Melos! Where are you going?
Nina, live on and be happy!
Melos! Don't go, Melos!
If you value your life,
you don't have to come back.
That way you will be saved.
Don't you value your life?
Melos, why are you hesitating?
If you value your life at all,
why bother coming back?
I can't run as fast as I want in this rain.
It's hopeless!
There's no way I can return in time!
If I can't get there in time,
I might as well turn back now.
Melos, you just need to give this
to your sister, right?
You two are the only children in your family,
so you must go, Melos.
I made a promise. Friend believed in me
and volunteered to stand in for me.
Friend... Here I come!
The hour of reckoning
is almost upon us.
I wonder if Melos, whom you believed in, will really come.
Whether you believe
in your friend is up to you.
But I don't see why Melos
would come back.
If he doesn't make it in time, you'll die!
If he wanted to save you,
he'd be here by now.
But Melos won't come back!
Why would he come back just to get killed?
Prepare for an execution!
Yes, sir!
There's no reason for Melos to return?
Are you saying Melos betrayed me?
But if Melos doesn't come...
If he doesn't come...
King, I... I...
Why are you looking that pale now?
You must have started doubting
that Melos would come back too!
Very well. Get on your knees
and beg for my pardon!
Admit that friendship is but an illusion!
All who trust others are fools!
Nonsense! Melos will come.
I know he will!
Melos will surely be back.
I believe in Melos!
Melos!
Nina!
Just a dream?
Oh no! I've completely lost track of time.
The sun... The sun is setting!
Friend, no matter how long we wait,
Melos won't come!
Melos played you. He betrayed you!
Believing in others is utter folly!
Let your death be a lesson to everyone!
What is Melos doing?
Poor fellow.
Another one will lose his life today.
Give up already. The sun has almost set!
And when it does, the bells will start chiming.
After the fifth chime, you'll die!
Mom!
He's here!
It's Melos!
He came back!
I can see him too!
It's Melos! Melos is back!
Melos!
He really is back!
Thank the gods!
That's right, King!
If you're going to kill, kill me!
How is this possible?
Melos!
M-Melos!
Friend!
Friend...
Hit me as hard as you can.
I was about to give up on returning.
I was about to betray you!
Melos, please forgive me.
I doubted you in my heart.
I wasn't sure you were
going to come back.
Friend!
Melos!
Wait!
You two trusted each other
from the bottom of your hearts.
I see now. I was wrong.
Thank the gods!
The king will stop killing people!
Hooray!
You did well!
Friend!
Translation &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
Nemesis
Paul Geromini
Omar Hidan