Now on Sale   !
BAKERY
Wait, you!
Haijima Akira
What? What's this?!
Kid.
Kansai Akisada Group Underboss
Bito
You dared to lay hands
on the boss's daughter.
You think you're gonna
get away with that?
You jerk, don't look down on us!
You brat!
How dare you mock us!
What are you doing? After him!
Y-Yes, sir!
That brat. If we catch him,
I'll kill him for sure! This way!
Yes, sir!
I'm definitely not welcome in Osaka!
Mellow
Orphan Fansubs presents
Tokyo, Yamanote Ward
HAIJIMA
Miss Akira.
Miss Akira?
Miss Akira!
It's Hiroshi. I'm trying to forget him,
but I just can't.
Haijima Family Servant
Ichiji Banji
I am profoundly sorry for your loss.
However, you need to begin working as a teacher
Haijima Family Servant
Ichiji Banji
at Hanamaru High School,
starting tomorrow.
Haijima Akira
No way. I can't climb the teacher's podium feeling like this.
But Miss Akira...
An old guy would never understand how a dumped woman feels!
How I feel, abandoned by the man I love...
Leave me alone, please!
Sir, if this continues,
we won't uphold the Haijima family motto,
which is, "Don't let the flame of teaching die out."
What should I do-
Hey, Ichiji!
That voice.
Ah... Master Akira!
Hey, Ichiji. Still kicking?
How rude! Talking like that when you've been away for two long years.
You were on my mind every single day!
I'm thirsty. Get me a cold beer.
You spent two whole years
flitting around aimlessly.
Don't tell me off like a dog!
You've been wandering around like a stray dog,
doing nothing useful whatsoever!
Ichiji, enough lecturing.
Lend me 500,000 yen!
Why do you need such a sum?
I'm tired of living
in this cramped country.
Thought I should try
going abroad for a while.
500,000! Do me this favor!
I will not.
You have the Haijima family fortune at your disposal,
which was passed to us
through generations!
Mr. Akira, by my name of Ichiji Banji,
how many times have I told you already?
Marker: Haijima Family Grave
The Haijima family has featured
a long line of educators.
Those who will not master
the teaching trade
cannot claim even a single yen
from the inheritance.
Your late father specified
that in his last will.
Oh come on, don't be so stingy.
I know, Ichiji!
Why don't we split the inheritance?
How could you ever come up with such a horrible idea?!
If we do as I say, we'll throw
a massive party for your funeral!
I'd be more than happy if only Miss Akira attended my funeral, even in secret.
I beg you! My life depends
on this! 400,000!
Even 300,000 would do!
Very well. I will give you a million.
A million?!
But there is something
I want you to do for me.
I'll do it! I will! I'll do anything!
What should I do?
Massage your shoulders?
Or perhaps, massage your waist?
Kill someone?!
Or could it be...
Gulp!
Don't tell me, Ichiji,
your bush got out of hand?
I'd be delighted to tickle it for you!
I want you to act as
a stand-in for Miss Akira!
Don women's clothes and
become a teacher in her place.
You'll work at Hanamaru High School.
In women's clothes? A teacher?
You believe it's impossible?
In that case, I'll keep the million...
W-Wait a minute!
W-Well, I never said I refuse!
Is that so? You'll accept this assignment?
What a relief. A relief.
Shit! Making me waste
my time like this.
The Next Day
Master Akira, that's a rather impressive transformation.
Shut up!
I'm sorry I have to ask
this of you, Akira.
It's fine. After all, it's only for three days, remember?
Use that time to forget him.
Okay.
Ichiji, a million, remember?
I'll strangle you
if you break your promise!
Right, right! In exchange, please take
every precaution to ensure
that no one finds out you're a man!
I know that! Being a woman teacher is a piece of cake!
Oh dear. Dog poop.
That's because you don't know when to shut up!
Venting your anger on me
isn't very manly.
What? Are you saying I'm unmanly 'cause I'm like this?!
You... You must absolutely never show
such a strikingly manly face!
When you flip out because of your short temper,
your face becomes manlier than ever.
You must never lose your temper!
It's okay to show this face?
I believe so.
By the way, Ichiji.
What am I supposed to teach them?
English, sir.
I see. A while ago, I lived with a girl
from America for six months, so I'll figure something out.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
You do H to her so that she does I!
Just Kidding!
Well, I'm off!
It's hopeless. I'm already worried sick.
A groper? Even though he has
the face of an office clerk.
Think I'll let you do it without a squeak?
Wh-What?
What do you think you’re doing?
N-No way! You're an okama?
I wonder what in the world
happened here.
I was too optimistic.
He'll last a couple of hours, at most.
Private High School
Hanamaru
Friendship. Hard work.
Hanamaru Private High School Principal
Ikebe Kokichi
Benevolence. Those are our school's core principles.
That's clear, right? Also...
Ah... Crap! I gotta bear myself as a girl.
Ah, my bad. I'm just getting a bit nervous.
Either way, please do your best
as a proud and self-aware educator.
Okay.
Kurohara, what class is
Miss Haijima in charge of?
Class B of year two, sir.
Haijima
Akira
That's my name. Nice to meet you.
Haijima
Akira
Akira?
Akira, like in Maeda Akira?
A guy's name!
Aw, shucks! I wrote
my version of the name.
Akira          (male)
Akira         (female)
Ha ha... Some dangling bits here.
Calm down. I can't afford to lose my cool.
Remember the million yen!
A cutter, huh?
Good for sharpening pencils,
but you can use it like this too!
Oh! Amazing! She nailed a fly with it!
W-Wow!
Getting this fly was no big deal.
Teacher!
Give me back my cutter, okay?
Fuwa Raiya
So it was yours?
By the way, that's an impressive scar!
With that, getting a job will be easy!
What was that?
Every yakuza gang will have you down
as their #1 draft choice!
I appreciate the compliment.
Those fightin' words'll increase my clout even more.
My, how scary.
If you think that, maybe I should scar your other cheek as well.
Very well.
Try to do it if you can.
I'd be glad to get scarred
by a sweet chick like you.
Wow!
You cow!
Think you can get away with using a blade on a defenseless student?!
But you said you'd be glad to get it,
so I did it for you.
Haijima
Akira
No need to get so worked up!
Haijima
Akira
Who the hell is this woman?
RECEPTION OFFICE
I see. She clashed with Fuwa right away?
Fuwa won't just let it slide silently!
After all, he's the worst troublemaker in our school!
Her predecessor, Hiraga,
didn't know what to do about Fuwa.
School Life Director
Anamizu Kuzo
Vice principal. At this rate, Haijima is sure to do something else soon.
If that happens, the principal
who hired her will be in deep doo-doo.
Vice Principal
Kurohara Noboru
That means your next principal's assignment isn't far off!
Anamizu, don't go around saying things like that so frivolously.
I beg your pardon!
That upstart new teacher!
She didn't know that mentioning Fuwa's scar really sets him off.
Yet she talked about it so brazenly!
And what about you?
No, it was just a slip of the tongue.
Look here.
In her next class, I'll cross her up.
Sounds like fun!
I'm bursting with excitement!
Let's go!
Make way or we'll beat the shit out of you!
Study Hall
Her first class is study hall?
That broad ain't no ordinary egg. Shit!
NO TRESPASSING
Protected Pond; students okay
Hanamaru Private High School
Seriously, man...
How did I end up doing something as stupid
as dealing with a bunch of smelly brats?
Thanks to all this beer, I'm overflowing.
Huh?
Jeez. Being a woman sure is inconvenient.
There, that's how you get rid of it!
Ah! That's better.
It's a student!
How long have you been there?
A long time.
Then you saw it?
Yes. I saw it all.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Oh no. He'll leverage this and
blackmail me to the end of the world.
In this school, the discipline is very strict,
for students and teachers alike.
If they learn about this,
they'll give you the boot for sure.
They'll fire me if my secret is leaked,
no doubt about it.
Did you say something?
Ah, no, nothing.
Teacher, have you ever thought about wanting to die?
I haven't.
I only think about dying, day after day.
After all, nothing in this life
brings me joy anyhow.
You're a high school student, bound hand and foot with rules and studying.
How is that supposed to bring you joy?
A life of joy is an adults' privilege.
If you don't know that,
you won't get to try the best things in life.
I can't understand
why you'd even consider suicide.
If I had a happy-go-lucky mindset like you, I'd be carefree too.
This guy... By "happy-go-lucky," you mean "stupid," don't you,
you depressed shrimp?
Still, I'm so depressed that I can't muster enough courage to kill myself.
Now, please leave. Or else I'll tell
everyone what happened earlier.
I'll tell... I'll tell...
You wanna die that badly?
Then go ahead!
You idiot! I can't swim!
Like a stone, right?
Someone! Help me!
Help me!
That voice...
Hey, you...
Hey, you! Hurry up and die! Die!
If you're a man,
get that out of your head!
What's that bitch Haijima doing?
Probably trying to save Yamazaki?
No, she's beating him up.
Help me.
I'm sorry!
I won't tell anyone you cut classes to drink beer!
Huh? Beer?
So he didn't see my willy?
And I got so worked up!
Oh my!
MEDICAL OFFICE
Yamazaki, we have eyewitness accounts.
Yamazaki, we want you
to tell us the truth.
Teacher Haijima saved me.
But the rumors say she tried to sink you with a bamboo pole before saving you.
No. Teacher Haijima taught me,
a suicidal neurotic,
the beauty and preciousness of life.
I owe my life to teacher Haijima.
She is the supreme teacher.
I'm in a cold sweat already, I swear!
Thank you.
Give me two more days.
I'll be ready to go.
Still, you're quite a pitiful woman, sis,
if Dad's will constrains you like that.
You think so?
"Don't let the Haijima family's flame for teaching die out."
That determination to uphold the will
caused Yoshida Hiroshi,
your true love, to dump you.
Please don't inflict any further distress on Miss Akira.
Well, you'd be better off just going about your life,
doing whatever you please,
like I do, big sis!
Miss Akira's path in life
is nothing like yours.
Did you say something?
No. Nothing, sir.
All right, how about I go get drunk?!
Pub Tama-chan
Hey! My snacks are late!
Sorry for the wait!
Girl, that's a nice ass you got!
Oh my, how dirty!
It's fine! Bring me another drink!
What a showy "old fart girl"!
I'm really annoyed.
First period is Haijima's English class.
Kumiko, I bet you can catch her off-guard with your returnee's English.
Okay. I'll humiliate her like
she's never felt before.
Good morning, everybody!
Are you doing all right?
Then, let's start, okay?
Teacher, before you start,
I have a question.
Go ahead, whatever it is.
Before you start the class, will you explain your teaching method and policy,
in contrast with the present Japanese educational system, in English?
Also, I want you to compare and contrast
the Japan bashing
and mole hammering, please
She was jabbering at amazing speed.
I couldn't understand a word!
She's the bane of an English teacher,
a returnee alpha-girl.
Now, what'll you do, teacher girl?
You'll lose face if you admit you didn't understand it!
What did you just say?
Don't play dumb.
Look, look! I couldn't hear you
because of this giant piece of earwax!
She’s trying to fool us now.
She didn't understand
and is trying to talk her way out.
Don't try to fool us!
What kind of English teacher are you?!
We boycott you! Boycott!
Boycott! Boycott! Boycott!
Boycott! Boycott! Boycott! Boycott! Boycott! Boycott...
I'm at the limit of my patience!
But for my million yen...
Oh! If you're Japanese, how about you ask your questions in Japanese?
Now you've done it.
This isn't a joke anymore.
Wh-Who? Who did it?
I can't take it anymore.
I don't care who did it.
I'm mad as a hornet!
Teacher.
Please use this.
Thank you.
The guy who threw the egg just now...
If he doesn't come clean,
I'll make him pay tenfold!
Teacher, please don't change the subject.
Aren't you just frustrated at not understanding my English?
What was that, you cunt?
Getting carried away
'cause you talk well?
Really, you can't speak English at all.
Shut up!
Hey, bitch! I'll stab you in the butthole
and get your shit out and clean you up!
You are my hostile. Want me to murder your butt again? Huh?!
What did she say?
Kumiko, try to translate.
No way. I can't translate that.
Amazing!
She spoke so fast the returnee couldn't make it out.
Probably on the level of a professor of English literature or higher!
I can't translate it. It's too obscene.
That was a close call.
The English a foreign woman taught me
a while ago finally came in handy.
Oh! Akira, I'm coming! Coming!
C-Crap!
Excuse me for a moment!
What's going on?
Maybe her period?
Really?
Make way, make way!
Men's Room
Ah! I forgot again!
I'm a woman now! Stop it!
Tsk. Missed my chance to enter the women's restroom.
You're my friend,
so I didn't give you away.
That's why I offered her a towel.
You're the only witness there is.
If you're my friend, you won't tell anyone, Takano.
But really, she's such a pretty teacher.
You didn't have to go that far.
What's so special about her being pretty?
A woman's looks and her true self are vastly different.
Women are all like that.
They hide their vile selves
under a layer of makeup.
All adult women are foul!
I understand that you still can't forgive your mother.
Don't mention her!
Do it again and you'll regret it!
All right, I got it.
So the culprit is Miyata?
Unforgivable!
STAFF ROOM
STUDENT
REGISTER.
BY CLASS..
STUDENT
REGISTER.
BY CLASS..
Miyata Fumio. Grades are about average?
Did Miyata do something
again, Miss Haijima?
Mr. Sokura!
Back in first year, he used to be
a good, honorable student.
What's his deal? I didn't ask anything.
He just started talking.
What happened then is...
Apparently, he saw his mother having an affair, with his own eyes.
Due to his severe Oedipus complex,
Miyata had harbored a profound hatred for all woman ever since.
Especially for older women.
Hey, Miyata. Ms. Haijima wants to see you.
Go to the warehouse by the court.
You ratted me out, didn't you?
No way!
Couldn't she have figured it out?
Well, I'll play innocent.
Teacher Haijima! Miyata here.
Yes, come in.
But man, why this warehouse?
Teacher, you want something from me?
Take this!
Why was I waiting in the warehouse?
Well, simply because it's dark in here.
Ouch... What are you doing?
You think it's acceptable to use violence?!
It's not violence, it's punishment.
No, that's still too fancy a word.
It's simple revenge!
What for...
Ask your own conscience.
Nothing comes to mind.
Why, you...
M-Maybe I threw an egg or something-
Well, well, look who's spilling the beans!
Please stop.
It's not my fault. It's all Mama's!
Why would Mama have an affair?
This isn't about who
your mother sleeps with!
I don't give a shit about your family!
She not only had an affair,
she tried to hide it from us.
She pretended to be a good mother and a good wife!
I couldn't stand that nauseating hypocrisy!
That's how I became
distrustful of all women.
Don't care.
Forgive me, Teacher!
Remember this lesson!
Please stop! I won't disobey you ever again!
It hurts! Women are really scary, jeez!
Hey, Miyata.
What happened to you?
I-I fell down the emergency stairs.
Don't play dumb.
Haijima did this to you, didn't she?
N-No, it's not like that. I just...
That swelling means you didn't fall down the stairs. You got beat up!
I can tell the difference, y'know!
I fell down the stairs! It's the truth!
Any witnesses?
It's true! Ah!
The Next Day
Today's my last day of work.
Tomorrow, I'm flying abroad and having fun with all sorts of girls, even the redheads!
Hey! Looks like you've recovered a lot.
Yes. Thank you, Akira.
I'll take over starting tomorrow.
That's a relief. Where's Ichiji?
Maybe the tatami room?
Ichiji, have you prepared
the million yen yet?
Yes. It is prepared.
That's a relief too!
Now that you've become a support for the family,
Master and Missus would've been delighted too. I have no doubt.
Therefore, please endure it
for one more day. That's all I ask.
I know, all right?
I ain't giving up on my million.
I'm off!
Take care!
I'm counting on you, Master Akira!
Please, look after Master Akira.
OFFERINGS
Help him make it through today
and complete his critical role as Miss Akira, okay?
Hey. Gramps, you live around here?
Yes, I suppose.
Take a quick look at this.
You remember seeing
this man somewhere?
So, Gramps? You know him?
Yes... I think I've seen him,
but I can't remember where.
He's supposed to live in this city.
Name's Akira.
Akira, huh? Then, might I ask
what this noble young man did?
He corrupted our boss's daughter.
He won't get away with it.
The boss's daughter?
So you'll cut off his pinky?
We ain't stopping at just a finger.
We'll cut off his dick.
If you see him,
call this hotel, will ya?
Tokyo Green Hotel
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
Kansai Akisada Group
Underboss
Bito Kazumasa
No doubt about it. It is Master Akira.
Of all people, the yakuza are chasing him?
So that's why he returned
from his journeys a few days ago.
He agreed to act as Miss Akira's stand-in so easily.
He also willingly accepted wearing women's clothes.
I wonder what he's going to do from tomorrow on.
Yes. You'll do just fine without memorizing these words.
But they're engraved in our minds now!
We can't forget them!
T-Teacher...
What is it?
I... I have a sudden stomachache.
Huh?
Fukatsu, you sly bastard. You just wanna ogle some D-cups. That's lame.
Will you be all right?
I'm sure I'll get better if I rest in the infirmary for a while.
Can I go?
All right. I'll carry you there myself!
There's no need!
Silence!
She's awfully strong.
Teacher, really, there's no need!
Teacher, what should we do after we write them down?
Self-study!
Self-
Study
Teacher, I can go there myself! Really!
You can't cling to me forever!
A stomachache! More like a sonic belch!
That's rude!
INFIRMARY
PE TEACHER'S ROOM
Pardon the intrusion!
Huh? Away?
Tsk. Not here?
Teacher, you can just leave me here.
Oh! It's been so long since
I slept on an infirmary bed!
To battle.
Ah, so comfortable.
I-I shouldn't look...
You should lie down too.
You have a stomachache, right?
N-No, I'm fine.
Come on, lie down, you!
I'm fine, teacher!
There, there!
P-Please stop, teacher!
Hey! What are you two doing?!
What the-
I-It's not what you think, Ms. Matsunae!
My stomach hurts,
so I came here to rest...
PE Teacher
Matsunae Utako
Then, you there.
Why do you need to lie down?
Well, that's what beds are for.
I do it all the time
at department stores.
Oh ho? Are you Haijima, the newbie teacher everyone's talking about?
Yes. Haijima Akira.
Oh!
Nice to meet you.
Oh my...
Huh? What about your stomach?
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Oh? Weren't you holding the other side before?
Ah? No... I was... It's here...
Just kidding.
You malingerer!
Return to the classroom at once!
Shoo. Shoo.
Okay, Fukatsu. Here's your
digestive medicine.
Ms. Haijima! What's the meaning of this?
Ah, that kid was just malingering.
Really, kids nowadays.
Then... please return
to the classroom too.
Very well!
By the way, Ms. Matsunae,
they say you hold an incredible record in the 100-meter dash.
I wouldn't call it incredible...
But on short distance runs,
I'd imagine you lose a lot of time...
when your bust is sloshing right and left!
What the hell is she doing?
We've got a bed, so I might as well do her right here!
Get out!
If only I'd found out
about her a day sooner,
I'd probably be nibbling
those D-cups already!
Forgive me, Akira.
At this rate, I won't be able to forget Hiroshi, no matter how much time passes.
Unless I go to his place in the US
and tell him off directly,
I can't let go of my feelings.
I can't start my new life.
Selfish as it may be,
I can't give up my place as a teacher.
Please keep up the role
for ten more days.
That's it. I'm done! Nothing's gonna burden my mind anymore!
Nothing...
Oh?
SWIMMING CLUB
They got a swimming club too?
I'll just peek inside quickly.
Girls Swim Club - No Practice Today
Are you kidding me?!
Today, of all days!
Girls Swim Club - No Practice Today
Might still take a peek or two.
A school swimsuit, isn't it?
Oh, it smells so good!
Ms. Matsunae!
Ms. Haijima?
You're swimming too?
No, just inspecting the school.
Inspecting the school.
If you'd excuse me,
I need to change now.
Go ahead!
What a perfectly plump breast!
Ms. Haijima!
Oh my!
Are you okay?
I don't care anymore.
I could die right here.
Now, then.
Have you guys seen my swimsuit?
Pretty sure I left it around here.
Ah! There is it.
Thank goodness! Nobody snatched it.
Excuse me!
BLARGH
H-Hang on, Ms. Haijima!
D-Damn it.
Master Akira, you have
every right to be angry.
But you need to consider
Miss Akira's feelings too.
Consider my dilemma as well.
Shut up!
Are you kidding? Why should I overlook you two breaking your promises?!
What's more, you want me
to just keep going?
I thought if I was nice to my big sister, she'd reciprocate!
Damn you! Shit! Shit!
Master Akira, calm down!
It's just ten days!
She said she'd be back in ten days!
Never! Never! I kept my promise and did it for three days! Let me go!
Right, right. Exactly so.
Perhaps I should hand over
the promised million.
Thanks a bunch!
I'll be over in Brazil tomorrow!
Bye, then. You just have to submit
a letter of resignation to the school.
See you!
Actually, Master Akira...
A yakuza underboss from the Kansai Akisada group approached me today.
Wh-Why're you associating
with the Akisada group?
No. They showed me a picture of you,
Master, and asked whether I'd met
a man like that in our city.
So what did you say?
About whether I'd seen that young man?
And?
I said I'd get in touch with them if anything came to mind.
If they find him, they'll cut off
his manhood, not his pinky.
My dick? Ichiji, are you threatening me right now?
Of course not! I'm just saying that
I sympathize with you.
Losing your manhood so young
would be the end of the world.
Ichiji, what's your point?
To sum up, for ten more days,
at least until Miss Akira returns,
I'd like you to continue as her stand-in.
And if I refuse?
I'll call the Akisada gang
and tell them all about you.
You must choose between cross-dressing or losing your dick. What's your choice?
Either means giving up your masculinity!
I'll take out this uncontrollable anger on my students instead!
Do this honestly and don't try to cheat!
Or you'll regret it later!
Start!
Fuwa.
Put your hands on the desk.
H-How did she know?
Chiji Rege, unroll the sleeve of your shirt.
S-Sorry.
Okubo, look at your own test!
Kokubu Kumiko, showing it is cheating too.
Tch.
Does Haijima have eyes
in the back of her head too?
A teacher's mirror. It's as simple as that.
Break Time
Anyway, I'll be lenient and overlook your cheating this time around.
But I have a condition.
What the hell is that condition?
Come on! Put more spirit into it!
Okubo, you don't have as much strength
as you have weight, boy!
It feels great! As if I was a queen!
Fuwa, polish it more diligently!
Haijima, you wench, you're about to have the tables turned on you!
Hey, hey! Don't slack off, shoulders department!
You've suddenly gotten much better at it!
Mm! Feels good!
Serves you right.
Ms. Haijima, I'd like to talk to you
in the vice-principal's room.
Haijima, what do you think is teaching is all about?
Up until now, I've turned a blind eye to your escapades,
because you're the daughter of our principal's former teacher. But I'm fed up!
I'm bring this up at the staff meeting after school!
Just you wait. You'll get
what's coming to you!
I wonder how Haijima will avoid
the vice-principal's wrath
at the staff meeting.
She can't escape. She'll get sacked.
I don't have enough self-confidence
to make it through the staff meeting.
CONFERENCE ROOM
And now, the first topic
is countering the rampant thefts of female students' bloomers.
IKARI
DESKS
Ikari Desks here!
IKARI
DESKS
OFFICE ROOM
We've been waiting!
We've brought 40 new desks and chairs.
Here's the packing list.
Each incident revs up my anger more,
and my super-manly face shows through!
Uh, sorry.
Oh, I'm busy, so busy.
Wait, you. You think
"Sorry" will be enough?!
A guy?!
A guy or not, you're a damn dimwit!
Hang in there!
I'm so screwed.
Here. It's here.
I saw Ms. Haijima suddenly attack Mr. Kase physically!
How outrageous!
Principal, this incident is certain to become a big scandal!
Principal, what should we do?
Please take a look at this.
This man was the bloomer thief!
We caught him thanks to Ms. Haijima.
Well, Ms. Haijima! You did well to avert the danger! Thank you.
No...
The winds have changed.
We'll do it next time.
Amazing! Such a distinct panty line!
Give it back, please!
What's interesting about
watching another woman?
I'll tell you a secret about Matsunae!
Huh? What's that?
This is just a rumor among the teachers,
but when Ms. Matsunae gets drunk,
her personality suddenly changes!
Like, she stops hating men?
She loses her composure, somehow.
She doesn't react her usual way.
Apparently, she won't reject any man
when she's in that state!
No way! She told me herself
she'd never even held hands with a man.
She forgets it all afterward!
A chance. This is my chance.
Now the only question is
how to lure her into a bar.
All right. We'll go see a movie.
Cinema
BIG ROMANCE
FOR TWO WOMEN
Cinema
BIG ROMANCE
FOR TWO WOMEN
Have a meal.
RESTAURANT
Eventually, I'll casually
lure her into a bar.
While she's drunk,
I'll look for a good time
to transform from Akira into Akira.
I'll say, "My sister asked me
to look after you."
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
Then we'll go to a hotel
and enjoy our youth!
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
OFFICE
.BUILDING
Hotel Saka
I'll make her on my own, unopposed!
All right. I don't have plans for tonight.
Let's do it!
Cinema
Two Women
A few hours later
A Romantic Masterpiece
Morning of Love
Ah, that was fun!
A Romantic Masterpiece
Morning of Love
Hey, Ms. Matsunae,
what do you wanna eat?
Ms. Haijima...
Actually, I'd like to ask you for a favor.
I want to pick up a guy.
What was that?
But I thought you hate men and all!
Yes. That's exactly why.
I don't get it. Why?
I actually intended to keep
avoiding them, but I'm 22 already.
I guess it's strange for me
to still hate men.
Half of my students are boys, after all.
SARI ROAD
You're very open with men,
and I've come to know you well.
SARI ROAD
I thought this might be my only chance! Therefore...
Better not think too hard about it.
Just drink some booze
and open yourself up.
If I rely on alcohol to overcome my shyness,
won't that get me in trouble at school?
But don't you want to hit on a guy?
It's disgusting to think about any man.
Except me.
Hang on a moment, you two.
Would you have tea with us?
Or maybe something stronger?
What a windfall.
I'll let these guys treat us to dinner,
get Matsunae drunk,
and then transform into Akira!
And that's how it was!
I laughed so hard!
Is something wrong, guys?
Well...
Ah... Ah, she's not really mad, just nervous because she's a bit inexperienced.
Is that so?
Would you like one more glass?
I'm good.
That miniskirt keeps ordering
the most expensive stuff.
It'll cost us a fortune.
And the busty one is unapproachable.
Maybe we should split them up?
That's what I thought.
Should we use that on the miniskirt?
Yeah.
Mixed with alcohol,
it'll knock her out at once!
Powerful
TRANQUILIZER
Oh? Where's Ms. Akira?
My friend offered to drive her home, so they went to the car.
They left together?
Which hotel should I drive you to...
You wanna drink something?
How about orange juice?
Sure...
Master,
a screwdriver for the lady.
Okay... you villain.
Geez...
I hit my head.
Woke up, after all?
Huh? Where's Matsunae?
Independent action!
She's having a good time back there too.
Did you put something in my drink?
Isn't it all the same to you?
We're both adults. Let's enjoy ourselves.
We could do that on a revolving bed.
Right?
Eck! A man!
Turn back at once, you stupid parasite!
A-All right!
When Matsunae gets sufficiently drunk,
she loses her composure
and won't reject anyone, they say...
Why the hell did you stop, asshole?!
The traffic light...
You think you're in a position to stop at a red signal?
Got it!
What's wrong? Would you like
to catch some fresh air outside?
Yes.
Come on! Get out right now,
you scumbag!
I'm sorry! My head's spinning!
Well done. Take care of this one too!
Forgive us!
Men that try to make women into objects with their dirty hands are the worst!
Ms. Matsunae becomes violent
rather than lewd.
Drunkenness takes her hatred of men to a whole new level.
I'll show this one too!
F-Forgive me...
They probably don't have to go that far.
Haijima is a monster
wearing a woman's skin.
No, a bitch. A bitch!
Ms. Akira!
Ms. Matsunae!
I truly hate men, after all!
Women are the best, aren't they?
You bitch.
I'll unmask you one day!
And so, the two pickup artists reportedly devoted their souls to God.
Translation
Translation Check
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Rezo
anonymous