About 300 years ago,
in the Italian town of Cremona,
there was a man who worked devotedly
to plant a maple forest.
When 20 to 30 years had passed,
he used the maple wood to create
wonderful sounding violins.
That man's name was Antonio Stradivari.
The more than 2,000 violins, cellos,
and other stringed instruments he made
are called Stradivarius.
They are some of the finest instruments,
coveted by the world's greatest performers.
"I'll make a violin like Stradivari too!"
That was the ambitious dream of a certain boy, living in rural Japan 70 years ago.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Starry Sky Violin
GRADE 6 BOYS GROUP
Homeroom Teacher: Otsuki
Early
Showa
Period
Present day,
Nakano City,
Nagano Prefecture
Hey, carve it more carefully!
O-Okay...
Oh? What do you have there?
He's good at it!
Almost like an apprentice!
Quiet.
Awesome!
Nagano Area Exhibition
Excellent handicrafts                                         from elementary schools
Best Work
Ozawa Kikuji
Well, it seems they've chosen your work
as the best one in my class.
It makes me proud too!
Hey, congratulations, Ozawa-kun.
Ah, Vice Principal.
Thank you.
How about it, boy?
Why don't you go to a technical school
and continue studying the craft?
But I have poor grades,
and I hate studying,
so they'd never let me
into a technical school.
That's why you need to study hard,
not just in art, writing,
and calligraphy,
but also in arithmetic,
sciences, and Japanese.
If you give it your all,
you can pass any exam.
Vice Principal, I don't think school
is the only place to study.
To further his gift, Kikuji could become an apprentice at a local wood factory.
Like becoming an apprentice
to a carpenter or a decorator.
But if you graduate from technical school,
you can get hired by a serious company,
become a great engineer,
and build a wonderful career.
But I have to take over
farming from my father...
Aren't you the second son
in your family?
Yes.
Well, Otsuki-sensei will meet your family
and talk it through with them.
Sound good, Ozawa-kun?
What are we going to do, honey?
If it's for Kikuji's future,
we'll make do, one way or another.
If we also work harder,
we'll be able to keep the farm going.
Kikuji will work the land
with everyone else.
That's what we settled on.
Sorry, Kikuji.
Brother...
Unlike me, my brother has good grades.
Once he graduates from technical school,
he'll be able to get a job wherever he wants, like Nagano or Nagoya.
That's why they decided
I'd take over the farm.
So that's what happened?
Don't worry. You can find time to study,
even while working on the farm.
No, because you'll be a farmer,
you must study even harder.
Okay.
All right, I'll bring you along as a reward for winning the grand prize, Kikuji.
Sign: Violin Concert, Hibikino Yurie
"Chaconne" (Bach)
That was my first time
listening to a violin.
Did you like it, Kikuji?
I did. I loved it!
Right, good to know.
Kikuji, you can understand
the language of music.
What's the language of music?
The composer who wrote the music,
the musician who played the music,
the trembling sound of the violin—
they all wanted to speak
to you through music,
with the language of music,
the only one they know.
You grasped it with your heart.
My heart, sir?
Yes. That's right.
How much does a violin cost?
Whoa there.
Are you really considering buying one?
I want to play the violin too.
I don't know.
For people like us, even the cheapest violin
out there isn't easy to come by.
This is the structure of a violin.
It has four strings.
The vibrations of those strings resonate
with its empty frame to produce a sound.
Brother!
Dad is calling for you.
Ah! What are you doing?
Hey, what are you building?
A violin.
And what do you need a vilyn for?
Stop bothering me!
If you don't come soon,
Dad will scold you.
Sorry I'm late!
What were you doing?!
A vilyn!
Vilyn? What's that?
A violin, a European instrument.
Oh, European?
Vilyn or whatever else, we can't have you
get distracted by your toys all day!
It sounds terrible.
Well, I can't exactly call it a splendid violin,
but it's impressive all the same!
Teacher, please show me a real violin.
A real violin?
I want to make a real violin.
I want to know what a real violin sounds like.
Yes, I'm counting on you.
Otsuki-sensei, some of the parents
have been saying you always favor
Ozawa Kikuji and overlook the other kids.
No, I don't focus all my efforts
on Kikuji alone.
I simply want to help that child
grow his talent. That's all.
I understand that, but please pay attention to the others.
If possible, please grant this boy his wish.
I beg you!
That's all we ask for.
Please.
I don't know.
It's a valuable item, you know.
Only for a day, that's more than enough.
Please, if you can...
Please.
Oh, you're making me feel bad, Otsuki.
Only for today, then.
What are you doing, you fool?
Two years later
Teacher, here it is.
Oh? This violin came out nicely.
Here you go.
Wow! It sounds majestic!
The tone is right there.
Yes, it sounds quite good indeed.
You think so?
Kikuji, how about we show this violin
to the music professor?
Huh? Are you serious?
Did you manufacture this?
Yes.
I see.
What do you think, Professor?
This isn't a violin.
It is a violin in form.
But this is merely an imitation.
But it sounds like a violin should.
No, this isn't the sound of a violin.
A true violin must have...
A richer sound.
"Meditation" from Thaïs (Massenet)
Making a violin is not that easy.
We're sorry for wasting your time.
Thank you.
Ozawa...
Kikuji, it was my fault.
I underestimated how difficult it really was.
I won't be trying to make violins anymore!
What are saying now?
Kikuji, once a man sets his mind on something,
he sees it through until the end.
That's right.
I borrowed this for you.
It's Antonio Stradivari.
Stradivari...
Stradivari, the world's
most renowned violin maker.
Ozawa Kikuji, who only knew him by name,
was then able to see many different kinds of Stradivarius for the first time.
And what shook Kikuji the most was...
He's chopping the wood?
What does this mean?
Why not just saw it?
I see. It lets you preserve the wood in its natural state, like when it was still growing.
If you do that...
The natural wood makes the sound reverberate louder and longer.
If I force the wood into a shape,
it just swallows the sound and doesn't resonate.
I see! It's important to pay attention
to the cross grain when planing it down.
Thus, Kikuji learned the techniques
of violin making through trial and error.
Two more
years
have passed
Kikuji searched for trees such as fir
and spruce for the top,
and Fullmoon maple
and Palmate maple for the back.
He roamed the mountains, playing a tree lottery.
If I go this way... Huh?
That must be it.
Abe-san?
Yeah.
I'm Ozawa Kikuji.
A lumber shop in Nagano
recommended you to me.
They told me I could find some fine Fullmoon maple and Palmate maple here.
I need those exact woods to make a violin.
I need your help!
Well, come in for now.
Okay!
Eat first.
Gladly!
In fact, I was famished
by the time I got here.
Thanks a lot!
So what was it about the maple?
A violin is made by
gluing together wooden planks.
And for the back...
Fullmoon and Palmate maples are perfect.
Besides...
Dad?
U-Um...
Good morning.
G-Good morning...
Is it you, Kayo?
Dad, what's going on?
This guy came with such a funny request
that it kept me up all night.
You see, he came here looking for maple wood. He needs to get his hands on some.
I... came from Hiraoka Village in Nagano.
Name's Ozawa Kikuji.
You can call me Kayo.
Why do you need maple wood?
I'm making a violin.
A violin?
Do you like violins too?
I love them!
Oh, I see...
How about this one?
If the wood grain isn't dense enough,
the sound won't bounce back.
Are violins really that complicated?
The best Fullmoon and Palmate maples
grow on mountain slopes
with about a 35-degree incline,
where it snows heavily in the winter,
facing southeast to west from the summit.
Mountain slopes with about a 35-degree incline, facing southeast to west?
That's right.
Maples that grew up on such a slope
have grain that's clean and perfectly dense.
The sound they make is absolutely lovely.
Stradivari went as far as planting...
his own maple grove for that.
You mean the Stradivari?
Do you know Stradivari too?
Yes, only by name, though.
I will become a Japanese Stradivari.
That's my heart's resolve.
Ah, that's wonderful!
You really think so?
Of course!
I see. Thank you!
I chased after rabbits on that mountain.
"Hometown" (Words: Tatsunobu Takano,
Music: Teiichi Okano)
I fished for minnows in that river.
I still dream of those days even now.
Oh, how I miss my old country home.
Were you born here, Kayo-san?
Yes, but I've worked as a civil servant
in Nagoya for a while.
I was in the choir during that time.
I chased after rabbits on that mountain.
I fished for minnows in that river.
I still dream of those days even now.
Oh, how I miss my old country home.
Greetings. I'm sure you're still working
enthusiastically on your violin.
Here in the mountains, it's autumn already.
The maple trees are turning red all at once.
I'm praying that we will somehow find the good wood you're looking for.
I see.
No, really, Sensei...
Kikuji-san, you look
a lot more cheerful these days.
Is there some secret to it?
It's not exactly a secret.
Oh? What do you know?
Kikuji found himself a mate!
No... It's not that, Sensei!
Oh? You've just confirmed it!
Otsuki-san, a telegram for you!
Dear?
I got it. Coming!
Thanks, much obliged.
What is it, dear?
It's from my father in Nagoya.
I've got a conscription notice.
Conscription notice... with your name?
I'm to report to the Nagoya regiment's camp within the week.
Sensei...
Headline: Imperial Punitive Expeditionary Force Dispatched
Headline: Japanese Flag Flies over Baoding
At that time, Japan was expanding the war
Headline: Taiyuan Fully Occupied
from northeastern China, known as Manchuria, to the whole of China.
Headline: Imperial Headquarters Established in Imperial Palace
Headline: Advance to Lishui Solidifies Control over Danyang
Headline: Thousand Year Storm
Parade through Nanjing
It was rushing headlong into a reckless war
with countries all around the world.
Headline: Great Air Victory over Hankou
Headline: Tripartite Pact between Germany, Italy and Japan Signed in Berlin
For that reason, many young men
were forced into the army.
Kikuji!
Kikuji! It's Dad... Dad!
What happened to Dad?!
He collapsed!
Dad!
Kikuji, did you finish your violin?
I did.
I see...
Dad?
Strivai...
Are you trying to say Stradivari?
D-Don't lose to him.
I won't lose. So please, Dad,
get better soon, okay?
Hey, Dad!
Kikuji's father, who had not necessarily
been pleased about his violin making,
departed this world too soon,
to the detriment of his family.
Perhaps to numb his grief,
Kikuji became obsessed with violin making,
as if a demon has taken over his body.
Three years later
Yes, I like the sound of it.
Congratulations, Kikuji-san.
I don't understand music,
but it does sound nice.
Yeah... Did you really make it yourself?
Impressive stuff!
No.
In truth, you don't know if it's good
until you get a first-class violinist to play it.
Oh, is that so?
Hibikino Yurie will be coming
to Nagano tomorrow.
Ah, Hibikino Yurie?
So I wanted you to come listen to it with me.
Please!
"Hungarian Dance No. 5" (Brahms)
I can't believe it's an amateur-made violin.
It's a very nice violin.
However...
I can't use it.
It's because the sound is not well balanced.
It's not gonna work in a performance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Keep doing your best and good luck.
Kikuji-san, don't lose heart.
But... I don't have the slightest idea
what to do now.
Listen, you need to look
at a lot more violins.
Then listen to a lot more violins.
And try making a lot more violins!
That's the only way.
I guess.
Don't stop, Kikuji-san.
Don't stop!
Got it.
Kikuji! Kikuji!
What is it, Mom?
A conscription notice.
You've got a conscription notice!
Conscription?
First they conscripted your brother,
and now you as well!
Excuse me! Is Kayo-san here?
Kikuji-san?
I've got a conscription notice.
They're sending you to war?
I may never make another violin again.
No, I may never even get
to touch one again.
It's not likely that I'll come home alive.
Please take it.
It's the best one I've made to date.
I report to the Kanazawa garrison
the day after tomorrow.
Kikuji-san!
Goodbye, Kayo-san.
Live!
Come home alive!
Come home alive...
Mudanjiang City,
Manchuria
9th Division Medical Corps
Kikuji was enlisted as a medical officer
and assigned to the military hospital at Mudanjiang.
Sugano, take good care of it.
Sorry to bother you every time.
Ozawa, how come you're this good
at sharpening scalpels?
What were you doing before the army?
Me? I was making violins.
Violins?
Doesn't matter now.
It's just a dream I left behind in Japan.
Now that it's come to this...
Are Privates Ozawa and Sugano here?
Yes!
Ozawa and Sugano, starting today,
you will take turns serving as orderlies for Lieutenant Tanaka.
Report for duty at the officers' quarters.
Yes, sir!
But it all worked out somehow.
Do you know what I mean?
Now I think I know!
Oh, it's finally here?
Hey! Orderly Ozawa!
Yes, sir! Coming, sir!
Hey, Ozawa! We're heading out!
I won't be back tonight,
so watch the house in my absence.
Yes, sir!
Who did this?
Is someone there?
Come out!
Tonpin! Please forgive us!
Tonpin = Mr. Soldier
Please forgive us!
Please, Tonpin! Forgive us!
Forgive!
Please. Something to eat. Please.
Please!
Please! Be kind!
Dad ill!
Dad ill.
Ill?
And where is your mother?
No mother.
Dad ill.
All right. You can take it.
Thank you, Tonpin.
Thank you!
Wait!
Wait just a minute.
Good evening.
J-Japanese?
Dad, he's an army doctor.
He's a kind soldier!
Let's examine you first.
Beriberi?
Tonpin?
He'll be fine.
I'll bring the injection
and medication tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Tonpin!
Thank you, Tonpin.
What are you doing?!
Show me what you just hid.
I-I'm sorry, sir.
Isn't it Barantorin?
What do you need this for?
Come clean this instant, Ozawa!
I was planning to use it
to treat a Chinese man I know.
What is this "Chinese"?
If that's what this is about,
why didn't you just ask me directly, Ozawa?
I apologize, sir.
I understand why you want to do it.
Very well, you can take it.
I'll authorize your leave while I'm at it.
Th-Thank you, sir!
Don't worry. This is
a very effective medicine.
Make sure that he takes it.
Thank you.
Thank you!
It's not such a big deal.
I'm Honran.
I'm Yuran!
Honran and Yuran?
Tonpin is Ozawa.
Tonpin Ozawa?
Tonpin Ozawa!
Thanks to Kikuji,
the girls' father quickly got better.
And then, when spring came...
I have two little hands, you see.
One is left and one is right for me.
Little hands, so soft and small,
Ten tiny fingers count them all.
"My Tiny Little Hands"
With these hands, I wash my face,
and brush my teeth to keep in place.
Dress myself and comb my hair.
Do my tasks with love and care.
I have two little hands, you see.
One is left and one is right for me.
Little hands, so soft and small.
Ten tiny fingers count them all.
Hello!
Hello.
Who is that person?
Lensky-san.
Violin expert!
Violin?
Where does he live?
Mudanjiang, Russian District.
Lensky from the Russian Quarter, huh?
Hurry, hurry, Tonpin!
Tonpin!
Violin...
9th Division Medical Corps
Hey, they've finally given us a furlough.
Wanna go downtown and unwind?
Sugano, I'm really sorry, but I really need to go somewhere else today.
Where's that?
The Russian Quarter.
The Russian Quarter?
A Japanese soldier wandering that area will raise questions!
They have a violin!
A violin?
Didn't you say you'd given up
on all that violin stuff?
I absolutely want to go!
I see. Take care, then.
Sorry.
There, that house.
"Melodie" (Tchaikovsky)
Hello!
Hello...
We brought you a guest.
How do you do?
Japanese soldier! No way, no way!
Hey... Please open!
I only wanted to look at the violin.
Please!
Please leave! Please leave!
I beg you! I need to meet Lensky-san!
Tonpin Ozawa nice person, please!
Who is it?
It's a Japanese soldier.
Is it you, Lensky-san?
Please, let me see the violin!
Soldiers have no business coming here.
Now leave.
The violin you were playing just now...
Please show me the violin.
It sounds so wonderful!
Just one glance is enough for me! Please!
Lensky-san?
I used to make violins
before I was drafted.
I made them with all my heart.
But they conscripted me halfway through.
I couldn't finish my violin.
I was heartbroken.
But I couldn't get my mind off violins.
That's why...
Come inside, soldier.
Thank you.
Go on, come closer.
This is the violin I was playing.
If you'll allow me...
It's a good violin...
Soldier, do you recognize this?
It...
It's... a Stradivarius!
So you do recognize it. Impressive.
2nd Movement from "Winter" (Vivaldi's Four Seasons)
I'm in the same room as a Stradivarius,
which I've only seen in pictures!
Stradivari carved this violin
with his own hands,
polished it with his own hands,
and put it together with his own hands!
Soldier, please don't hesitate
to come visit me anytime.
Looks to me like you're pretty keen about it.
Well, of course I am, Father.
When Kikuji-san returns,
I'll need to have all the best materials
ready for him. Right?
I guess.
9th Division Medical Corps
Hey.
Did you hear that Tokyo and Osaka
were hit by air raids?
Really?
Yeah.
I heard senior officers talking about it.
It looks like Japan is done for.
Then, will they finally be sending us
to the front lines down south?
Seems so.
Hey, Ozawa!
Oh, there you are!
What's wrong, Ozawa?
I want to make a violin.
What are saying?!
Are you out of your mind?!
Let the past go!
Forget about violins.
No, I won't forget about them.
I'll never forget about them!
Ozawa, what are you...
Tonpin Ozawa!
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour,
but I need a favor.
Please listen to my wish.
Your wish?
Lieutenant Tanaka, sir!
It's you, Sugano? And where's Ozawa?
Sir! Private Ozawa is undergoing emergency medical treatment for severe stomach pain.
Really, Ozawa? That's bad.
I'll go check on him later.
N-No, it's just some minor stomachache,
so he should be fine.
Crap, it's the military police.
Hey! Stop!
Who goes there?!
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Dammit...
You! Why were you running?
What's your name?
What? You're mute?
Check what he has on him.
Okay.
He's carrying this.
What is this paper?
There's nothing on it.
Whatever. Get going!
Lensky-san...
Ozawa, what brings you
here at this hour?
I need a favor from you,
and you must hear me out.
Please allow me to sketch
your Stradivarius on paper.
Sketch it? And what do you want that sketch for?
I want to come home alive
and start making violins again.
Very well. You can study it
to your heart's content.
Thank you!
Thank you very much, Lensky-san!
When I return to Japan,
I'm going to make a violin
that's as good as Stradivari's.
Please use it to make a wonderful violin.
I wish you the best of luck.
Thank you, truly.
1st Platoon, forward...
march!
Ozawa!
Tonpin Ozawa!
Ozawa! Don't go!
Ozawa!
Tonpin Ozawa!
Don't go, Tonpin Ozawa!
Don't go!
Tonpin Ozawa!
Don't go, Ozawa!
Eggs for Tonpin.
Eggs.
Train!
Tonpin Ozawa!
Honran! Yuran!
Ozawa!
Goodbye!
Take care!
Ozawa!
Thank you! Goodbye!
Kikuji's medical corps was transferred
from Northeastern China
to Okinawa just before
the American invasion began.
Okinawa
Somebody... Give me water...
Some water, please...
Lucky you... Even at times like this,
you can look at that thing
day after day and never get tired of it.
I'm making sure it doesn't get wet,
even if it ends up in the water.
My whole life is in it.
Survive and go home, Ozawa.
Sugano?
Now I also want to see
the violin you make, sort of.
Sugano, I will definitely
survive and go home.
Kayo! You must take
better care of yourself.
I'm all right, Mom.
It's just a small cold.
Don't worry.
I hope the war ends soon,
and Kikuji-san returns home alive.
He will return. I know he will!
Enemy planes! Get down!
Oh no!
Hey, where are you going?!
It's still dangerous out there!
That guy...
Watch out!
Ah! The bag!
You wait here!
Sugano!
Stop! Leave it, Sugano!
Are you okay, Sugano?
That was scary, seriously!
Are you injured?
Oh, nothing serious.
Ow! Ow-ow-ow...
But that is serious!
Nah, it just grazed me.
Because I'm so clumsy.
Why... Why did you run there for me?
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry, Sugano!
A few weeks later, Kikuji's unit
was transferred to Taiwan.
Japan's defeat was already
looming in the air.
Sugano, what are you going to do
when the war ends?
I wanted to be a gymnastics
teacher at a school.
But I guess, with this leg,
I'd better give up on it.
Don't talk nonsense.
That leg will heal in no time.
Sugano...
Let's both come home alive, Ozawa.
I can't wait to listen
to the violin that you make.
I'm sure you'll get to listen to it.
What's that?
Enemy submarine
spotted off the port bow!
A torpedo!
Torpedo incoming!
Ozawa! Ozawa!
What are you doing?
Hey, hurry up!
A torpedo!
Chikata! Are you all right?
Yes!
Hey, stay strong!
Don't you let go!
Don't stop! Don't stop paddling!
U-Uh, Sugano!
Sugano, stay awake!
Hang on tight, okay?
The tides flow fast around here.
I'm sleepy... How strange... I wonder why...
Has my wound opened? Sharks...
Crap! The sharks will sense it!
Sugano!
Don't fall asleep!
Hang on tight! You can't fall asleep!
Ozawa, be sure to return to Japan...
Come home alive
and keep making violins...
Sugano... Sugano!
Grab my hand, Sugano! Sugano!
Sugano!
Hey! Anyone!
Is anyone there?!
That one's already bought it.
Hey, have you seen Sugano?
I see.
Sugano...
Sugano,
I will definitely return to Japan!
I can't...
Violi...
Vi...
Okay.
Here.
Nagano Station
The war was over.
Cigarettes, anyone? Cigarettes!
Vegetables here! Vegetables!
So? Anyone needs cigarettes?
Kikuji became a prisoner of war.
He was finally able to return to Japan six months later.
I'm home!
Ah! Kikuji?
Mother!
Mom! I've returned!
Kikuji! Thank God you're alive!
I'm home...
Brother!
Hiroe! Look how big you've grown!
Thank God. Thank God!
Grandpa!
Brother!
Kikuji is back!
Kikuji!
Brother!
Welcome home.
What a relief, Kikuji!
I'm home, everyone.
Is that so?
Well, have some more!
C'mon...
It's real tasty!
It's strong stuff!
Where are you going again
so soon, Kikuji?
To Abe-san from Niigata.
To Kayo's place?
Yeah. But I'm only going there today
to say hello, Mom.
I'll be back in the evening.
What's wrong?
Did something happen to Kayo-san?
Actually...
Mom!
Come on, Mom! What is it?
To tell you the truth, Kikuji, Kayo-san...
Kayo-san passed away.
Kayo-san is...
gone?
You're kidding, right? Right, Mom?!
I-It can't be...
It can't be!
Mom, it's been three months already
since Kikuji returned.
Do you think he's not going to make violins anymore?
Who knows?
Without Kayo-san,
it's as if his very soul has left his body.
Otsuki-sensei!
Hey, Kikuji. Welcome home.
Sensei!
I almost got killed too,
but I made it back in the end.
These past few years
must've been tough on you.
By the way, Kikuji.
Yes?
You're still making violins, right?
Cleanliness
and Order
Kikuji.
Cleanliness
and Order
Do you remember this?
I-It's...
That's right. It's the very first violin
you ever made.
You were truly inspired
when you made this.
It's all in the past. I don't want
anything to do with violins now.
What are you saying?!
A great many lost their lives in this war.
But you came back alive.
If you, who survived,
abandon your own aspirations,
what'll become of the hopes
of your fallen comrades?
Take Kayo-san, who passed away
while waiting for your return.
What would Kayo-san think?
Kikuji, this is the moment.
Doesn't your true journey
as a violin maker start now?
Sensei...
It's you.
I'm Ozawa.
It's you, Kikuji-san!
Good job surviving out there!
It was just before the end of the war.
Her chest condition had gotten worse,
but she still worked herself to the bone.
Going to the mountains...
One day, she collapsed
right there on the mountain.
When we found her, it was too late.
Mom...
Kikuji-san...
She clutched it till the end.
She asked me to give this to you.
Here.
To Ozawa Kikuji
Ma'am...
"Kikuji-san,
I believed in your return, so I planted saplings
of Fullmoon and Palmate..."
of Fullmoon and Palmate maple.
A mountain slope where it snows heavily,
facing southeast to west,
with an incline of about 35 degrees.
These days, people say to me,
"What's a violin?"
But when the war ends...
Kikuji-san, please take a look at that.
Kikuji-san, the war is over.
You can now devote yourself fully
to violin making.
Even if I can't...
help you anymore...
Kikuji-san, I'm sure you'll become
Japan's Stradivari!
I know you will!
Fifty years have passed.
Even while farming full-time
and tending his apple orchard,
Ozawa Kikuji still pours his heart
and soul into crafting violins to this day.
Translation &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
Uchuu
WOWmd