Mushi Productions
Young 'un, tell this poor beggar something.
What's the name of this town?
Black Hills Bay.
Thank you.
I'm told there's an inn called
the Admiral Benbow here.
Do you know where it is?
I live at the Benbow.
I'm Jim, the son of the owner.
You're in a tight spot, huh?
My mom's nice, so she'll give you something.
Come with me.
Ah!
Don't hide anything from me, kid.
You have a guest named Billy Bones
staying with you, right?
That hurts! That hurts! Let me go!
Well? Hiding it won't end well for you.
It'd be easy for me
to break an arm or two.
I-I don't know!
We have a guy called "Captain,"
but he won't see anyone!
Then show me the way.
Don't raise a fuss.
If you do, then rabbit's my favorite dish.
Where is it?
All right.
Kid, when did this "Captain"
come to your inn?
A month ago.
Every day, he drinks and gets rowdy,
so people stay away.
Every day, he stands on the hill and
watches to see if someone's coming.
Who's he looking for?
I don't know, but it's a one-legged man.
One-legged, you say?
Orphan Fansubs presents
New Treasure Island
Booze, booze!
Get me another rum!
What're you staring at?
I want rum! Rum! Rum, I say!
Hurry and bring it here!
Why is everyone looking at me like that?!
Fifteen men on the dead man's chest!
Yo-ho-ho, and a bottle of rum!
Drink and the devil had done for the rest!
Yo-ho-ho!
Hey, all of you!
Why won't you sing with me?
So rude!
You.
F-Fifteen men on the d-dead man's...
You're awful!
Stop that, Billy Bones.
What did you say?
Listen, Billy. I'm telling you not to cause trouble for others.
You greenhorn!
Hey, greenhorn, you've got
an awfully big mouth on you.
Who do you think you are?
I am Dr. Livesey,
but I'm also a magistrate.
If you are going to bare
your fangs at innocent people,
I'll have you collared like an animal and thrown in prison.
Understood?
Shut up!
Well, if talking won't make you see sense, so be it.
Fine. I'll take you on.
Get lost!
Captain, there's a guest for you!
Captain... No, Billy Bones.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
P-Pew?!
It's been a long time since you vanished.
You were hard to find.
Here, take it.
I don't know what it says,
but it's a message from One-leg.
So long, Billy.
I-I've gotta run.
M-My luggage.
I-I still have time.
F-Five hours.
We'll wait until 11
Jim, are you okay?
Hm, he's dead.
It's a heart attack.
He drank too much and got worked up on top of that.
His heart couldn't take the shock.
"We'll wait until 11"?
What's this about?
I have a bad feeling.
I'll go to the police for support.
Sorry, but could I borrow a horse?
Sure!
He's late.
Dr. Livesey's still not back, huh?
It's already 10:00!
The bad guys might attack
in another hour.
That customer was a real troublemaker.
Not that I want to speak ill of the dead.
He never paid for his rent or his drinks.
He might have left money
in his room, Mom.
You're right.
We can collect his rent from there.
There's a chest!
It's locked.
A key!
There's money, Mom!
Oh, a knife!
And a pistol!
Oh?
What could this be?
Don't touch anything you don't have to.
We're just collecting his rent.
Understand, Jim?
The inn's right over there!
It's the baddies!
This is the inn. Just charge in there.
What should we do, Jim? They'll kill us!
Hey, get out here.
Hey!
Hurry! This way!
This is dangerous, Jim.
Has he run off?
Right, his room's on the second floor.
We need to get that map.
If he's here, we'll beat him up.
He's not here.
He must've run off!
Ah, the chest's been ransacked!
Where'd the map go?
I don't see it.
Is anyone out here?
Not outside, either? He runs fast.
I smell them still hiding in this house.
Oh, Jim!
Listen, I'm going to chase them out now.
I'll drop them out of this window.
You pump 'em full of holes. Got it?
Got it!
Oh, Jim, what am I going to do?
Don't Shoot! It's me! It's me!
Oh, no! It's the lawman! He's coming!
Run for it!
Jim!
Where's Jim?
Here! Doctor, this package is-
It's a map!
It's a map of an island somewhere.
Squire, I've heard you know the sea. Can you tell us about this map?
This is a map of Treasure Island!
What? Treasure Island!
Yes, Flint's Treasure Island!
Jim, the map you found
in the man's trunk
leads to the island where the infamous pirate Flint buried his treasure.
The man who stayed at your inn was fleeing with it.
The blind man and his mates
were after it.
It's supposed to be an incredible sum.
Whoever finds it will be
the richest man in the world.
Treasure! A treasure hunt! This will be marvelous!
Let's go to Treasure Island!
With a map, it'll be easy!
Oh, wow! Take me with you!
But I'm a little worried, Mr. Trelawney.
They say those obsessed
with treasure go feral.
If we find it, I don't want to become a wild animal,
and I don't want to grow claws.
I agree. I'm a gentleman, after all.
For now, let's gather sailors and set out in secret.
This is our secret. Don't tell a soul.
Hey! Buy a ship so we can go to Treasure Island in a hurry!
She's a fine ship.
Yes, a real fine ship.
You'll get 15 knots out of her, no problem.
Perfect for a trip across the sea.
Wonderful! Beautiful! Splendid! Cool!
Oh, I see you know your ships.
You may lay to that.
I was in the navy, you see.
Lost my leg in the war.
You can trust me on anything
to do with ships.
Oh, pardon me.
My name is John Silver.
It's a pleasure to meet you, sir.
A navy man, are you?
That's just perfect.
What do you say? Are you free?
Will you board my ship?
I happen to be looking for hands.
I can't get enough men together.
After all, the fact we're going to Treasure Island is- Oops!
That sounds like a hassle.
Why not leave it to me? I'll find you a large number of good men.
I'd appreciate that, but can you do it?
Just you watch me, sir.
If I give a holler...
What do you say? I know a lot of people.
Now that was a surprise!
They're all real fighters.
And they'll work for half
of normal wages. It's a bargain.
What? They come at a discount? I like it!
Hold on, Mr. Trelawney.
I'm very much against it.
C-Captain?
Let me warn you.
I can't take responsibility for a crew gathered without proper checking.
Well, Captain, you just
worry about the ship.
It's not your job to worry
about the sailors, is it?
I can't do that!
I'm quitting.
Huh?
W-Wait!
Don't get mad.
I'll double your pay.
And throw in a bonus!
You can have my vacation house.
You can have my land.
And a plantation.
I'll throw in my best wine too.
And a barrel of honeyed apples.
Honeyed apples?
Fine! I'll give them a taste.
If I don't like them,
then I absolutely refuse.
Bring them here!
Go ahead, Captain.
Wow!
Prepare to set sail!
Set sail!
Hey, mister.
Hey, Jim.
Hey.
Hey, Mr. Silver.
Salute, Captain Jim!
Very good.
Report on tonight's dinner.
Yes, sir. First, fried tuna with potatoes.
And raw oysters with pepper and cooking sauce.
And for dessert...
Apples with lots of honey.
Ugh, again?
Why honeyed apples?
I'm sick of them.
Captain's orders, I'm afraid.
But I've got something secret for you, Jim.
Look. I fixed you a special desert.
Wow, thanks, Silver. This is great.
I am honored by your kind words, sir.
I know! I have something even better.
It took me years as a sailor to save up all of these.
Open her up.
They're so pretty.
You're really giving these to me?
Take a whiff. You'll smell all the seas of the world.
Hey, why'd you gather all these shells?
Weren't you going to give them to someone?
I have no parents, siblings,
or other relatives.
So I was planning to come home,
find a beautiful bride,
and build a nice house.
I was going to use those shells to decorate the rooms.
But a sailor's got no business settling on land.
You really are a nice guy, huh?
It's a squall. No big deal.
It's a storm!
Captain, it's a storm!
Why are you sitting here?
The ship's going to sink!
Do something!
It's fine.
No, it's not.
Hurry up and direct the men.
Hard to starboard!
No, I meant larboard!
Don't panic!
I can't take this hurricane.
Hard to larboard.
Captain, I'll be straight with you.
I can't stand how you run this ship.
I am the owner.
Obviously, since you're the captain, I leave the ship to you,
but I can't have you just doing whatever.
The men don't trust you.
Is there any value in a captain who's not trusted?
That cook Silver's a far better man than you!
Jim! Fetch me some honeyed apples!
Yes, sir!
There you have it.
Will you join us too, young man?
So then? When we get to Treasure Island,
we steal the treasure and the ship?
Yeah. The treasure'll be an even split.
It's Captain Flint's amazing treasure.
And you're going to give me a share?
You mean it, Silver?
Yeah, Mr. Silver was a member
of Flint's crew.
Do as he says and you won't go wrong.
Then what about the captain, the squire, and the doctor?
That's obvious.
We kill the lot of them
once we have the treasure.
Ha! If we're gonna off them,
no point waiting.
Why don't we do it tonight, Silver?
You dolt!
They have the map.
Instead of killing them now, we'll let them run free.
They'll find the treasure for us.
It won't be too late to kill them then.
Don't reveal yourself before that.
Work like normal. Got it?!
My throat's dry from talking.
Get me an apple.
Sure thing.
Wait!
Huh?
Show me your hands.
Your hands. Show them to me now.
Idiot!
You're growing claws.
We're not animals!
Pull those claws in now!
But, Silver, they come out on their own
when I think about treasure.
I get down on all fours and
want to bite people to death.
Listen, we're pirates, not animals.
Look at me!
I've never grown claws.
When this job's done, I'm gonna build
a house with the money and live in peace.
Yeah, that's my dream.
I want to live like a proper gentleman,
for once in my life.
Now, we need to go back in
before they get suspicious.
W-We've got trouble!
Silver... Silver's saying he'll steal the treasure and kill us all!
Silver's a pirate!
I-Is that true?
Yeah, I just heard him!
Most of the men on this ship
are his lackeys!
How careless we've been.
Captain, I was a fool.
It's just like you said.
Okay. We'll have to get our men together and fight back.
It's too soon, you fool.
It would be bad if they realized we know.
Play ignorant, so they let their guard down.
Leave the rest to me.
Jim, you watch what they're doing.
I'm counting on you.
Aye aye, sir!
It's hot.
Treasure, treasure...
Treasure, treasure, treasure.
Treasure, treasure, treasure, treasure, treasure, treasure, treasure!
You idiot.
What's wrong with you?
I told you to hide your claws until we have the treasure!
You stupid morons.
This is a critical time for us!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Do it again and I'll string you up from the mast.
Now get back to work!
Aye aye, sir!
I see the island! I see the island!
Land ho!
It's Treasure Island!
I see Treasure Island!
Hurray!
We made it!
Lord, please help me.
We made it, Mr. Trelawney.
Yeah! We're finally here!
Here's where it gets hard.
Be on your guard.
Gentlemen, we made it here without a hitch, thanks to your hard work.
I'm giving you the day off!
You may go ashore and relax!
Yahoo!
Huh?
Hands up!
Wh-What's this about, sir?
We know what you're plotting.
Stay quiet.
Darn it...
I've got it!
Stop resisting.
You're going in the brig for now.
Hurry and pick up your pistol, Mr. Trelawney.
What now?
We go to the island secretly and find the treasure.
Then, we'll maroon them all here.
Huh? Jim's missing!
Hey, it's Jim.
I never noticed.
When did you get aboard, Jim?
Jim, you little sneak.
You've got a face like George Chakiris.
Treasure Island's right before our eyes!
Be jollier!
Jim? What's up?
Jim!
Hey!
Hey! Jim!
Help!
Help, please!
You were in a real pickle, brother.
Wh-Who are you, mister?
Ben Gunn.
Poor Ben Gunn.
Why are you naked
and walking on all fours?
You're like a lion.
That's right, brother.
Once I was a seaman
on Captain Flint's ship.
Ever since I was marooned, I've spent every day searching for treasure.
As I did, I started smelling
more and more like an animal.
Now I can only walk on four legs, and my claws are always out.
You were possessed by the treasure, huh?
I sure was, brother.
But I want to put clothes on and live a normal life again.
Do you know Silver?
Please, help me. He's a villain.
Let me aboard your ship.
Sure, I'll ask them to let you.
Thank you!
As thanks, I'll do anything for you.
You're a good, merciful boy.
Gather round!
Listen! We've made it
to Treasure Island!
Soon we'll set our eyes
on a great treasure!
Don't rush and mess it all up!
As soon as you hear the word treasure,
some of you bare your claws and fangs and get down on all fours right away.
We're not animals!
Got it?
And Jim was acting strange earlier.
One of you go find Jim and bring him back.
Hold it!
Why are you looking like that?
Stick that tongue in.
You're slavering like a dog.
Hmph! What a sermon.
I didn't come searching for treasure so you could preach at me!
What, then?
You don't want to follow my orders?
Yeah! I won't rely on you.
I'll search for the treasure on my own.
Oh, yeah? Then suit yourself.
I'm going. Who'd hold back
on your account?
Amen.
Anyone else want to run off on their own?
Hey, we've got trouble!
I see a boat over there!
What'd you say?!
It's the captain, the squire, and the doctor.
Darn it. They're planning
to escape, are they?
Hey! Head to the ship and tell the guys
there to open fire immediately!
But there's no point if we lose the map.
Tell them to hit the boat,
not the people. Got it?
Look! It's Silver's parrot, brother.
Those lubbers!
Cannons! Cannons!
Just you wait, you lubbers!
The target's two hundred meters away!
Fire!
Don't hit the people!
Hit the boat! The boat!
Hey, hey, hey!
What?
Hm? It's a bombardment!
Shoot! It looks like they cut their ropes and signaled to the guys on shore.
We need to hurry ashore.
If we dawdle, we'll be caught by attackers on both sides.
I see a little house there!
It has a stockade too!
If we secure ourselves in there, we can fend off the pirates.
This'll be a fine fortress.
Look, there're loopholes.
This must've been where the pirates lived before.
Anyway, let's get our stuff inside.
Guns and powder go there.
Food goes there.
All right.
The pirates will show up soon.
We're three, they're eighteen.
We'll need serious determination to face eighteen with just three.
Still, we absolutely must win.
Captain, take the loopholes to the north.
Mr. Trelawney, take the ones to the south.
I'll target the enemies
in front from the door.
Who's there?!
It's Captain Silver.
Captain Silver?
I don't know anyone like that!
Who are you?!
I just became captain.
There's a captain here for direct talks.
Do you mind if I come in?
Fine, come in!
But no funny business!
Okay, stop.
Don't move.
What do you want to talk about, Silver?
Make it quick.
Well, Doctor, I'm here to make a deal between leaders.
Doctor, we want the treasure map.
You and your friends want to live.
So, I was thinking you'd give us the map,
and we'd spare your lives.
What? I'd never accept a deal like that.
If you don't like this deal, I have bad news for you.
My men will tear up this hut and rend your flesh from your bones.
You're okay with that?
All right, here's my response!
We will never hand over the map.
You're the ones who'll be torn apart.
If you surrender now, I'll forgive you.
Well?
That's your response?
If you act tough now, don't cry to me
when you regret it later, Doc.
Get lost! You animal! You nincompoop!
What?!
Get lost!
Don't cry later, you reckless fools!
It's quiet.
Are they coming up with a plan?
They're teasing us.
It's quie- a-achoo!
Have they run away?
They lost to our spirit.
Huh?
It's a bombardment!
The ship's firing! Something's happened!
Silver must've started it.
I gotta go back to the ship, Mr. Ben Gunn.
I'm borrowing your boat.
Be careful then, brother.
They're coming!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no!
Save me!
Hurry! Hurry!
Ow!
How'd you like that, you pirates?!
Ow-ow!
Ah! Captain!
Captain!
The map's gone. The treasure map's gone!
You lubber.
You lubber!
Hold it, you lubber!
You won't get away now.
I'll burn your heart black.
DANGER
All right.
I won! The ship's mine!
Right! I need to let the captain and Dr. Livesey know!
Silver and his men will be shocked
when they find out I took back the ship.
Serves you right, you pirates.
Silver!
What are you doing here?
You murderer!
You pirate!
You animal!
Don't be so mad, Jim.
I have my own circumstances.
I'll never let you take the treasure!
It's the map!
That's right. It's the map.
Too bad, Jim.
H-How?
Easy. This parrot swiped it
from the squire in the confusion.
They must be blue in the face
looking for it now.
What do we do with him?
Kill him!
Yeah, off him!
Kill me! I'll die like a man!
Wait!
Hey, keep your hands off Jim.
Anyone who wants to lay a hand on Jim has to go through me!
Come on, you lubbers!
Let's stop wasting time and go!
The sun's gonna set!
March!
We're lads hoisting sail in the far seas
We trust ourselves to the wind
Aye aye, sir!
Cause some trouble
We're friends, aren't we? Right?
Jim, they were going to beat you to death if I didn't intervene.
Now it's your turn.
If the treasure drives me crazy, then save me, will you?
Okay?
A quick trip
Aye aye, sir!
A quick trip, a quick trip
Aye aye aye, sir! Aye aye, sir!
A quick trip around the seven seas
Aye aye, sir!
Everyone, stop!
I'll check the map.
Eagle Mountain, skeleton's eye,
south-southwest, tall tree.
There's Eagle Mountain.
The map say's it's on Eagle Mountain's right shoulder.
It says one person should dig up the treasure alone.
I see.
Look. This is more like a large rock than a mountain.
Look at the base.
It's so shaky and unstable.
Just try and climb up there together.
The center of mass would shift,
and it'd fall over.
That's why only one man can go up.
I'll climb it!
No, me!
What? No, me!
Me!
No, me!
Hey! You can't all climb together!
That's dangerous!
There's the tree! It's around here!
It's the treasure!
Go!
Hey! Where's the treasure?
It's not here.
No sign of it.
Who beat us to it?
Drat!
Who was it?
He tricked us!
Silver, how dare you swindle us!
Jim, look out.
Darn it.
Heh, what a bunch of animals.
You think a bunch of lubbers
like you can take down ol' Silver?
Jim, do you hear anything?
Listen.
There's some kind of rumbling.
Oh, yeah? So it's started then.
Hurry! To the tree!
Tie us to the tree.
Quickly!
If we die, we die together, Jim.
S-Save me!
Not again!
W-We're saved.
Just now, I realized there are more important things than treasure.
Hey, Jim!
Dr. Livesey! Mr. Trelawney!
Dr. Livesey!
Jim? You're not hurt, are you?
Silver!
I ought to make pork cutlet out of you, you scoundrel!
Mr. Trelawney, please forgive Silver.
He saved me.
I'll do it because Jim asked me to,
but you're despicable.
The treasure wasn't where
it said it would be.
Was the map a lie?
No. It was dug up a long time ago.
What? Who did it?
Ben Gunn.
Yes, I found it and took it back to my place.
Yahoo!
Let's hurry. I want to see
the treasure quickly.
Treasure! Treasure! It's finally ours!
Mr. Trelawney!
The treasure isn't just yours!
Mr. Trelawney, listen!
Mr. Trelawney!
Captain Flint was a wild dog.
He wanted to gather bones
from butchers' shops all over the world.
This was Flint's treasure?
Is it even treasure?
Hey, everyone.
What's wrong, gentlemen?
Silver!
Silver ran away.
Silver! Come back!
I'm sick of hunting for treasure.
Treasures are so boring.
People who hunt for it
are even more boring.
If we found the treasure,
I was planning to give you half,
but now all I have to give you
is those shells.
Forget about me.
Take care of yourself, Jim.
Silver!
Become a good person!
The End
Translation
Additional Dialog
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Iri
kokujin-kun
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Uchuu
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
WOWmd