Look! It's the Northern Corridor!
The legends of my northern tribe
have proved correct!
Now it's time for the people to set out in search of a new world. To cross the corridor!
O God, you guided us along the way.
You helped us survive
starvation and freezing.
We will head to the warm and fertile land, the promised paradise.
Orphan Fansubs presents
Across the Surging Times
This is no ordinary cave.
It's more like a rift in the Earth.
The lake I wanted to show you is hidden
all the way inside this deep cave.
A mysterious underground lake
you've just discovered?
Pulling the cord from a generator to such depths was no small feat, was it?
Was it long enough?
Yes, it covers about half the path.
After that, we'll have to rely
on these headlamps.
Not to worry.
I already climbed down there once
to see if it's safe.
Ouch! I'll get things ready.
I still can't believe it.
Here, in the middle of this desert, a conical crater resembling a doodlebug pit trap,
and a lake deep inside it.
Wow, this is actually amazing.
Millions of years ago,
this place was at the bottom of the ocean.
Are you sure?
You'll know after you've explored it.
Radiolaria, foraminifera, and fusulinida...
The organisms that lived in different eras have accumulated here
and formed layered sediments.
That means we won't just be going down to the depths of the Earth,
we'll be traveling to the distant past through the ages of time.
Precisely.
And then, as the weight of time fills you,
you'll find yourself by an underground lake.
The air and the peculiar stalactite patterns
of that place will move you deeply.
In other words, I hope this tour will inspire the luminary of current composers,
Leslie Mardoff, to write a new concerto or symphony.
So that's why the famous music producer
Gilbert brought me all the way here?
Of course, I hope for that too.
That's good. Because if this plan succeeds...
No, I'm confident it will succeed.
And then we'll take the world by storm.
Well now.
Let's go, okay?
What's wrong?
Hey, Leslie.
We'd agreed to keep this project
secret until we were done.
We're still good, right?
What do you mean?
I mean, you didn't tell a third party
that we were coming here, did you?
Ah... Well, about that...
You'd better be careful.
Leslie Mardoff is a famous playboy.
Do you remember the suicide attempt by an idol he was dating at the time?
I know it was before we hired you,
but it was all over the media at the time,
so you have to know.
He's actually gotten into other,
similar scandals too.
With an actress, a singer, a model,
and even one of his innocent fans.
He's got quite a reputation.
But no other composer rivals Leslie Mardoff
in popularity among the young.
Isn't that right?
That's undeniable.
Every piece he writes gets
a rapturous reception from critics.
His newly released CDs
always top the US charts.
I'm a fan of his too.
No, I mean, of the music he writes.
Naturally, it's going to be
the first time we meet in person.
Hey, maybe I shouldn't have
taken on this project?
Absolutely not.
The brilliant young composer Leslie Mardoff
shapes the music of our era.
You were given a chance to land
the first successful interview with him.
Something like that would definitely make the headlines for next month's issue.
But be careful, Flora.
Leslie Mardoff despises the media
with a passion and has a difficult personality.
Companies fight tooth and nail for a chance to interview him,
but he just turns them all down.
The reason I'm saying all that is...
You've worked here for less than two years.
You're still a rookie by journalistic standards,
yet you landed an interview
with him effortlessly.
All it took was one phone call, didn't it?
I find that hard to take at face value.
I couldn't believe it either.
I was sitting near the phone
for a while, doubting myself.
"Whatever. Even if he turns me down, so be it." I made up my mind,
mustered up my courage, and dialed.
And then, I got lucky. He was there and said "Okay" without a second thought.
But he said that to get in the mood
for the next symphony he's composing,
he's going to an underground lake,
and he'll let me take pictures of it as a bonus.
Imagine how surprised I was!
I wonder if that's some new ploy
for picking up girls.
No way!
How could he know what kind of girl I am
just from hearing my voice on the phone?
I was kidding.
But this certainly has a mysterious feel to it.
Flora, I'm sure your strong resolve
provided you a stroke of good luck.
Do your best, and I'm sure
you'll turn this into a great scoop.
My, oh my! Even the bugs are attracted to your extraordinary luck!
Better not scratch it too much,
or it will swell.
Ugh, not again!
This just happens to me from time to time.
These red spots appear out of nowhere,
even without any bugs biting me.
But it'll be gone soon enough.
So it's another one of our playboy's tricks?
Hm. As if I'd ever fall for that!
You invited some female journalist here?!
Leslie, why are you like that?
Don't get so mad, Gilbert.
Our interview isn't scheduled for today.
We'll do it tomorrow afternoon
in the motel lobby, after we're done here.
You probably also promised her
to come back here
and take some pictures with
the underground lake as the backdrop.
Because of course you'd be kind enough
to assume some contemplative pose for it.
It's a free time interview,
so it shouldn't interfere with my work.
Kid, that habit is gonna be your ruin.
What do you mean?
I mean that.
Whenever a pretty girl is involved,
you start fawning all over her.
Would you have agreed
if it'd been a seasoned veteran reporter?
I mean, I knew about your playboy demeanor,
but I didn't think it was this bad.
After just hearing her voice on the phone!
Wait a minute, Gilbert!
It's not like I had any ulterior motives in mind
when I accepted an interview with her.
For starters, that'd be
a comically elaborate scheme.
Besides, I still have no idea
what kind of person that reporter is.
However, when I received
a call from her that night...
Hello, Leslie Mardoff?
My name is Flora. I work as an editor at Log Book Inc.
Flora?
Excuse me, is something wrong?
I know it sounds completely bonkers,
but when I first heard her voice,
I was overwhelmed by dizziness.
I don't know why, but I felt like the passion
of a distant past had been awakened.
As though a stream of cold water had suddenly run through dry, parched land.
A shock went all through my body,
electrifying every cell in it.
I've heard of love at first sight.
but I've never heard of anyone getting
so agitated by the mere sound of a voice.
I imagine she must have
a very captivating voice.
This magazine reporter named Flora.
We're here.
If we had proper illumination here,
the sight unfolding before your eyes
would be much more subtle and profound.
Somehow, the weight of time pressing down on me here
feels oddly familiar to my body.
Tell me, Leslie.
I've wanted to ask you for a while.
What's up with that stone pendant you keep toying with?
You mean this?
It's quite old.
It reminds me of ancient people's amulets
from museum exhibitions.
Oh? It has a drawing on it too.
A red deer, huh? Interesting.
Gilbert, I told you before
that the blood in my veins is about a quarter Native American, didn't I?
The Natives' oral tradition holds that
deer are endowed with a strong spirit.
So this is my charm.
Oh?
For a long time, I've been pursuing one particular theme.
No, it'd be more correct to say
I've been pursuing a certain image.
I'd like to know where my ancestors,
the Native Americans, originally came from.
A long time ago...
Right, over 10,000 years ago,
in the closing years of the Pleistocene epoch,
my ancestors came here
from a distant region in Asia.
They crossed the Bering Strait
and populated this continent.
Those Native Americans used
a glacial road in the far north.
It's called "Beringia."
Beringia.
Behind that word lies the life, death,
and essence of my race.
You said that this place once
used to be the ocean floor.
It might well be that we're currently standing on the stratum
that corresponds to the time of Beringia,
when my native ancestors decided to cross.
I can hear them.
The agitated voices of their ice-bound journey, echoing through time.
The squeaking of carts,
the neighing of horses.
Every single sound becomes a particle
that enters my body.
The Prehistoric Era
____ The Prehistoric Era ____
There, eat this!
Bogud!
If you're looking for Bogud,
I saw him going to the valley, alone.
Oh, really? What'll I do with that kid?
Oh, Bogud!
Hey, Fayau.
Mom has been looking for you for a while.
She has?
Yes, for a few days now!
She was sure you were slacking
off somewhere, as usual.
She'll probably give you a scolding!
Elder!
How are you?
Hold it right there, you lazy young man!
Hold it, I said!
Tell me, Bogud.
I'm pretty sure you're turning thirteen this spring.
Yeah.
According to our laws, a boy who turns thirteen must go out hunting alone.
I hope this fact hasn't completely slipped your mind, huh?
I know.
When summer comes, I'll start training.
And when fall comes, I'll go hunting.
You're so inept, the most impressive prey you'd be able to hunt down is a pig.
But good luck all the same.
The spirit of the first animal you bring down
will become your guardian spirit, deciding your whole life.
If you bring back a pig's spirit, you'll never have trouble finding something to chew.
But eventually you might end up
becoming a chronic glutton.
After all, animals like pigs are only born
to be eaten later by humans.
What a spiteful elder.
Bah!
Yeah, bringing a pig would be a disaster!
Even you of all people should be able to hunt down a rabbit.
The rabbit's spirit isn't bad.
It's nimble and cautious.
Though he might seem placid,
he's actually quite courageous.
In fact, I have a rabbit
as my guardian spirit myself.
But of course. So that's why you drink
until your eyes turn red.
Shut up!
I don't want to kill
either a pig or a rabbit.
The animal I'm gonna hunt down is...
a red deer!
A red deer?!
That's a good one. Right.
Go and tell that to our elder.
He'll burst out laughing in your face.
You know, back when I was around your age,
I dreamed of that too, once or twice.
Right.
The legendary red deer.
They say the red deer has the strongest spirit of all the animals out there.
Since time immemorial, every boy
approaching his thirteenth summer
has wanted to fell a red deer.
That's right, every single one.
But even to this day,
no one's succeeded.
Do you remember Koriko?
He also went on a journey
to catch a red deer.
He was a hefty fella.
People gossiped he was gonna be
our tribe's future leader.
He was a promising fella too.
And what a tale it was. In the fall,
he went to the mountains alone.
He didn't return all through the winter.
He only showed up in the spring,
when the ice at Selenge River thawed.
Gaunt and emaciated.
Lifeless like a ghost.
At first, nobody even realized
it was him, Koriko.
He was bedridden for the next four years
until his untimely death.
That boy was only 17.
What animal did Koriko fell?
I don't know, but you can be sure
it wasn't a red deer.
It's not a bad thing to allow yourself to dream big,
but don't you get carried away.
You see a rabbit... You get a rabbit!
It tastes good enough too.
Nothing wrong with
a rabbit's spirit, Bogud.
But I'd really appreciate it if you helped
me with housework a bit more.
Even your little sisters are doing what they can.
So what are you doing
with all your free time?
Nothing, really.
He's probably hiding somewhere
and drawing whatever pictures he wants.
But if you're serious about going hunting,
you need to start practicing with a bow!
What did you draw last time?
I drew...
the usual things: flowers, cows...
You haven't been drawing
humans, have you?!
Don't worry. I haven't.
That's good. Nothing wrong
with drawing pictures.
You can draw cows and horses all you want
and do well in our Tangad tribe.
But not humans.
Doncha ever dare draw humans.
That's another one of our tribe's laws.
You know, right?
Yeah.
But Dad, why is that?
Why can't I draw humans?
Hey, Dad.
Ain't it obvious?!
Mom, do you know?
No, it's a mystery to me.
You should try asking the elder.
So you want to know?
Yes.
Well, truth be told,
you're good at drawing.
Eventually, you can become my assistant
and draw pictures that we'll dedicate to God.
For such an outcome,
it'd be better if I told you now, perhaps.
You want to know?
Yes.
Now, how should I put it?
Here, we don't have to worry
about others overhearing us.
Listen. This is very important,
so don't you ever tell anyone else.
Okay.
If you draw a picture of a person,
you'll lose that person forever.
Death or lifelong separation...
It could be either.
In a sense, it's a curse.
If this secret became widely known,
well, people would spend all day smearing the Earth with the faces of their enemies.
Because that's how jealous humans are.
That's how resentful they are,
deep in their hearts.
For that reason,
it's customary not to say why,
just that drawing people is a no-no
and don't ask questions.
That's too unreasonable to be true.
I carved it because I love Fayau.
And the price is death
or lifelong separation?
The red deer.
That's it. The spirit of the red deer
will simply shrug off the curse.
It's the strongest of all.
This autumn, I'll hunt down
the legendary red deer.
And then... And then, I'll take Fayau
as my wife, and I'll make her happy!
Bogud, don't lose any food along the way.
And be sure to come back before winter!
Remember, a bird in the hand is worth
two in the bush. A rabbit is fine.
If you catch a rabbit, eat it
and come back before it starts to snow!
Oh, oh? Our Bogud is finally setting out?
I hope you don't forget
to aim for the pig's butt.
It's big enough so you
probably won't miss.
I'm going.
Bogud, stay strong!
Remember to be careful!
No. My target is the legendary red deer.
It's good to be a horse.
You can live on nothing but grass.
Stand up! C'mon!
We have to keep going.
Is this really how you want to die?
Stand up now!
I need to stay focused.
If I doze off now, I'll freeze to death.
I'm so hungry.
I haven't eaten in three days.
A mouse?
I could eat a mouse!
I'm so hungry and exhausted,
I can't even catch a single mouse.
Don't be stupid!
What's the good of catching a mouse?
I'll just get a filthy spirit
that begets diseases.
That's how it was for Koriko.
Koriko succumbed to his hunger
and ate a mouse.
The red deer, huh?
I wonder if there really is one.
I should've followed Dad's advice
and settled for a rabbit.
When it was still autumn,
I could've caught all the rabbits I wanted.
I mustn't fall asleep.
Mustn't sleep...
Mustn't...
I need to do something
to distract myself.
The red deer...
Yes, yes. You're good!
They look so alive, you'd probably find the real thing less convincing, Bogud.
I guess the spirit of the red deer
really does possess you, after all.
Whatever you try to draw,
it turns out spectacular.
To tell you the truth, I didn't want to believe
you'd brought down a red deer,
which had proved too tough
even for Koriko.
Why... You lucky rascal!
What's more,
you even managed to make Fayau,
the fairest woman of our village, your wife!
You, yes, you, the lucky rascal!
Because word is, you've actually been smitten with Fayau for ages.
You lecher!
What's that?
Did you really expect us to overlook
that sudden fatherhood?
What do you mean?
What now? The two of you live under
the same roof, yet you didn't realize it?
Congratulations, buddy. Congratulations.
Your mother is gonna be overjoyed
to hold her first grandchild this fall.
You lucky bastard!
You, you! Yes, you!
Where's Fayau?
Fayau!
Hold it there, Bogud!
There're more plates to paint!
Maybe I should've kept that
to myself this time.
Even I have a loose tongue every now and then.
Fayau!
Bogud!
We did it! We did it, Fayau!
Huh? What's the matter, Bogud?
Don't keep secrets from me!
The elder told me the truth!
I've poured a part of my soul into this red deer amulet.
I'm sure that the deer's spirit will help
to protect you and our unborn child.
Bogud...
Fayau.
By drawing another person,
you bring misfortune upon him.
But that curse is powerless
against the power of the red deer.
Look, we found our happiness,
and we're not about to let go of it.
What's wrong?!
Fayon!
Sir!
What is that?
It's a picture of a woman.
I know it's a picture.
What ritual was it carved for?
Let's see... The Tangad tribe lives
along this part of the river.
I wonder which deity they worship
by carving a woman's picture into the stone.
The Tangad tribe has a woman
this beautiful among them?
Fayon!
Sir!
We'll attack Tangad!
Huh? B-But sir, we need to head north
as soon as we can.
Right, about that...
The snow on Jinst Uul peak
didn't melt last year.
That means we can cross the Northern Corridor this year to the new land
that we left our homeland for.
But look at that.
The long journey's used up nearly
all of our food supplies.
We need to attack and plunder Tangad for food and warm clothing anyhow.
And if they also have a woman this beautiful
among them, I'll take her as well.
Let's go!
I can't believe my ears, Bogud!
So you did break that law, after all?!
You drew a picture of another person?
Look. A catastrophe befell
our whole tribe, not just you.
Our men slaughtered, our women abducted.
Food, livestock... They took everything!
Tangad has been...
razed to the ground!
Fayau... Where's Fayau?
The northern tribe took her.
Fayau!
Where do you think you're going?
What are you going to do?!
Fayau... I'll save Fayau!
You big dummy!
You gonna do that in your current state?!
Now, let's calm down, Bogud.
You've been badly injured.
You slept for three days and three nights.
Groaning from fever too.
You can be sure that the northern tribe is far, far away by now,
heading for the Northern Corridor.
The Northern Corridor?
It's a legend of their tribe.
If the snow doesn't melt
on Jinst Uul all year round,
in the following year, the Northern Corridor will emerge from the ocean floor.
By crossing that,
they're hoping to find the new world.
The new world?
Never mind. Similar legends have been passed down in every tribe.
For example, some legends say
you need to head south instead of north.
South?
"Make your way south, and cross the sea
on a wooden vehicle they call a boat.
And you'll reach the new world all the same."
Our tribe was blessed with verdant lands.
The thought of abandoning our homeland
and taking our families on a meandering journey never crossed our minds.
But the northern tribes weren't so lucky.
So I suppose their chieftain Shalab
finally decided to take the plunge.
Where are you going?
After them. To the Northern Corridor.
I need to catch up with them
as soon as I can and take Fayau back.
Don't be stupid! It's way too late
to catch up with them now.
Bogud! You're supposed
to help me bury the fallen!
Don't you understand, Bogud?
You brought this disaster upon us!
The northern tribe probably stops to rest at night.
If I ride day and night at full speed,
I'll catch up with them sooner or later!
Fayau!
Fayau! Fayau!
Bogud!
Bogud! Bogud!
Fayau!
Fayau...
The spirit of the red deer
is watching over us!
...watching over us...
The spirit of the red deer will never give up!
...never give up...
Fayau!
Fayau...
I'll come for you! Believe me!
Gilbert, this is it. Yes, I'm positive.
This piece is going to be more captivating
than anything I've released so far.
Well, that's a relief.
It was well worth the effort
of showing you this place.
Okay, let's return to the hotel.
I want to write down the score tonight.
You'd do me a big favor.
Once we get back to New York, I'll have
to make the rounds of studios and players.
Ah, one more thing, Leslie...
What is it?
Well, I think I owe you an apology.
I shouldn't have said it.
About the reporter girl and all...
Whatever. I've forgotten it already.
Gilbert!
It's an earthquake!
How is everyone?! Anyone hurt?!
Man, that was one helluva earthquake.
It's not over.
The earthquake will strike again soon.
All my life, I've had this mysterious precognition ability.
I remember what happened
many years ago.
Back when I lived in San Diego... my grandpa...
That's how it happened, Flora.
In bygone times, our ancestors
built a big, big raft and crossed this wide ocean on it.
Yay! Big raft! Big raft!
Jeez, the birthmark's gotten bigger again.
Really, lotsa weird stuff's happening today.
It's here!
The Historical Era
____ The Historical Era ____
Something unheard of
is coming to our island.
It's a perfectly and unquestionably
isolated island.
Hey, Tyler, how far do you think we've drifted?
Ah, I've also been thinking about that
for these past few days.
Since we drifted south from the equator,
we're probably somewhere north of Tahiti.
Huh? Tahiti?
Tahiti is regularly visited by English ships.
Maybe one of those could rescue us.
Yeah, that's what I thought, Channing.
You're only saying that nonsense
because it gives you peace of mind.
What was that?
Hey, Jones?
You know it as well as I do, Tyler.
If sailing vessels ever visited this place,
the island natives would know about it.
If you don't believe me,
just ask them yourself.
Jones?
Nobody believes it when I tell them
about ships propelled by the wind.
When I tell them about giant vessels, holding hundreds of people,
they just laugh in my face.
Enough, Jones.
They've never seen
a seafaring ship in their lives.
This island is far from any English maritime trade route.
We're nowhere near Tahiti.
Jones, you've said enough!
Channing. Hey, Ed Channing!
You've upset Channing.
He was the one on lookout that night.
But no matter who's on lookout, you can't avoid an underwater volcanic eruption.
It happened too suddenly.
Listen, Jones, you should stop
blaming that on Channing.
He's easily disheartened.
I wasn't putting the blame
on Ed Channing.
If I had to blame someone,
I'd blame you first, Tyler.
And I'd blame myself for the sins
I indulged in during those 20 days adrift!
It's over now.
Forget about it and move on!
I can't possibly forget it! Twelve sailors took refuge on the boat.
But only the three of us survived!
And yet you were among those three.
Channing! You clumsy twerp!
The ship ran aground
because you didn't pay attention!
Captain! But you were also
dead drunk and asleep!
Silence! How am I to explain
this enormous loss?!
The ship's hold is still
chock-full of barrels!
And those barrels are full of whale oil!
That oil would fetch a fortune in gold!
Save your breath, Captain.
There's still a chance the ship won't sink!
In any case, we should take shelter in the sea,
or else we'll get caught in the next eruption!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Another one will blow the ship to smithereens,
along with our whale oil!
Whale oil is all you care about!
If it's so important to you,
why don't you return to the ship
on your own, Captain?
Fine! I'll do just that, you coward!
Turn the boat back, deckhands!
It's hopeless!
Huh? Look!
Hey! Look at this!
What is it, Channing?
The officers' boat is gone.
No sign of our whaling ship either!
What? The boats were supposed to be tied together with ropes.
Also to the raft with all our supplies and water!
It's been cut!
Cut with a knife.
What's the meaning of this?!
What happened last night?!
How come we can't even see
our whaling ship now?!
The officers abandoned us.
That's the only explanation!
Jones, do we have any water
or provisions on this boat?
None, except for a single barrel of wine.
Wine will do for now. All right...
Listen to me, everyone. There's no way
to know how many days we'll be adrift.
Or if we'll be saved at all.
That's entirely up to God's grace now.
But we'll do whatever we can, regardless.
From now on, I'll be deciding how much wine
each man gets daily to quench his thirst.
And I won't tolerate anyone disobeying that rule.
When you can't take it anymore,
start cursing the bastards who marooned us!
For the first ten days,
everyone put up with it.
But all hell broke loose
in the next ten days.
Everyone was at their limit.
Men started going crazy with thirst,
and things were about to turn ugly.
But Tyler, nobody on that boat
was as fiendish as you.
You showed no mercy to those
who transgressed the rules.
You made Ed Channing and me
jettison bodies into the sea every day.
What could I do?
It was all in hope of a better tomorrow.
Hope? What kind of tomorrow
do you envision for us now?
That swine...
I'll take Captain Violet's head
for what he's done.
That's... my hope.
No... They hadn't caused
that extraordinary sensation.
Oh! Now you've done it!
There!
What is he thinking?
I see you've been busy, Jones.
While resenting our situation, you're actually enjoying your island life, aren't you?
I think that girl's name was Laia?
You've got a good eye, friend.
A castaway romance?
Good for you, but don't get used to it.
What do you mean?
Eventually, we'll get out of here
and return to England.
What are you gonna do with Laia then?
Leave her behind?
I'll take her with me, of course.
Will Laia agree?
If you take her to a bustling city,
her island beauty will soon wither.
Don't you think so?
Will you still love her
like you do now?
No, I'm not reproaching you,
just telling you not to take it to heart.
Even if you say so, Tyler,
it's been half a year now.
We've burned countless smoke signals,
but not a single ship has ever stopped by.
Nothing but seagulls
crapping on it every now and then...
I'm really starting to lose hope.
Maybe finding a new wife and settling here isn't such a bad idea, after all.
Some amenities are missing, but other
than that, it's a relaxed, carefree paradise.
Maybe it's a paradise, maybe not.
But the truth is,
this island bores me to death!
Channing, let's build a ship.
A ship?
I've changed my mind.
If no ships are coming our way,
we should build one ourselves.
You're a shipwright, aren't you?
If the three of us join forces,
we can build a vessel big enough
to take us to another island. Right?
Jones, what are you doing?
Making a confession.
Confession? What's a confession?
I confess my sins to God
and ask for forgiveness.
But God is not here.
No, it's not someone who is here or there...
God lives on the mountain.
Laia.
Listen, Laia.
Because you're going to England with me someday, I need you to remember this.
God... is unseen by the eye
and imperceptible to touch.
Laia knows. Laia saw God.
Jones!
Here. God. Here.
Jeez. Where's that loafer Jones
when you need him?
I've told him over and over to help us!
Oh, he probably found some secluded spot
and is having a good time with Laia there.
'Cause she's the only thing on his mind.
You've gotta be kidding me!
We three need to work on this together,
or else we'll never leave this island!
I wish we could ask the locals for help.
Ain't getting anything from them, I reckon.
Fayau!
Fayau! Fayau!
Laia?
I'm doing it. I'm crossing the southern seas
to the new world.
Fayau, I'll find you,
and I'll see you again!
Wh-What is it?
We... help you.
The men of the island
will help with your work.
Well, I'd... appreciate that.
But we have a condition.
What condition?
We build a big boat.
One that takes every person on the island.
This condition... You accept?
What's gotten into you?
Where will the islanders go
after leaving such a nice island?
We go to the eastern continent.
Eastern? Maybe he's talking about South America?
Long ago, our distant ancestor
got stranded on this island.
It happened while he was trying to cross
the sea and get to the eastern continent.
But he couldn't build a ship big enough.
Our ancestor passed away on this island.
It is essential that we go east.
That's quite the news!
Why are you only telling me now?
We forgot. We angered our ancestor.
Look.
We've woken up to our fate...
to leave this island.
What? You can't see it?
Idiot! Did you fall asleep there or what?
What is it, Victor?
Our idiotic lookout let the Florence
slip out of sight.
Frodo, you scallywag!
You're not eating tonight!
Are you sure they didn't notice us?
That's not funny, after we've trailed them for so long!
Those spices are currently
the priciest commodity in the world.
But the Florence is hiding
where they're getting it really well!
So you decided to follow them in secret
to get a piece of it for yourself, huh?
Aren't you a cunning devil?
Now that they've slipped away, it's a fiasco!
Blast. All that money, wasted!
I'd rather have your problems after losing
both my ship and my oil to the sea.
I ended up washing up at Tahiti
and rotting there for a year.
Show some gratitude. I only saved you
because I owe you one!
We're not making as much progress
as I thought we would.
It's Jones.
That bastard must be out of his mind.
Did he ever come here
to lend us a hand?
All he and Laia ever do is
go hiking in the mountains!
Yeah, they're visiting the stone monument
with the engraved red deer.
When I asked him why,
he said they're looking after it.
Like, they mow the grass there,
polish the thing.
So I told him, "Forget about the damn monument and come help us on the beach!"
That nearly brought him
to tears, apparently.
"I have to listen to my wife now!"
Look, Tyler, what I've been thinking is...
The elder suddenly expressed a wish to head east.
Could it also be connected
to the restoration of that monument?
Cut it out. You're freaking me out.
You think that monument was a vessel
for their ancestor's despair,
and now that's transferred
to the islanders?
No, it only affects Laia.
See how good I am? Your tattoo is identical to the carving!
Now you, Jones.
Laia, what's this all about?
Why do we have to tattoo a red deer
on our shoulders?
The red deer is our guardian.
For Laia and Jones.
It will protect us and our child.
Our child?
L-Laia!
The spirit of the red deer protects
the future of children.
I really had no idea, Laia.
That's great!
So we're going to have a baby?
It's useless. They shook us off.
Can't be helped.
We'll track them from Tahiti once more.
Victor, look at that island.
What?
First time I'm seeing it,
but that's very timely.
Our freshwater supplies are running low.
Helmsman, hard to port!
Well, I think it turned out
not half bad. Right?
Tyler, this jerrybuilt thing
isn't going anywhere.
You're a navigator yourself, so you ought to know.
What are you saying, all of a sudden?
The islanders are totally invested now!
That's just them.
But I'm not boarding this junk.
It has a large frame,
but nothing holds it together.
You go tell that to them!
I'll watch you getting stoned!
What's wrong, Laia?
It's here.
What?
What's here?
Laia!
What happened?
Oh? Oh!
Hey, Tyler! It's a ship!
What? What did you say?
Tyler, can you believe they've arrived
at such a good time?
We can go home! We can go back to England on a normal, seaworthy ship!
Wait, Channing!
Huh? What's gotten into you?
The slipshod raft we put together
is nowhere near as safe as that ship!
This is our best hope!
Let's meet the captain and ask for help!
Don't be so impatient!
Let's observe the situation first.
Nothing but a line of clueless faces.
They'd probably be happy to fetch all the water we need for a glass ball.
Prepare to disembark!
Wait a minute, Victor.
That island has more to offer
than just some water.
What is it?
There, hiding in the shadow of that palm tree,
an excited crowd of young women.
Every single one is an exquisite beauty.
What are you getting at?
Victor! Capturing them and reselling them to a slave trader, of course.
And who's the cunning devil now?
Ready your muskets, you scallywags!
It's a ship!
A normal ship!
Jones?
Do you get it now? They're pirates!
Heh, I don't care if they're pirates.
If they can save us,
I don't care what they do for a living!
Get it together, Channing.
We owe the islanders big time
for what they've done for us.
I'll take a closer look
at the pirate captain.
No need to rush.
They're still stunned by that last volley.
Load your muskets slowly.
Violet!
Man, this is flabbergasting.
Why is Violet here?
No, whatever. That doesn't matter.
It must be God's gift to me.
O Lord, I am grateful.
Amen.
I'll kill him now!
Tyler!
Channing!
Hey, Jones, stop Tyler!
He's going to attack the pirates
all on his own!
You'll just get yourself killed!
Jones, by God's grace,
my boredom is over.
I can now kill that swine Violet
without going anywhere.
But why...
Tyler, is it really worth throwing your life away for this?
Have you forgotten already?
Before getting here, we had to throw nine of our crewmates into the sea.
Whose fault was it?
Violet's!
Jones, it falls to you to take the islanders
to the eastern continent.
Laia fell in love with you.
It's your fate.
Channing, have some confidence.
This vessel you built is magnificent.
Yes, it'll cross the Pacific and beyond in a breeze. Okay, Channing?
Take care!
Tyler!
Isn't it about time
we rounded up the women?
What?!
Violet!
How come...
It's him!
he's here?!
Jones!
Laia, hurry up!
It's here.
What do you mean, Laia?
The biggest one yet... is here!
Oh! I-It's a miracle!
Our raft is afloat!
Head east, my descendants!
Cross over to the eastern lands,
following the guidance of the red deer.
Oh jeez. The birthmark darkens more and more.
I wonder how long we've been here.
I lost all sense of time a while ago.
Gilbert, what was that?
Well, probably deep cave creatures.
Deep cave creatures?
Life forms that adapted to living in constant darkness in the depths of the earth.
But because it's so dark in here,
there's no way to tell what they look like.
So the sound is the only evidence
of their existence?
Leslie? What's so funny?
I thought to myself,
if Leslie Mardoff disappeared
without a trace,
what evidence would be left
of his existence in our era at all?
For some reason,
that seemed funny to me.
You've released countless pieces already,
enough to leave a mark.
Maybe, but it would probably
be my reputation
as an infamous womanizer,
involved in many scandals.
Even if they're all fictions that the media made up on the go.
The scandals are untrue?
It was too much of a bother,
so I never took the trouble to deny them.
Gilbert, I believe firmly there's a person in this world who's destined to be with me.
Laugh at me for being old-fashioned,
but I've always believed that.
Gilbert!
Leslie, forgive me.
I shouldn't have brought you
to this god-forsaken place.
Stay strong! We'll be saved!
Someone will save us.
Yes, I don't know why,
but that's what my intuition says.
That's because you're still young.
No, it's because I believe in destiny!
Gilbert... Gilbert!
Gilbert!
It’s a tsunami!
That last earthquake caused a tsunami
in the underground lake!
Gilbert!
Hello? Is someone there?
Hey! We're here!
Hang on! I'll lower the rope now!
What's this?
Must be the deep cave creatures.
The light emitted by creatures living
in constant darkness proves they really exist!
Catch the rope!
Hey! Can't you lower
the rope a little more?
Huh? What?
The rope! Just a little lower!
When you fall in love with someone
The excitement pushes you forward
With just a glance at your profile
I fall in love with you before I know it
I fell in love long ago
But it feels strange, as if we're inside a myth
When I'm with you, my heart fills with light
Warming me up even during the coldest winter
It's dizzying to follow the fate of a shooting star
But it'll lead the two of us down the path of love
Intuition tells me that our encounter is no coincidence
And it is surely bound to last
You're the only one who can reach my heart
But it's so painful, I can't find the words
Even if it's going to be dizzying,
I'll follow you to the ends of the earth
I always knew it would come to this
It'll be dizzying for sure,
but I know I'll fall in love with you
I know I won't be able to stop loving you
Translation & Timing
Translation Check
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Yume
Collector
ImAWasteOfHair
Topper3000
Uchuu
anonymous