During the war, many girls in Hiroshima
studied and worked as
streetcar conductors and drivers
in place of the men
who had gone off to battle.
This story is an animated adaptation
based on the memoirs of former
female streetcar conductors.
Orphan Fansubs presents
The First Tram
Runs To Hiroshima
Summer, 1944
Rise and shine! It's morning!
Tae-chan, this is my head!
The ladder is more to the right.
Sorry.
We gotta hurry, or we won't get seats.
Yayoi-chan, save my seat too.
Tsuki-chan, you stare into the mirror every morning. Don't you ever get tired of it?
She must have a real funny face
if she doesn't get bored looking at it.
That would be you, Tae.
Ah, shoot!
This bit here is sticking out.
Just lick it down. It'll stay.
The military police ain't gonna yell
at you 'cause your hair's a mess.
Come on, let's go.
We need to look presentable.
We see tons of people every single day.
Even in wartime, we've gotta look proper.
We're representing the nation, after all.
You say it's embarrassing, but isn't
looking neat the same as looking pretty?
I just wanna look put-together.
Very well, we'll make you
look put-together!
Tae!
Ah... Not much there.
Mine's gotta be the scrawniest of all.
They were all the same.
That's what you get for relying on others.
First come, first served.
Which means mine is the scrawniest, after all?
Quit it.
You're already taller than us.
You don't need extra.
And you're tiny, so you can get by with less.
I said quit it.
Yayoi-chan, your mom lives nearby.
What's that got to do with anything?
If you go see her,
she'll give you something else to eat.
Yeah, you can lean on her anytime.
I won't lean on her.
But you go to your mom's inn
every time you have a day off.
Even if I go there, she's working.
I'm not getting any special treatment.
If that were so, there'd be no need to go at all.
Fine, then I won't.
See you after lunch.
Yeah.
Bye!
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Kageruu
Tange Sazen
Restoration
Sorry, is there anyone else
without a ticket here?
Excuse me.
Yes, here you go.
Next stop is just up ahead.
Take a break while you can.
Hurry back to the rear.
Oh, right.
Please move all the way inside the car.
We'll be departing shortly.
Yamamura-sensei!
Hey! Thanks for the hard work.
Teacher, hurry, hurry!
Perfect timing.
That's better!
We're actually on our way back to the depot.
And when you get back,
you'll have classes, won't you?
Yes.
So my voice'll be your lullaby today?
Sorry.
Guess I'll take it easy today
and pretend I don't see you nodding off.
No, I'll stay awake as much as I can.
What's there?
My mother works over there.
I see.
If she's that close by, dorm life
shouldn't feel that lonely to you.
You can go see her anytime.
No.
Just seeing the building whenever the tram
passes by makes me feel better.
I try not to go too often.
It's not fair to the others.
When Japan wins and the war ends,
we'll all be able to live our best life.
Till then, I'll be doing my best
to serve my country as a conductor.
For your country?
Yes.
Of course...
Indomitable Spirit
Hey, wait!
I found a pretty seashell!
Where? Where?
First place, wins!
Hey! No fair!
Here! Here!
Wait for us!
Teacher.
Aren't you supposed to be teaching?
This is part of class too.
You're just goofing off.
What are you plotting?
Nothing at all.
Isn't this fun?
It is!
It's fun, but...
Is it okay to have fun when everyone else
is working so hard for the country?
Of course, we have to work hard too.
What I mean is...
How should I put it?
The trams you girls run
take people where they need to go.
Take them to places they enjoy.
The trams are the symbol of Hiroshima,
the embodiment of our pride.
So I want you to have happy memories too.
Especially in times like these.
Oh, stop already!
I hope we can all come again next summer.
That'd be good.
Yayoi!
Let's take a picture!
Sure!
Summer, 1945
Thank you.
We'll send word to each neighborhood.
So this road's going to be cleared out?
Our house is being torn down too.
Guess I'll have to go back to the countryside.
This area really is a danger zone, huh?
Hey... Tae!
First come, first served!
Think war's "first come, first served" too?
Of course.
Then what're you supposed to be first at?
The first to land on enemy shores,
to carry out an air raid, in everything!
In everything, huh.
And yet, you girls have yet to get there.
Get where?
Your first period.
Tsuki-chan, already?
First come, first served. Right, Tae?
I never aimed for that.
It doesn't count as losing.
That's what I'm talking about.
Laughing at others is rude!
It's no time to be laughing.
That's over Kure.
This one's real.
Kinda pretty, isn't it?
What are you saying?
There've been a lot of them lately.
Don't worry.
Hiroshima's the capital of water.
Somebody said even America won't bomb us
out of respect. I heard it on the tram.
But others say they just might.
I hope everyone's okay.
I hope Mom's okay.
I wanna go home...
Don't be such a baby.
Stop acting like you're the only grown-up.
Well, I am grown-up.
I'm a kid, and I wanna go home.
Tae-chan...
Yayoi.
Mom...
What's with the long face?
There was an air-raid warning.
I was just wondering if you were okay.
That's all.
Come on, get inside.
Really?
Come on.
Okay.
Myotoku-in Temple Seido Kokinkyo
You must be hungry.
Wow, red-bean rice balls!
I'm still on shift, so eat that
and go on home, okay?
What's wrong?
I wonder if Yasuo and the others are all right.
A letter came from their evacuation place.
They're doing fine and studying hard.
So don't worry about them.
And our uncle in Shimane...
You think he's all right?
I hear they're all doing fine.
Everyone's doing their best
for the country.
And you're also doing
important work on the tram.
Even if you're lonely,
you've gotta hang in there.
I know.
Eat, then head back.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Your daughter left?
Yes, she just did.
You could've stayed with her a little longer.
You live so close, but you hardly see each other at all.
She's decided not to come too often.
She doesn't want to get spoiled.
Yet people are saying that whenever her tram goes by, she always stares out the window.
Just got to hang in there a little longer.
Myotoku-in Temple Seido Kokinkyo
Folks, we're passing the Gogoku Shrine.
Please offer your prayers.
May the divine wind come soon.
What are you doing?
We're getting off too.
We're getting off! We're getting off!
Yayoi.
Wake up!
You fell asleep.
If you're late for curfew,
you'll get scolded.
Mom...
Still half-asleep?
Since when did you get so spoiled?
Yayoi.
Here.
Fujishima Shrine
I already have a charm.
It's a charm for safe delivery.
Your father put it in your hand
when you were born.
Maybe it'll watch over you.
Welcome back.
It was a close call,
but we covered for you.
Thank you.
Here.
Red bean paste!
How many days has it been
since I last tried it?
Sorry, Tae-chan.
I ended up chasing after my mom.
Since you're giving me this, I forgive you.
No way. You were awake?
Is your mom okay?
Yeah.
Well, that's all good, then.
All right, I gotta sleep now.
I'm on the first shift in the morning.
Goodnight.
Miyajima, huh.
Hard to believe it's been a whole year.
That sure was fun.
I wish we could all go again.
I don't want that...
I wanna go with my family.
Me too.
Looks like it'll be another hot day.
Sure does.
At least the late shift's cooler for us.
But I guess Tae always prefers
the early shift, for some reason.
'Cause it fits her motto
of "First come, first served."
See you later, then.
Yeah, later.
Yeah.
Can you hear me?
Anything hurting?
Tsuki-chan...
I got unlucky.
Tae-chan...
Shimada
I don't think she wanted
to come first in that.
No, she didn't.
You okay on your own?
I'll be fine.
I just need to go check
if my mom made it.
Harukawa
She's fine.
You should rest too, Yayoi-chan.
You look pale.
Maybe you've got a fever.
I'm fine. If I take a break when I'm not even hurt,
it wouldn't feel fair to the others.
I'm hungry, that's all.
You should try looking
for your mother again.
Uno, how are you feeling?
Much better.
I'm young, after all.
Good.
Teacher...
What happened?
Japan lost?!
Hiroshima belongs to America now?
No!
Hiroshima is Japanese!
It's our town. It doesn't "belong" to anyone.
But it's dead now!
Yayoi-chan...
It's not dead. It just... stopped.
They dropped some new terrible type
of bomb on it. A lot of people were killed.
But some are still alive.
Plenty are still alive.
If people live, the town lives.
Harukawa-kun, could you do
something for us?
We need to run a tram.
The Koi-Tenma line.
Head office wants us to operate it.
Teacher...
You said the tram is the symbol of Hiroshima.
It takes people where they want to go,
takes them to places they enjoy.
I don't want to go there.
That place is hell.
I don't want to go to hell.
Harukawa-kun...
A tram doesn't go to hell.
That's why we run it.
To show everyone this isn't hell.
Are you all right?
You can sit down if you want.
Okay.
It's a rough duty for both of us.
But we're alive, and that's all that matters.
Everything's a mess.
Nothing in sight is still standing.
Oh, we don't charge people anymore.
Just take them aboard.
Driver?
What are those?
Oh, that? Because there were so many corpses,
the maggots infested a lot of them.
Really, I wonder how many were killed.
H-Hey...
Won't you take us on?
Wait!
Can we get on?
Where's this going?
Bound for Tenmacho.
That's a godsend!
No fare needed.
Thank you.
We're going to Tenmacho!
Bound for Tenmacho. Get on.
Tenmacho bound!
Can't sleep?
You know, when I last visited my mom,
I had a dream.
My dad was there, and my mom and my little brothers too, and I was the conductor.
So my dad got off the tram,
and then my mom went with him,
but no matter how hard I rang the signal,
the tram wouldn't stop.
Yayoi-chan...
If Mom were still alive,
I'd have found her by now.
The other day I rode a tram out from Koi,
and I was scared.
Scared I was boarding a tram bound for hell.
But when the passengers got on,
and it started moving...
I don't know why, but I felt relieved.
I don't even know why.
Yeah.
I want to ride the tram again.
I want to ride again soon too.
Tenmacho bound!
The First Tram
Runs To Hiroshima
The End
The First Tram
Runs To Hiroshima
The End
Translation & Timing
Editing
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Collectr
Uchuu
anonymous