"Dioxin" Movie Production Committee
Gogo Visual Planning
Magic Bus
Amusement Media Academy
Nippon Publishing Sales
This story is based
on real events.
1976, Summer
Northern Italy,
the town of Seveso
Get ready!
Start!
Giulia! Good start!
Looking good, Lucio!
You've almost caught her!
Brother! Go for it!
Not even a ten-meter
handicap could help me!
I can't compete with you at all!
That's nothing new. You couldn't compete with me in a million years.
Congratulations, Giulia.
It's a new personal record. Look!
Yay! I did it!
Amazing, Giulia! You broke
your record on your birthday!
Life on Earth
Congratulations, Giulia!
Congratulations, Giulia! Congratulations!
Thanks, Enrico, Lucio.
Thanks, Maria, Angelo.
My name is Giuliana Bianchi.
Today, July 10th, was the start
of summer vacation.
Right on my 11th birthday!
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, amazing!
Looks totally delicious!
Yummy, looks great!
Your mama and I made
this cake together.
And I helped too!
That's right. Marco helped us by putting on the candles.
Right. All eleven of them.
It's 12:30 already?
Tonio and Anna sure are late.
I hope they come soon.
My stomach is growling.
Same here.
Dear! Dear!
What's the matter?
Tonio just called from the hospital.
From the hospital?
Something happened to him?
You could say that,
because Anna is expecting a child!
Anna is expecting a baby?
I-Is that true, Milena?
Yes. He said she's in her second month.
She'll give birth next spring!
Really? So I'm becoming
a grandpa soon?
All right! Everyone, let's celebrate!
Agreed!
To celebrate Giulia's birthday,
and Anna and Tonio's child...
Cheers!
ICMESA Plant
What the hell is that?
What's this powder?
That cloud looks like it'll be here soon.
The wind is blowing it this way.
What's this stench?
It smells like chlorine.
Everyone, get inside the house, now!
Leo, come with me!
Milena, Giulia, shut the windows tight!
Leon, come to me, please!
Maria, hurry up!
I'm coming!
Are you all right?
What could this be?
I don't know, but I feel like
something terrible has happened.
Тоnio!
Anna!
Anna, are you okay?
My eyes are burning!
Anna! Anna!
Not long after that, the white powder stopped falling from the sky.
Not even a single cicada was chirping.
Everything was silent and white.
It was an eerie sight.
The next morning, the thick layer of white powder had nearly disappeared.
However, in the sky to the southeast,
an ominous gray cloud still floated eerily.
Good morning, Mom.
Good morning. Giulia, look at this.
I picked them just now.
They're all covered with some kind of oily film.
What a pity.
I wanted to take them to Anna
when I visit her later.
Visit her?
She felt poorly and was very sleepy.
But she now has a baby inside her,
so I'm worried sick.
Maybe it was that white powder?
Perhaps. I can't be sure,
but Tonio complained about a headache
before going to work.
Mom, take me with you.
I'm worried about Anna.
I'm coming too!
Marco, weren't you going
to the pool today?
I'll go after we come back from Anna's.
Mom, are you okay?
I have a bit of a headache too.
Are you all right?
My eyes hurt a little.
Perhaps it's because of that white powder, after all.
Coming!
Oh, it's Anna's mother.
Why, Grandma Sonia!
Sister!
Are you all right, Anna?
Yes. My headache and the pain in my eyes
have subsided a lot.
Really? I'm glad to hear that.
Tonio can't get any rest because
he's so busy at the vet clinic.
Grandma Sonia really helped us out
by agreeing to look after me.
Thank you very much.
No need. Anna and I are neighbors.
It's only natural.
One way or another, eat a lot today,
and have a good rest.
You can't let it affect the child in your belly.
That's true. Now's the most crucial period for its development.
Right.
Get ready! Start!
Go!
Run, Giulia!
Are you okay, Giulia?!
My eyes still hurt,
and my stamina is gone.
Maybe you shouldn't
force yourself for now?
Perhaps you're right.
Okay, let's call it a day.
Hey, any idea where Enrico is?
It's really unusual for him not to be here.
Maybe he's busy with something?
Well, let's go to our usual hangout for now.
Maybe he'll join us later.
That one!
Thank you. Whoa! It looks delicious!
Hey, maybe we should peel the plums
before eating them?
You're right. There's some sort of oily sheen on them.
Maybe it's because of the white powder?
Don't worry about it.
Just wipe it off, and it'll be safe to eat.
Yummy!
Still, I'd rather eat it peeled.
That cloud's still there.
It makes me uneasy, somehow.
Come on!
It will disperse when the wind picks up. Don't worry.
I can't stop worrying,
even if you tell me to!
My stepsister's body went haywire
after she got showered with that powder.
Just what could that powder have been?
Hey, have you heard?
Apparently, the white powder fell
because of an accident at the ICMESA plant,
about two kilometers north of here.
The ICMESA plant?
Yeah. The newspaper had
a small story about it.
What were they producing at that plant?
Some chemicals, apparently,
but I couldn't tell which ones.
Hey!
Enrico's here!
Guys, you mustn't eat those plums!
Huh? Why?
Some guys from the Health Department​
came to see my dad in his office.
I overheard a bit of their conversation.
Sorry to bother you on Sunday.
No problem.
The Health Department has been swamped
with inquiries from local people, Mayor Carlo.
Then give me all the details about the accident at the ICMESA plant.
The ICMESA plant is owned by a company called Givaudan, based in Switzerland.
In turn, Givaudan is a subsidiary of the Hoffmann-La Roche company.
Roche is a multinational conglomerate that makes pharmaceuticals and pesticides, right?
Roche?
As far as we know, the ICMESA plant was producing a chemical called TCP.
TCP?
Yes. The full name is trichlorophenol.
It's used in the production of perfumes, cosmetics, surgical antiseptic, and so on.
The chemical reaction used to make it
caused yesterday's accident.
So it's likely that the compound
released into the air was TCP.
However, even though TCP
is a powerful irritant,
able to cause temporary
headaches and eye pain,
we believe it has
no other harmful effects.
Really? Well, that's the first comforting news today.
Thank you both for letting me know.
So they say the headache and burning eyes are only temporary?
See now? There's no reason
to worry at all!
I wouldn't say that.
As soon as the Health guys left,
some top executives from the ICMESA plant came to see my dad.
Executives?
And I can't help worrying
about what they said.
We've sent samples of what fell on Seveso to Roche HQ in Switzerland.
Until the analysis is available,
we'd like you to discourage the residents of Seveso
from eating locally grown fruits,
vegetables, and the like.
You're saying that eating plants affected by that powder is harmful to people?
No, I didn't say that, exactly.
Still, Mr. Mayor, even if
we find it's totally harmless,
you can never be too cautious.
As they say, better safe than sorry.
I hear you.
Please notify me immediately
when the results of the analysis are available.
Something's not quite right here.
Strange, isn't it?
They say that TCP does no harm,
yet they don't want us to eat local produce?
What's this mean?
Hey, why don't we try to find out for sure
by going to the ICMESA plant together?
Find out for sure?
We'll sneak into the plant, secretly.
Sitting here and fretting
won't get us anywhere.
Giulia, say what you want, but that's obviously going too far. Right, guys?
No, I agree with Giulia.
It's worth looking into.
I think so too.
We may learn the truth
if we go to the site.
And you, Maria?
I'll come too. Better that than worrying.
Now, what about you, Angelo?
Are you in or out?
Sheesh, fine. I'll come too.
Great! Then the ICMESA accident
investigation team is ready to go!
Yeah!
Now then, how do we sneak in?
Leave it to me. I have just the plan for it.
Even though you didn't wanna come in the first place?
Now I'm committed to doing it right.
So what's your plan?
Maria and I will try to distract that guy, somehow,
while you, Lucio, and Giulia sneak in.
But I don't think I can.
Don't worry. I'll do the talking.
Excuse me, sir?
What is it?
We seem to have lost our way.
Where were you going?
The northern train station in Seveso.
It's supposed to be this way.
Yes, it is.
Well, then. You start here
and pass by two traffic lights.
Then turn right and walk for 200 meters.
On the street corner, you'll see a school.
I suddenly remembered where it is!
Thank you, sir.
Thanks.
But you know, it's a mighty strange thing.
The guys managing this place flatly refuse
to explain what the hell happened.
What do they take us workers for?
The big shots who own it
are hiding their dirty laundry.
They think it's okay to dump the chemicals they're making into the plant's wastewater.
I wonder what they're doing.
They seem to be wiping up
the white powder that fell yesterday.
I still can't believe it.
The pressure in the heated reactor over there
got so high that the safety valve blew.
Yeah. It was left unattended and overheated badly.
He said, "The heated reactor"?
So it's in that building?
Come on.
Wow! It's huge!
Is this the reactor
that caused the accident?
There are piles of white powder on it.
Oh! There's a hole over there!
It must be where that cloud came from.
Hey, you!
What are you doing here?
Will Enrico and the others be okay?
Maria, Enrico is the only thing
on your mind lately.
Is that so?
What are those guys up to?
Where are they going?
Let's follow them.
Yeah.
So you sneaked in here to find out more about the accident that happened yesterday, huh?
Yes. Some of the things I heard
about it were really worrying.
Like what?
So the plant managers were
discussing it with the mayor?
Exactly. Why would they first say that TCP is harmless,
but then forbid eating local produce?
Don't you think that's odd?
It felt fishy to me too.
They're hiding something about this plant.
Why's that?
When the accident had just happened...
Everyone! Hurry home at once
and take a shower!
Boss, what just happened here?
What's this white powder on all of us?
We don't know yet!
We'll explain later, but for now, just go home! Got that?
It wasn't like him to be that flustered.
Immediately after the incident, Roche sent
a team of soil technicians to the area.
Soil technicians?
What are they doing?
I don't know.
I'll go ask.
W-Wait, Angelo!
Sir, what are you doing here?
You're working?
Yes. Uh, I'm sending soil
samples to Switzerland.
Why are you sending them to Switzerland?
So they can be analyzed at Hoffman-La Roche.
Hey! We're supposed to keep our mouths shut, even with kids!
Ah, right. I'm sorry.
I'm very busy. Off you go.
Hoffmann-La Roche?
Good. You can leave this way
without anyone noticing.
Thanks.
But that was a close call.
Don't risk coming here again.
My name is Vito.
If you need more info,
I'll tell you what I know.
Come see me at this address.
Okay!
Huh? So this guy Vito helped you,
just like that?
Yeah.
Vito also thinks something fishy's going on at the plant.
Hey, look!
They're all the way out here?
Are they the soil technicians that Vito mentioned?
Yeah.
Why does their headquarters need so many samples from here?
Vito and his guys don't know either.
One thing we know for sure. The plant managers are hiding something big.
And now, a special bulletin.
New details about yesterday's accident at the ICMESA plant
indicate that the leaked chemical was probably a substance called TCP.
There is no cause for concern,
but as a precaution,
pending further investigation,
residents should not eat locally grown fruit or vegetables.
I repeat...
"As a precaution?" What does that mean?
I have a bad feeling about this.
The next day, that ominous cloud
was no longer looming in the sky.
Apparently, a strong wind off the Alps blew it away.
It doesn't have any injuries.
Seveso City Hall
Mayor, you have a business call
from the Hoffmann-La Roche company.
From Roche?
It was flapping frantically,
and then it fell down.
Maria! Hang on! Maria!
What was that?!
The white powder was toxic?
Yes. After extensive analysis
at Roche laboratories,
we've established that the powder
contained small quantities
of an extremely toxic substance.
Wh-What substance is that, exactly?
We aren't sure yet. We have just started analyzing the first set of samples.
Once we've received more test results,
we'll contact you again.
What was this "extremely toxic substance" they were talking about?
How will it affect people?
Still, if I release a vague statement,
the town will descend into panic.
God, what should I do now?
The next day, we gathered at Maria's house.
She called us over because Leo was acting strangely.
He became very ill yesterday, quite suddenly.
He's been unable to eat ever since.
Hey, Maria, you should take him to my brother Tonio's vet clinic for a checkup.
That's a good idea, right?
Yeah.
The vet clinic was full of animals
that had suddenly become very sick.
He's suffering from acute organ failure.
I can't do anything more for him.
Why is this happening to Leon?
I'd like to know myself.
All of the animals I've seen today
are suffering from the same symptoms.
Brother, can't you do anything at all?
I can only shorten his suffering
by giving him a peaceful death.
No! Not that! I can't let Leon die! Never!
Maria...
Leon, I'm sorry. Leon!
This was beyond your control, Maria.
Now animals are dropping dead in droves.
What the hell is going on here?
We'll find out.
Sitting around will get us nowhere!
We'll form a detective team
and find out what's really going on here!
A detective team?
I like the idea.
I'll help you too. I won't sleep a wink until I know what happened to Leon!
I'll help too, Giulia.
And that's how we started
the Seveso Detective Team.
It's so hot! And the AC finally conked out.
I've had my fill of this junker.
And today, they send me to cover
an accident at a rural chemical plant.
I'm really out of luck.
And later this evening, I have to cover
a fashion show in Milan.
Seriously! My boss sure is a slave driver.
Oh, you poor thing.
Still, it's your own fault. You should know better than to fly into a car's windscreen.
It's dead.
What's going on here?
Ten days after the accident,
we heard that Grandma Sonia
was in the hospital.
Before, only my eyes and head hurt,
but now I also have a rash
on my hands and feet.
My belly is swollen too,
and I have trouble walking.
Say, what do the doctors think?
The doctors believe I may be suffering
from some acute allergic reaction.
But then, it has nothing to do
with the white powder?
I don't think anyone knows for sure.
Oh, my... So they can't
even establish a cause?
I appreciate your concern, Anna.
But I'm worried about you, dear,
far more than about me.
Is your baby doing well?
Yeah.
Good. I'm glad to hear that.
So this rash appeared on your face on the second or third day after the white powder fell?
Yes. In addition, I feel nauseous and have a headache.
Nearly everyone here today
has the very same symptoms.
So that's how it is?
Um, one moment, please.
Yes?
Would you mind showing me the way
to the ICMESA plant?
The plant was shut down two days ago.
What? Shut down?
The mayor ordered the plant closed
until the end of the investigation.
What a pity.
Excuse me, did you have business with that plant?
Yes. Actually, I'm a reporter for the Italian branch of a Japanese newspaper.
Ando Shiro.
Right. I was sent here to cover
the accident the other day.
But now I'm in a bind...
How can I write an article if I can't get information about the plant?
I know! You could interview Vito instead.
Vito?
He's a worker at the ICMESA Plant.
He was there when it happened.
Right there?
Yeah.
So can you tell me
how the incident unfolded?
The heated tank that housed
the chemicals for producing TCP
had a safety valve on it,
to prevent the tank from exploding.
So when the temperature got high enough,
the valve opened,
blowing the tank's contents into the air.
What's the normal temperature range for the tank?
Usually, it's between 140 and 170 Celsius.
Then do you know what tank temperature would cause the safety valve to blow?
The safety valve wouldn't release
unless the temperature reached 320 degrees.
In other words, the temperature inside must have been at least 320 degrees?
Yes. Actually, when the temperature in the tank gets too high,
a cooling system kicks in automatically,
knocking the temperature back down.
But it didn't work, for some reason?
That's right. Our site operators
had to start it manually.
Right afterward, we were told to go home
immediately and take a shower.
But nobody would give us an explanation
about what was going on.
We believe that the big company
behind this must be hiding something.
But then, what was the ultimate purpose of making TCP?
I don't fully understand it myself,
but I think it's used to make herbicides and surgical antiseptic.
Herbicides?
Before I was hired at the plant,
I heard it was used as a defoliant
during the Vietnam War.
A defoliant? Like "Agent Orange"?
Listen to me! I can't go
to the fashion show tonight!
Yes.
I've heard that before, boss!
I understand we're short-staffed.
But the Seveso accident is far more serious!
Like I said, I can't leave here, period!
Damn it all!
Mr. Ando, maybe you should cover your next story?
Don't worry about that.
This is just my intuition,
but during the accident,
more than just TCP fell on the town.
I have a feeling that something
more toxic was mixed in with it.
Something more toxic?
What could that be?
To find out, we'll need to consult an expert.
Of course! There's a Galileo Research Institute in Milan.
It's a world-renowned
bio-medical research lab.
If we get them involved,
we might learn something.
Really?
All right, let's go ask them right away.
Everyone, get in the car.
Mr. Ando!
Are you all right, Mr. Ando?
I'll be fine. This happens to me all the time.
Um, if they're all that renowned,
will they listen to what we want to ask?
Yeah, you're right.
We shouldn't expect them
to conduct an investigation
at the request of an unknown
journalist like me.
Then let's ask the mayor to do it for us!
The mayor?
Enrico, we're counting on you!
Hello!
My, if it isn't Enrico. Hello.
I've got something urgent I need
to discuss with my father.
Can I go see him now?
Yeah. He doesn't have any appointments right now, so it'll be fine.
The mayor is in his office.
Thank you. Guys, this way!
Hey!
Hello.
U-Um...
Thanks!
Yes, come in.
Enrico?
Dad, I'm sorry to barge in like this.
What brings you here
with all of your friends?
And who exactly is this man?
I work for the Italian branch of a Japanese newspaper.
My name is Ando Shiro.
He's here to write about the recent accident.
Then what can I do for you.
About that... We have a favor to ask you, as the mayor.
We wanted you to ask
the Galileo Institute of Milan
to examine the white powder
that fell on Seveso.
No. If that's what interests you,
we'll be informed of all
the details before long.
Roche has been uncooperative about sharing their results,
so I've sent my attorney to ask their executives about the situation personally.
How long will it take?
Not long.
As soon as the analysis results arrive,
I will make an announcement.
That's why I suggest you
return home for now.
Enrico, you and your friends should go too.
We won't!
You really think that Roche will tell your attorney the truth about this?!
Right now, we're the only
ones after the truth!
The Institute is in the best
position to help with that!
And the sooner, the better!
But...
Dad! Small animals are dropping dead one after another.
Birds, chickens, cats, dogs!
At Lucio's brother's clinic,
they've had to put them all down
because there was nothing
else they could do!
Who do you think will be next?
People!
I got it, Enrico.
I'll ask the Institute to look into it.
Yes, that's right, Professor Marella.
The plant confirmed that the main component of the released material was TCP.
But we'd like to know
if it was only TCP.
So you'd like to find out whether anything other than TCP was released?
Yes. By the way, according
to a worker at the plant,
at the time of the accident, the temperature
inside the reactor exceeded 320 degrees.
I see.
I'll look into it right away and call you if I discover anything.
Exceeded 320 degrees?
And then, ten minutes later...
Hello. Professor Marella?
Ah... One moment, please.
Mayor! Please pick up the other phone and listen with me!
After reviewing the information you provided,
I have found something terrible.
Dioxin?
Yeah.
Yeah. The TCP powder that fell on Seveso was mixed with a substance called dioxin.
And what is this "dioxin" stuff?
It's a byproduct of a runaway reaction that starts when TCP is heated above 200 degrees Celsius.
At the time of the accident,
the reactor hit 320 degrees.
So there's no doubt that
some dioxin must've been produced.
So the reason why animals are dying and people are feeling sick is this dioxin?
Yes. Dioxin is much more poisonous than TCP,
to an almost incomprehensible degree.
M-Mr. Ando, there's no need
to get so excited!
But did he say anything about how poisonous this dioxin is?
According to Professor Marella,
if you mixed a kilogram of food with just one gram of TCP and fed it to rabbits,
half of those rabbits would die soon after.
But dioxin is poisonous on a different scale.
It would only take one part in a hundred million to kill as many rabbits.
One part in a hundred million?
That's so crazy, I can't even imagine it.
Then here's a simpler explanation.
Dioxin is about a thousand times
more toxic than cyanide.
It's not as fast acting as cyanide,
but eventually, one gram would be enough
to kill 830,000 guinea pigs.
One gram would kill 830,000?!
How many people would that kill?
I don't know. Nobody would dare
perform an experiment like that.
I see.
Oh, you no-good hunk of junk!
Why did you break down right now?!
The Mayor's attorney won't get
anything useful out of Roche.
They'll just skirt around the truth.
We have to hurry.
Mr. Ando! Can I help you somehow?
There's no need. Better change into the clothes we borrowed.
What's the use of Enrico putting on the mayor's suit?
If we don't catch up with the attorney, then Enrico and I will barge in.
Hoffmann-La Roche
........x....Headquarters
What? The meeting with the President has already begun?
Yes.
I showed the mayor's attorney to the President's office just a little while ago.
Damn, we didn't make it in time.
Excuse me. Would you please direct us
to the President's office as well?
Um... Excuse me, but with whom do I have the honor of speaking?
I am the son of Silvio Carlo,
the mayor of Seveso. Enrico Carlo.
I wonder if Enrico's all right.
He'll be fine. Besides, he's got Mr. Ando with him.
Right, Lucio?
Yeah.
Enrico, we're meeting
Roche's big shots now.
Show them you're no pushover.
Take the fight head-on.
Okay.
A-Are you okay, Mr. Ando?
Oh? I'm fine...
Thank you for coming
out of your way to meet us.
Mr. President, well, Seveso's mayor...
I'm sorry for being late.
Who are you gentlemen?
I am the son of the mayor of Seveso, Enrico Carlo.
My father ordered me
to be present at the meeting.
My name is Rudolf Söll,
Chairman of Hoffmann-La Roche.
And I am Don Partfogel.
I am president of Givaudan,
the parent company of the ICMESA plant.
This is Mr. Ando Shiro.
A consulting journalist.
A journalist?
Nice to meet you.
Well, regarding the incident...
So, can you tell us...
how much dioxin was blown into the air
over Seveso as a result of the accident?
W-We don't know.
As we've said, our investigation
is still underway.
I see. So they did know
about the dioxin.
That's not what I meant.
If you measured the amount of TCP inside the reactor at the time of the accident,
you should've been able
to make an initial estimate.
N-No, even making an estimate like that would be difficult.
After all, we don't know the temperature
in the reactor at the time of the accident.
I wouldn't say that.
It's no secret that the reactor's safety valve can handle temperatures up to 320 degrees.
Even I know that much.
Someone in your position must know this.
He's right.
Using 320 degrees as a lower limit,
you can make a crude estimate.
It's all right if you're unable to answer us.
We can make the calculations ourselves
and publish them in the morning news.
If you've already gone that far,
it's out of our hands.
We were cautious about publishing crude numbers from superficial calculations.
But we estimate that two or three kilograms
of dioxin were released into the environment.
Just one gram of this dioxin
can kill 830,000 guinea pigs.
And you released two or three kilograms?!
Can you even imagine how many people that amount will harm?!
You! You knew these facts all along, but you hid them from everyone!
That's a blatant criminal act, if you ask me!
I wouldn't be so sure.
When the results from analyzing
the first samples arrived on July 14th,
we informed the mayor that the white powder was mixed with an extremely dangerous toxin.
You cannot credit or blame us
for the measures the mayor did or did not take in response to this information.
That means...
my father knew all along that the powder contained a powerful toxin,
but he decided to keep it a secret?
That was our assumption as well.
Is that so?
I see.
After Enrico told his father about the meeting,
Mayor Carlo set to work at once.
The TCP released during the accident at the ICMESA plant
was mixed with an extremely toxic substance called dioxin.
Residents of Seveso, you must not eat vegetables or fruits grown in the area, no matter what.
Also, please watch for further instructions.
Dioxin?
Through the mass media, Mayor Carlo declared a state of emergency in Seveso.
He immediately set up an emergency team to counter the threat of dioxin.
He also assembled a council of scientists, led by Professor Marella,
who got to work without delay on analyzing dioxin.
He worked tirelessly, with no breaks.
Yes. Come in.
Oh? It's you, Enrico?
Dad, I brought you a change of clothes.
Sorry to bother you so much.
You won't be coming home
anytime soon, huh?
Yeah, I'm waiting for reports
on the degree of contamination.
Then I'll come up with a plan for countermeasures.
Please tell your mom I won't be coming home for two or three days.
Dad...
What is it?
You should take care of yourself.
Thanks.
That means... my father...
knew all along that the powder contained a powerful toxin,
but he decided to keep it a secret?
That was our assumption as well.
That's what my mom said. We can't see the white powder anymore,
so it means the dioxin
must have disappeared.
I've been told that yesterday's downpour
washed away all the dioxin.
Then we're out of the woods already, huh?
Are you really sure about that?
Hey!
Mr. Ando!
Lucky I came across you.
You guys wanna come with me?
Where are you going?
To see Professor Marella.
I wanted to ask him for more details about dioxin.
So dioxin has no color or taste?
Right. And dioxin doesn't disappear,
even if it's washed away by the rain.
It remains soaked into the soil.
So it's still everywhere around us,
even if we can't see it?
Correct. To make matters worse,
it's quite a stable chemical compound.
What do you mean, "It's quite stable"?
Dioxin is heat-resistant.
Acids, alkalis, and microorganisms
are unable to decompose it.
Once an area is contaminated,
it will remain so for many years.
Moreover, once it enters the body,
it's almost impossible to remove.
And what happens once
it enters the body?
Dioxin accumulates in the liver and kidneys,
destroying their function.
In addition, it degrades the immune system significantly.
You become defenseless
to the slightest malady.
It's also believed to be
a powerful carcinogen.
In many cases, after ingesting
a lot of dioxin,
people became seriously ill,
and some even died.
Then... as long as we keep on living here,
this deadly colorless and odorless
poison will continue to affect us?
Yes.
No!
That morning, they showed a detailed map
of the dioxin contamination.
The contaminated area is divided
into three zones: A, B, and R.
The three zones were based on the wind direction on the day of the accident
and the location of dead animals.
Our house, as well as Lucio's,
Anna's, and Grandma Sonia's,
were located in Zone A,
the most contaminated of all.
Maria's house was in Zone B,
with intermediate contamination.
Enrico's and Angelo's houses were in Zone R,
designated as "caution required."
And then, they announced that
Zone A had to be completely evacuated.
Why? Why can't I take it?
He sat in the closet the whole time.
There's no dioxin on him!
But you see,
they'll only allow us to bring one suitcase per person to the evacuation shelter.
Please bear with us for now, Marco.
We'll definitely come back here,
and then you'll see him again.
But really, will they allow us
to return here?
Without a doubt!
I've spent twenty years building this house!
Where else could we go?
Even these windows.
I made them bit by bit every weekend.
Right, and we had to repaint them twice.
We moved in here not long
after Anna was born.
And then came Giulia, and Marco too.
Yeah. And with each one,
we added a little to the house.
I'm not going anywhere!
I want to stay here.
Marco!
Thus, my family, as well as Lucio's
and the other inhabitants of Zone A,
left our beloved homes.
We moved to a hotel in Milan that
the city had arranged for the evacuees.
No one's allowed in Zone A anymore?
Yeah. I don't think we'll be gathering under that mulberry tree ever again.
Beginning of August
Mr. Ando, Enrico, and the others came to check on us at the Milan hotel for evacuees.
Lucio, Giulia, are you okay?
You don't seem well.
Well, you know,
I'm sad because Anna's baby could have birth defects from the dioxin.
N-No way!
It hasn't been born yet.
How can you assume that?!
Similar defoliants were used
in the Vietnam War.
Defoliants?
The Vietnam War began in 1961.
It was a testing ground
for many new types of weapons,
including herbicides.
Defoliants and similar chemicals
were widely used.
The lush jungle prevented the US military from locating the enemy,
so they sprayed huge amounts of defoliants over the area.
At the time, they called it Agent Orange.
It made the jungle trees wither away,
but it also polluted the rivers and soil.
And then, when the war was over,
many local inhabitants
were affected badly.
Women exposed to it gave birth
to children with deformed limbs,
or children lacking part of the skull.
The number of conjoined
twins also increased.
But... it wasn't just the Vietnamese
who suffered.
Returning American soldiers suffered from numerous inexplicable illnesses.
Do you know why this happened?
The defoliant they used contained the deadly poison dioxin.
This dioxin must be an invention of the devil.
Yes. If these man-made chemicals aren't handled properly,
they can cause very serious problems.
What should I do about this?
I can't come to a decision.
I have no way of knowing
if my child will be okay.
I... I won't give birth, then!
Many women who had been exposed
to dioxin during pregnancy
decided to end their pregnancy by a surgical abortion.
The government made a temporary exception for them.
Hello, Grandma Sonia.
Oh, Anna!
Are you feeling better?
Thank you for asking.
Even though I've been moved to a Milanese hospital, I don't feel better at all.
What's wrong, Anna?
You look even sadder than me.
You're worried about your unborn child, aren't you?
I... I don't know what to do.
Poor girl.
Normally, you should be filled
with happiness right about now,
but instead, you're faced
with a terrible decision.
You know, Anna,
I want you to remember one thing.
People make their way through life
by supporting one another.
No matter what you decide,
or what happens in the future,
we would never let you
suffer through it alone.
Grandma Sonia...
A few days later, they reopened bus service to Zone B.
We, the Seveso Detective Team,
met at Maria's place
to exchange our findings about dioxin.
Hey, have you heard?
The ban on selling Seveso's foodstuffs is understandable,
but now they extended it
to furniture and crafts too!
Yeah. My dad's factory was shut down,
so now he's unemployed.
Everyone's having a hard time.
They are finally waking up
to the full horror of dioxin.
You might feel healthy now,
but there's no telling
what'll happen in three months.
Some people are suffering
from chloracne.
Chloracne?
You get rashes all over your face and body.
Oh! Awful!
What's in that newspaper?
Remember how they made us
take a blood test the other day?
The results are in here.
The article says that
one-tenth of the people tested had
a steep decline in their lymphocytes.
So what's so special about
a decline in lymphocytes?
It undermines your ability
to resist illnesses.
Worse still, it increases your chances of developing leukemia.
And...
What else is there?
Nearly all the children from Zone A
have a decline in lymphocytes.
R-Really?
So on top of losing our homes,
it screwed up our health as well?
I said "nearly all." That doesn't mean 100%.
I'm sure you'll be all right.
Easy for you to say we'll be all right!
You live in Zone R. How can you understand how bad we feel?!
Lucio...
Anna!
What's the matter?
Are you all right, Anna?
The baby moved.
It just moved!
Our baby is alive!
In there, eager to start living!
Tonio, I will give birth to this child.
The possibility of birth defects
won't stop me.
I'll live with the weight
of the responsibility!
Anna,
whatever happens from now on,
I'll do my best to protect our baby.
Mid-September
Today, Mr. Ando gathered
our Seveso Detective Team
to share some of his shocking
findings with us.
There was no exhaust trap tank in place?
Usually, plants like ICMESA that produce dangerous chemicals
have an exhaust trap tank
after the safety valve.
So even if harmful substances were emitted in an accident,
they would end up trapped
inside that tank.
However, there was no exhaust trap tank
at the ICMESA plant.
Then the dioxin that formed
in the reaction tank during the accident
was blown out into the air intentionally?
Yes.
But why would they do that?
Adding a trap to every tank would cost a small fortune, I imagine.
Damn. This plant doesn't care at all
about the people living near it.
They only care about
fattening their wallets!
The dioxin that fell
on Seveso after the accident
at the ICMESA plant
was detected in the soil
down to depths of 25 cm.
The specialists say the soil contamination is of major concern.
The town of Seveso,
inundated by dioxin from the sky,
has already been dubbed a "Chemical Hiroshima."
A "Chemical Hiroshima"?
Hiroshima... Isn't that the Japanese city
struck by an atomic bomb?
Yes.
In Hiroshima, the atomic bombing claimed more than 100,000 innocent lives.
But it didn't end there.
Those who survived suffer to this day
from leukemia and other
radiation-linked conditions.
Moreover, it may have affected their children as well.
So it was just like Seveso.
They didn't call it a "Chemical Hiroshima" for no reason.
I've had enough!
Why must we put up with this injustice?!
I'm not just talking about disease.
Our homes too!
The other day, we were happy that we finally found a decent temporary apartment.
But then, what do you think it was like?!
It's next to another plant,
stinking all day long!
Why do the big shots put us
through all this?!
It's like they don't give a crap!
Does your father care about us at all?!
Isn't it obvious that he cares?
Then why is he leaving us
to the whims of fate?!
Your father sits in his fancy chair, ignoring the suffering
we in Zone A are going through!
What do you want him to do, then?
Yes, perhaps we fared better than you did.
But we all live in Seveso.
We also know the terror
of dioxin first hand.
The mayor is just a human being.
He can work infinitely hard, but he can only do so much, and he makes mistakes!
Enough, Enrico!
No more excuses about
your dad's screw-ups!
What's that?! I dare you to repeat it!
Wanna fight?!
Stop, Enrico! Let go!
Calm down, both of you!
You don't understand
anything and never will!
You're only thinking about yourself!
What's that, you prick?!
That's enough, Enrico!
You heard me!
Why?
Why is this all happening?!
The mayor is just a human being!
He can only do so much,
and he makes mistakes!
"Mistakes."
I was wrong to say that.
Dad.
Enrico.
You're still awake?
I need to talk with you.
May I?
What is it?
Dad...
I heard that after the incident,
you were told that the white powder
was mixed with a highly toxic substance.
Tell me, is that true?
That's what Roche said
when I went there!
They said the mayor got an official notice!
It's true Roche told me that an extremely toxic substance had been mixed in.
Then why didn't you disclose it right away?
Why did you hide vital information from the people?!
That's what Lucio asked me:
"Does your father care about us at all?"
How am I supposed to answer him?!
Roche...
Roche didn't tell me what
the extremely toxic substance was.
I feared that if I made
a public announcement quickly,
without naming the substance,
I'd make the situation worse
by throwing people into a panic.
Dad...
There was no right answer!
The real world is not
as simple as children think!
Dad...
I may be a child,
but I can understand that much.
People come first! Politics and chemistry come after that!
If we forget that, there'll be even more incidents like this one!
Two months after the accident.
People began showing
chloracne symptoms en masse.
It hurts! It hurts!
Marco!
Marco... My poor... My poor son...
Who deprived Seveso of its peace?!
Who?!
Who robbed us of our well-being?!
Give us back our homes!
Give them back!
Guarantee us a healthy life!
Guarantee!
Stop this demonstration immediately!
Anyone resisting will be arrested!
Demonstrating is our right!
You want us just to put up with it?!
Out of the way!
Arrest them!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Don't you lay a finger on these people!
B-But Mayor...
That's enough!
These people have already had
their share of undeserved suffering.
I wonder what'll become of us after this.
I want to return to my own home.
I'll go there right now.
I'm going too.
My cosmoses are probably starting to bloom already.
The saffron too. And the asters.
I wanna go home!
Let's go back!
Everyone, we're returning!
Nothing has changed at all.
Marco will be happy too.
Don't you agree, dear?
Sure. He'll be delighted.
Beautiful. They're blossoming
just like last year.
As if nothing had happened.
I knew you'd come here too, Lucio.
It feels like something's out of place.
It's no different from before the dioxin fell.
But I guess none of us will be able
to run across those fields ever again.
And it's not just here!
As long as we're obsessed about dioxin,
we won't be able to enjoy running
all out, like we used to!
Why did it have to be us?!
Why did this happen only to us?!
Still, if you take that frustration out
on Enrico, it won't change anything.
Complaining about it
to someone else is easy.
Still, I think just talking
about problems
is the same as running away from them.
Before we start blaming someone else,
shouldn't we at least try to face the problem ourselves?
You know, I really like
to watch you run.
Aiming to be as fast as the wind,
as if trying to outrun yourself every time.
Just from watching that, I could feel
new strength emerging inside me.
Giulia...
Lucio, we'll run again.
One day, we will. I'm sure of it.
Ah, Angelo? What happened?
What? Maria?!
That's when we learned that Maria was showing symptoms of chloracne.
Maria, it's me. We're here to check on you.
Angelo and Lucio too.
Enrico is here as well. Come on, Maria!
Go away.
I don't want anyone to see me!
I beg you, please go away!
What's the matter, Enrico?
I'm sorry, guys.
I feel that I should apologize, somehow,
to Maria, to you, to everyone.
The mayor...
My dad... My dad may have made a terrible mistake.
What do you mean by that?
Right after the accident,
Roche gave my dad a clear warning
that an extremely toxic substance
was mixed with the white powder.
However, he decided to keep
that fact to himself.
He didn't know the exact chemical.
He could only guess.
He feared an announcement
would incite panic among the people.
But it's clear now that whatever data he had,
he should've disclosed it sooner.
If he'd done that, we wouldn't have carried on heedlessly,
and dioxin wouldn't have gotten to us!
Maybe Maria would've been spared too!
I'm sorry!
Guys, I'm truly sorry!
The dioxin fallout wasn't the mayor's fault.
And it wasn't yours either.
I stood by and did nothing,
except for taking it out on you
and running away from the truth.
But you... You faced reality head-on
and tried to fight it.
I'm sorry, Enrico.
Lucio...
At the end of the day,
dioxin took its toll on all of us!
Yes! Seveso got smothered in dioxin
because of Roche!
If we don't expose this,
countless more tragedies
like this one will occur!
Let's get to work! We have to protect the future with our own hands!
A press conference?
Yes. Roche is meeting with
the Milanese government tomorrow,
to negotiate compensation for the victims.
After that, Roche has invited journalists in for an official conference.
Who will be there for Roche?
Probably Chairman Söll and Partfogel.
The company's top brass, for sure.
Maria, it's me, Angelo.
Tomorrow, we're all going
to the Roche press conference.
I felt I needed to let you know.
I don't know what'll come out of it,
but I'll come again to tell you.
Maria!
My face... is hideous, isn't it?
I know...
We've decided to move
away from Seveso.
Dad wants to go somewhere
with no dioxin.
But I don't want to leave everyone!
Maria...
I like you very much.
And so, I will never forgive Roche
for causing you so much pain.
Angelo...
On the day of the press conference,
a large crowd of Seveso inhabitants gathered in front of the venue,
to protest to the Roche representatives.
Even the rear entrance is guarded.
Still, it seems easier than the front.
This way!
No admittance to the venue!
Turn back at once!
They damn well showered us in dioxin!
We got questions for this Roche guy!
Exactly! Let us go! Let us in there!
No, I said! No way!
Now's our chance!
Turn back!
Disperse right now!
Give us Roche!
On the right, Partfogel from Givaudan.
On the left, Chairman Söll of Roche.
So the press conference is
hereby declared open.
Allow me!
Why exactly would you want
to produce a substance as dangerous as dioxin at your plants?
We are not in the least interested in producing a substance as troublesome as dioxin.
However, among our products is a surgical antiseptic. Its production process
requires a certain chemical called TCP.
And unfortunately, during the synthesis of TCP,
a negligible quantity of dioxin
is created as a byproduct.
Negligible quantity?
If we had an alternative to TCP,
we'd be more than happy to use it instead.
Unfortunately, the hard reality is that there's no substitute.
But if you discover one,
be sure to let us know first.
Allow me!
So you're saying, despite the risks,
you had no choice but to use it?
In that case,
shouldn't you have installed
all possible precautionary measures?
According to my investigation,
the reaction tank synthesizing TCP
was not equipped with an exhaust trap tank of any kind.
What can you tell us about that?
It's... The thing is... You see...
This country's high court is currently deciding
whether we are to blame in this situation.
You're dodging the question!
Weren't you just negligent,
slacking off on safety measures?!
Not at all.
The ICMESA plant had
safety measures intended
to prevent overheating
in the reaction tank,
in particular, an emergency cooling system.
Then why didn't it operate this time,
preventing the accident?!
Regarding that, our internal investigation had shown that the worker
controlling the cooling system made an operational error.
What the hell?!
That's a lie!
Giulia!
We went there and talked
to the workers who were present!
The cooling system was supposed
to operate automatically, but it didn't!
So it had to be activated manually,
by an emergency lever!
The workers didn't make
any operational mistakes!
The cooling system plainly failed to work,
because the company neglected the safety equipment!
That's my sister!
Lucio!
Giulia! Angelo!
Enrico!
What are children doing in here?
Who let them into the venue?
Who are those children?
Please, calm down, everyone!
They are the children of Seveso!
They've been on the front lines of dioxin from the start!
They're infinitely courageous!
I can testify to what they said
about the cooling system malfunction!
What now?
Do you have any simple and precise answer
to the issue these kids just raised?!
This... We'll discuss this issue
only after there's a verdict.
We have no answer for now.
Why do the trials prevent
you from answering?!
Because if you tell the truth,
you'll undermine your position in court?!
No... The thing is...
If you can't answer,
here's another question!
Right after the accident,
you were aware that a large dose of dioxin had been released!
And yet, you only warned the mayor about some vague, negligible risks!
Why did you do that?!
Dioxin lay thick on the ground.
How many days were you
planning to hide that?!
It's... It's unthinkable
that we would hide anything.
You must understand that
analyzing samples takes time.
You're lying again! The moment the accident occurred,
you already knew that dioxin had formed!
I-I don't understand
what you're talking about!
It was unthinkable at the time
that so much dioxin
could form in a reaction like that!
Stop lying to us already!
Apologize to the all the people of Seveso!
Apologize right here!
We want at least an apology.
Maria is crying all day long!
Apologize, you!
Do something about them already!
Stop!
Hands off the children!
Let me go! Stop it!
Let me go! Let me go right now!
Let me go! I haven't finished speaking!
Stop it! Let us go!
Leave me alone. Leave me alone!
Stop it! Let me go!
Giulia... Enrico...
Lucio... Angelo...
People are still suffering!
All because of dioxin!
Their sufferings will go on!
Apologize! Apologize, you!
Apologize, I said!
This press conference is temporarily suspended!
The conference is temporarily suspended!
In the end, our cries fell on deaf ears.
As usual, those men were concerned
with their profits above all else.
Companies that mass-produce goods,
aiming to improve people's lives on a grand scale,
are always built on the misery of other people.
And that's not how it's supposed to be.
But for me...
For all of us...
We finding convenience in abundant manufactured commodities.
Would anyone say they'd prefer
not to have them?
Detergents that clean effortlessly,
pesticides that protect crops from insects,
various handy things
we use in our everyday lives,
all come from man-made chemicals.
And that's not all.
Dioxin also forms when vinyl and many other types of plastics are burned.
The mountains of miscellaneous household waste piling up
are yet another potential source
of dioxin emissions.
We always seek greater convenience.
But what if someone else...
No, do we ever ask if we might become
victims of our own devices as a result?
The responsibilities we bear to the future
always lie within ourselves.
In February of the following year,
Grandma Sonia passed away.
And in March,
Anna's daughter was born.
A healthy, adorable little girl.
Still, we didn't know whether dioxin might affect her in the future.
Rather than dissipating, our anxiety
about the child only grew after the birth.
But at least one thing we know for sure.
Whatever happens from here on,
we won't let my sister and her baby
face difficulties on their own.
And so, a while later, it was time
for the Seveso Detective Team to say goodbye.
Take care, Maria.
Maria, goodbye.
Goodbye, Maria.
I may be going away now, but I'm still a Seveso Detective Team member!
Don't forget me!
Maria, be sure to write to me!
Goodbye, Maria.
Maria! Maria! Maria!
Angelo, I'll never forget
what you did for me!
Thank you all!
Thanks!
Left already?
Mr. Ando?
Actually, I'm going back to Japan.
Today is goodbye.
You're leaving too?
It'll be lonely here.
The dioxin problem is not unique to Seveso.
I plan to work harder than ever in Japan
to ensure this tragedy never recurs.
I consider it my duty as a journalist.
And you?
For our part, we learned a lot
about dioxin, thanks to you.
It's clear as day. This terrifying man-made chemical
will catch up with you,
no matter where you run.
We have to take a firm stance
and face it head-on.
It's for our own sake.
But even more, it's for the future
of this beautiful Earth.
It's sunny in most places
Only small areas are in shadow
In this frozen time
We pass the long summer day
Eucalyptus scents the air
Seeds are sown in the spring
The sun peeps through, glittering
On the road by the river
Unreachable voices
Thoughts that grow rusty
I chase a rainbow that won't disappear
A brand new day
Only starts now
For hundreds of millions of years
It's been the very same way
Repeating over and over again
What will happen this time?
Wrapping everything up
The morning begins
Reincarnation
A brand new day
Only starts now
For hundreds of millions of years
It's been the very same way
Repeating over and over again
What will happen this time?
Wrapping everything up
The morning begins
Reincarnation
Translation
Translation Check
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
M74
NoraInuG, Perevodildo
M74, Collectr
Collectr
Nemesis, Rezo,
Topper3000
AnimeGorodok
M74 & Orphan Fansubs