This is a pilot film made in 1981.
Combining the mystical legends of
ancient India with fantasy based on
The Adventures of Sinbad the Sailor,
this work is a new type of sci-fi heroic fantasy that combines
the past and the future, that is, legend
and sci-fi, and it breaks away
from the conventional patterns of sci-fi animation.
There was once a planet.
It was said to be the most beautiful planet in all the star streams.
It had a moon as bright as a pearl.
It glowed like a blue gemstone.
Now, however,
it's just a legend passed down
from generation to generation.
The planet Purusha is a wasteland
walking the path to destruction.
In one of the planet's deserts,
deep underground,
there is a long forgotten
spherical city called Shurti.
When this spherical city of Shurti appears on
the surface of the Earth once every 100 years,
a curious and fearless boy named Shudra,
a brilliant learned priest, Brahmana,
an unparalleled shaman healer, Rajani,
a petty villain, Vaishya,
and a girl as fair as winter snow, Soma,
begin their journey
to the sacred land of the Moon Gate.
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
They are led to the Moon Gate
by the mysteriously beautiful King Ashura, who is feared as an evil spirit
and who spreads destruction and carnage.
After that, they overcome many difficulties
and challenge the guardian deities
of the Moon Gate, Varuna and Mitra,
with the holy sword
given to them by King Ashura.
When Shudra breaks the seal
of the Moon Gate with the holy sword,
the planet of Purusha is reborn.
This is a story full of the dreams and adventures
of young Shudra, a descendant of Indra, the god of military prowess.