2001 NIGHTS
SPACE FANTASIA
ORPHANS OF SPACE
2058 A.D.
Humanity begins to take its first leap into space.
An almost unbelievable plan, which would be its first step
toward interstellar travel, was conceived.
This project for expansion into outer space
will most likely be repeated several times.
We hope that at least one of them succeeds.
We thank you two for your cooperation
with this program, Mr. and Mrs. Robinson.
Put it on the screen.
With our present technology,
manned interstellar spaceflight is but a dream,
incurring truly astronomical costs.
Therefore, we have developed
a method of traveling using comets.
Abundant energy sources, such as water and deuterium, can be taken directly from the core.
We have named this comet "Ozma III".
In other words, we will use
the comet itself as a spaceship.
It's a natural interstellar spaceship, you see.
However, there is a fatal problem.
Space is vast.
Even if you traveled with Ozma III
at a speed of 80 kilometers a second,
how much time do you think it would take
to travel to Alpha Centauri,
the star closest to our solar system?
A staggering 16,000 years.
It would take over 50,000 years
to cover the distance of 10 light years.
Therefore, enormous acceleration is absolutely needed.
And so, after we've mined its resources,
we will explode the comet's core.
The energy of the blast will accelerate
the ship to 10,000 kilometers a second.
However, the human body is unable
to withstand this tremendous acceleration.
The only things that could survive it are machines
and frozen sperm and eggs.
Thus, life will truly begin with a journey.
However, Mr. and Mrs. Robinson,
I hope you don't misunderstand us.
We are not playing God with life.
What if it misses...
What if there are no planets that can support life,
what will happen to these...
children of ours?
They will return to nothingness.
That's all there is to it, Mrs. Robinson.
That is, in that case, the ship will be permanently suspended, at the computer's discretion.
The defreezing system for the eggs and sperm
will never activate, and nothing will be born.
These are our children.
If they do get born...
they'll be all alone,
out in the far reaches of space.
It's too late.
We can't do anything about it now.
This way, please.
We'd like to show you one more result
of your cooperation with us.
Hannah... bear a child.
Our child.
Let's make ourselves a family too,
here on Earth.
Hey, what is it? A boy or a girl?
It's a boy. See, it's got one!
Let me hold it, Mom!
Me next!
That's the 23rd one, huh, Dad?
What will you name him?
Joachim.
Mom and I decided.
What a weird name.
We should give him a better name.
Let's vote on it.
Joachim, these are your big brothers and sisters.
You must be surprised to have so many!
Dad, let me hold him!
All right. Don't drop him.
Wow!
Now, now. We need to give him some milk.
Mom, let me give him milk!
What's wrong?
We have an air leak.
It's nothing major. I'll go fix it.
Be careful, okay?
Dad, I'll go on ahead!
That's not fair, Chris!
You did it last time! I'll go too!
Tau Ceti, huh?
Yes, that's what they called that star on Earth.
Its size and brightness are a lot like the Sun's.
Dad named the second planet
of this system Ozma.
That's the name of the comet
that brought us here.
Darling, check the angle
on the solar panel while you're at it, okay?
Somebody's fiddled with the console, it seems.
Roger.
Again, huh? Oh well.
Dad, can we really live on Ozma?
Of course.
The computer decided that.
The computer found this planet and is investigating it right now, while we're in orbit.
Yep. While that was happening,
you were born and have grown up so much.
Chris!
Here you go, Mom!
Does Ozma look like Earth, Mom?
Yes, it was big and blue like that.
The Earth Mom knows
is from a long time ago, though.
Is the Earth far away?
Don't you and Dad want to go home?
Mom and Dad have you.
And you have Ozma.
Remember this well.
That star is the Sun.
Since ancient times, people on Earth
have looked at the stars like this and said:
"I'd like to go to that star someday.
I wonder if I'll be able to someday."
And while they thought that,
people lived and died,
and now, we're the first
to go to one of those stars.
Do you understand, Maureen?
Yeah.
Oh my, Chris, what's wrong?
It's the same disease that hit Harry.
His fever is so high.
Why so suddenly?
Let's move him to the medical capsule.
It's no good, Dad! The capsule's broken!
Then get him an oxygen mask, quickly.
Chris... Chris, hang on!
Toby, get the cardiotonics.
They're on that shelf! Hurry!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Maureen
The day we land on Ozma is near.
Let's have a big birthday party.
This will probably be our last...
Last?
Uh, no, I mean the last party on this ship.
Now, those of you who were born this month,
Toby, Maureen, Mark, blow it out together.
Here, your presents.
Wheat seeds for the boys
and sunflowers for Maureen.
Grow them with care.
Man, this is good!
There's wind!
And so many smells!
Whoa, so much space!
This place is huge!
The sky and the water are so blue!
Mom, Dad, come here!
Amazing... This place is amazing!
You can see mountains!
They go on forever!
Careful, Joachim.
I'll take you there.
Quick!
Mom, Dad...
Go with them, Joachim.
This world belongs to you kids.
There's nothing more we can teach you.
Radio transmissions carrying the report that 22 children
had landed on planet Ozma
in the Tau Ceti system,
11.9 light years from the solar system,
later reached Earth.
But those involved in the plan
would never receive this report.
It had been 375 years
since the spaceship left the solar system.
Humanity's greatest discovery
in the latter half of the 21st century
was uncovering the true nature of
the tenth planet of the Solar System.
Surprisingly, this dark super giant, named Lucifer,
was composed of antimatter.
Harnessing it would provide access
to truly unlimited amounts of energy.
The Space Age entered a new stage
which humanity had never anticipated.
At the same time, the cutting edge of physics was on the verge of completing a theory
of hyperspace travel based on
the rotational confinement of micro black holes.
This combination of infinite energy
and the latest technology
introduced an age in which interstellar flights of tens of light years could be completed in an instant.
The curtain had suddenly opened
on humanity's great expansion into space.
A GIFT FROM EARTH
This ship will now transition
into hyperspace travel.
So this is the kind of planet...
the kind of world you're aiming for?
For now, let's set the boundaries
around here, Miller.
We'll blast this stony bedrock
and turn it into soil.
We need as much organic material
in the atmosphere and crust as possible.
What about the enhanced microbes?
They're multiplying well.
As soon as the soil's ready,
I want to distribute the plant life.
Speed it up as much as you can.
Roger, Adam.
It's an additive with organic matter
that also serves as a fertilizer.
This planet is nothing but solid rock.
Just smashing the stones and spreading seeds
around won't be enough to grow anything.
Let's add that area over there
to the development.
Jeez, what a depressing planet.
And the development's far behind schedule.
Who knows when we'll be able to go back to Earth.
But the Robinson Foundation's pretty impressive.
They say the entire Foundation
is focused on this project.
They'll probably start advertising it
once the environment's mostly set up.
"Build a villa on a green planet," or something.
Yeah, at a hundred times the normal price.
Master Adam!
I'm saying this as your financial advisor!
Even the Robinson Space Foundation's capital has its limits!
If you continue this large-scale construction,
the Foundation will go bankrupt!
Gilford, no matter how often
you say that to me,
I'm not going to abandon the project midstream.
Master Adam!
Your father's involvement in a top-secret
Space Agency project is what allowed him
to establish himself in the space industry.
I think he amassed his enormous wealth in the Lucifer Development Project
when he was about your age.
Now then, in my position, I cannot let this lie.
This'll become an issue that we'll have
to deal with once we return to Earth.
Goodnight.
This lake is the furthest thing along in the project.
We're almost done with the landscaping,
and our aquatic cultures are developing well.
All that's left to do is to fill it
with water from the canal.
I'm sure this will be wonderful to look at.
Once we finish this,
maybe we should take the day off?
What an awful rain.
You'd never see this kind of downpour on Earth.
Our atmospheric terraforming may have
disrupted the planet's weather patterns.
Hey, Adam.
I know that you're committed to this project.
But as your science advisor,
let me tell you this much.
This is another planet.
It's not Earth.
The changes we make to the environment
will be strictly temporary.
You shouldn't expect them to last.
In 600 years, everything will return to its original state.
That's more than enough time, Miller.
We're not the ones who need to think
about 600 years from now.
Ah! What?
Alarm!
Hurry!
What is it?! What happened?!
The lake overflowed!
Fill up that valley
and change the flow of the water!
That's impossible!
There's not nearly enough time!
But if we do nothing,
the plants will be destroyed!
Working in this rain is dangerous!
You need to fall back now!
If the water comes
before we dam it up, we're dead!
If we abandon the plants
that have finally budded, it'll all be for naught!
Stop the water even if you have
to use every man we have!
What a mess.
In the end, it was all for naught.
Please, send us back to Earth.
I don't ever want to do
something that dangerous again.
We should leave as soon as we can.
Will the Foundation be able to survive this?
Very well.
A ship carrying equipment will arrive soon.
Those who wish to return on it may do so.
Thank you for your hard work.
That's it.
Take care of the rest here.
Brothers and sisters.
In 300 years, you will reach this planet.
I leave this message for you.
50 years ago, humanity's desire and rush
toward space led to a desperate plan.
In short, they put frozen human sperm and eggs
on a spaceship and sent it to this planet.
The ones who provided them
were the Robinsons.
My parents.
Brothers and sisters.
My as yet unborn brothers and sisters,
heading here at full speed
from the depths of space...
Brothers and sisters.
My as yet unborn brothers and sisters,
heading here at full speed
from the depths of space...
In time, thanks to plant photosynthesis,
the atmosphere's oxygen content will increase.
We can't recover that ship halfway through its journey?
It's 11.9 light years from here to Earth.
Only God knows where they are now.
This was the will of my late parents.
The funds of the Foundation
were to be used for this purpose.
Brothers and sisters.
My as yet unborn brothers and sisters,
heading here at full speed
from the depths of space...
Please, take this small gift from Earth.
And never forget that your mother,
your father, and I... are with you...
Most of the colonies established throughout the Galaxy
have been abandoned due to epidemics,
wars, and natural disasters.
The massive investments
have gone completely to waste.
Instead of sending any more men into space,
we should address the more pressing issue
of sustaining the lives of the 7.2 billion people here on Earth.
To that end,
we must strive for the utmost optimization of all necessary management and streamlining efforts.
The Space Age is in the past now.
THE SONGS OF DISTANT EARTH
Wait!
Hurry!
Here I go!
Karen!
Not bad!
Way to go, Toby!
Awesome!
Well done!
Joachim, come back!
It's dinnertime!
Hey! There are scary bugs over there!
I'm going to find cricky-crickies, really big ones!
What's that?
Ah! It's people!
You're right, people!
Dad?
Joachim, that's not Dad.
You just can’t breathe air this fresh
on Earth anymore, can you?
Earth?
Earth? He said Earth...
Huh? They came from Earth?
From Earth?!
Really?
Ah, I wanna go there too!
I wonder what it's like...
Hey, tell us!
The Earth...
Our little brother built it
so that we could always gaze at it.
Spain,
Finland,
USA,
Corsica!
That's not a country, Joseph!
Hey, tell us about the Earth, mister.
There's gotta be a lot of people! A lot!
Is it bigger than Ozma?
Is the sky blue? And the water?
There are animals, right?
Hey, what's it like?
Are there fish?
What about fish?
Well, it's not really that different.
This planet was terraformed to be like Earth.
But now...
Ellen, bring some water.
No, it's fine.
It'll pass soon.
What's your name?
Karen Robinson.
I'm the eldest.
We should've disembarked fully
right from the start!
What's the captain hesitating about?
There's no need to worry about those kids.
If we need to, we'll use force.
Smith, try to look for a possible
settlement area while they're gone.
As large a one as you can.
Understood.
They've split up.
Harry, you follow him.
But I wanted to ride the shuttle
with everyone else...
Stop wasting time and get moving!
Okay.
They're planning something, sister.
You can't trust them.
Or that Captain Adam.
That's right.
There were many settlements made in space.
There were even planets where tens
of thousands of people had migrated.
But they're gone now.
All were abandoned.
Why?
Why, I wonder...
Maybe space was too vast.
No matter how far we went, it never ended.
In the end, maybe that vastness
scared humanity.
Then there's no reason for us
to stay on Ozma, is there?
We'd like to return to Earth.
We should have that right.
What's that?
Wow!
Cool!
Is that a spaceship?
Impressive.
It's a starseed!
A starseed?
I've heard that they were discovered
around a star in the constellation Orion.
It's packed full of plant seeds, wandering through space in search of a place to grow.
Why would they do that?
Who knows? They make their own offspring
travel aimlessly through space.
Maybe their home planet's
environment was ruined?
Or maybe...
they just felt compelled
to leave their mark on the Galaxy.
What are you doing?!
We're burning down this ugly shack.
Stop it!
Damn you!
Let us go!
It's for your own sake.
Better just forget about Earth!
Look, this is Earth.
The aging, decrepit Earth!
This spaceship will not return to Earth.
The Earth has changed.
Humanity wanted to reach out into space.
It was an irresistible urge.
370 years ago, in an era when interstellar travel
was thought totally impossible,
you were a symbol of humanity's dreams
about space, a source of solace.
That still hasn't changed.
No, ironically, now that all settlements have been lost...
Everyone, come.
There's something I must have you see.
Go away! Get off of this planet!
Wait!
Captain!
I'm not going to force you
to accept those people here.
This planet...
belongs to you.
Robinson left it for you and you alone.
How do you know that?
Robinson...
I'm a descendant of the Robinson family too.
B-But Adam, we came here as the last colonists,
searching for a new frontier.
We can't leave here now.
The children need us too!
A-Asimov...
If the children refuse...
we will leave.
That was the agreement.
We would take upon us the fate that was laid out
for these children: become a starseed ourselves...
and simply find another planet.
Adam...
Forgive me.
I only wanted to meet you kids
at least once before I died.
We kept this planet
in our hearts for generations.
No one ever forgot about you.
The Robinsons gave us life,
love, and the Earth itself.
Adam...
Rest in peace in this land.
The history of this family
mirrored that of the Space Age,
which had lasted for four centuries.
Right now, the dreams of humanity
seem to have changed completely.
But someday, a time will come
when another generation
will challenge endless space once again
and have the courage to cross it.
Original Subtitles
Translation Checking
Editing
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Raw
Presented by
Kanjisub & SHS
Perevodildo, Darkonius
Collectr
Perevodildo, Collectr
Uchuu, VigorousJammer
WOWmd
Batty
Orphan Fansubs
(and friends)