Persia
Magical Star
Magical Emi
Magical Fairy
Magical Angel
Creamy Mami
Mami, Persia, & Emi
Charming Trio
Magical Girl
Orphan Fansubs Presents
v
Wow!
Looks good!
Let's eat!
Excuse me.
Not fair, Persia.
You're only taking meat.
It's not my fault meat sticks to the side dish.
Huh? It's you who's only taking meat, Yuu!
N-Not at all!
Underneath that green onion,
it's nothing but meat!
H-How strange! Maybe it got stuck to the green onion?
Excuse me.
Well then.
Now there'll be plenty of meat again.
Panpuru pinpuru pamupoppun!
Thank you for your attention.
It's great!
So great!
Excuse me.
Perukko raburin kurukuru rinkuru!
Pararin ririkaru parapora majikaru!
Thank you for your attention.
"Blue scroll, red scroll, yellow scroll!"
Sheesh.
Mai's sure late.
Ah, it's going to boil down soon!
Oh well, let's start without her.
Fine by me!
Let's eat!
Not fair!
Really... Why didn't you wait for me?
S-Sorry...
Geez.
Let's eat.
Excuse me.
Let's go!
Hurry!
Ah! Made it!
Let's go with "Bamboo bush got burned."
That's not a tongue twister.
Oh, yeah.
Then how about,
"The other guest eats persimmons"?
Better pick an easier one.
Well then...
"Toukyou patent office."
H-Huh?
Then how about this?
"Frogs hopping, three hops..."
"...gather hopping, six hops."
We did it!
I have the first turn.
I'm Yuu.
I'm Mai.
I'm Persia.
The three of us together are
the shining magical squad Sun Vulcan!
Just kidding!
By the way, the stuff playing
now is my video.
I collected Love Powers by transforming
into the beauty Persia.
Wow, that's impressive.
And then there's also Persia's
wonderful boyfriend.
I'm jealous.
Kidding.
Don't you have one too?
Not fair.
You have one too, Yuu!
Oh, right. A suggestion.
What is it?
Since we three gathered
and went to a hot spring together,
let's call our boyfriends one by one
and introduce them to the other two.
Wow! Sounds interesting.
I agree.
Then, first is...
Persia.
Yay! I've been waiting!
I'm kinda shy about it, though.
Let's see...
Persia, what's your boyfriend's name?
Gaku and Riki.
But Riki's actually
Sayo-san's boyfriend.
Yes, hello?
Hello, Riki?
It's Persia.
What are you calling for?
Forgot something?
No.
I thought I'd introduce Gaku
and Riki to Yuu and Mai.
Where's Gaku?
Not there?
He's out now.
Just me.
Oh, that's a shame.
Then, just you will do for now.
I'll do?
Really, I'm just a spare for you?
No.
That's not it.
I'll put Yuu on now.
Hello?
Nice to meet you. I'm Morisawa Yuu.
Hi! I've heard about you
from Persia sometimes.
Really?
Good things?
Well...
Anyway, I heard you're
a really unique girl.
Yay! Next, I'll put Mai on.
Hello?
Nice to meet you. I'm Kazuki Mai.
Mai is putting on some airs.
Oh, you're Mai-chan?
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
U-Um...
Riki-san, you have a cool voice.
Do I?
Well, you're... making me blush!
Since when have you been
such a sissy, Riki?
Huh? When Persia come back on the line?
Hey, next time bring
Yuu-chan and Mai-chan home.
No way, I won't.
Cute girls are your ultimate weakness, so it's dangerous.
And Yuu and Mai are both very cute.
Geez, Persia.
Really! Even if it's true, don't say it like that!
By the way, how is your joint trip going?
It's the best ever!
What are you doing now?
With just three, you're one
short for playing mahjong.
Riki, you big dummy!
Right now, while watching
my videos from back then,
and we're gossiping about our memories.
Oh? Sounds like fun.
I guess a lot has happened.
That's right.
And I'm very happy with it.
Because I love you both, Gaku and Riki.
Thanks for that.
When Gaku returns, I'll tell him.
Yay!
Later, then.
And don't let Sayo-san bully you too much.
You little...
You stabbed my weak spot.
You too, Persia. Don't overheat from
soaking too long in the hot spring.
None of your business.
Then, please expect souvenirs.
Sure!
Good night, Riki-san.
Good night.
Yeah. Later.
Persia's boyfriend is absolutely cool!
I think so too.
I'm definitely gonna be a fan of his.
And I'm still a little embarrassed.
Well then, let's continue watching Persia's video.
Yeah.
Kazuki Mai, going in!
I'm Yuu.
I'm Mai.
I'm Persia.
The three of us together are The Candies!
Just kidding.
Let's see.
What's playing now is Mai's video.
In it, Mai transforms into Magical Emi and becomes a magician.
That's cool!
Which means, next is Mai's turn.
Call him, right away!
Okay!
Second, Kazuki Mai, calling.
Mai, what's your boyfriend's name?
No way! He's not my boyfriend.
He's just Shou.
So Shou's his name?
Hello?
Shou?
It's me.
Oh, Mai?
What's up? You're calling me so suddenly.
Forgot something?
Geez, I thought I'd introduce you
to Yuu and Persia.
Oh, that's an honor.
Then I'll put Persia on.
Yay!
I'm Hayami Persia.
Nice to meet you.
I heard you're dabbling in boxing.
That's right.
He's always making me worry.
Who's the one causing worry to the other?
And who's the girl who whines
every time she slips up?
That's mean! Shou, you jerk!
Ouch!
Mai, why did you kick me?
I'm sorry!
Kicking Shou's leg is my habit.
Too bad I'm on the other end of this phone!
So, anyway, I'm Morisawa Yuu.
Nice to meet you.
Right. I've heard about you
from Mai sometimes.
Really? Good things?
I'm not sure. Well, anyway, I heard you're a really cheerful girl.
Yay! I'll put Mai on, then.
Shou, do you miss me?
The hell you say.
By the way, what are you doing now?
With just three, you're one
short for playing mahjong.
Geez. There's no way innocent girls
like us would play such naughty games.
Right now, we're watching my video from back then and talking about our memories.
Seems like fun.
They must be fond remembrances,
your time with Magic Carat.
Oh yeah, just now I showed
my magic to Yuu and Persia.
Did it turn out well?
Y-Yup, it was perfect!
I only fumbled it a bit!
No, you didn't.
Mai's really good at magic.
That's right. She'll surely be
a wonderful magician.
Thanks.
I'll keep doing my best!
Later, then.
Don't overheat from soaking too long in the hot spring.
Not on my watch!
How about you try not to get yourself hurt during boxing?
Sure, sure.
Good night.
Shou-san, good night.
Later.
Mai's boyfriend is cool too.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Mai, you seem down somehow.
Not at all.
I just...
I just remembered about Topo
while talking to Shou about magic.
Topo left without
even saying goodbye.
I'm also now remembering Geragera,
Mesomeso, and Puripuri.
I wonder how Posi
and Nega are doing.
I'm sure they're all doing great.
I guess so.
Of course they're fine.
Wow, we're so serious and pensive now.
This doesn't suit us at all.
All right, then.
Let's have some shots and enjoy.
Wow!
Yuu, you brought sake?
Wow, you're such a delinquent!
Let's not be so prudish this time.
Come on now, sit down.
Well then, to our memories.
To the unbounded future ahead.
Cheers!
Yep.
I'm last!
Yay!
Ouch.
MORISAWA YUU
Topo, you're the best.
Geragera, Mesomeso,
and Puripuri, you're all great.
Posi and Nega, you still alive?
Gaku and Riki, you big dummies!
Shou, you jerk!
Seems you're really into it.
Toshio, what a hunk.
Yuu, you traitor!
I won't forgive you for taking advantage of the fuss!
Wow. Are you going to hit me for real?
Yuu, give me another glass.
Mai, you have such bad habits.
Yup, she's bad.
Anyway, what's playing
now is my video.
I, Morisawa Yuu, can transform
into Creamy Mami using magic.
Who cares about that?
Hurry and call your boyfriend.
Sure, sure.
Let's see, the phone number is...
Yuu, your hand is shaking.
Can you do it?
Shut up!
If you keep chattering in my ear,
I'll dial the wrong number.
Hello, this is Ootomo.
Toshio?
It's me.
What, Yuu? Why are you calling like this?
Oh! You forgot something?
Hey, don't make fun of your Yuu-sama!
Are you drunk?
Come on...
Don't be so strict.
I'll introduce you to my friends now.
I'm Mai-chan.
Hi.
If you wanna know, Yuu never gets tired of bragging about you, Toshio-san.
You jealous?
I'm gonna be Toshio's bride.
Hey, Yuu!
When did we decide that?
Just did!
We're going to have a wedding
at the white chapel on the hill.
I'm in a wedding dress.
Toshio's in a white morning suit.
Enveloped in the organ's
sound and celebrating people,
we two walk down along the virgin road
as I hold a pure white bouquet in my hand.
Wow, you have such
a well-developed imagination!
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for that.
Now give me more sake!
Slow down.
Don't rush!
I'll invite you to my wedding too, Mai.
Really?
Oh yeah, I forgot.
Toshio-san, I'm Persia.
Nice to meet you.
Wow!
Like Shou-san's,
your voice is cool too.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm at a loss.
No, I mean, people say it a lot.
Hey, Toshio!
Since when are you such a sissy?
Huh?
It's Yuu?
Well, you know, both Mai-chan and Persia-chan sound pretty cool.
Geez, you're praising them already.
Toshio, you jerk!
Toshio, you... Nibushima You!
Huh? You're not making any sense!
By the way, how is your hot springs trip going?
Oh? It's the best!
Usually I have my hands full
all the time, looking after you.
It's good to take a break sometimes.
The hell you say.
Anyway, what're you doing there?
With just three, you're one
short for playing mahjong.
Well, earlier, we saw Mai's magic,
then we were watching our old videos
and discussing our memories.
Right now, my video
from back then is playing.
Oh? That sounds like fun.
Anyway, they say, "Get three women together, something something mayhem."
I guess it's true.
Get three women together... beautiful!
Get three women together... sexy!
Geez, you three really are cocky!
Wow! Thanks for the compliment.
Huh?
Later, then!
Don't overheat from soaking
too long in the hot spring.
Okay!
Okay.
Well, Toshio...
Good night.
See you later.
Hey, Mai, you have bad habits.
Well then, good night.
Yeah.
Hey, you three,
you'd better not drink anymore.
All right...
Another glass!
I can't drink anymore.
But... gimme another one!
Feels good.
Let's hit the bath again later.
I agree!
But before that,
let's try to wrap up properly.
Sounds good!
Here we go.
I'm Yuu.
I'm Mai.
I'm Persia.
The three of us together are
The Charming Magical Girl Trio!
After all, you can't get drunk on juice.
That's for sure.
Original Subtitles
ARR
Transl Check & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Muzussawa
Nemesis
Uchuu
Encoding
anonymous
Notice.
Notice from the Pierrot Fan Club!
Right now, at the Pierrot Fan Club,
in response to your requests,
we've upgraded the Creamy Mami corner.
If you join the Pierrot Fan Club,
you'll get info on our works before anyone else,
Pierrot newsletters, and birthday cards.
Now join the Club,
and be an even bigger fan of Mami!
Notice from the Pierrot Fan Club!
Right now, at the Pierrot Fan Club,
in response to your requests,
we've upgraded the Creamy Mami corner.
If you join the Pierrot Fan Club,
you'll get info on our works before anyone else,
Pierrot newsletters, and birthday cards.
Now join the Club,
and be an even bigger fan of Mami!
Emi, Mami, Persia
Complete Fantasy
Monthly OUT Special Issue
Magical Century Good Sense MOOK
Coming mid-May from Minori Shobou
Price 1800 yen
Magical Century Good Sense MOOK
Coming mid-May from Minori Shobou
Price 1800 yen