Wait!
I'm not even trying!
Ihatovo. Ihatovo. Terminus.
Those heading for Sanmutori, please change trains.
Neri! Neri!
I'm here!
Volcanology
University
Did your pastures fare well this year?
Yes. Thanks to continuous spraying,
they did exceptionally well.
Glad to hear that.
Now, get in, everyone.
Thank you so much
for doing this each year for us.
Don't stress it.
Now, please.
Gusko
Budori
Woodcutter
and his wife
Brother Budori, dad, mom,
I came to see you this year, too.
Thanks to your blessing,
our pastures are doing great again.
On the way here,
we stopped by Mr. Redbeard's place.
He greeted us with his usual hearty laugh.
Everyone was cheerful.
I'm sure, everyone's laughter
reaches you too, right?
Life of Gusko Budori
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Don't! I swear...
I'm gonna get to you!
Neri
Budori
Cuckoo-birds cannot pass through here!
Cuckoo-birds can—
Cannot pass through here!
Neri, what is all this?
Bro, you're pitch-mucky yourself!
What did you say!?
All mucky!
Cuckoo-birds cannot pass through here!
Help me!
Stop!
Like I'm gonna!
Neri, let's hurry home.
What happened, brother?
The rain starts any minute.
You've done enough!
Go back inside!
It's alright!
Dad just needs to sell this lumber in the city!
Then, we'll finally have a dinner!
Brother, what about school?
Well, no one attends it anymore.
It's as the teacher said.
Because of the famine, everyone is in dismay.
Because of famine?
We're all in trouble as long as we can't harvest
a single grain of rice.
So we're not the only ones
having an empty stomach?
Yeah. It's this way for everyone.
Even though dad is selling the trunks that big, he can only afford a handful of wheat flour.
But I have been hungry for so long...
Neri, you can eat this.
It's not enough to have a fill, still...
More than that — not just mushrooms or oak acorns,
but you can also even eat the wood bark!
Next time, take me along.
I'll get my fill!
I will.
Really? Make sure you do!
~First thing of which I'm afraid
is a nanny's wretched fate~
~Second — making my dear mad,
third is getting sworn at~
~Fourth is someone smearing me,
fifth is being found guilty...~
What is this sound?
Your father is getting the horse out to sell it!
Move it! Get out! Get out, you nag!
Stop it!
Dad! Don't do it! Don't sell her!
I'd better go play in the forest!
Does it bite?
Say, brother,
when is dad returning home?
Empty again...
Let's go, Neri.
Dad may have already returned.
I'll go look for your dad.
You two stay here.
And don't you think about going outside!
There's... There's flour in that cupboard.
You two eat it, but only a little.
Stay indoors!
What a pair of unruly children I have here!
Neri, let's eat.
Come on, Neri.
Neri!
Mom!
Good evening.
Is anyone home?
Dad!
I have been sent here
to deliver this region from famine.
Now, eat some.
Come on! You should eat.
You look like good children.
But just being good children rotting in here
is besides the point.
You should leave with me.
The boy may look strong,
but I can't keep you both.
Hey, the girl one. If you stay here,
you won't be getting anything more to eat.
Move to the city with daddy!
There, you won't ever feel short of bread.
Neri!
Help me! Brother!
Brother!
Neri!
You finally woke up?
Planning to keep starving further on?
How light-headed.
Neri, dad, mom...
It's famine, after all.
We have the likes of you all over the place these days.
Well, no use to overwork yourself.
You tripped over in the forest.
I went through trouble
to watch over you for 6 days straight!
Keep going!
So I reckon, isn't it about time
you return the favor?
But…
This is... Neri's!
And this... is our house!
And a chimney?!
Ihatovo
Silk
Factory
Ihatovo Silk Factory?
No way! This is our house!
There ain't no house of yours anymore.
Only my silk factory.
Both this house and the forest
around this place — I bought everything!
Well, don't droop,
After all, you can't alter the famine's ways.
Besides, you still have to return the favor to me,
as to someone you owe your life to.
And if you believe you're above that,
feel free to get lost to the four winds!
Just keep in mind —
there won't be any food wherever you go.
In that case...
I see! Now we're talking!
I need your help hanging the nets.
You will be hanging the nets
on chestnut trees in the forest.
Then, we'll breed silkworm with it!
Look there!
Do silkworms really breed there?
They breed!
Hey, don't bring bad luck,
Why would I set up a factory
in a place where silkworm can't breed?
It must breed well!
For your knowledge, it's not just me —
a ton of other people already make living out of it!
Now, you go there too, and get to work.
To work! Hurry!
How limp can you really be?
You sure are one unbearable fellow!
Look, you can have this bun,
but you owe me even bigger one now!
Sure is one unbearable fellow!
You there!
Make sure to tighten that one better!
This way, we won't have any silkworms!
You there! Hang it higher!
Firewood! Start gathering firewood!
Ihatovo
Silk
Factory
Budori! What is taking you so long?
The hell!? What? Huh? What was that?
The sky!...
It's coming!
What do you mean?
What is coming?!
What's going on?!
This must be the volcano eruption.
It's over.
Damn it!
My silkworms are all done for!
No way, no way!
I tell you, no way this works!
Whatever I suggest,
you always dismiss me as a crank!
I'm just telling you to stop, so stop!
Negative! My estimate is certain that this year will be as hot as the previous three together!
In other words,
I'll harvest three years' worth of crop!
Drop it, crank!
Negative, doing it!
I'll have to spread three years' worth of fertilizer as well!
Sure as hell it's a plenty of work!
So I came to you to ask for a helper!
Please let me help you!
Alright, you seem capable enough for that job.
Let's not waste any time.
Follow uncle Redbeard at once!
Forget it!
You snooze — you lose!
I'll see you again by fall.
With three years' worth of crop. Three years' worth!
Redbeard! You'll regret not listening to the elders,
when it's already too late!
A cute child, isn't she?
I'm sure, the day will come,
when you get to see your sister again.
Neri, you're doing well, aren't you?
Sir, something happened?
Contracted a disease!
Your head hurts?
It's not about me. Rice. It's rice!
Look.
Those red speckles are the disease?
Exactly that!
Honey!
Hey, honey! Is it true that they say our rice
had contracted a disease?
It's too late now.
There should be something we can do!
Too late anyway.
It's like five years ago all over again.
Haven't I told you
to drop those ventures because of that?!
In your obsession of harvesting three years worth of rice,
you've wasted three years worth of fertilizer!
And the old man was trying to talk you out, too!
All right!
In the paddies of Ihatovo,
there's no other farmer quite of my magnitude!
Like hell if this discourages me!
Alright! We'll try again next year.
Won't we?
Budori, ever since you appeared at my place,
you haven't had a single good night's sleep yet.
Now! Be it even five or ten days,
you can sleep all you want!
After that, I'll make sure to surprise you
with a magic trick!
In the meantime, the house is going through next winter
with nothing but buckwheat.
You sure like buckwheat, don't you?
I'll purge this disease once and for all, now.
But how are you...?
Dousing in oil kills diseased species?
Of course, If a fellow had his head
kept into oil, he would die, too!
Now, Budori, it's finally time to make buckwheat noodles.
Oil run its course.
Okay.
Hey, Budori!
Come over for a second.
Okay.
My late son's room.
Budori, our paddy is one-third smaller this year,
so it would be much less laborious to till.
On that occasion, I want you to devote yourself fully
to studying the books my son used to read.
So that everyone who had laughed at me before,
calling me a crank,
would go "WOW!" at the sight of the magnificent rice,
that you'd help me grow.
If I'm a crank,
then my head is in the clouds!
Kubo's Earth Science
Very well.
Will do my best.
Professor Kubo,
I have finished mixing the fertilizer.
This won't do.
After all, professor Kubo
is running his own school in the city of Ihatovo.
I wish I would also be part of it.
You think that's how it should be, too?
I'd really like to have more to study.
Besides, Ihatovo City is the largest one around.
Maybe I can meet someone who knows a thing or two
about dad, mom, and Neri.
I get it, I get it! Thanks.
Budori, what is this thing for?
For milling the grain.
Budori!
Yes! Here!
Sorry to bother you, but would you go
to a neighboring village tomorrow to buy this?
Sure... But what kind of thing is that?
If they don't have it there,
keep going through towns and villages until you find it.
Okay… But what about my work?
What are you talking about?
This year, we are all completely out of work.
Bus stop
Rice contracted a disease again!
If even the oil treatment is futile,
what else should I try?
Let me give it a try this time.
I think, I can make it work.
Alright! Go ahead!
Thanks a lot.
Hey, Redbeard,
are you sure about giving it a go?
Hey, Budori, what is that thing?
Wood ash and salt.
You think that'd kill the disease?
Can it really cut the job?
Budori, any progress?
Yes, the disease is apparently suppressed.
What?!
You did it, Budori!
Yes.
Budori did it!
I have been dismissed as a crank for four years straight,
but now I'll have four years worth in one go!
This is rather good enough, too!
I was frankly skeptical myself,
until Budori came into picture to save your bacon!
Yeah, dead right!
And thus, the crank's estimates
were without mistake!
Here. Have a snack too, Budori.
Mistress, thank you for everything.
You have helped me a great deal
in locating my family.
What are you saying?
I was just...
I am grateful, deeply.
Oh my, you are such a gentleman.
By the way, did you learn something?
I see.
You really are a wonderful boy.
If only my son had still been alive...
Budori, if you'd like it better, our doors...
Hey, mistress, we're out of booze!
You know, Budori, I used to be
one of the most prominent farmers of Ihatovo.
I came here with a sizeable seed capital.
But as for now, with droughts and frosts following one after another, my paddy shrank to one third of its former size.
I don't even have any fertilizer left for next year.
And it's not just us.
Within Ihatovo, there's hardly anyone
able to afford fertilizer for the next year.
That's how it is.
In the light of this, there's no telling when I will,
if ever, be able to repay for your labor.
It'd be such a pity for you to slave away
the prime of your youth in the boondocks!
It pains me to say, but you should take this
and try to seek your fortune somewhere less hopeless.
Somehow, I'm sure,
you'll find your own safe haven!
It's the cry of a turtledove.
Though Neri's was head and shoulders above mine.
When I do this,
it's like we're reunited.
Ihatovo. Ihatovo. Terminus!
Ihatovo. Ihatovo. Those changing trains, please hurry.
Sorry to trouble you, little one,
but please make way.
Sure.
I'm sorry, but don't you happen to know
about Kubo's school?
Let's see...
Excuse me, dear.
This boy is looking for Kubo's school.
Do you know anything?
I do!
Oh, my! Hey, hey,
you should ask this lady to help you.
Okay.
Kubo's school is a fine one.
It does a great job
connecting those starved for knowledge.
Is that so?
There, it's inside that forest.
Look for a big white building.
Okay. Thanks a lot for showing the way.
Best of luck.
Alright!
With that in mind,
we arrive to the following conclusion...
The short moments of resting from work
I spent crying, absorbing the musings  into my soul.
Strong buds shoot from it,
though there's no telling how high they can climb.
And thus, I believe, a new field of study rooted.
Hello?
Hello!
You there sure is a noisy fellow,
but I'm in the middle of a class!
If you have business with me,
you join us inside and pipe it down!
Eight Gamma, E six, Alpha.
Particularly striking example
is the Large Magellanic Cloud.
Using the light, all the plants can redox glucose
in their chlorophyll-containing lateral buds.
Well, you can say they are effectively
tugging at heartstrings.
Is that the "History of History" mock-up,
described in Mr. Kubo's book?
It's a ship now!
And now...
Now it's a centipede!
That's a cool one!
And thus, for a case like that...
We can produce a diagram like that.
You really hope to redraw that diagram from scratch?
What's the name of that professor?
It's the Professor Kubo!
You don't know even this?
If you don't even know that,
how can you hope to understand anything?
It took me six years of listening
to the very same lectures!
As for now, the evening is well underway.
This also concludes my course of lectures.
Those of you who wish to apply for the scholarship,
must indeed, as per our custom,
present the notebooks to yours truly,
and after a few further examinations passed,
we will decide on your affiliation.
Excellent. This diagram
is remarkably faithful to the original.
And what in the world is that part?
Let's see. This paddy fertilizer part,
or the one about horse forage...
Then I should ask you to answer this:
When a factory's fireplace is lit, do you know
the colors of smoke curls leaving the chimney?
Yes. Black, gray, yellow, brown, colorless.
It's a mixture of those.
You mentioned colorless, very good.
Care to tell me about the shapes?
Sure!
In a windless weather, the smoke, accordingly,
rises vertically, as the dome tends to disperse.
On the days with clouds hovering low, the plume
first rises towards them, then starts to disperse sideways.
On windy days, the plume slants,
with the tilt angle in direct relation to the wind velocity.
The plume is subjected to the vagaries of the wind,
if it blows in a wavy or linear way.
But fume and chimney peculiarities
also get a say in it.
When the smoke output is negligible,
it assumes the corkscrew shape.
And if some heavy gas is mixed in,
it tufts after exiting the chimney's vent.
It then rushes downwards,
in one or all directions.
Excellent.
You're no stranger to labor, are you?
Yes. I arrived here to look for one.
I have a job just for you.
With my business card,
you can head there at once.
Now, here it is.
Thank you so much!
Then, if you excuse me.
The heck? They are burning their garbage now?
Sorry?
Around that neighborhood.
All right...
Watch out!
If I sort out the job question,
to study won't be an issue.
Maybe I'll even get a chance
to look for dad, mom, and Neri.
I need that appointment, whatever it takes.
Volcanology University
Oops, sorry, little one! My bad!
Hello? Is it for an official business?
Yes.
You see...
Here, this is it.
Reception
Sure, follow me this way.
And that's why I'm telling you it won't work!
Let's put it to the test again.
You go that way.
It's still too early for that.
I beg your pardon.
You must be that Gusko Budori guy.
And here is my business card.
"Volcanology University chief engineer, Pennen Nam?"
I got a call from Professor Kubo not long ago,
so I've been waiting for you.
Starting now, you can work and study here with us.
How about that?
Excuse me, here?
This place only opened up last year.
To tell you the truth, it is a highly responsible job, conducted half of the time on a volcano that may erupt at any moment.
Besides, the behavioral patterns of a volcano
is still a major enigma of Science.
We will need to redouble effort
to our duties, from now on.
What do you say?
Can you do it?
Yes!
Glad to be working with you!
I see. Let us both do our best,
starting now.
Now, this way.
Yonder, there's a room for you to stay
from tonight-on.
For the remainder of the day,
use that room to get a proper rest.
Then, tomorrow,
I'll show you every corner of this facility.
Okay.
This concludes your first look at the organization.
Budori, did I tire you out?
No, it's just that I'm deeply impressed with your incredible equipment and your research efforts in various fields.
Budori, Ihatovo alone
is a home to over 300 volcanoes.
So one can spend his life away just studying
how they impact people's lives, each in its own way.
What you and me are struggling with
is not just volcanoes, but the very nature.
And that struggle has yet merely started.
We're knee-deep in riddles.
Still, one at a time, we approach them,
build new machinery to better comprehend.
And in the end, we don't even get any choice,
but to observe and move on.
After all, it took the entities we're struggling with
millions of years to get where they are now.
I see now.
What happened to dad, mom, and Neri...
And uncle Redbeard.
If only I could deliver everyone
from hardships they lived through...
To do that, I must keep studying.
Try harder, harder, in this place.
Shoots!
There you are!
Morning, everyone!
Good morning, Budori.
Budori, can you take care of that? Thanks.
Okay.
Done.
A little deviation is starting to manifest.
I think we should at least notify
the second floor guys.
Sure, I will go there at once.
You sure?
Then, I'll be on my way.
Thank you.
Excuse me, but it's better
that you change the settings on this one a bit.
Let me see.
It manifests down there, too?
Yes.
I see.
We'll fix it now.
Please do.
Thank you, Budori.
Excuse me!
Budori, it's still at it?
Yes.
Very concerning.
It has been this way for about 5 minutes now.
Sanmutori has been dormant
up to this morning.
Yes. I have never seen Sanmutori active
up until now.
This must be an impending eruption.
Ten kilometers north of this mountain
is the city of Sanmutori.
If it explodes now,
Scorias the size of a table or a cow
and hot gas with ashes will pour over Sanmutori.
At any rate, the only thing we can do now
is to drill an aperture seawards to release the gas.
We're going there at once!
Okay.
This is Budori.
Me and Pennen head out at once
for Sanmutori volcano.
Please take care of everything.
Volcanology University
Your reckoning have something to say
about the time we have until the eruption?
Yes. A month, I think.
A month?!
It can't be more than 10 days!
If we don't get to work fast,
it will be beyond saving!
I'm sure, yonder is the thinnest part
of the slope facing the sea.
It should have no more than two layers of lava.
The rest is soft volcanic ash and lapilli.
In addition, the road to that grazeland is in fine shape,
so transporting equipment would be optimal!
I will get it underway.
Put me through to Director.
Yes, Pennen Nam speaking.
That's right, we have an emergency.
Budori, gauges!
Conduct a check!
Okay...
Hello? Yes!
Form a construction battalion at once!
Yes. Then, I'm counting on you.
The construction battalion is en route.
I say "construction,"
but half the mean is "kamikaze."
Not yet once I had to do my job
in such proximity to the danger!
It must be your first time
working on a near exploding volcano, isn't it?
Brace yourself.
The time to get truly terrified
has yet to come.
Budori, get a grip on yourself!
Can we really... make it in time?
We have to do it!
Even in 10 days, if need be.
Three days for the setup.
Pulling the power lines
from Sanmutori power plant...
Maybe 5 days.
Well, either way, Budori,
why don't we boil ourselves a cup of tea first?
Okay.
After all, the scenery is still breathtaking.
Professor Kubo!
Professor...
Stopped by for a cup of tea.
Got some boiling?
We don't yet have any.
The magma, though...
Pennen!
Yes!
Whatever it takes, we must finish
the construction of tidal power plants next year!
Once we do, whenever something like this reoccurs,
we can start working that same day.
It will also allow for a widespread use
of Budori's suggested paddy fertilizer.
Drought would also be go—
We'll do it, we will!
Now this one must be perceptible enough
even all the way down to Sanmutori!
Just now, in about a kilometer north of our footing,
approximately 700 meters deep into the earth,
a chunk of rocks, roughly 60-70 times this shack in size,
plunged hard into the lava!
I see.
I shall thus have my leave.
Professor?
Budori, I look forward to seeing
how you handle this assignment.
Here.
The rest is up to you.
Here they are, here they are!
The construction battalion.
Well, I'll be on my way, too.
Okay.
Alright, now for a long way down.
You stay here to manage and monitor
the machines at all times.
Keep me informed of the situation
via that phone.
Hang in there.
Okay.
Yes?
This was a strong one.
You have the gas pressure and mounting rate?
Yes.
There has not been a major change in comparison.
I see.
Here, the seismic activity
is too strong to keep going.
But everyone is doing their best.
Then, till later.
Budori? Budori!
Hey, report! Are you alright up there?
Report!
Something's wrong?
Answer me!
Budori!
Hold on!
I'm on my way, don't give up!
Neri... Neri! Neri!
Budori!
Pennen?
You made it out in one piece...
Yes.
But we only have 5 to 6 hours before Sanmutori erupts.
Before that, a smaller eruption will also occur.
We have to somehow finish it in just 4 hours.
At least you are alright.
Let's hurry.
Everyone, please wake up.
We are starting.
Please wake up! We're starting.
Volcanology University
The power plant is on the line.
Alright.
Commence the operation!
Yes.
Why the wait?
Budori, redial them.
A moment, please.
It's here.
That way!
Everyone, take cover in tents! Now!
And you too, Budori!
Thank you.
Quick!
Would that be enough?
It was a success.
I checked with the Volcanology University.
It's just as you said.
Everything went exactly according to the plan.
Is that so?
It's a relief...
At last, the plan for 200 tidal power plants
has been carried out swimmingly.
Yes, a new era is in sight.
Still, much more is yet to be done.
Yes. Today as well,
Budori is running around volcanoes.
What a diligent young man!
Alright, let's go with that.
Hey, it says the fertilizer will be raining from the sky!
Like the usual rain?
Preposterous!
Nitrogen fertilizer is being sprayed.
This summer, along with the rain, the ammonium nitrate
will fall out on everyone's rice paddies and vegetable plots.
If you already use fertilizer,
please include this dose in your reckoning.
Planned dose is 120 kilograms
per 100 square meters.
It will also cause a bit more rains.
There'll be enough drop for the crops
to be irrigated even in case of drought.
If you have paddies left fallow
due to concern about water,
this year, sow these the heart light.
- Ihatovo Volcanology University.
It's almost time.
It's out!
And... now!
Volcanology UnIversIty
Perfect!
Perfect, that's the way.
Budori, down here, all's in order.
It's pouring rain!
The airship has just returned.
I think that's enough for now.
Commence the operation!
Okay, got it.
Ammonium nitrate
is already being exuded into the rain.
The amount is also nigh perfect.
Keep it going for another 4 hours or so!
Roger.
Did it!
Volcanology University —
the new hope for agriculture!
How do you like that?
Here, too.
The breakthrough idea,
suggested by a young scholar Gusko Budori
and Professor Kubo, has been fearlessly implemented
by Volcanology University staff!
Here. Once again, filled with thanks.
That is the most solid proof of how everyone's hard work
brought blessing upon countless people!
Still, what about the leading protagonist?
Budori said the Tachina volcano
is gnawing away at him, so he went to examine it.
Naturally, as a hero of our ranks would!
Excuse me, don't you have any bread?
Bread we have,
but it's not for people to eat that bread.
They mixed up "grain" with "gravel" for this one!
Volcanology University
Hey, you there!
Are you that Budori guy,
who, with electricity, made fertilizer rain this summer?
That is correct.
Hey! Budori from Volcanology University is here!
What, did you say Budori?
For real?
The one from University?
Son of a dog!
Thanks to your darn electricity,
all of our rice wilted before it could mature!
Wilted prematurely?
But haven't you seen the posters
we put out at spring?
A son of a dog, and a noisy mouth at that!
Wait!
This place...
Yes?
Pennen?
Recovering by leaps and bounds, are you?
Yeah, but I'm still clueless as to what and why...
That was a bit of a fiasco.
The village mayor has already brought
his apologies to the University.
But what really happened
to the rice in that village?
About that, the village's main agronomist
made a blunder and mishandled fertilizer use.
Then he thought it convenient to put the blame on you,
so praised by the newspapers.
Can you believe that?
And that's it?
You injuries are still fresh, you know?
Yes.
But there is, actually, one more
very special visitor you got.
So I'll leave you at that.
Special?
Sorry, but...
Sorry, your hat...
Sorry, can I help you?
Neri?
You really are...
But how?
Since then, I got married.
I see...
My husband was listening to morning news,
and then...
But then, that man has...
Yes.
Since then, I have been crying all the time.
He could no longer bear it,
so after 2 or 3 days of carrying me,
he dropped me near a small ranch and fled.
There, the ranch owner found me.
He took pity on me and let me into the house.
There, they let me babysit and do the housework.
Eventually, there was not a single job on the ranch
that I haven't mastered.
Then, 3 or 4 years ago,
I married the eldest of their sons.
As for now, we also have a son.
Ours was a measly homestead, but this year,
the fertilizer was raining, so we had a record yield of maize.
The ranch was faring well again,
and we were all over the moon with it.
All this time, we were so busy with work,
we barely had any time to read newspapers.
Sounds as you've had hard times.
No, you did.
Yet you achieved such heights nevertheless.
It's nothing, I'm just an apprentice.
Brother!
I was...
I was sure, I am now all alone in this world!
So I married.
Yet I kept looking for brother,
with whom our separation was so gust-like...
Neri, I feel you, but there's no need.
We are hereafter reunited.
Right, Neri?
Woodcutter
and his wife
What's the matter?
Budori, you look panic-stricken.
Meteorological survey report:
If you look at the sun's condition and the...
And the ice observation data in the northernmost regions...
Budori, I know exactly what you're trying to say.
Moreover, Professor Kubo is already losing his sleep
trying to come up with a solution.
Then!...
It is expected, a once-in-decade severe famine
will hit Ihatovo this year.
Knew it.
Then, what do we do about it?
I have told you this once:
Since it's the nature itself we're struggling with,
it's always one step forward, two steps back.
This cold season will extend into spring,
and summer is also expected to be colder than usual.
Farmers are advised to take caution.
- Meteorological survey.
What's the meaning of this?
The crop is going to be poor again!
What should I do?
If no measures are taken,
that famine will rear its head again.
Neither Professor Kubo, nor Volcanology University,
have the power to avert it.
What should I do?
Master!
Budori? What brings you here in the dead of night?
And without any cover at that!
Master, please hear me out!
I'm sorry for bothering you at such an hour,
but the matter is most urgent!
Regardless, you should first come in and warm yourself.
Thanks for your trouble!
Master...
Hang that thing and have some tea.
It's about the Carbonado Volcano.
A volcano detonation of this scale
would massively release carbon dioxide gas!
Hang that now!
And then enjoy your tea thoroughly.
Master, if the carbon dioxide gas concentration rises
in the stratosphere, the climate will get warmer, won't it?
That is quite possible.
The commonly favored theory is,
ever since the earth formed,
carbon dioxide gas concentration in the atmosphere
is determinant in its global temperature.
Budori.
I also tried to calculate that:
"Should Carbonado Volcano erupt now,
the gas would soon dissipate in upper tropospheric currents,
eventually spreading to the entirety of the globe."
Yes.
"Consequently, preventing planet's heat
from leaving lower troposphere.
That, I reckon, will lead to the temperature rise
by an average of 5°C across the Earth."
That is correct.
That's why I came to you...
Slow down, Budori.
You can't just casually summon an eruption.
For starters, a long list of conditions must be met.
And I have found
just the way to fulfill them!
I have found it too.
You really did?
We probably have the same thing in mind.
This is something Sanmutori tipped me off, then.
I have...
Not so fast. There is one more big issue
you don't take into account.
Issue?
That assignment would be
beyond difficult and demanding.
The machinery would require at least a single specialist
to stay on site until the operation's conclusion.
Master, I have this sorted out.
Please let me take care of that.
If that would not trouble you much,
I would like you to send to Engineer Pennen
your word of approval.
That, I cannot do.
You are still so young.
There is no one in sight
to relieve you from your current duties.
From now on, you'll be getting a handful
of the likes of me.
Their capabilities would be immeasurably wider
than mine had ever been.
Their work would be more ingenious, results more arresting,
and smiles more broad than mine had ever been.
Master.
This discussion is going nowhere.
You should bring it personally
to Engineer Pennen.
Because it would be too difficult to control anyway,
we use this kind of procedure to pour in the seawater.
I see.
The experimental approach
we've tested on the northern volcano?
That's right.
On Sanmutori over here.
I see now.
Seems worth a try this way.
Indeed.
I understand.
That duty is mine to perform.
I am on my own,
if I were to die there,
then I could wish for nothing more.
Master, with all due respect,
there's still too much "if's" in that assignment.
Even if we succeed in provoking the eruption,
the rain may scatter the gas away before it takes any effect.
Or, just like it always does,
everything else may go off the rails.
And that's why I should...
I will do it myself.
In the meantime,
I'm sure, you and Professor Kubo
would steer the operation,
taking measures to offset various contingencies.
"Our struggle is against nature..."
These were the words of wisdom you taught me.
Why, it is time for the Star Festival already...
Hey you, do you have a death wish?
Neri?
Why are you here, of all places?
Right now, Professor Kubo is awaiting me
for a consultation.
I'll meet you on my way back.
How come there's no choice
but for you to perish?
You, of all people!
I see. Professor Kubo gave you an insight, didn't he?
That explains why he summoned me so suddenly.
Turns out you also went to Professor's?
Forgive me, Neri.
I intended to tell you everything myself,
when the time is ripe.
But why?
Why does it have to be you?
You have so many other employees
in Volcanology University!
You know the answer to that, too.
Because I was the one who suggested it.
Because I'm the one most qualified to do it.
And perhaps, because nobody else can.
You can't...
You shouldn't!
My brother by the name of Gusko Budori
is just one and only such person!
There's not a soul who could take your place!
Neri, I want you to understand...
At last... At last, I was reunited with brother.
And now you're leaving me all alone again?
No, I'm not letting you away!
Brother!
Thief! Stop, thief!!
I'm sorry.
It seems all I'm doing is making you suffer more.
But mind it, Neri,
the last time that famine came,
we had to go through much more suffering and agony.
If that famine returns now, many more people
would be subjected to the misery we endured.
At the price of long studies,
I came up with a method to ward off famine forever.
If success means safeguarding the children forever
from a fate as ours, don't you think it's worth a try?
It's because in the whole world,
we only have each other.
Okay? And that's why I want you to understand, Neri.
Brother...
My only...
brother...
What's the matter with Budori?
Now!
Off
Half
Brother!
Brother Budori!
- Cuckoo-birds cannot pass through here!
- Cuckoo-birds can't...
pass through here!
Now, Mrs. Neri.
Professor Kubo is awaiting us.
Let us be on our way.
Okay.
Professor Kubo is also is looking forward
to seeing children every year.
Professor, too, is ever so cheerful,
be it rain or shine.
Both me and professor feel obliged to carry on the cause
Budori bequeathed to us.
I have this intuition,
ever growing in intensity and clearness,
that brother, though unseen,
keeps walking always by my side,
extending his arms to me.
And to my family as well.
This may sound peculiar,
but to me, it is as if it wraps around
the entirety of Ihatovo,
in a gentle hold.
Timing & misc             Аццкий Критег
& World_Houp
Translation             Perevodildo
TLC/QC             Ziusudra
The End