Toki Shouzou's Private Detective Trouble Notes
Harder! Like this, like this, like THIS!
I am coming! Coming!
Right, getting there.
Sorry for this.
Crap. I wrecked it...
Hello, Mister Toki? Is something wrong?
No, I am all fine.
This is the Telecom Service.
A client phoned your office. Connecting you right now.
Yes, please do.
Hey, how were you expecting a call in my house?
Shush!
Yes, Toki's detective agency here.
Detective agency?
No, have no worries.
A 24 hour help time limit still is our motto. From now...
Never mind, it's no problem at all.
From now?
Aoyama's Elf coffee shop.
Got you, I'll meet you there in 30 minutes.
First job in a long time.
If he calls in the middle of the night,
that's a sign of a great distress.
How can I leave him hanging?
Hey, what was all that about?
Are you a private detective?
Never introduce a man in your bed
before you know his name and profession.
But I never heard yours!
Since you had been so playful,
I didn't want to ruin the mood.
If you are to be my friend, you should have known better.
What are you saying?!
We've been together for two weeks!
I wish I could stay longer, but duty calls me.
You're a brute!
Cretin!
Women and their tantrums...
The drill is as old as the time.
Whenever the phone in my shabby office rings,
the agitated voice of the call forwarding service girl
invariably finds me in my lover's bedroom.
Toki?
The client?
You surely are an impatient one.
I didn't have a chance to even tell you my features.
Well I'm a Tokyo native!
More importantly, this guy definitely deals in showbiz.
Such was my first impression of the client.
It may seem a bizarre request,
but I'd much appreciate if you took it up.
Surely an odd one.
You want me to befriend that man
to then better spy on him.
At the location specified here,
I need you to make him meet a certain woman
as if completely by chance.
However, you already have that guy's name and address.
Why not a direct approach?
I need it to look as a coincidence, by all means.
Something only a savvy pro such as you can handle.
I see.
Very well. I accept the job.
Much obliged, here is your advance.
By the way, I was wondering,
why picking me out of all the detectives?
Actually, you are the fifth choice.
Oh, I see.
On the spot, the previous detectives
didn't quite meet my desired image.
You can channel enthusiasm and spirit, can't you?
Enthusiasm? Spirit?
Hardly. Is that a nice way to say
you want me to play the goof?
So this guy, Tashiro Seiji,
turns out to be a real estate agent.
Shinshu Soba
Welcome!
Here you go.
Thanks for the meal!
You don't ever see the guy smile.
A taciturn man.
Such is a profile of him based on interviews.
How can that tight-lipped guy
be an actual real estate agent?
This doesn't make it one bit easier for me,
a complete stranger, to make friends with him.
He looks like a type of guy who'd choose the horse
with a counting rhyme when betting
and would end up winning.
He's everything that I'm not.
Guess I have no choice but to refund the 150,000 advance.
Eugh.
Hey, small fry. Don't you feel like wiping it?
This was actually brand new.
Asshole! Quit acting unconcerned!
Whassat, whassat, eh?
The bastard spilled beer over me and now act carefree.
What? Is 'dat so?!
Aye? What's with ya?
I like him. After getting three scattered blows,
still landing a one-hook right K.O.
I haven't met a man that tough in a while.
Why, you...
Cash that out as a payback for the stain.
Time to make an exit.
How many beers did you have?
Two bottles. And two tipples.
You paid this low end pub way too much!
That one was a good punch.
As good as your succor. I mean it.
I just couldn't stay idle.
Aren't you now short of one place to hang out at?
No worry. I got a principle
of not getting caught up in that kind of thing.
Good, how about we resume the drinking at my fav' joint?
This time, it's on me.
I'm Toki, Toki Shouzou.
Private detective.
I'm Tashiro.
Thus, the client's assignment has been fulfilled.
Moreover, I didn't even have to fake the friendship.
Well, during my student days,
I was in boxing gym for some time.
That should explain some things.
I knew it.
In fact, I was once longing to become  a boxer myself,
even joined a gym for that.
We had one hell of a good time back then,
with all the guys from the golden age of boxing...
Fuji Takeshi, Gushiken Yoko,
Pressure Onishi!
Pressure Onishi... Truly fine times.
Yeah, He's the fighter I most looked up to.
That being said, I recently stopped
dropping by the Korakuen Hall.
Same for me.
There are no longer any matches I'd pay money to see.
Yeah, boxers these days have plenty
of better side occupations, fighting merely as a hobby.
A gospel truth.
The ring calls whom has nowhere else to go.
Those guys are in no way qualified to be boxers.
In short, if there was a machine to weight the soul resolve,
during a pro test, it's ditch all the scum on the spot.
Huh?
Yo, Housemousie.
What gives?
Preparing for the battlefield of some exam?
Huh?
Under the watchful eye of his mother,
he is made to frog jump back and forth around one spot...
Don't you ever question yourself
if that's how it's supposed to be?
Mister, are you one of those tax auditors?
Dufus.
My job's private detective.
And your income?
Depends, different every month.
Well, long story short, I don't want to end up like you.
Go for it! Go! I count on you!
Once again, the guy's lights are completely out.
Hurrah! No. 3, you're the best!
Tonight, we're celebrating!
I'm that lucky for the first time in months!
Look, just enjoy life, you'll meet even cuter babes.
Let's go party!
No, I prefer this place better.
You sure like stiff drinks.
Gaudy places aren't my thing.
Then, let's just hit the red lights district!
Please, nothing about women...
Are you... One of those?
Nonsense!
I just feel that way right now, that's it.
Gotcha.
Is it a cold woman that looked down on you?
Well, let's stick with that.
A sociopath?
He won't drop a word extra.
That Tashiro guy reverted back to being impenetrable.
As if after a terrible throwback.
Detective Toki listening.
Hello? Hello!
After finally mustering enough guts to call a detective,
would you really just hang up without saying a word?
You're a lucky one, as I am a detective,
whose most outstanding quality is being understanding.
Now, as frustrating as your trouble is, my rate is fixed.
Have no worries on that.
My situation is special...
Huh hmm,
I see.
Okay, let me handle it.
State your name first.
Mr. Onishi...
Onishi Shugoro...?
Unless, don't tell me you're...
Pressure? Pressure Onishi?
I was... No. I still am a huge fan of yours!
Your reversed techniques, like the rear uppercut!...
Yes. Got it!
See you at your designated place, looking forward to speaking to you then!
Thank you.
Pressure Onishi, to talk to him was a honor.
However big of a fan I am, he's still over a hour late!
Damn.
How... How did you tell?
How could I forget the face of a boxer
I so admired in my young days?
This was more than 15 years ago,
since then, I've lost way more than I won!
These days, I'm just a punch-drunk bum.
You're a fighter!
It confused me when you told me on the phone
that you are a fan.
This doesn't justify running away.
Fair enough, so can we talk business now?
You said it was about the opposite sex, wasn't it?
It's about Kuniko. She's turned her heart away from me.
I'm sure of it.
I've been cheated on!
She preferred the neatness of a young salaryman!
I think I understand. A rival in love.
Right... And I want you to investigate it.
Assignment accepted.
I'll beat him to death.
Don't do that!
They don't treat such things lightly these days.
I beg you, I've no one else to rely on!
I'm in high demand lately,
About time I bring one of them to completion.
Hello?
This is Toki calling, I need Mr. Kubo.
Oh, Mister Toki?
Oh? Have you been doing well with the case?
Yeah. About time for the next step.
Wait just a moment.
Checking the schedule.
By 9:30 pm on the 18th bring him
to the Figaro restaurant in Roppongi, okay?
9:30, got it.
We'll know who we need to meet once we walk in?
Very well.
At this rate, it will fall upon me
to socialize my friend Tashiro.
It's Tashiro.
Hey, Toki.
Much obliged for last night.
Never mind it.
Are you available this Thursday evening?
Yeah, every once in a while, I hang out in trendy places.
I don't mind at all.
But instead, how about tonight?
It's the payday, so I can repay for yesterday.
Hmm, working?
Yeah, got work to do tonight.
Then, come along. Cause we're friends, aren't we?
Listen, I'm going to that bar because of the job offer.
Try to keep a low profile and don't talk about my work.
Understood.
So, what are we looking for?
Can't tell yet.
There's a gag order involved after all.
Fair enough.
But please, let me treat you tonight.
Gonbei Tavern
Here, this is the place.
Refill.
First time here, gentlemen?
Kinda. On the way from work.
So, you aren't in this district for fun?
This place is the closes to the Bay Area, right?
Isn't it crowded with youth in the summer?
Occasionally, yes.
I see.
But I imagine, whenever that lively bunch comes in with all that energy, they ruin the atmosphere of your place.
Dealing with youth can get tiresome,
a matter of age probably.
She's a good woman.
Such a smooth skin texture,
a mature woman in her prime.
Madam, the bill please.
Okay.
She's a fine one.
Don't you think so?
Is she?
Still, you seem to not appreciate womanhood,
An everlasting aftermath?
I can't say so.
You should have had at least some dating experience,
with a girl or two.
That, I have, of course.
That man sure experienced a hard break-up.
Heh, you've seen a lot of these, Madam?
You were betrayed by a woman, weren't you?
Is that the reason of your mistrust?
Nothing of the kind happened.
Still, you can't recover from it.
I don't know what's on,
but I'm fine with what I pieced together.
Please keep it that way.
Yeah. No problem.
Although it's not habitual in my trade, I will.
Are you a weekly magazine reporter?
Ah, no...
In due times, I'll tell you everything.
Gonbei Tavern
Madam, please give us the bill.
Huh? Ah... Don't mind me.
Please take your time.
Sorry for the trouble.
Have a nice evening.
Hey, I recognize that guy.
It's... It's...
It's him!
Darling, stop! You've got it all wrong!
Calm down, Onishi!
Hey! Toki, watch out!
Toki!
Darling!..
Toki! Toki!
Hang on!
You two better run away now. If he regains consciousness,
you're not having it easy!
Right! Our bill...
Never mind that, just go!
We're sorry.
Well then...
Are you alright, Toki?
Yeah.
Made it out in one piece.
Still, how uncanny.
What was his deal?
That man was actually the husband of tavern mistress.
That man?
Unbelievable.
On the inside, men and women can be equally as soft.
That may be so.
I'm no less surprised than you are.
What could you grasp about that man?
By his punch and stance, certainly not an amateur.
He's a former pro, the name's Onishi.
Onishi? Pressure Onishi?
Exactly.
No way!
If it was him, he'd never let me land a punch like that!
I'm lucky to get off that easy. Knowing the guy,
it probably has to do with him being soused.
This fist connected Pressure Onishi's face,
surely a lifetime memory.
Ditto.
Not everyone can brag being KO'd by Pressure Onishi.
Yes. Toki's detective agency.
Toki, is that you?
Are you fine speaking right now?
No, actually, I found something of interest,
so I decided to call.
What is it?
A real estate advert?
That bar is for sale?
Yeah, although the other company manages it,
this place ringed a bell. It indeed is last night's Gonbei.
But the hostess never told about putting it in the market.
Is she really plotting to run away with another guy?
Or, possibly, just running away from Pressure Onishi.
Thank you, I'll be on it.
We'll get in touch later.
Currently, I dread that Pressure Onishi
is going to commit a homicide.
After all, I'm his loyal fan.
Now then, about the young paramour
of a woman in her prime...
Gotta be him. Young lover.
Hello?
It's Futaba Real Estate's Satou.
This property... Yes.
Gonbei Tavern.
I think it meets your requirements very well.
Yes. It's pretty worthless now.
This is going to be really cheap deal.
Yes...
I'm sorry for last night!
Are you hurt?
No, I'm alright.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
I'm the one to be sorry.
Actually, this is my occupation.
So, you're a private detective...
As a matter of fact, Pre...
Onishi was the one who hired me.
With what bidding?
More importantly, is Onishi often like that?
He goes on rampages every three days or so.
Huh?
The doctor said he developed a punch-drunk syndrome,
from being punched too often.
Punch-drunk syndrome?
Initially, that was the main issue,
but it has been getting worse ever since.
These days, his idée fixe is me having a young paramour.
Huh? So, about that young man...
Can it be that he asked you to investigate it?
Yeah.
Found anything?
No. Dead end.
Can I ask you about one more thing?
Why is this place on sale with such a low tag?
It's getting too tiresome...
It's between me and that man. All the deal's money
will go to him as part of an agreement.
I can't see it any other way.
Going someplace far away is my only exit.
Starting it from a clean slate.
You know what I mean?
In just a week the deal will be over with!
Please help me get him to see sense before then!
I tried making him see the sense.
How what he's doing is unbecoming of man.
How uncouth he looks,
chasing after an innocent woman with such hatred.
Damn idiot!
You've been fooled by her as well!
Calm down, Mr. Onishi.
You all treat me like a punch-drunk bum,
making a fool of me just like that!
That's not what we think.
You... You sound like someone asking
for another punch from me!
A man and a woman passing through the night
You better disappear from my sight, get it?!
Bitter drops are shed
Well, until she flees, I gotta do something.
No way I resign now, concluding there's no stopping
this Middleweight boxer's rampage.
The demon, heralding my death - this is liar's blues
As you keep crying out to me,
will you one day let me sleep soundly?
And my mind is unsettled, like an untamed horse
Whoa-oh-oh!
In my heart,
only the melancholy
Even on this last night, I wander about in hesitation
Blues
I've been watching Pressure's back ever since.
Still, you think it's fine for us
to show up at Roppongi again?
Yeah, I don't really care that much.
The scent of local refined ladies is too giddy.
Which of the women? Who is our contact?
Our manager, Mr. Kubo, will be an hour late, it seems.
Isn't that Shijo Eiko from "Japan's got talent?"
That's what you can find in Roppongi...
Tashiro...
Eiko...
Oh well.
His problem with women
is much less a mystery now, somehow.
Toki!
It's been a long, long time.
Well, what a great success it was!
You could have spared me the shock,
if you told that the third party was TV celeb Shijo Eiko.
What on earth happened between those two?
I thought confidentiality to be part of a detective's policy.
It is, of course.
Here is the rest of the money, all for the grand finish.
Right. 'Been a pleasure.
If you excuse me, then...
Not the conclusion I expected, but a deal is a deal.
That leaves only Pressure to put a check to.
This boxer seems to be ruminating
over a shattered dream...
Bewitching woman and her shape ups
A week has passed since Tashiro's last call,
But even if I don't initiate it myself,
I'm sure he'll get in touch with me sooner or later.
Yo, Housemousie.
Full of energy, as ever!
Mister, I am spent.
Whatcha say, isn't she a fine woman?
I'm sure you know.
Just some old hag.
Only you see her this way.
I don't mean no offense, but just maybe you should
consider getting a new job now? A real job.
No, I'm completely fine with that one.
How so?
Well, long story short, I don't want to end up like you.
See you around.
Ah, Toki! You're finally here!
Mr. Kubo, what happened?
Oh my. I couldn't reach you by phone,
so I've been waiting here for eternity!
Actually, Shijo Eiko and Tashiro
disappeared into thin air!
Huh?
Since things came to this, I should tell you all the details.
Shijo Eiko signed an important contract with sponsor,
concerning her appearance in this new TV drama!
What contract?
They would extend it to one additional cour.
But in exchange, Eiko must lose five additional kilograms.
5 kilos?
For actresses on American television,
it's a common practice...
So as her manager, I saw it as a chance to recapture
the sharpened beauty from the time of her debut.
But she rebelled against it.
I was prepared to do anything it takes
to honor our contract.
She lacked the motif to go to such a radical weight loss?
Yes, precisely.
Hence the matchmaking with a lover
from the time of her debut as a last resort.
And so, you asked me to become friends with Tashiro,
to bring them together again?
Seemed like a viable idea in paper.
Intense romance and sex are a surefire way
to make those five kilograms vanish in a puff of smoke!
And the result is evident.
That's what I meant! It's the source of all the trouble!
The word of Shijo Eiko's new lover was starting to get out.
And as soon as yellow reporters
started to spy on them, both disappeared!
Uh-huh.
Please!
If the girl stays on the lam, we're screwed!
Anything comes to your mind that might help?
Name your price, I'll pay it!
I heard you, I'll get back to you if there's anything...
Please do, I am off to get more help! Excuse me!
I'm going to Hokkaido.
Whatever happens in the future,
me and Eiko will live as decent people.
Tashiro.
Nothing comes to my mind.
Onishi looks a bit different from yesterday.
He might suffer from another fit.
The hell are you doing?!
Hey! Return my truck!
He's driving that truck right into that shop,
to commit a double suicide with her!
When he's in such a state, if I risk it
to try and catch the usual timing of his right uppercut...
Don't do it, Pressure Onishi!
Your trademark uppercut - just about anyone
would have been mesmerized by it!
Nobody quite compares to boxers in being moving.
Isn't that enough for you?
Quit acting like you understand anything!
That woman would be happier away from you!
What you said... It was a lie, wasn't it?
That she'd be happier away from me.
As bad as it sounds, it's true.
Detective guy, I owe you big one.
No, I haven't done anything out of the ordinary.
Can I ask you about one last thing?
Yeah?
Are you still deeply moved by my fighting style?
Yeah. Every match still sends chills down my spine.
When you feel them fighting to death -
that's what the real boxing is.
As for me, I crave to see bouts as thrilling again one day.
And to see you live a long and productive life,
instead of boozing it away.
I am sure many feel the same.
I see.
It was really that moving?
Night, fists.
And finally, the men's dreams -
everything dissolved in this heavy fog.
My assignment ended there.
A man and a woman passing through the night
Bitter drops are shed
RAW, encoding
Translation
Quality checking
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
The demon, heralding my death - this is liar's blues
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
As you keep crying out to me,
will you one day let me sleep soundly?
And my mind
is unsettled, like an untamed horse
Whoa-oh-oh
In my heart,
In the melancholy,
Even this night, I wander about in hesitation
Blues...
The city, blooming at night, is calling out to you
Can you hear its cries?
In you... It's all in you, dear -
my gloomy blues
If I suddenly fall in love, oh...
Will you smile for me again some day, my dear?
And my mind is completely restless,
like an untamed horse-oh-oh!
Whoa-oh-oh!
In my heart...
In melancholy...
My tomorrow looks just as hazy
Blues...