Proceed!
Nobody told me they have actual fire power!
Shit, we need to reorganize
our formation for actual weapons!
Pull back! PULL BACK!!
Do you think simple police tanks are enough to stop us? Your anti-terrorist countermeasures are a laughing stock.
If our demands are not met by the next hour,
Tokyo will get acquainted with an epidemic outbreak.
Our intentions are quite serious,
so I really hope there would be no misunderstanding.
Misaka, dispatch!
Misaka
Prepare the main weapon! Aim at Tokyo.
What?
We are under assault?
What's going on?
Offshore, it's the Japanese Coast Guard's jurisdiction.
You are behind it, dirtbags!
Women?
It's too late!
Once detonated,
the projectiles will spread anthrax through air!
Thanks to you, all of Yokosuka will perish,
become the capital of death!
Nonsense! You managed to defuse it in such little time?
Field Operations Planning Center
It was a call from Public Safety Bureau?
That's why we decided we'd better let
National Defense Force handle it.
Gentlemen, the incident has been resolved.
Are you sure, vice-minister Awataguchi?
The leader of terrorists is dead.
His crew has been decimated as well.
Well, well.
In the end, it settled down
without the National Defense Force.
Don't think you can cut down
the National Defense expenditures based on that only.
Politicians failing
upwards in the military better be less vocal.
Police officers are in no position to patronize me.
Come on, come on, let's not squabble
with each other after this happy resolution.
Vice-minister Awataguchi, who exactly sorted out this mess?
The Secret Anti-Terrorist team.
Of which I only know the code name: The Siamese Cats.
- Mission...
- Complete!
The Siamese Cats: First Mission
Today, let the sounds of pop electrify you with "City Navigation!"
How does it feel on the road?
Your today's navigators are Jun and Naomi!
Make it Naomi and Jun, okay?
Does it really matter?
Meanwhile, today's last news.
This night, in Misaka park in Yokosuka,
a terrorist cell hijacked
the memorial warship Misaka and skirmished with police.
Kanagawa's police safely quashed
the terrorists' coup de force with organized response.
We're starting to live in times where there's nothing to fear.
Dear listeners, keep
a vigilant eye on red flag signs of terrorist attacks.
Well then, before we could notice,
it is time for us to bid you good night!
Already?
But remember -
24 hours a day, this station allows you to stay up to date.
And now a couple of tunes that best fit this night.
A New Century song, performed by diva Nao, "Do Willingly."
We'll transmit the data feed as well,
don't forget to download it!
Going down into the subway, my usual way,
or leaving out back into the light,
It feels every corner of this bustling city
is buzzing like a busy bee
Gradually, I myself grow to understand,
I actually rejoice along with it inside
Then it feels like one big refresh
Is there anyone who would make me stop,
who would say I'm doing something wrong,
If I indulge myself to lots of fun,
taking a peek into every single store?
Walking in the crowd, passing various people,
bumping each other on the shoulders,
We experience something new everyday.
Now things go like clockwork,
simpler is the life, clearer is the way.
And in the city, too -
everything becomes interesting,
Everything becomes the way I want it,
just like I was hoping since long ago -
I wished, I looked, I sought,
To really live as I always dreamed of
For real,
To stay forever in the "interesting now,"
forgetful of the trouble
Then, see you next week.
Jun and Naomi, signing off.
Ahh, another day, another dollar! That's it for today's grind.
Too bad there is also data parsing left to do.
Ippe!
Coming!
Why do we have to do everything, even data parsing?
We already do everything else - A to Z!
Couldn't Awataguchi delegate it to a penpusher?
If we want it done well, we must do it ourselves.
I suppose...
Then, I'll do my share, listening to the voicemail.
"My old man next door
complains about the dog being noisy, help!"
What do you expect me to reply?!
It's not even that bad!
Hear this one: "The old man next door
speaks directly to my head, as if on... a walkie-talkie."
We get it, the old man should get a life!
This! You might want to check this out.
What is "this?"
The National Defense Forces conduct night exercises in Odaiba.
Naturally, this is a hush-hush sneak picture.
National Defense Forces? Aren't these ordinary ones?
There is an unidentified object they are hiding, though.
Just a moment please...
Hold on as I analyze it for now.
What is this thing?
Can't tell for sure, but it looks like some sort of weaponry.
But why is it floating in the air?
Well, it's a new weapon at army's disposal.
That's about as much as we can tell from here.
But I've never seen such a thing.
Just in case, inquire about
whether Awataguchi is aware of National Defense's agenda.
Okay, I'll see to it as soon as I can.
I got a mail from cutie pie Naomi!
Mail is as follows...
"Hi Awataguchi, how are you?
This recent anonymous tip-off caught my attention.
I have attached the image file.
It appears to be some new kind
of National Defense Force weaponry.
You know anything?
If you know furthermore, tell me.
See you around!"
Is that a leak of Project Artemis??
Jizzbag!
Someone help!
I grew so tired over all this walking...
How about a little cruise?
Incredible!
I know right.
Of the entire model range, she has the smallest clearance.
[4:30AM at Shibaura, north exit blocked]
[4:30AM at Tatsumi junction, east exit blocked]
[4:45AM at Oi Tunnel,
the disused drainage tunnel next to subway line 13 is flooded]
The 13th line reports,
the tunnel suddenly collapsed.
Same goes for the Tatsumi junction!
Someone is trying to isolate the island of Odaiba!
You, there!
Final assessment: all clear!
Next, we may get phase two of the operation started!
The terrorists are occupying the entire city gulf area!?
Gee. Can't even catch the breath after Misaka warship in Yokosuka.
This time it's the entire gulf area?
As if the safeguard system
of the National Defense Forces is a lip service.
I told you that many times! We should have started funding those off the police budget!
The funding of defensive system
was not even taken into plan!
Vice-minister Awataguchi, any information about the backdrop of these terrorists?
Yes, take a close look, please.
Kaido Shunsuke!
Him, indeed. Kaido Shunsuke, aka the Scourge of Asia.
Self-Defense Forces veteran.
For his radical views, was discharged from army in 2000.
In 2001, he acquired notoriety
following the ethnic uprisings in Africa.
Was pulling the strings
for various Arab countries in oil cake conflicts.
During the Reogio's coup d'etat, commanded many guerilla attacks.
Some say he was personally in charge behind the assassination of the president.
Negative, guerillas were their own side as they were fighting both belligerents, for a share of the wealth.
He made a fortune of billions protecting the interests of wealthy states.
I see.
I have my own viewpoint,
but it is a matter for another session.
According to my sources,
Kaido should currently still be involved in ethnic wars someplace far away.
Unpredictably so, he ended in Japan...
So why exactly a professional terrorist like him
would go and seize an entire bay through military action?
The government channel
just received a transmission from Kaido.
I'm casting it over there.
Japanese government, how does it feel to realize you are country's expendables?
I take it that you are
well acquainted with I, Kaido Shunsuke.
Let me go straight to the point - our demands.
As has been demonstrated, we are perfectly capable of carrying out operations on a global scale.
So, to fund our future endeavors,
we expect a $800 billion donation in cash.
$800 billion?
The entire national budget?
A trifle, to spare Prime Minister Nozaki and the entire population of Odaiba -
think of it as a price for all of their lives.
It's actually rather cheap.
The countdown for you to respond starts right now.
I'll let you have 24 hours to do it.
A disregard of the deadline, even by a margin of minutes,
will cost the lives of the
Prime Minister Nozaki and 35,000 Odaiba inhabitants.
This concludes our report.
Be prepared for the next communication after 24 hours, and think wisely.
By that time, I expect you to make a sound decision.
Wait, Kaido!
What are you waiting for, reestablish communication!
I am trying my best,
the other end is blocking the query!
He expects us to accept
all the demands unilaterally, without any negotiations.
This all may very well take
a global scale, so our decision has to be total.
Try to reconnect to the line as soon as you can.
All right, I'm sending an emergency deployment mayday to the National Defense Forces.
The prerogative to deploy
Defense Forces is exclusive to prime minister.
So go contact Prime Minister Nozaki!
That Prime Minister Nozaki
is in the hands of terrorists right now!
Alright, then get that Hamazaki wimp as his replacement!
Before answering to Kaido's
demand, can you give me 12 hours to act?
I'm considering sending in the same team
that repelled the terrorists' hijacking of Misaka in Yokosuka.
The one whose codename is "Siamese Cats?"
We can't leave this critical matter
to a muddy bunch we don't know a lick about!
For a case just like this, our National Defense Forces have a top secret anti-terrorist team of their own.
Major Isurugi, come in!
Isurugi, standing by.
Before your eyes,
National Defense Forces anti-terrorist department commander, also known by the name of Mighty Dog.
Major Isurugi.
Major Isurugi, how long
would it take for Mighty Dog to resolve the incident?
The plan of a special
tactical operation has already been prepared.
It would take about ten hours for us
to have the situation firmly under control.
How about it, Awataguchi?
Isurugi can show you the way out
two hours sooner than your Siamese Cats.
Time is a factor of the utmost importance now.
In that case, we'll let Mighty Dog deal with the incident.
Is that fine with you, Awataguchi?
You can have it any way you want.
But wouldn't it be wise to still introduce Siamese Cats to the case just for insurance?
With due respect,
I think allowing multiple similar organizations into the actual battlefield would only bring about confusion.
Well, well, Isurugi.
You can't belittle Awataguchi's
Cabinet Intelligence and Research Office,.
Understand?
Yes sir.
It's the data from Mr. Awataguchi.
Here goes our hard earned holiday...
Well, at least I have this
American souvenir from Awataguchi. Glock 26 gauge.
I really fancy this. Nice to meet you, my newest partner.♥
The Gulf Area is occupied by international terrorists under the command of Kaido Shunsuke.
We need to get rid of the terrorists in the shortest term.
Among hostages are Prime Minister
Nozaki and the entire population of the Gulf Area.
Therefore, this time we are working along with
the National Defense Forces anti-terrorist detachment.
Mighty Dog was also deployed for tactical operation.
Their side is calling the shots,
so please avoid turning it into a helter-skelter,
I cannot stress it enough.
This data will automatically self-destruct now.
Even this knickknack talk must self-destruct... As if it was something important.
[Central Headquarters of the National Defense Forces]
Captain Isurugi!
For this tactical
operation, we were advised to use those P90s.
Mighty Dog is ordered to gather in the briefing room.
Roger that!
Captain Isurugi, what kind of people are these Siamese Cats we must jointly work with?
Excuse my impertinence!
Huh? Isn't this the briefing room assigned to Mighty Dog in Ichigaya Garrison?
Place and time don't seem wrong, it appears.
Are you the "Siamese Cats?"
- Here's Jun!
- And Naomi.
Together, we are the Siamese Cats!
Hey, hey, hey, you ham it up.
That heroic A-list team is made of two women?
You have a problem with women?
National Defense Forces anti-terrorist unit, Mighty Dog, with major Isurugi at their head.
Pleased to meet you.
How about having a post-operation dinner?
Sorry, I cannot mix work with pleasure.
Isn't that uncute?
Allow me to detail the proceedings.
According to the military satellite's intelligence,
The enemy forces are 2 submarines, 30 boats, 10 combat helicopters, and finally, leg infantry - about 100 men.
From their modus operandi,
it is obvious they were premeditating it for a long while.
The Police precinct, the new Parliament building,
and Prime Minister's official residence
are already in full control of enemy's infantry.
Ariake Nuclear Power Plant is also occupied.
It must not be downplayed that in the worst case scenario, there's a chance nuclear reactor runs out of control.
Therefore I expect you to act with extreme caution.
If Ariake nuclear reactor
is out of control, what are the consequences?
The entire Kanto region
simply becomes a giant exclusion zone.
Moreover, here is restricted information
that was previously classified as A-tier:
This designated spot contains
the National Defense Forces facilities for weapon R&D.
Development code "Artemis."
The first in the world weapon making use of a force shield.
Even at the army's level, this is top secret knowledge. There only supposed to be a handful of people knowing about it.
The harder you try to cover it up, the more info is prone to leak.
Whether Kaido is aware
of Artemis' existence is the real issue, am I right?
Artemis falling into the hands of terrorists
is something that must be prevented no matter what.
Even if it means Prime Minister Nozaki's sacrifice.
Gee, poor Nozaki fellow.
This is the Cabinet Crisis Management Center's guideline.
Hold on, you wouldn't trade the entire population's life for this operation's success, would you?
We will engage the area from underwater.
This is the disembarkation point.
From there, we launch a blitz
to recapture the facility and push back the enemy,
thus ensuring Artemis' safety.
On your part...
...Make away with the bozos occupying the power plant.
In other words, our job is to minimize the possibility of Gulf Area population being exposed to danger.
A standard anti-terrorist goal during wartime is to first shut the enemy's ears and eyes.
If you manage to seize the power plant,
you will be able to stop the electricity supply.
That's how to cause confusion in their midst.
One way or another, all is fair in love and war.
Captain!
I have an objection to this plan.
Are you sure it's safe to entrust
the nuclear power plant to a bunch like this?
How about instead of dispersing troops, we...
Firstly, a word of advise,
Don't look down on them for how they look like.
They have their own reliable sources.
Top-secret as it is, the existence of Artemis was no mystery whatsoever to them.
Then, remember how effortlessly
they crept into the very heart of this garrison.
Besides, in the recent
Misaka warship incident, they were the duo that resolved it.
Then, we can now proceed to the execution part of the plan.
Equipment is a special wristband.
The operation plan
was downloaded in everyone's personal memory.
Roger!
Good luck.
Same to you.
May seem rude, but are you eyeing up who I think?
Maybe?
Anyway, I wonder if they're ready to put the residents at risk.
We will settle score before it becomes an eventuality.
True.
[Telecom center]
Do you guys have a single idea about what you are doing?
We will never negotiate with terrorists!
Had we been average terrorists, I think I'd do so myself.
However, whether the government decides to buy you and the entire gulf area populace outright,
by paying up the ransom or not paying -
is of very little concern to me!
What is on your mind?
You don't have to pretend.
I will now dispel all your doubts at once. Come in!
Professor Kaneko!
Prime Minister, why are you here?
Wait. By bringing
professor Kaneko here, don't you mean to say...
Don't tell me your true goal is...
Forsooth. Development code "Artemis."
The next-generation weapon
at the forefront of Japan's scientific capabilities.
But it's supposed to still be far from completion!
There is no use to feign ignorance now.
Isn't that so, Professor Kaneko?
Rest assured, Prime Minister, for it's still far to be completed.
Too bad for you. You came through so much trouble to come here just to have your hands on a pile of scrap iron.
Professor, next you are going to tell me
that the army's inner circle was not informed of completion...
Very well then.
Saito, report your progress on Artemis.
Roger.
As I speak, the tech crew
executes a meticulous inspection on Artemis in the hangar.
With much effort, we deduced that part of the algorithm that connects to the mainboard section is missing something.
What is missing?
The key-holding factor
was seemingly deleted by hand or omitted.
Is that why you claim it to be incomplete?
What is that key-holding factor then?
About that... Unfortunately,
it'd take a lot of time to explain the basics.
I understand.
Try to hasten up the analysis on your end.
On our end, we'll also fish for extra information.
Roger that.
In the meantime, try to politely untie professor's lips.
About what this key factor thing is.
I insist, be straightforward but stay polite.
Roger that.
Torture me all you want, I won't spill a thing!
Allowing Artemis to fall into your terrorist hands!
The world... The world will not slide into chaos!
"World will not slide into chaos."
It rings good as a slogan...
Don't you think so too, Prime Minister Nozaki?
The world has long been sliding into chaos,
ever since it has given birth to devils as you!
That's good, you really put it splendidly.
[Ariake Nuclear Power Plant]
Well, I leave the rest to you, Ippe.
Alright, I'll carry on until further orders.
Meow~~😼
Hi!
Jun, mission...
Getting started!
This way.
Close call.
Two mice sneaked in.
We ain't no mice, mind you.
Listen carefully now.
We do in the wicked scum, we are team...
Siamese Cats!
How pretentious!
Stop! If we destroy
the control systems, we will be all screwed.
Quite right.
While it doesn't concern me in the slightest
if some control system here breaks or whatnot.
Main system failure. Switching to subsystem.
So, what's your call?
Wanna go on fighting like that?
Or act with gumption and not sacrifice Tokyo's capital populace along with the gulf's?
It's time for an entertaining interrogation!
Who are you affiliated with?
If you don't fess up, you'll end up as the old mook over there.
Now...
Fess up!
Speak!
It's no fun at all this way. Let's spice it up, then.
Before we resume, how about
I put the old geezer out of his misery?
Stop that, you.
Perfect. I love this gleam of anger in your eyes.
Stop it!
Yes.
Yes. Roger that.
Luckily for you, I have other fish to fry.
Until I come back, behave and be quiet.
Professor!
Are you okay, Professor Kaneko?
And you are...
Vice-minister Awataguchi from
Cabinet Intelligence and Research Office sent us.
Awataguchi then...
I see, you must be the Siamese Cats!
Alright, time to make an escape!
Listen up, I managed to stifle Kaido,
As his main target was Artemis all along.
These troublemakers don't know
what is the key factor, required for boot up.
But they'll figure it out eventually.
Key factor?
That's right. An ingenious system to prevent Kaido and the likes of him from employing it for ill purposes.
It was designed to only be possibly
activated by a person carrying a specific genetic code.
What do you mean?
So... who is this person, carrying a specific gene?
It's my grandson Kazuhiko.
Please, protect Kazuhiko from these villains.
We've got you.
You did a great job, Siamese Kittens.
Now that we know the catch, you are no longer of use.
Meet your demise.
Hurry, they are running away!
Hang on, professor!
Are you okay, Professor Kaneko?
Not at this rate...
I can see them! This way!
They're running away!
You can leave me here. Forget about me and flee!
My grandson... Protect my grandson Kazuhiko.
Dammit!
You're late!
I'm sorry, there has been a confusion in the upper ranks.
Instead of securing Artemis,
we were suddenly ordered to exfiltrate Kaneko.
Then, we'll entrust Professor Kaneko to you.
We have some other place to go now.
Professor Kaneko, we'll honor our promise.
Until then, take care of yourself.
Where are you going?
Geez.
Geez, the kitty cats sure are wayward.
Professor, let's get you out of here.
No, I can't go yet.
We need to make a detour via my laboratory.
At any cost, I must set off Artemis's self destruction.
This isn't part of our orders.
Screw the orders! Fate of the whole world is on the line now!
I got you.
Ippe, do you copy?
Operation plan changed, resurface at once!
Here we go.
Ippe, get us to Tokorozawa, will you?
Tokorozawa?
Am I a taxi driver to you?
Not quite, but close enough.
Anyway, hit the gas!
Gotcha.
The enemy went down!
Don't let them get away! Follow the trace at once!
Roger!
Just as I thought, we are
already tracked. So let's spur the horse!
They sure aren't taking it easy!
Look at the road!
'Kay, 'kay.
Shoot-shoot-shoot!
Hey, it's only the shore there!
Well, enjoy the hustle!
Huh... Follow along!
Not bad, right? And that's a fraction of my abilities.
What a bright boy!
Awataguchi from
Cabinet Intelligence and Research Office or not,
why are we away from all the terrorist action?
I know right, it's more like we are on a babysitting gig!
Where is this helicopter going?
No clue.
Closing in on the dropping point.
Anti-terrorist units of police are here to protect the target.
Stupid flatfoots!
Fire at will!
Blast it, look at what they did!
And we still aren't in the know!
Alright, the storm troopers can now retrieve the key factor.
No way, you got in Tokorozawa as quickly as we did!
Making the impossible possible is our job.
That's Siamese Cats for you.
Nailed it!
Let's make sure of it.
What the hell... was even that?
Who knows...
Poor fella.
There's another one.
Chances of surviving such a crash are nearing zero.
What?
Bullshit...
Are you a Terminator, or what?
Stop right there. And drop the whip.
Got her!
Idiot, it was me!
Game's over now.
Wait, you won't land a hit!
Jun!
Jun...
Wait for me, Jun!
Two more left...
Last...
It's moving us somewhere!
Sluice?
Auto-tracking: Lock on!
Here!
Grab it!
Faster!
Good lord...
Cabinet Intelligence and Research Office, huh?
I've never seen a license like that.
Anyway, I'd like to thank you guys for your service.
When you have a chance, tell nice words about us
to Vice-minister Awataguchi from Intelligence, will you?
As per his orders, the Siamese Cats
have taken Kazuhiko under their custody.
- Bye.
We are never in the know about all this secret mumbo jumbo Cabinet Intelligence stuff!
They're so cocky, amirite?
Dreamy...
Say, sis...
My granddad... He's all right, isn't he?
Your granddad is perfectly fine.
After all, we personally made sure of it.
But that means granddad was in danger?
Somewhat, but now he is in the clear,
He was lucky to cross the Siamese Cats's way.
Granddad...
You love your granddad, don't you?
It's all good now. No need to worry.
Everyone, buckle up! The ride is gonna be bumpy!
Steer through the woods!
Roger!
[National Defense Forces R&D Facilities]
Enemy is near! Regroup!
Scatter!
Captain, we will buy you time
so that you set off Artemis's self destruction!
Professor Kaneko, why did you start it?
The self-destruction system
also draws energy from the reactor.
Booting up the machine is an unskippable step.
There's 10 minutes on the countdown.
Understood. Buy us 10 more minutes.
I'll think of something.
I count on you.
In just a bit more, I'll protect Artemis from those devils.
Thank you, Professor Kaneko.
Not only you told us where to look for key factor, you were also so kind as to guide us through the start-up procedure.
Kazuhiko will also soon arrive here.
At this rate, you'll get used to moving reunions.
Stop it! Don't you dare to lay a finger on Kazuhiko!
Leave him be, he is toothless now.
We're in the open already?
Where else should I go?
Tokorozawa forest is not that wide!
Sister.
Here.
What is it?
Sis, by any chance, are you gonna meet granddad first?
Yes, it is likely.
Then, I want you to give it to granddad.
He said
I must hold onto it in times of danger and keep it close.
But... Right now, I believe
granddad needs this more than I do!
You're a nice kid, Kazuhiko.
I got you. Sis will make sure to pass this to your granddad.
Pinky swear.
Sack of shit!
No good, I can't lose it!
Dammit, it never goes as planned!
Ippe, faster!
Shit!
Kazuhiko, can you hear me?
Your grandfather is with us...
Granddad!
Don't, Kazuhiko!
Get out at once.
Otherwise, you won't see your grandfather.
Moreover, you'll get blown up
along with the good-for-nothing bunch.
Kazuhiko!
Wait, don't go!
If I obey, does it help granddad?
It sure does.
And big sis's group?
Naturally.
Kazuhiko, don't listen to them!
Kazuhiko!!
Damn it, we are helpless in protecting a kid!
Key factor successfully secured.
Well done, head straight towards the laboratory.
Roger.
Key Factor in arrival.
We could have been fellow scientists by now!
Aren't you ashamed?
Kazuhiko!
Granddad!
I beg you, he is an innocent!
Don't do a boo-boo to granddad!
Not if you do a thing for us.
Artemis...
Airlock chamber extended.
Airlock chamber opening. Key factor loaded!
Airlock chamber insertion complete.
Initial connection pending.
With the key factor in,
Artemis's algorithm is finally complete.
Are we going to see the machine in action?
All external power is off.
Unplug connections.
Roger.
Your Grace, preparations went OK.
Artemis, boot up!
First lock released!
Boot up command confirmed.
Main bridge disconnected for start-up.
Second lock released.
First supporting leg removed.
Analogically, second supporting leg removed.
Auxiliary power supply shut down.
Internal power supply cord: no detected issue.
Artemis: take-off preparations complete.
Stop right there,
Artemis must not be used for devilish purposes!
Professor Kaneko, thanks to you, finally, Artemis became mine.
Don't you see how you are paving the way for the world's destruction??
Thank you for the constructive input, Professor Kaneko.
Artemis: take-off!
Artemis, as a tryout, aim at Hamamatsu.
Splendid! Destructive power is beyond expectations!
The world is doomed...
Delta 1 reporting, closing in on the target!
The target is confirmed dead ahead!
Moving in to attack!
A shield!
Regroup for evasion maneuver!
Is there a nation able to stand in the way?
With only 10 more Artemis...
No, even 5 will be enough.
World hegemony is no longer an unreachable dream!
Tactical withdrawal!
Major Isurugi...
The allotted time
to neutralize the terrorist menace elapsed.
It's over! This is the end of Japanese sovereignty.
Awataguchi, what did happen
to your vaunted Siamese cats?
There is still one hour left
for the Siamese Cats on their tactical operation time.
One hour?!
Within this hour, Artemis is going to absolutely level Tokyo!
This is Isurugi of Mighty Dog.
Major Isurugi, current whereabouts?
I humbly apologize, at the moment, I am chasing Artemis.
Please tell me about Artemis's weak spot!
Weak spot you say?
She'd never become a perfect weapon if she had any!
Isurugi, this is Awataguchi
from Cabinet Intelligence and Research Office.
Artemis's weak spot is the shield generating head!
Awataguchi! This is a state secret disclosure!
Now, the integrity of the nation is at stake,
It's certainly not the time to keep secrets!
Thank you so much, vice-minister Awataguchi.
What a pain,
now what spot to aim at, in this Kebab machine?
How is it going, Ippe?
The connection is done.
OK...
Will this thing really be enough?
I fiddled with it on the go.
I can't offer any guarantee.
It consumes the energy
of the entire nuclear power plant. A Beam Bazooka.
But it siphons out a lot of energy,
so you only have two shots.
Just two shots?
We will make do with that.
Hold a minute!
Of course, it's in vain!
I don't like this, we are next on its list!
Here I go!
It's now!
Awesome!
Hang on!
You...
Ippe, this contraption is useless.
What did I told you!
Of course it can't penetrate the shield!
Artemis has...
Take it easy.
Artemis' weak spot is the head.
The shield generating system.
Understood.
After we pull through, how about we have a dinner?
Can be somewhat cute after all?
Ippe, look after Isurugi please!
Roger that.
See you.
Jun!
Artemis's weak spot is in its head,
Once the shield is disabled, hit there!
Got it!
Kazuhiko...
Well done! She managed to sneak behind the shield!
Jun, don't rush. It's far from over yet, Jun.
Don't do anything reckless, Jun!
I'll catch my breath before the last push.
See how scary I am if you piss me off!
She did it!
Close call, close call...
She effin' nailed it, Naomi!
The shield is disabled, now!
Once Jun is out of harm's way, I'll go for it.
Gotcha!
A regenerative function?
Naomi! The new shield will be deployed in a moment!
Shoot the second one right now!
What are you saying?
Hurry up and escape from there!
Bad news, the shield is recovering at a fearsome pace!
Quick, don't mind about me, Naomi!
Jun!
Hurry!
Shoot...
Let's make it, Jun.
Jun!!
Naomi, where are you going?
Naomi?
Evacuation!
Your Grace Kaido, please hurry!
When they saw the opportunity,
they lent a helping hand,
but now they scamper like mice from a sinking ship.
However, this is not the end of Kaido.
Saito, have you brought along Artemis's data?
Yes, Artemis's algorithm data
was recomposed and stored in here.
Watch out!
Kaido.
You are beyond forgiveness.
Naomi, right?
It's been a while since Africa,
I didn't expect a reunion in Japan.
Is it as foe or friend, this time?
I surrender.
If it means being shot by you, I regret nothing.
Have you forgotten the way of a warrior?
Asshole, still as underhanded as you were then!
Underhanded?
To the terrorist, that's rather a compliment.
Farewell!
Jun!
As ever, falling prey to compassion, Naomi.
But how? Jun, how did you make it out alive?
Remember when Kazuhiko gave me this locket?
Turned out to be a mini shield grenade.
Jun!
Kazuhiko?
Kazuhiko...
It was thanks to it that we all got saved.
I'm so glad!
Gentlemen, the incident has just been resolved.
Prime minister is safe.
Prime Minister Nozaki?
After all this Artemis chaos, I completely forgot!
The death of the mercenary leader Kaido Shunsuke is confirmed.
The remainder of his forces likely all deserted.
Brilliant as always,
Awataguchi. This time again, we owe you one.
Yeah, I always knew the Siamese Cats would save the day.
My patience with them paid off!
Hi fellow listeners! Today, we have a special edition of
"City Navigation," live from the formerly occupied gulf area!
The gulf area, as well as the neighborhood has suffered a significant damage from the terrorist attack.
But through the cooperation of police
and National Defense Forces, it went under control.
Congratulations, congratulations.
The remaining terrorists have been promptly cornered and arrested by the forces of order.
So what did we do at the end of the day?
Just provided a succor for those girls?
These two are lovely.
The policemen seemed relieved to get this together.
And now, we present you a new song,
Nao's second hit, KEΦI.
After this song, we'll continue our live feed, so stay tuned.
Mission...
Complete.
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation: Perevodildo
Quality Control: Ziusudra
Raw by... no clue who, but mikezilla2 sent them to me so there's that