It's something that every person has​ ♪
It's something that every heart holds​ ♪
Held deep within, even before time itself began​ ♪
It's hidden inside every person​ ♪
It's hidden inside every heart ♪
Transcending absolute darkness ♪
It's our ultimate spirit force ♪
Through charitable acts​ ♪
Through practice of Samadhi ♪
And focused study ♪
We can open this realm ♪
Through enlightenment ♪
And achieving Nirvana ♪
Even someone as you may freely catalyze this power ♪
Clairaudience, telepathy, retrocognition, mental immunity ♪
Transcending absolute darkness ♪
Realm of Transcendence
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 1
Levitation!
The Holy Spirit of Truth is the guru Asahara Shoko.​
Our leader found salvation through early Buddhist teachings.
In pursuit of the Supreme Truth,
He studied intensely to get spirit force.
And earned many spiritual powers along the way.
With their help, He became familiar
with the rules of cosmos,
waking to keen awareness of Nature's phenomena.
Using this strength,
He strives to bring happiness to every soul.​
In "Chouetsu Sekai", we will present key moments
when the Leader realized his powers.
Chouetsu Sekai Episode 1: Levitation
This story is dedicated
to His struggle towards ultimate enlightenment.
Reminding soaring birds,
he climbs the sky.
This air gliding phenomenon
is known as levitation.
Seven years ago,
I discovered it to not be a pipe dream.
This was a sublime realization.
Soul of Truth
Reverend Asahara Shoko
That's right, I found myself suspended in the air.
After the fact,
I was enrolled in a meditation program.
Something felt different...
Something was different.​
Despite keeping my eyes closed,
I saw odd light rays emanating from my body.
The top of my head felt hot.​..
How unnerving, I couldn't stand it.
But I couldn't stop halfway.
I pushed myself forward.
​For an instant, I felt spiritual energy rush from the bottom of my body to the top.​
My body started bouncing like a rubber ball.​
​And then, after a last leap, I found myself suspended in the air.
I experienced levitation for the first time.
At the time, I was focused on searching nirvana.​
Without a guru, I carried on alone.
I refined my technique through trial and error.
After levitating, I built confidence in my study methods.
It was bliss.
Because in line with the Buddhist scriptures,
it is one of the six miracles
unlocked with proper training.
Chouetsu Sekai Episode 1...
How was it?
With none to guide him,
our Leader trod on an unknown world.
We hopefully conveyed fairly
His emotions in this episode.​
Just as our Leader, those who do not study
under the guidance of a guru,
​but allow their souls to achieve nirvana
are known as achievers of the Supreme Truth.
Only an infinitesimal amount
of these souls makes it.
It is all the more difficult
to attain without a guru.
But in Aum Shinrikyo,
our Leader succeeded in that,​
And He is guiding us towards that path.
Thanks to His mastered stage,
our training is certain to bear fruit.​
Would you also like to meet our Leader,
experience spiritual awakening and develop your soul?
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 2
Rumor from another dimension!
We are the most blessed disciples,
of the Holy Spirit of Truth
Asahara Shoko.
Doesn't he know way more
about ourselves than we do?
The hidden depths of our heart
are opened to our comprehension,
much like self awareness of material bonds.
The Leader is quick to raise the flaws.
And He bestows the most appropriate and compassionate advice on us.
The same may apply to whoever He meets,
even a first-time with the Holy One
bares your true self in a most heartrending way.
No need to fend for yourself,
no attachment to cash,
no need to lie to yourself,
or kowtow to others.
It may lay to waste before our Guru.
I'll now deliver you an episode on which
such a venerable Teacher makes use of His Spirit Force.
Enjoy "Chouetsu Sekai" Episode 2:
Rumor from Another Dimension.
We are 700 ordained disciples
and 10,000 laymen.
How can one possibly lead so many of us?
Isn't that too much?
That's the common think.
But how many
or how far apart we all are...
are irrelevant questions.
Because my Transcendental Power
is based on Holy Truth.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
Today, I have the pleasure
to introduce you to a new mystery episode.
- Aum Shinrikyo's Dojo of Supreme Truth -
Juniors train under me
with the aim to become ordained monks.
Of course, they must not disregard strict rules.
Among them, the obligation of abstinence.
Regarding sex, it is forbidden
to express interest in the opposite gender.
Once, I had an astral projection shooting from my material body...
And it escaped to the Realm of Form.
In margins of the crowd,
I overheard a rumor.
Say, say, have you heard about it?
Michiko and Yoshio have a love affair.
What?
If the Holy One finds out, it'll go sour quickly!
Hello? Michiko's speaking.
Stop chasing after Yoshio.
S-Sorry...
Hmh? How did I found out your secret?
In the Realm of Form I heard about it.
Besides, what do you find in that disciple?
I can't let him forget himself.
Change your mind and focus, got it?
Our Guru said that no matter
how many disciples you have,
no matter how far apart,
be aware about their frame of mind.
By the way, the word to keep in mind is "precept."
Trainees must follow all the ten of them warily.
In following order, they are...
About intolerance,
do not kill.
About stealing,
do not steal.
About Evil,
do not be evil.
About dishonesty,
do not lie.
About falsehood,
don't speak untruthfully.
About slandering,
don't slander anybody.
About duplicity,
don't mislead one another.
About attachment,
don't covet others.
About malice,
don't harm others.
About delusion,
don't deny the Truth with ignorance.
If we uphold these precepts,
we won't doom ourselves
and reincarnate in a lower world.
Everybody, why not question your daily actions,
words and thoughts
in the light of these commandments?
See you next time.
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 3
Incarnation's Experience
We all have a physical body.
So, its existence
implies physical pain and tormenting thoughts.
With a body the fatality of death is around,
as such, a body deteriorates over time.
A body also endures sickness.
A body commands the existence of hunger and thirst.
A body bears the discomfort of heat and cold.
And because of a body
you can't move as freely you like.
Yet, through strict training, can't you project
your conscience to an incarnation state?
The third episode of "Chouetsu Sekai"
addresses this topic.
Let's all project towards this way!
An incarnation is another body that we have.
With it, we can tread upon the ground,
or conversely take off from there.
You are free to go where you want to go.
You can also freely morph in appearance
through willpower.
You can teleport and traverse walls,
roofs, buildings and more...
Even plunge into earth.
Walking upon water is also possible.
Besides, as previously said,
we can get to the Realm of Form.
They can manifest themselves and act before us.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest Leader Shoko Asahara ~
Eh, isn't that the Guru?
It is Him.
Quite unusual to see Him walk alone here.
Yes, let's give Him our regards.
Guru!
Strange, seems like He doesn't want to interact.
Huh? It's odd, we can't catch up with Him.
Even worse, He seems to outstrip us.
We lost Him.
How uncanny.
That's right.
Anyway, let's return to the Dojo.
The course starts at 6 o'clock.
Yes, let's get going.
Ah?
Why the weirded out faces?
We saw you on the streets just before!
I have been here all the time.
But how can it be?
He really was meditating until now.
Huh?!
Then, who on Earth did we spot?
That was my incarnation.
What??
During a deep state of meditation,
your incarnation may freely roam around.
Alright, give your very best!
Yes!
Just like this, a trainee able
to project his incarnation is free.
Also, the avatar can also end up
in alternate worlds and dimensions.
First hand familiarity with the inner workings
of the Universe and Supreme Truth starts from there.
So, what is the point of using an incarnation?
It is Equanimity (Upekkha)
separation from this world.
Our physical body is bound to the empirical world
because our consciousness
is bound to our material desires.
See you next time!
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 4
Fateful Meeting!
The defunct Spirit of Truth,
revived through Guru Shoko Asahara.
It was attained thanks to His study of the earliest Buddhist scriptures.
His divine power
stems from a source transcending human nature.
We are always surprised
to see His spirit force in action.
The episode we deliver you this time, is a romantic foray into our leader's Transcendental Power.
Let's get started with "Chouetsu Sekai" part 4.
- His Eminence Kalu Rinpoche -
I had a life changing interaction with Kalu Rinpoche,
As if guided by the hands of fate, that Zen monk appeared to me.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
I am the Zen Master,
Kalu Rinpoche, a Tibetan lama.
What is that vision I just had all about?
Without a doubt, a true Zen master
is still present in this world.
I must meet him in person, no matter the cost.
Thus, the search of that person
from my vision began.
From Japan, with his name as only hint...
I took a plane in direction
of Delhi, India, Darjeeling, Calcutta.
And it First landed in Hong Kong.
I was able to meet him right there.
Undoubtedly...
He was the person from my vision...
He was a head lama from the Tibetan Kagyu school.
As you can see in this episode,
a deep state of meditation allows two beings
to meet in the Realm of Form, beyond time and space.
This way, Kalu Rinpoche
was also able to anticipate my coming.
He asked his entourage:
"Let me know whoever arrives today for a visit."
This way, both of us...
Were able to form
a mutually beneficial bond around Faith.
Isn't it mysterious to find a stranger
only using a meditating vision?
Mostly given how our leader and Kalu Rinpoche knew each other's existence through spirit force.
After meeting in Hong Kong,
our Guru stayed at a temple in Darjeeling
where Kalu Rinpoche lives,
then, he returned the favor and preached
in the Mount Fuji dojo branch of Aum Shinrikyo.
Rinpoche, coming from eastern Tibet, had practiced meditation in the mountains for a long time,
After China's invasion of Tibet, he found refuge
in Bhutan, a Buddhist country, before going to India.
Still, everything is subjected to impermanence...
As the hour to say good bye struck.
Thus ends episode 4 of "Chouetsu Sekai".
See you next time.
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 5
Farewell!
Everything changes,
coming to a close before vanishing.
Our lives are no exception...
A beautiful encounter
is always seeding a definitive farewell.
No one can avoid it.
Likewise, it applied
to Asahara Shoko and Kalu Rinpoche.
They also had to part ways.
"Chouetsu Sekai" Episode 5: Farewell.
...This is why.
Do you understand?
Oh, hold on...
Thank you.
This was surely the voice of Kalu Rinpoche.
He thanked me,
and his notification made me question.
That's right,
I ought to meditate and ask the gods about it.
His Eminence Kalu Rinpoche...
I guessed so.
Kalu Rinpoche reached for me to say good bye.
The gods confirmed
that he is on his way to the afterlife.
I am affirmative that he is
either dead or living his last moments.
As you know, there is no telephone coverage
in the area where Rinpoche is located...
As soon as we get our visa, we'll fly to India.
Agreed!
A few days later, our Guru and his party
arrived in Delhi, India, under a scorching heat.
Leaving the car behind,
they walked towards Rinpoche's temple.
Look who's here...
How miraculous, coming so quickly!
Even though the telegram announcing his death
hasn't reached its destination yet.
In fact, it came to my awareness through my Transcendental Power,
I had a very last contact with Rinpoche's soul.
Our guru bid his last good bye.
Also, he fondly remembered Rinpoche's lifetime effort to protect Buddhism during Tibet's greatest upheaval.
He never set foot on his birthplace ever again.
In his eastern Tibet temple, a tree once planted by a young Rinpoche still stands quietly...
Waiting for its caregiver.
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 6
The Guru Disappeared!
Long ago in Japan, there were people known as ninjas.
They were highly trained, especially in the field of espionage.
Intruder!
Over there!
This is the end...
He's gone!
Ninjas have perfected the art of stealth.
They disappear from the scene, as if a shape shown on a television suddenly switched off.
But is this stunt realistically possible to do?
The answer is no.
It is nothing more than a myth aggrandized by popular culture.
However, the Supreme Truth from the Buddhist scriptures makes it possible to disappear.
It brings forth a divine power beyond people's imagination.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
Observe me closely.
I am going to disappear.
He's gone!
I really can't see him.
But, I am not sure whether it's some optical illusion.
It really is a miracle, fantastic!
What's the matter, fellows?
I told you I'd disappear, didn't I?
B-But, it was way too spectacular!...
An energy field enveloping my body is causing this.
By now, you should be fully aware of my spirit force,
still, skepticism is understandable.
A divine power beyond Humanity, the spirit force.
Our Guru faced many hardships in life...
Since His heart secedes from earthly suffering,
His strength opens a higher sphere of existence to Him.
It is said that this mysterious power
spontaneously manifests.
This transcendental state
proves that we reached absolute Freedom, absolute Blessedness, absolute Bliss.
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 7
Exceeding modern medicine with spirit force!
Any adept of Aum Shinrikyo can apply to get
a secret yoga course, directly carried out by our guru.
Many of us can recover from illnesses
through this secret yoga!
- Aum Shinrikyo's Suginami Dojo -
On this day as well, the leader was consulted about a certain disciple's ailment.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
Mr. Yamada, your cancer will recede.
Stay confident, please!
Is that really so?
By the grace of your personal strength and practice, you will be cured.
Let me introduce you
to Aum Shinrikyo's practitioner.
He is a brilliant physician.
Please confide in his guidance.
Vajratissa, can you also see the shadow
on Mr. Yamada's right lung?
Is there anything bad in this spot?
No, there is nothing unusual.
Is it divine will?
You may want to check it more closely.
- Aum Shinrikyo's Affiliated School Clinic -
Did the guru really find anything through cursory inspection?
I wonder.
Ah, show the image again.
This is...
Lymphadenitis.
It is certainly so...
Even though it's tiny, the guru was able
to detect it at a very early stage...
Sure enough, the leader knew.
I am awestruck
at how His Transcendental Power preempted science.
Every time I see His power avert something so terrible,
I feel so proud being His disciple.
Mr. Yamada, the Guru said you will recover,
you are in the clear,
stay strong!
Yes.
I believe I'll overcome cancer, if I place faith in our Leader.
I'll hang in there!
Our guru accurately pinpoints diseases through His spirit force,
and gives proper guidance towards remission.
Miracles do exist.
Just being by the Holy One's side
will make you recover.
The empowerment to fight against cancer
is an instance among these miracles.
While doctors unrelated to Aum Shinrikyo may fail families of patients with serious condition,
Aum Shinrikyo helps them fight with a better chance,
Aum Shinrikyo makes them
step towards existential truth.
The Holy one's Transcendental Power is really something to reckon with!
Here ends "Chouetsu Sekai",
stay tuned for the next installment...
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 8
The Far away Tibet!
Let's travel to Tibet, this secluded country.
Its biggest city is the 1300 years old Lhasa.
It has flourished as the political, economic, cultural and religious heart of Tibet.
The Holy Spirit of Truth, the noblest leader Asahara Shoko, visited this place in the summer of 1991.
It will be difficult for the Dalai Lama to leave India and return to Tibet.
Tibetan Buddhism is dying out...
How regrettable.
By the way, I am going
to Drepung monastery tomorrow.
Drepung monastery?
Going to Drepung?...
If that's the case, why not also visit the First Palace, they're neighbors.
I cannot, they're not at the same place.
The guidebook tells:
The First Palace is westward of Drepung monastery,
10 minutes away.
It's in the same place, you'll find out once there!
And on the next day...
Rarer oxygen in high altitude sure is painful, right?
I already passed out because of it, yesterday.
I now have a portable oxygen bag.
Ah, Guru, excuse me...
Could you pose for the camera?
Excuse me, venerable monk, what is this building?
The First Palace.
Huh, the First Palace, you say?
What about Drepung Monastery?
It is close by.
See, that's what I told you, in the same place.
In my fifth life, I reincarnated as the Dalai Lama in Tibet.
Do you still remember
the pain of your predestination?
About this, I remember it vividly,
it's my guidebook.
Well then, let's go!
Just like this, spirit force allows one to recall past life.
It is called "retrocognition".
This is the ultimate stage in meditation...
After passing The four levels of Samadhi.
Incarnation's Experience,
Divine Hearing Experience,
Mind Reading Experience.
The fourth one is Transcendental Power.
If you can reach this heightened state,
you will remember what went on through cyclic metempsychosis...
What kind of world you were born in,
what kind of life you lived, and how you died...
Past conditions, relationships long past era,
your previous lives...
Also, the laws of karma.
You will find yourself aware of so many things firsthand.
They are linked to predestination pain,
as accounted in our Guru's experiences
and secret techniques.
Part 2 of the Secret of Transandence series is detailing everything you need to know about the topic.
Please read it by all means.
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 9
The guru looks out!
The Holy Spirit of Truth, Asahara Shoko...
Closely looks after his disciples, making it difficult to devote Himself to His strenuous training.
In His infinite compassion,
He redeems His adepts through spirit force,
This episode is dedicated to his struggle.
Now on with "Chouetsu Sekai"
Episode 9: The guru looks out.
Our leader Asahara Shoko was undergoing
a demanding practice in the Genkan of his pavilion.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
I was standing by in a separate building
with somebody else.
The guru was meant to contact us by radio,
provided that he had any need.
The only problem was that my co-disciple was bedridden with a high fever.
The snow keeps falling...
Can I take a look at your temperature?
Oh my, it's this high?
What's the matter? Don't exert yourself!
Well, I'll get going...
In your state? You cannot walk, stay put!
I need to talk to her, don't get in my way!
It's snowing outside, don't!!
Something is wrong...
Are you going to your death?
Guru...
Thanks to the guru, he was convinced
to go back to his bed.
Even being familiar with His formidable spirit force...
It is humbling to see him use it.
Our leader is so concerned about our sake,
I nearly swoon.
Would you also like to feel as welcomed as us?
The Holy One's Divine Spirit Force
Part. 10
The Miracle Surgery!
I am Noriko!
I am Kansai, I follow the way of the Truth.
This last autumn, I was taken to India for more advanced education.
But I cried and cried so much
while taking the plane, what was the matter?
Noriko, what's wrong?
If you don't properly sit, your neck will hurt again.
Be good and sit down.
What's wrong?
Does your neck still hurt?
It's painful!
Feeling any worse than before?
Ye-yeah!
Me is not fine...
Mhm, how worrisome...
What should I do?
Noriko sweetie, wait for me,
I'll ask the guru for help.
Ω Holy Spirit of Supreme Truth Ω
~ The noblest and purest leader Shoko Asahara ~
Uhm, guru?
Hmm, what's the big matter?
Noriko is crying because of neck pain,
standing in a strange way, not wanting to sit down.
I see.
Then, bring Noriko here.
Achari, leave your seat to Noriko.
Yes.
Come on, Noriko, sit right where Achari was.
I will take away your pain.
Noriko...
I'll perform astral surgery on your pained neck...
Well then, Noriko, let's get started with Astral surgery.
It won't hurt at all.
Alright, Noriko, the astral surgery is over.
Your neck won't pain you anymore.
See for yourself.
It really doesn't hurt, not anymore.
Thank you, Guru!
Amazing!
Being able to kill pain with only astral surgery,
our Leader is out of this world!
The spirit force of our guru is such,
Uma Parvati Herself would be surprised by His Shakti.
His power is like an inexhaustible spring.
Because there are so many people in pain,
plagued by intractable diseases...
Our guru is selflessly dispensing his mystical energy to them.
Miracles are bound to happen with Him around.
For instance, he made an elderly person unable to walk without a cane for 10 years, move around without aid.
Any abdominal pain making anyone wince in pain
is gone in no time at all.
Cancer patients even get respite.
There are many doctors in the ranks of Aum Shinrikyo.
Witnesses to our guru's powers,
which exceed the boundaries of modern medicine.
In a way, during the healing process,
the guru also takes away everyone's karma.
Then, His good deeds made Him never fall sick,
not even once or twice.
Even He was told He had two more months to live because of liver cancer caused by others karma.
For that reason, our guru replenishes Himself through intense training.
He carries much of the burden by Himself,
so that person determined enough
can reincarnate in a higher world.
And stay happy in this world in spite of their nature.
To strive and turn suffering into bliss,
also making somebody else's suffering theirs.
This is the calling of the Holy One,
the world's savior of souls.
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"