Disclaimer: due to the condition of some of the original masters, there may be some image distortion or noise.
Papa
Mama
Bye Bye
Three houses were built on the hill.
Whoa! Ow-ow-ow!
B-But I'm the one who fell!
Really?
Ah! Kuro! That's not a toy!
Kuro!
Get back, Kuro!
Give back the birdhouse!
Kuro!
Get back here!
Kuro! Stop!
Give it back!
Over there!
Stop!
Kuro! Kuro, wait!
Stop, boy! Stop!
Stop it!
Kuro! Wait!
We got him now!
Really... I won't forgive you!
Stop, Kuro!
Come on!
Kuro!
Stop!
Give it back, Kuro!
Give it back!
Kuro!
Oh no! You bad dog!
Mom won't let you get away with this mess!
Kuro!
Got you!
Stop!
Goodness me, what happened,
Yuu-kun, Yasu-kun? Kaori-chan too?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Idiot! Kuro, you idiot!
Kaori?
Is it you, Kaori?
Goodness me!
The flowerbed's a total disaster!
What happened?
Why'd you have to wreck the flowers this bad, Kaori?
It's Kuro... Kuro...
Stole the birdhouse...
I'm sorry...
My, that's quite serious!
Yuu-kun, Yasu-kun!
Goodness, it's like a hurricane
went through here.
We're deeply sorry!
The flowers you poured
so much pains into...
Oh no, flowers are no big deal.
I'm more surprised no one got hurt!
We're so sorry...
Come on, Yuu-kun, Yaku-kun,
you apologize too!
It's all right!
No need to cry.
Anyway, aren't you hungry?
What'll I do with these children...
Grounded!
Kids who can't even say sorry after misbehaving deserve to stand on the porch!
Oh? What happened?
Did he make you two stand there?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Yuu-kun, Yaku-kun.
It's my fault...
You shut it!
You're the one the most at fault here!
You don't deserve to be fed!
Huh?
They're gone!
H-Hey! The children are gone!
Huh?
They're probably there.
Where...
We're sorry, mister.
We're sorry, ma'am.
We're sorry, flowers.
My, you two are such good kids,
Yuu-kun, Yasu-kun!
Apologizing requires a lot of courage.
I'm really proud of you two.
See? We've restored the flowers
to how they were, so don't worry now.
It looks like you know
your flowers, mister!
Like you know!
Do you boys like flowers?
Yeah!
You know, I grew up
in a damp house with no sunlight.
So it has always been my dream
to be surrounded by flowers
under this clear sky.
All right...
You know, papa and mama told us it's gonna be
plenty of houses in this area soon.
Yeah, they said.
Well, when that happens, I'll make even more flowers and share them with everyone.
Oh, even with me?
Sure. When this one blooms into a beautiful shrub, I'll gift it to you two.
Really?
Really!
Breakfast!
We're home!
I'm hungry!
Sorry.
Sorry...
Did you say something?
Sorry!
Hey, that's my mask! Unfair!
Now, wash your face and hands.
Okay!
Gimme water too, Yasu!
You're so spoiled!
But you're the one most spoiled here.
That's right.
Oh, maybe it's grandma
who is actually the most spoiled here?
Impossible!
If there’s one thing I’m not, it’s spoiled.
Hurry up! Breakfast!
Breakfast, grandma!
Okay!
Sit up straight when you eat.
Thanks for the meal!
Good luck!
Yeah...
Kaori’s been a handful
for you this morning.
Hop on, I'll drive you to the station.
Oh, you're being too considerate...
Bye, Papa!
Off I go!
Bye-bye!
See you!
Oh no, Kaori, you need to run too!
What are you waiting for?
You're late!
I'm off!
Kaori-chan is late! Late!
Late!
Watch out, you!
Why don't you watch out?!
Oh, you're going
to Class 3-2 this year, right?
I'm Shinpachi from Class 3-3!
There's no one in the third year
who doesn't know me!
Hey, wait!
Okay, Yasu-kun, start throwing!
Ready!
There!
No, you can throw better than that!
All right then...
There!
Nice!
Ready, Yasu-kun?
Yeah!
There!
Wait!
Caught it!
Yes, thank you!
Mama! Throw it!
Okay, here I go...
There!
Impressive, Yuu!
Me too!
Okay, Yasu's turn now.
Here I go...
There!
Another one!
All right...
There...
You hit it!
Wow, amazing!
Going shopping?
Yes. You look like such a happy family.
I guess I actually
want to have a boy, after all.
You'll know soon enough.
Who knows.
The due date’s in the fall, after all.
Ah, would you like to apply for the same kindergarten as Yuu-kun?
Mama, the ball!
Yuu-kun, remember that you and Yasu-kun can't go down the hill on your own.
We've just moved here,
so you don't know the area yet.
We don't want you to get lost, do we?
Don't forget.
Okay!
What about you, Yasu-kun?
Oh? It's written on your face,
"But I want to go!"
I mean it. Only go with your grandma
when she does groceries.
Okay...
Huh? What's that?
What is it?
It's a pigeon!
Okay, after it!
Catch it!
That one can't fly!
Ah! It went that way, Kenji!
Huh? Where?
Flank it! From there!
Kenji, you go over there!
Okay!
After it!
There!
Huh? Not here?
That's strange...
Did we lose it?
Tsk! You two are useless!
Ugh... We almost caught it!
Huh? Hey, have you seen a pigeon?
An injured pigeon!
Ah! Th-There it is!
We found that pigeon! Give it back.
Why should I give it back?
The pigeon is no one's property.
Besides, it's very weak, its wings are broken, and it's injured.
We need to treat it and release it back.
If we give it to you,
you'll just kill it for sure!
Dumbass!
Even I know how to keep a pigeon!
No way we're giving it to you!
Let's go now.
H-Hey!
Why didn't you two say something?!
But they're too strong.
Are you stupid?!
They're just girls!
But even if she’s little, Hanaiwa can still
scratch your face to ribbons!
She's fast too...
She pounced on my face
the other day—like that!
And the lanky Norikawa
is going to the karate dojo.
Ouch...
Tsk! Cowards!
Wait, Boss!
Coo, coo, coo,
pigeon coo, coo.
If you like beans, come down.
Let’s all eat together...
Not bad!
Okay, one more time.
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
If you like beans, come down.
Let’s all eat together...
Why, you!
Then how about this?
H-Hey, take it easy, Yasu-kun, Yuu-kun!
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
Pigeon flap-flap, pigeon flap-flap!
Hey, Mama, get ready for Yasu-kun!
Would you look at this friendly ghost!
There, who's flapping now?
Doesn't hurt!
Sure, here you go.
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo!
Easy now.
Sit still.
Wait, get back! Yasu-kun!
Coo, coo, coo!
Papa, you always sing that pigeon song when taking a bath.
Why not change the song sometimes?
But Yasu-kun likes that song, that's all.
No, don't run, Yasu-kun! Hey!
This way, Grandma!
You'll catch a cold!
Hey, Yasu-kun!
Give grandma a break.
Hey, stop!
Oh, just do whatever you want.
Guess I might as well
not tell you about Kaori's pigeon.
Pigeon?
Hey, what was it about Kaori's pigeon?
I don't know.
But I'm actually a good boy.
Good boy, you hear?
Good boy!
No! You can't scare it!
You have a home, Kuro.
Coocoo doesn't have one,
so you can't get mad at it!
Be quiet, Kuro!
Kuro is jealous!
Hey, Kaori's brother,
why did you tie up the Coocoo?
Oh, it's because its wings are broken,
so we have to fix them in place for them to heal.
Bear with it, Coocoo-chan!
Okay, it's almost done.
Hey, big bro, when you’re done with this nest box,
you should carve "Pigeon’s House" into it!
Sure, I'll put a drawing on it—
"Pigeon's House."
No, no! It's "Coocoo's House!"
Coocoo's House!
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
Get better soon, won't you?
So you can fly as soon as we let you go.
Not-not-not-not fall!
Coocoo
Yasu-kun! Yasu-kun, come to eat!
Okay!
I'll see you again soon.
Coocoo, bye-bye.
Yasu-kun! Yasu-kun!
In a minute!
Come on, I need to go to town, Yasu-kun.
I won't go!
I wanna clean out Coocoo's house
before Kaori-chan comes home!
I'm staying too.
Grandma, buy us some ice cream, okay?
Buy ice cream!
Lend me that, Yasu-kun.
Here.
They're both so obsessed with that pigeon.
Are these all your photos?
Yeah.
Wow, you were a baby too, Kaori-chan?
Of course I was!
What are you laughing at?
Kaori, your friend has come.
Got it!
Ah, it's him!
It's that hooligan Shinpachi.
Wait here for a minute.
And don't come out yet, you two.
Hey, Kuro!
Hey! Get up! Kuro!
Please, we need you! Come!
Kuro, see that boy at the gate?
He's a baddie who came to bully Kaori-chan.
Go there and bark him away!
Hey... It's not the time for this!
Kuro!
Go! Go! Go.
I'm serious.
I'll train that pigeon
into a perfect courier pigeon.
Give it to me.
No can do.
Hey, I can give you this.
Wow! So you're a fan of Momoe-chan too?
D-Don't misunderstand!
I-I've taken it from my sister,
although she values it very much!
We're not going to keep that pigeon forever.
If it recovers enough to take
to the sky again, we'll release it.
Carrier pigeons always fly freely
all over the sky!
Forget about that!
It's not even clear whether or not it'll be able
to fly again at all. It's been hurt badly!
That badly?
Yeah.
Ah? Shinpachi-kun! What did you come to Kaori's place for? You're not welcome here!
It's none of your business!
Well, I'm leaving.
I don't fight girls.
You really like that Coocoo, don't you?
Ma'am, Coocoo won't eat its food today.
It only drank a bit of water.
That's not right...
Poor thing.
Here you go, Yasu-kun.
Thank you, Mister!
Good morning, Coocoo-chan.
I brought you a flower today.
Come on, cheer up,
eat some beans.
Coocoo! Coocoo!
Coocoo!
Kaori-chan! Kaori-chan!
Coocoo won't open his eyes!
His body is still!
No way...
What is it?
Brother...
Coocoo...
Hey, is Coocoo not coming back now?
Yes. We buried Coocoo,
he can't come back anymore.
Really? Kaori-chan, big bro?
You can only live once.
You must cherish life.
That's what the teacher
from my previous school said.
Coocoo! It's Coocoo! Coocoo!
There are so many
kindergartens around here.
Yes. I've checked them all.
This one looks like a nice place.
They say the facilities are among the best in the prefecture,
and the principal is a famous teacher.
I like this one more.
The principal is a young child educator
with her own unique approach.
Take our Yuu-kun—
his health isn't the strongest.
He's prone to catching a cold in the winter.
Huh?! Is this the unique approach
you're talking about?
Exercising barefoot and naked?
My word...
Yasu-kun will go
to the kindergarten next year.
If he becomes any more fond of running around naked, I won't be able to take it.
Grandma!
Oh, it's already nap time for Yasu-kun.
Yasu-kun? Yasu-kun! Yuu-kun?
Yasu-kun, Yuu-kun?
Are you here? Are you not?
Yasu-kun?
They're both gone.
How very strange.
Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun?
I've not seen them.
I see. We thought maybe they went to play with Kaori-chan...
Ah, no.
But it's strange for Kaori as well.
She’d normally be home ages ago by now.
M-Madam, isn't that Kaori's?
Dear me! When did she...
Could it be...?
Huh? What?
No, I mean...
The other day, Kaori took
Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun with her.
She said they were going to Otamaga Pond,
so I stopped her firmly.
What? Otamaga Pond?
It used to be called
"Devil's Pond" back in the day.
It swallowed up so many people...
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
If you like beans, come down.
Let’s all eat together.
There!
Wow! It's a pond!
Yay! It's the pond!
A big pond!
It used to be even bigger in the past.
Oh?
Ah! Flowers! It's flowers!
Wow! Butterflies!
What's that?
What are you? Wait!
It's a grasshopper!
Huh? Where did you go?
Huh? What's that?
Oh! What's that?
Ah!
Ouch!
It's called a "snail."
No! No! It has horns, look!
Look, a ship!
That boat is too shoddy to sail.
Don't walk that trunk too far!
It's dangerous, Yasu-kun!
Ah! But there's something on the boat.
A frog?
Y-Yasu! Here! Take my hand!
Take it!
Yasu-kun!
Yuu! Yuu!
Wait, Yuu-kun!
Help!
Yasu-kun, don't stand up!
But... Water! Water! Ah!
Help! Quick!
Kaori-chan, help!
Yasu-kun!
Help me!
Help! Help! Huh?
See, Yasu-kun?
Yuu!
Look, it's funny! So many clouds!
That one's Kaori-chan.
Then that tiny one must be Yasu-kun.
Maybe the one next to him is Yuu-kun?
The one with the plump belly is Kaori's dad.
No, it's the madam
from the house with the flowers.
Okay...
Kaori-chan!
Yasu-kun!
Yuu-kun!
Papa!
Mama!
Okay, they're dry now.
There.
Ah, it's Coocoo!
Where? Where?
There, that one!
Ah! You're right!
Coocoo flies!
Hey, Yasu-kun!
Yasu-kun, we're going home now!
Just a little longer! Over there!
Yasu-kun!
You hear?!
Oh come on...
Kaori?
Yuu-kun?
Yasu-kun?
It's Kaori's.
Kaori!
Kaori-chan?
Say, you don't suppose...
Don't worry. This pond is too shallow.
Where could they have gone?
Let's make another round,
try searching for them more.
I'll go over there.
Then I'll check here.
Kaori-chan, where are we?
Who knows.
Looks like we're lost.
Lost?
Don't worry. As soon as we figure out which way home is, we'll find our way at once.
Now, where to go next?
Yasu-kun, are you tired?
Does your belly ache?
Come on, I'll carry you the rest of the way.
It's my...
fault.
Yasu-kun, it's okay.
Come on, take my hand and let's walk.
Ah, it's a pigeon!
There! Coocoo went that way!
Okay, let's go. Get on.
Wow, I can see our houses!
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
Oh?
If you like beans, come down.
Let’s all eat together.
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
Yuu-kun! Yasu-kun!
It's mama!
Mama!
Thank god!
I'm sorry.
We got lost.
I'm really sorry.
It's all right.
You were already going home when you met me, weren't you?
If so, you don't have
to apologize that much.
It must've been hard for you
to carry Yasu-kun.
Madam!
They merely went on a big
daytime adventure.
And you panicked as if it were
an earthquake or a fire.
We were really scared.
For a moment there,
I also could feel my heart sink.
Hey, Papa, since we didn't get a chance to scold them tonight, will you lecture them tomorrow?
Hm... I don't know.
From the way it sounds, Kaori-chan and Yuu-kun actually come off as pretty dependable.
No, you can't let them get away with it.
You must draw the line firmly.
What if Yasu-kun gets lost again?
If Yasu-kun gets lost, he'll probably be able to find the police box on his own.
Or at least a patrol car for sure.
It's nothing to laugh about.
Children need disciplining.
Sure, sure.
You're lucky to have two children.
When there’s only one kid in the family,
like Papa was, they end up
spoiled at best—selfish at worst.
The parents can't make up their mind!
Well, I learned something
nice about you, Papa.
Anyway, let's put them to bed now.
Grandma, maybe today's episode
of "Mito Komon" is not over yet?
Ah, that's right. Goodness me...
Kneel and show due reverence!
Do you know before whom you stand?
Tremble with awe, for this is none other than the former Deputy Shogun, Lord Mitsukuni of Mito!
Lower your heads, all of you!
Ah, not again...
It's summer vacation!
There!
Here!
Hey!
Okay... Here I go! There!
There!
Yasu-kun!
Are you all right, Boss?
That was rough...
Yasu-kun, are you hurt?
Hey!
You! This ain't no playground
for pipsqueaks!
Not a pipsqueak!
Kaori-chan said
this park belongs to everyone.
Kaori? Oh...
So you two are Kaori's henchmen?
What's henchmen?
You don't even know what
a henchman is, you pipsqueak?
Listen up. What henchman means is...
Well... I mean, henchman is...
Hey, Kenji, you, tell them.
Huh?
A henchman is... Like a retainer!
Yeah! That's right.
What's a retainer?
You guys aren't watching the TV or what?
Kneel and show due reverence!
Do you know before whom you stand?
Tremble with awe, for this is none other than the former Deputy Shogun, Lord Mitsukuni of Mito!
Lower your heads,
bow before his presence, all of you!
But Kaori-chan is not Komon!
Tsk. As expected of Kaori's henchmen—
they're just as cocky as she is!
We're not henchmen, are we?
Yeah, not henchmen, friends!
Oh? Then what are you playing together, as friends?
Role-playing with dolls?
Or maybe folding origami together?
Not at all, cat's cradle probably.
No we're not!
What, then? Picking cicadas?
Picking rhino beetles?
Catching crayfish?
What say you?
Shinpachi-kun! If you bully others,
the teacher will scold you again.
Kaori the Toady.
The Imitator Kaori!
Kaori the Crammer!
Why won't you teach them something useful instead of bullying?
Why won't you do it yourself, Girlboss?
Fine by me!
Girls can do anything they want.
What's so funny?!
Then try riding this.
A unicycle?
Yasu-kun, hold it for a moment.
Here I go!
Watch out!
She did it!
Damn you...
How was it?
Okay...
But can you do this?!
But can you do this?
Then, can you climb that tree?
How about this, Kaori?
Careful!
Do your best, Boss! Ah!
Watch out!
Oh goodness me.
No, you shouldn't be climbing that tree!
But aren't you curious boys—you're even interested in playing with little kids?
You'd make a nice big brother.
Good boy.
You boys too. Good boys.
Hey, let's go.
Wait, Boss!
Come play with them again!
Man, it's hot...
But it wasn't too bad!
Boss, you caught plenty today as well!
It's only natural!
Huh?
Isn't this where the pipsqueaks live?
Next to Kaori's house?
It's the bastards who embarrassed us the other day!
Take care of it, then.
Still, I'm a bit worried.
Even Kaori-chan or her big brother
can't stay with them today.
Don't worry!
We can watch the house just fine!
We can!
All right, and we'll try
to come home as soon as we can.
But it's still dangerous
to leave them two alone...
It's fine!
I'll leave it to you, then.
Make sure to close the door.
And have a lunch at three.
Yeah! Got it!
No, I think, I should stay after all...
It's all right.
Bye-bye!
"Bye-bye"—snotty brats!
Dumbass! They'll hear you!
All right, they say?
Okay, let's give them a scare!
There!
Okay, preparations finished.
Let's go?
Yeah.
Rock-paper-scissors!
You'll be the alien.
I'll go hide now.
I just need to say numbers
from one to ten, right?
Yeah. And count slowly.
One, two...
You get what I mean?
Yeah.
Mild at first, but more intense later.
Yeah!
Nine.
Ten!
Where are you?
I'll eat you if I find you!
Are you here?
Ah, there!
Found it! Let's get full on these first.
Found Yuu!
That's sneaky, Yasu-kun!
Mama said not to touch these until three!
Don't whine when you're hungry later!
I'll be fine!
When that happens,
I'll just follow it up with your half.
Huh? No fair!
There!
Eight.
And...
Ah, on the second floor?
Nine, ten!
I'll eat you this time!
Huh? He's not here.
What?
Is it you, big bro?
Yuu!
Where are you?!
Yuu?
Yuu!
Seems like he's running all over the place.
All right, it's about time
we dealt the final blow.
Yuu, are you here?
Yuu!
Okay. One, two...
Yasu-kun!
Yuu!
It's a phantom!
It scared the crap out of me!
It's not supposed to be flying this low.
Did you know?
"Phantom" means Yokai in Japanese.
Now the, it's time for the finishing touches.
Come on, bring the bucket.
What was that sound?
The aliens!
The aliens are here!
Who is it?
Aliens!
Hey, let's take another peek inside.
Maybe they fainted from this one?
Don't do it, Yasu-kun.
Maybe it's the burglars?
No, it's the aliens!
Yasu-kun!
Don't show them your face!
Boss!
Hey, wait for me!
They weren't aliens!
Yeah. But they did look
like aliens when scared.
And then we went on a long-awaited beach trip with the whole family.
Ready? There you go!
Yay! It's finished!
I-It tickles!
Yay!
Wow, so pretty!
Oh! I can see it!
Look!
Yasu-kun! Yasu-kun, what's wrong?
Seems like Yasu-kun
had a pretty scary dream.
Look, Yasu-kun. Kaori-chan and the others are watching the ships.
Ah! A ghost! A shark ghost!
That's an American aircraft carrier.
Oh? Aircraft carrier?
It's a warship that carries a lot of planes on it.
But I'm sure it's a shark ghost, all right.
And then autumn came.
Sakura Kindergarten
Goodbye!
Bye-bye!
Welcome back, Yuu!
I'm home!
Close hands, open hands,
Open hands again, clap hands.
Put those hands up...
My, that Kaori-chan...
Hey, will you come to watch
our sports festival tomorrow?
It's going to be exciting—
in the third-year competition,
I'm going to run a race
against Shinpachi-kun.
Yay! Kaori-chan's going to win!
Who knows.
Shinpachi-kun is quick too.
But you're even faster!
Yeah! Faster!
Hey, you'll win, right?
We'll come to root for you!
We'll come, so win! Win!
All right, I'll do my best!
Make sure to come!
Ready... Go!
See that you don't fall!
That's called "rainbow!"
Rainbow? Wow!
Big rainbow, pretty rainbow!
Yasu-kun, are you okay?
Yeah.
No! Don't start crying, Yasu-kun.
I know!
Daruma-san, Daruma-san,
let's stare at each other!
If you laugh—you lose.
Take a look!
My! What are you doing?
You'll catch a cold!
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Autumn
sports
day
Mom!
Where's my cap?
My cap!
My athletic cap!
Shh. Even the neighbors
will hear you, Kaori.
If Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun throw a tantrum about wanting to go again, it'll stink.
I'll be on my way!
Come on, it was right there!
And don't worry about Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun catching a cold.
I'm off!
Grandma!
I'm feeling better already.
I'm better too!
Let's see...
No, not yet.
See? That's what I mean.
Ah, Yasu-kun, your nose is running.
Here, blow!
I'll go to get the medicine for you.
Try to get some sleep in the meantime, okay?
Yes...
Hey, let's go.
To the sports day.
How are our patients?
Look, the flower came to check on you.
It's the one I promised to gift to you once.
That flower has finally bloomed.
So, isn't it pretty?
Yes, very!
Thank you, Mister.
Get better soon.
Okay!
There! Now's our time!
All right, I'm done.
Huh? What are you two doing naked?
The neighbor brought us a flower!
Hey, isn't it pretty, Mama?
Oh, it's you!
How are Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun?
They're at home.
I didn't want to put an extra strain on them.
Here for examination?
Yes.
Good.
What's the expected date?
The 5th of next month.
Oh, I'm sure you'll have a safe delivery.
And then the Big Bad Wolf
went first and ate Grandma.
Hey, Mama, do you think
Kaori's begun competing already?
You've been asking that all morning.
Hey, Mama!
I wonder if she'll be okay
if we don't come to root for her.
Well then, why don't we
root for her from here?
How?
Yeah, how?
Go, go, Kaori-chan!
Great! Mama, you're so good at it!
Before you were born, Mama and Papa
worked in the same company.
Papa was a player on the company baseball team, and I often went to cheer him on.
Did Papa win when you went
to cheer him on?
He did win, time after time.
Let's do it! Let's cheer, Mama!
Ready?
3-3-7 claps for Kaori-chan!
Mayday! Mayday!
The engine is on fire! We are going down!
Mama!
An American jet crashed on the hilltop!
Hang on!
Hey, are you okay?
That was one hella crash!
My sons...
Please... My sons...
Kaori!
Kuro!
Where's mom?
Come on, where's mom?
Mom!
No, not so fast!
My mom...
She's from that burning house!
Nobody can come through!
Mom!
Yasu-kun! Yuu-kun!
What's there?
Hey, stay strong!
It's the JSDF rescue helicopter!
Help has come!
Don't die, pipsqueaks!
Hey!
Where are you going?!
Yes, thank you.
B-Bastards...
Cowards!
This way! Hurry!
Mom...
Mom!
Kaori,
you don't need to worry, I'm fine.
How are Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun?
It hurts!
It burns!
Yuu-kun! Bear with it, Yuu-kun!
I'm burning!
Give me water!
Give me juice!
We can't do that now.
Drinking water will only
make it even more painful...
Yuu-kun?
Papa...
Papa, Mama, bye-bye...
Yuu-kun... Yuu-kun!
He just said, "Papa..."
Yuu-kun...
Yuu-kun!
Please come right away!
It's about Yasu-kun.
Yasu-kun!
Yasu-kun! What is it? Papa is here!
Yasu-kun! Do you recognize me?
What's wrong?
Cheer up!
Our Lord in heaven...
What? What are you saying, Yasu-kun?
Coo, coo, coo,
pigeon coo, coo.
If you like beans...
It's "pigeon coo, coo!"
Coo, coo, coo, pigeon coo, coo.
If you like beans, come down.
Let’s all eat together...
Coo, coo...
Yasu?
Yasu-kun!
Ya...
Y-Yasu-kun!
Yuu-kun, Yasu-kun...
Mama...
Mama!
Hey, Mama, stay strong!
How are Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun?
They're both okay.
Thank god...
Are you... Are you hurt, Papa?
Yes. But don't worry, it's nothing serious.
Bring the children.
I want to be with them...
Sure...
Papa, I want to be with them...
Yes, I'll ask what the doctors
can do about it.
Right, Ms. Nurse?
Yes...
I want to be with them right now...
Yes, I understand. I'll ask if that's possible.
But you must stay strong.
They wanted to stay alive...
And now... it's just Mama...
Papa, Mama, bye-bye!
Maybe he went out looking for pigeons,
maybe to chase and lock them away.
While everyone was asleep,
while everyone was dreaming,
he slipped through the gaps
between dreams and said,
Papa, Mama, bye-bye!
Perhaps he turned into a dove
from the treetops in the park,
and flapped its tiny, first-ever wings
in the wind, flying away.
O dove, with your little feet,
your palms, your chest,
your life, spread your wings
and let your white bandages
that flutter in the wind
turn into pure white wings.
Papa, Mama, bye-bye!
As if engraving all the words you know,
and all the letters still unfamiliar,
into the morning wind,
you said your goodbyes as a good boy should
and flew off, heading towards the sky
in the morning wind that will soon be upon us.
Papa, Mama, bye-bye!
My mother, who had suffered severe burns,
was eventually discharged from the hospital.
However, Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun's Mama
underwent over 60 long and painful surgeries
to replace all the skin on her body.
Even though Papa and everyone else had wished so hard for her to come back, she never did.
She believed that Yuu-kun and Yasu-kun
were alive until the day she died.
The wreckage of the jet that took the lives of three people was cleared away quietly.
The two pilots who parachuted out
returned home with no consequences.
Shinpachi-kun!
Is it you, Shinpachi-kun?
Why do such cruel things
just have to happen out of nowhere?
Why?
Why's that?!
Why's that?
We won't forget you,
Yuu-kun, Yasu-kun.
The End
Encoding
Translation
Quality check
UCCUSS
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer