You punks!
If you slack off just because you're first-years,
you're gonna pay for it later.
Summer supplementary classes
are mandatory for everyone.
Sir, aren't the supplementary classes
supposed to be voluntary?
You idiot!
You think a brat like you can survive
in a free-market world?
Look at Watanabe.
Be like Watanabe.
He doesn't waste even a second
of the homeroom time,
mechanical pencil in his right hand,
study guide in his left,
English tapes in his ears, sweat of studying on his forehead—what a beautiful sight.
As expected from top-rank freshman
Watanabe Kenichi.
That's the kind of student I love.
Yo! If you're heading home,
I'll give you a ride.
Maybe next time.
Cold as ice, huh.
Hey, get back here, Kenichi!
You're in the track and field club
starting today, no excuses.
Cut it out, I've got cram school now!
We've been classmates since middle school,
do me this one favor!
We desperately need new members.
We just need to show our seniors
how fast you run, so let's go.
Hey, Sakura!
Oh, Shigeru?
Forget that gloomy nerd.
For you, Emiko, I'd show up
for the track and field club anytime.
You know how I feel, right?
Zip it, dropout.
I prefer productive people.
Right, Watanabe-kun?
Tagawa-kun, did you just get dumped?
This unrequited love torments me.
Oh, look at that "cool" guy!
If only he'd drop the sleazy attitude.
Joining some biker gang... I'm embarrassed to admit
I went to the same middle school as him.
H-Hey! Watanabe-kun!
Last year, while cramming for high school exams,
I kept thinking about it—when did I turn into this?
That goody-two-shoes face... sickening!
Elementary school, middle school, high school—I kept living up to what my parents and teachers wanted.
If I keep this up, I won't have a life of my own—
just one spent playing the dutiful kid.
So I devised myself a plan—
a second, secret life.
CITY PARK
I secretly got my license, told my parents
I needed cram-school money,
CITY PARK
and finally bought this bad boy!
Good boy, you waited for me.
Club "Cockroach"
Pelican Road
Heading for the sunlit circuit,
I gun the machine till it snakes and howls.
Even that lonely, beaten-down season,
I'll shake it off at the hairpin turn.
Baby, have you ever
seen the colors of the wind?
Baby, let your dreams blend into a clear and bright rainbow.
Runnin' through, wandering,
Runnin' through, in my heart,
If freedom hits me now, oh...
Runnin' through, a brand-new
Runnin' through melody—
I'll find you, eight-beat teenager.
Runnin' through, a brand-new
Runnin' through melody—
I'll find you, eight-beat teenager.
Runnin' through, wandering,
Runnin' through, in my heart,
If freedom hits me now, oh...
Runnin' through, a brand-new
Runnin' through melody—
I'll find you, eight-beat teenager.
Look at this 50cc punk,
thinking he’s hot stuff!
Come on, let’s see you ride that thing, huh?
Faster, faster, come on, floor it!
Hey, your banking is shit!
Try not to piss yourself!
Come on, knock it off already!
Why won't you just leave me alone?
Hey! Let's use that.
All right!
Sniff you later!
I'm such an idiot!
Should've just stuck to studying...
Hey boy, keep the throttle steady.
It's straight for a while,
so you'll be fine. Follow me.
That bright-red BMW... who's that?
I'll be breaking through, then! Ready?
One, two... here we go!
I'm saved!
Those brats... They leave me no choice.
Back up a bit.
Wh-What the hell?!
Ya wanna do it, huh?!
Taking a hairpin at this speed?!
No way, I can't keep up!
What's wrong?
Go ahead and laugh. I was staring at you
and jumped the curb.
I won't laugh.
Everyone's a beginner at first.
Don't worry about it.
Well, then, those punks probably learned something from cracking a bone or two.
See ya.
U-Um... Your name?
Pelican Express.
Just a low-tier press rider.
If you keep riding, we'll meet again.
Bye-bee.
A press rider?
Special couriers who haul articles reporters write
straight to the newsrooms?
Speed's everything to them.
No wonder she's good.
And then that bright-red BMW
came flying out of nowhere.
It was an old R90S model, and it knocked all our senpai off their bikes.
Even the 50cc punk who picked the fight got wiped. Total disaster.
Watanabe!
You even know what a BMW is?
Probably not, little book-worm.
Crap! Those guys from last night
were our students.
Come back soon!
Oh, Kenichi?
Dad, going to work now?
News don't wait for day or night.
What about your cram school?
I'm kinda tired today.
Oh yeah, about the boarder we were looking for. We're taking in a young rider.
They're here, go say hi!
A boarder?
Hey, Mom!
Where's the guy who's boarding with us?
What a rude thing to say!
She's a young lady.
Hi!
Her name is Okazaki Kanako.
Okazaki Kanako?
Wait, that rider was a woman?
Didn't expect to meet again this soon.
C-Crap!
Come here for a sec!
Kenichi, what are you doing?
Keep your biking a secret?
If my parents find out, I'm dead.
I'm begging you.
Oh? So that's your weakness?
Well well, good to know.
Hmm, interesting. I see.
Watanabe!
Answer the roll call for me
in gym class today, won't you?
I gotta meet our senpai from the hospital.
You mean the one
who got wiped out by that BMW?
Yep. He got off with just
a dislocation and a sprain.
Thank god! Glad it wasn't worse.
Thanks!
But why are you so happy about it?
First-years, class one, line up!
Ah, the slave driver is here.
See ya. It's the ward hospital.
I gotta hurry.
What? The ward hospital?
WARD HOSPITAL
CITY PARK
Watanabe!
Found that 50cc from the other day!
The battery was dead,
so it's a free-for-all!
Hey! What are you doing, skipping the class?!
Stop!
What now, Watanabe? Trying to score points again? You're such a suck-up!
N-No! It's not like that, I swear! Dammit!
Hey! Try and catch me, you bookworm!
Isn't that Watanabe-kun?
Huh?
Ah, Captain! That's Watanabe-kun,
the kid whose running I wanted you to see!
Hey! Time him, somebody!
Shigeru, stop it! Watanabe-kun's been running nonstop for over an hour!
Watanabe!
Watanabe-kun!
Stretcher! Somebody get a stretcher!
Watanabe... don't tell me this bike...
That was amazing, Watanabe.
You did a total of ten kilometers at least!
And you went all-out in the second half, too!
Interschool-level at least!
Heya! Move aside.
Track and field club coming through.
Watanabe, I'll guarantee you a spot on the team.
You're welcome anytime.
Captain, now's really not the time for that!
I really screwed up.
I'm home!
Oh, welcome back.
Have you eaten?
Yeah, I already did.
Sorry about earlier.
Never imagined that bike could be yours.
Here, this one's on me.
Forgive me, okay?
Shigeru, you work here?
Yeah. I'm saving up for a Kawasaki 400GP next.
Gotta at least get the down payment saved.
Shigeru, and Kanako-san too,
everyone's got their goals lined up.
I'm the only one wandering around
aimlessly, clutching to a bike.
Damn it...
Yes!
Eat that!
Damn it! No way I'm losing!
I—I won't lose!
Hey, boy! Got guts, don't ya?
Shut up, you old wave!
Watch it! An obstacle dead ahead!
I'm home.
Nobody's here.
All that worrying for nothing.
Ow... Ugh, that stings...
Ken-Chan, can I use the bath now?
Uh? Kanako-san!
It was crazy hot today too.
Hot!
Right? Hard to believe it was
rainy season just a while ago.
What're you embarrassed about?
I grew up in a family with all brothers.
Doesn't bother me one bit.
Oh? Ken-Chan, you scraped yourself, didn't you?
No use hiding it.
Big sis sees right through you.
I'm a pro, you know.
Go ahead—speak up now.
I raced an AR50 in a signal-start race,
and then I slid right under a truck that was turning.
Wow, that's some good experience.
How is that good?
They say mistakes are the best teachers.
Look at me—I'm covered in scars head to toe!
Here, look, look.
Oh, welcome back!
Sorry I'm late.
Where's Kenichi?
He was tired from cram school,
so he went to sleep.
Thanks!
Oh no, it's Mom!
Ken-Chan,
are you asleep?
By your smiling side,
I take in your burning feelings.
From a little distance away,
I'm the one who tries to solve love's mystery.
If your whisper brushes my lips,
It'll only end up hurting you.
Oh no... Oh no... Wooh.
Endless my love.
Hello, happiness!
Sharing our tears.
Endless my love.
Good-bye loneliness.
Filled with passion!
Lady... Lady... Wooh...
Kanako-san... I love you.
Watanabe. Watanabe!
Huh?
First time on the night shift, huh?
This place turns into a mini-disco in the evenings.
We remodeled it with a ton of money, right, Master?
Yeeeah!
Such loud places are just not for me!
It's fine, just relax!
Sakura!
Eek! Why... Why is Watanabe-kun here?!
Watanabe, it's getting crowded, so...
Emiko!
If someone finds us here,
we'll get grounded!
Oh, come on, it's summer vacation.
Hey, how is your boyfriend Watanabe-kun doing?
I'm Takagaki Yuniko,
Emiko's cousin. Nice to meet you.
Hey, Shigeru, is it okay
for employees to be goofing off?
Cute! Yuniko now wants a boyfriend like that too.
If you want to work, go ahead.
I won't stop you.
Jeez, every one of them is wearing
such bright, happy faces.
Do none of them have problems?
Sorry.
What?
I—I said sorry!
Ugh... That guy's out for the count,
but I'm not done here yet.
Well, guess I'll settle for this.
Good work, kid.
What the hell're you doing, brat?
You little...
I'll kill you!
Hey, taxi!
This old man's had too much. His place is in Narita.
Wake him when you hit the airport.
Go to America or wherever, you pig!
Fighting doesn't suit you at all.
When you've cooled off, come back.
I'll cover both our shifts.
What was that for?!
Thank God you're alive!
Watanabe-kun, enough already!
Oh, let him be.
Anyone should be allowed to drink now and then.
Watanabe-kun, Watanabe-kun,
won't you walk me home?
Yuniko is scared to go alone!
Right, Tagawa-san? Can he?
Huh? Oh... sure.
I'm going home.
Emiko, I'll be done here in like 30 minutes!
Let me walk you home, won't you?
Come on, Watanabe-kun...
All right!
I-I'll drive you home on my bike!
Whoa! Hooray!
Damn it!
Come out, you damn cops!
D-Dead drunk tandem riding here!
Got a problem with that?
Watanabe-kun, why'd you suddenly stop?
I—I feel sick...
What?!
K-Kanako-san...
Riding tandem while drunk?
Yes.
Watanabe Kenichi-kun, give me the keys.
You don't deserve to call yourself a rider.
With my key taken away,
second semester began.
Watanabe. After the opening ceremony, I'm going for a drive with the first-years. You wanna come?
Shut up!
Don't you dare talk about bikes to me again!
Huh?
Emiko, why's he so down?
How would I know?!
Hey, gloomy boy!
Huh?
I borrowed this Katana from a senpai for you.
Borrowed?
Whatever happened to your 50cc from the park? D'you wreck it?
Well, not that I care about the reason anyway.
You need to ride this bad boy once to feel better.
Whoa... Power's on a whole other level from a 50cc!
It's totally different!
The whole world feels different!
Damn! What a rush!
Shigeru?
Welcome back.
What happened?
Total disaster. The seniors worked me over,
and threw me out of the gang.
Crap... Can't get up yet.
Why'd they do that to you?
Forget it.
I'm such an idiot.
I borrowed that bike without telling 'em.
Getting punched for it was fair.
You did all that...
for me?
Hey, Shigeru.
Wanna ride together from here on out?
Sounds good.
Ugh! It's terrible!
Heard you quit the gang, Shigeru.
Maybe you squared things with the seniors,
but ditching us first-year buddies
with no goodbye is just bitchy.
Come, we'll give you a proper send-off.
Hey, Kenichi!
Eh?
Wh-What?
I heard it all from Yuniko.
Everything.
Oh, right! Shigeru knocked down
a couple of his senior gang members.
Now the first-years in the gang are hunting him.
Come to think of it, Shigeru
and some guys stepped out just now...
What the hell!
Where are you going?
Sixth period's about to start!
Attendance number twenty-five,
leaving early for personal reasons!
You're the last guy I wanted to fight, Shimizu.
With that difference in strength,
I stand no chance.
We were hoping you'd take over
as our next leader.
I actually liked you, man.
Thanks.
Which is exactly why...
I can't forgive you.
Stop it!
This is the price of your betrayal.
Damn it!
Asshole...
Time to say goodbye.
Sh-Shigeru's bike!
Watanabe!
Idiot! If you rev it any further...
You alive?!
Shigeru... I'm sorry... y-your bike...
Don't cry, you dope!
Look at this guy—
he can't fight, he's dumb,
he's got no skills, and every time he gets on a bike, he does something reckless.
But nobody's got more spirit.
Yeah. I think so too.
This happened because of your sloppiness.
Yeah! Not only did we lose Shigeru,
now even Shimizu's hanging with those guys!
Can't even put a scare into deserters anymore!
Some “East High biker gang,” what a joke.
Gimme a break!
B-But the third-years
don't come around anymore,
and with Shigeru and Shimizu
gone as first-year leaders...
Yeah... Honestly, our crew's
gonna break up next year.
Are you kidding me?!
Let's go, girls.
Cops've been cracking down hard lately.
Don't make things too flashy.
If the gang leaders want to do things that way, fine, let them.
We'll be the ones to settle things properly.
Don't give up!
Watanabe-kun!
Hi!
She sure is cheerful.
Huh?
It's Emiko. She's been really upbeat lately,
almost like she's forcing it.
Forcing it?
Check this out—brand-new and still shiny!
You bought it?
Yay! I'm sooo happy!
Officially a mid-class rider!
Kanako-san.
Four, three, two, one, one, two!
Ken-Chan, you haven't eaten yet, right?
Do aerobics with me.
E-Excuse me.
Didn't you come here for something?
No, I can come later.
Just wait, I'll be done in a sec.
Four, three, two, one!
Oh? A girl in your class
forces herself to be all cheerful?
Why would she force a smile so hard
soon as I started dating another girl?
You're cold.
Cold?
Yeah.
She likes you—that's as clear as a day!
Of course she's shocked to see you dating someone else, how could she just accept that?
Even I—if I saw my man with another girl...
Huh?
If I saw my man with another girl...
I'd probably force myself to be cheerful too.
So Kanako-san has...
her man...
Kanako-san already has...
a man she loves.
Kanako-san...
What's this?
M-My bike key?
I'm giving it back.
But why now?
You made me remember
my own high school days.
At first, any bike was fine for me.
Just riding like the wind made me happy,
with the throttle wide open.
But that's not all there is to it.
A bike's more than that.
Ken-Chan, you know “Red Dragonfly”?
The ones flying in autumn?
No.
During the Pacific War, they used
that trainer plane to train Zero fighter pilots.
Every famous ace pilot started on that,
before they could fly a real combat plane.
You need to treat your 50cc
like your own Red Dragonfly,
if you want to become a real rider.
Kanako-san...
Go on, take it.
I left it at a friend's garage
so they fixed it to mind condition.
Ride it till you're satisfied, then say goodbye
and move on to your next bike.
Speeding down the dawn highway—hell yeah!
Hey!
Here he comes.
Not there.
Watanabe-kun, where the hell
are you wandering at a time like this?
Yuniko...
So pretty...
I rode all night. Got it out of my system.
Now I can let it go anytime.
Next time we meet,
I'll be a little better than before. Promise.
He didn't come home?
No... when I came...
His parents were out,
and Kanako-san, the boarder, left for work.
Nobody seems to know much.
How's Shigeru?
They just took him into the ICU,
or whatever it's called.
Emiko! ICU is for people
who are at the brink of death, right?
What do we do?
Shigeru's gonna die!
Yuniko, get a grip!
There's no way he's dying!
That idiot...
What happened?
Bike accident. Someone scattered steel balls at the S-curve exit.
Looks like some biker gang ambush.
You got any idea who'd do that?
No...
It's Shigeru's!
Excuse me... Is the injured guy
going to be okay?
I wouldn't know.
They took him to the university hospital.
Watanabe-kun!
How's Shigeru?
They say it's bad.
He's been in ICU since the evening.
You should prepare yourself for the worst.
Shigeru...
Shigeru!
Doctor, is he going to make it?
It's extremely serious.
At his age, complications
can happen any moment.
Don't die!
Now, you kids need to quiet down!
Hang in there!
Old man, hey...
Huh?
He fell down the stairs apparently.
Didn't know he knew all of you.
Shigeru! Where've you been till now?
Oh, zonked out in the surgical department.
Why?
Y-You...!
CULTURAL FESTIVAL
Yes, come all, the famous cockroach race
is here, in first year, class one!
Teachers you like, teachers you hate—
we've got 'em all!
Tanaka-sensei (Science)
Kajikawa-sensei (Music)
Cheer 'em, boo 'em—whatever!
Time to blow off steam!
Tanaka-sensei (Science)
Kajikawa-sensei (Music)
And the race begins!
Hey! Math teacher Tanaka, eyes front!
Go, principal, go!
Matsuda-sensei, you can do it!
I never thought it'd be this popular.
Naming it after the teachers
was a stroke of genius.
Feels good being the one who came up with it.
Hey, producer!
The P.E. teacher Suzuki just wiped out.
He'll run if you slap him.
He's just lazy, that's all.
That's weirdly realistic.
I'll go for a stroll.
All the teachers have escaped!
H-Hey! Wait!
Stop!
Yuniko?
I skipped school to hang out with you.
Where's Watanabe-kun?
I don't know, and I don't have time for that.
Shigeru! You here?!
Where have you been, Shimizu?
Come on, help out!
Idiot!
Watanabe?
Come on, fight back a little, will you?
That goody-two-shoes act pisses me off!
You do the same crap as the other biker gangs,
so what makes you think you're different?
We're not the same.
Take that back.
Take it back!
We're not like them.
How are you any different?!
We just are!
We are!
Damn it...
You bastards!
Knew you'd show.
Let's send you all straight to hell.
I don't think you will.
Razor Yuniko, the top sukeban
of Toyo High is coming to the rescue!
Huh?
You fucking meddlers...
Kill her!
Shimizu!
Yeah!
No! Where are you grabbing, you idiot!
Get this!
Hard to fight with girls seriously, huh Shigeru?
Grab her!
Come on, come on!
What happened to all that bravado!? Pathetic!
Senpai, with flowers today?
Drop dead!
All right, we'll start with your face!
Dammit, where'd everybody go?
They were all “Watanabe, Watanabe”...
Eek! Cockroaches!
It's so funny my stomach hurts!
So, have the biker girls
backed off since then?
Yeah. They were not prepared
for the cockroach attack.
All right, let's gun it on the way home.
Long time no see! Can't believe
you're still riding that junker I patched up.
Tatsuya...
So you're back?
That's so unfriendly of you.
You moved and didn't even tell me.
Tatsuya, your lap girl's sulking.
She's just a decoration for the passenger seat.
Or what, Kanako, you jealous?
You know what, Tatsuya,
I can't stand that attitude of yours.
Let's go, Ken-Chan.
Who was that guy?
A senior from my college club.
Huh? But that means...
Quiet a second.
Kanako-san...
Don't tell me that guy...
Come on, don't tell me he's your...
What do you want?
Hey, is Kanako's place around here?
Heard she lived nearby.
You know it?
Who's Kanako?
Hang on, I'll “take care” of you later.
What business do you have with her?
An old lover came calling.
Lover?! I'm going home!
Hey, hold up!
C'mon, no idea why you're sulking,
but you could at least tell me.
Or are you Kanako's boy toy?
Someone like you...
Someone like you
would never know
how Kanako-san feels!
Too bad. A pro rider can't afford to get hurt.
A pro...
A pro rider...?
He came, didn't he?
He was the one who taught me
to ride a bike, in high school.
My brother's friend,
he made it as a pro rider,
but he remained a hopeless playboy.
Even when overseas for races,
he only chased girls.
Why'd you ever fall for him?
Who knows.
Ah, here, your umbrella.
You'll catch a cold.
Let's go home.
Ken-Chan!
The swaying highway where my feelings will never reach you.
The two shadows
that never even look at each other,
are drifting apart.
Like unraveling a tangled thread,
I entrust my heart to the wind.
It's flying across the distant sea, the fleeting clouds,
the shadows of the disappearing stars,
lonely rider, racing without looking back, falling apart.
I'm just a kid. Not even grown yet.
Makes perfect sense.
Really? That unyielding attitude you showed the other day—you've got potential.
You're no simple kid.
You don't have to cheer me up
out of pity, senpai.
No, it's true.
You're just a little... underdeveloped.
So?
Want me to “develop” you?
Seriously? Right when things were getting good...
Well, maybe it's better for you that way.
Sorry, Nishi-senpai.
Watanabe! That's one hella riding.
You're like a new man!
Hard to believe this is your first time on a 400.
Even the cops wouldn't buy that.
That's right, Shigeru.
Starting today, I'm changing.
Kanako's got her own life,
so I'll find my own path too.
That beat-to-hell Harley
is catching up to us!
Shigeru, sorry, but I need to settle this
with him personally.
So hey, Harleys are like 80 cubic inches,
so 1300cc, right?
Not something you can beat.
Shigeru!
Win this, Watanabe!
Well... Not like you'd be able to.
All right... Let's go!
Don't be in a hurry to throw your life away, kid!
Damn it...
Damn, this sucks...
K-Kanako!
I dodged the baby.
Can I get an A+?
Tatsuya, you idiot!
What's the big idea,
racing a high school kid?
What would've happened
if I didn't go out to look for Ken-Chan?!
Yeah, sorry.
Isn't that just awful?
Ignoring someone for a whole year,
and then you finally show up
with a girl in tow to visit me?
Told you—she was just a decoration for the...
Shut up!
What are you doing? Let go!
I was wrong, I'm sorry.
But Kanako, you won't ride
the pillion seat with me, will you?
The one I want on it is you.
Only you.
I'm tired of riding alone.
I get enough of that while racing.
Please, just understand.
This is how I feel.
Huh? So Watanabe,
you beat the Harley, huh?
It was beaten,
but not with my power.
It's fine, practically the same.
Why don't we start a club of our own?
With Watanabe as the head.
Totally agree!
Then in spring we can go on a group tour.
Wait, me, head?
I'm weak in fights.
Being head isn't about fighting—it's about hitting it off with guys and girls alike.
We'll need a good club name too.
How about "Club Caroucha?"
It means “cockroach” in Portuguese.
And that's how Club Caroucha started.
We worked our part-time jobs hard and got
to get our mid-sized licenses and bikes by spring.
Ken-Chan.
I'm sorry.
I really appreciated your feelings.
I just wish you were the person
I'd fallen for first.
Kanako-san, I can say it now.
Thank you.
As if to shake off the meter of sadness, I speed on, spring on the run.
With each turn of the wheel, memories drift away.
Rock'n roll dreaming,
and I chase after it.
Grabbing at something new, something to hold, okay,
the signal points to tomorrow.
Good luck!
Golden Faraway,
with wings that make your heart shine!
beyond the wind!
RAW
Translation & TS
Ukyuu
Perevodildo