Hey bro...
Calm down, won't you?
Three more minutes!
They'll be there in three minutes!
We're in Ueno, sir.
Floor it!
Please die for real this time!
The Quiet Don
I am Akino, the designer in charge.
First of all, the cups of this bra are made entirely of tulle lace, providing a flexible and fast fit.
The main selling point
is this boldly-placed zipper.
All right, Akino-kun, we find that idea interesting, but doesn't it hurt?
Excuse me? Hurt... how?
No, I mean...
When you close it, does anything ever get caught in the zipper?
No, I wore it all day myself,
and that didn’t happen even once.
Oh, I see! You wear it too?
All right. We approve it as Pretty's
new product line.
Thank you.
That was very impressive.
Next is Kondo-kun.
Yessir!
If you would look at these shorts I designed...
Huh?
Hey, it's my turn to present.
What's the matter?
Move it, come on!
What are you doing?
All right, thank you for waiting.
What?!
These are the diaper shorts I designed.
Practical shorts with excellent liquid absorption...
What is this?
Even if your underwear gets soiled by discharge,
which is common among women,
you won’t have to worry with this.
Yes, Kondo-kun, I think we've heard enough.
Planning and Design Bureau
What were you thinking with that diaper?!
Our company makes women's underwear,
not baby products!
Is that really the design for the once-a-month prototype presentation
everyone worked on for two days straight without going home?
Because...!
The result was the same as if you hadn't come to work for two days straight!
Thank you ever so much for embarrassing me today!
Yes, Pretty Design Bureau.
Yes. Kondo? Who's asking?
No, Kondo is away right now.
Yes, he's been absent since yesterday.
Dammit!
Personal calls on the company phone are not allowed, you know!
Return to your desk and do something good!
That was a little unfortunate.
Akino-san...
Focusing on diaper shorts for women is an interesting perspective,
but they can’t be worn under tight skirts.
Yes, I suppose...
Director, it's almost time for our commercial to start.
Oh, you are right.
Regarding last night’s attack on the leader of the Shinsen Family, the police
have announced that they will work with with the Osakan and Metropolitan Police Departments,
since the evidence suggests that the perpetrators belong
to the Kansai-based Choshu Group,
who may be part of a larger conspiracy.
Shinsen Family President Kondo Isamiashi is currently
in the police hospital under intensive care.
In other news...
Metropolitan Police Hospital
Get out of our way, you idiots!
Let us in, goddammit!
Boss!
Pops...!
Y-Young boss!
We're sorry! We're sorry...
I was by his side all the time, and yet...
So my father is dead?
Aye...
Father...
Dear, Shizuya came to check on you.
He died mere moments ago...
I called...
I called you time and time again...
Yes.
Funeral Ceremony
Namakura, what's the meaning of this?!
Boss Hijikata, counting on ya to cover my back!
Are you stupid? You're at a funeral!
Tsk. They're already fighting
for the front row seat.
These two underbosses are the most powerful figures in the family,
now vying for the position of successor.
Successor? I thought Shizuya-san was the heir apparent.
The young boss is not cut out to be yakuza.
Even if the madam is still trying to convince him.
So quiet...
Yes.
You can't even hear the sutras here.
That's not what I meant.
I'm saying that you are being very quiet.
Huh?
Your father was murdered,
yet you are unfazed.
Before, all the hotheads of the family could only imagine Kingoro Choshu in that coffin.
You're not a mere bystander, you know.
Yes, but being in the underworld...
It's like you're stuck in a perpetual car crash.
Shizuya, from today onwards,
you are the third president of the Shinsen Family.
Hijikata and Namakura are about to clash fiercely for the right to succeed our father.
But if you do it instead,
there won't be bloodshed.
B-But mom, I already have a proper job...
Do you think this is a job worthy of a man?
M-My prototype...
The rejected breastfeeding bra!
Don't ridicule me like that...
You’ll lead a double life as both an office worker and the president of the Shinsen Family.
You'll become the Quiet Don.
Investigators on high alert—unrest within the group?
A war with Choshu is coming?
The third president takes over the Shinsen Family,
the largest in the Kanto region
Hey, Kondo, is that you?
Walking here all alone.
Huh? Yes... I felt that I would endanger others by walking with them.
What's dangerous 'bout that, huh?
Afraid they might trip over you?
Mister, mister! We are offering a special service to commemorate our opening!
All-you-can-drink for just 1,000 yen and an extra bottle to take home!
And right now all our girls happen to be free!
You're not messing with me, are you?
Only 1,000 yen?
Hey, let's carry on here!
I'm sorry, Chief, but I'm abstaining, so you'll have to go without me.
What was that?
We just met and you wanna leave us already?
Whatever, come on in, Chief.
You can still tag along, Kondo-kun.
We'll order some oolong tea for you, okay?
Yes...
Four customers—go welcome them!
Boop! Oops, I did it again!
You need to stop!
We're not that kind of establishment!
Then you ought to start doing that starting tonight!
At least once its dark, come on, babe!
Oh no!
What's with you, Kondo?
Drinking nothing but oolong tea tonight?
Are you making fun of our company,
which sells women's panties and bras, huh?
N-Not in my life, sir!
What'd you take that last week off for, then?
It was for business...
Now, Chief, how Kondo chooses to use his paid leave is none of your business, is it?
Akino-chan, there's no need to get so defensive, you know!
Unless you're secretly into Kondo?
"Ah, I'm such a lonely woman...
Comfort me already!"
Nakaoka, we need another
round of refreshments!
Yessir!
Chief, please stop here.
Drink!
Giving him straight whiskey when he's abstaining is reckless!
What harm will a single cup do?
Kondo-kun, you don't need to push yourself.
It's fine, I'll drink it.
Kondo-kun!
Yep, that's better!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
Bottoms up! Bottoms up! Bottoms up!
We hereby recognize Kondo Shizuya
as the third president of the Shinsen Family, the legal heir of the previous president.
Please drink it when your mind is made up.
Let the ceremonial sake permeate through your soul.
Right, congratulations are in order!
This marks the official birth
of our third president!
Hold it together, Namakura!
At least during a solemn ceremony!
Why's that?
Shouldn't we be celebrating the birth
of the third president?
Unless you're dissatisfied with this choice of successor, huh, Hijikata? My, oh my...
It seems you're unhappy that Shizuya-san, the son of our beloved second president, took over?
You've got some nerve to say that in front of the many bosses who came from all over the country!
When did I ever say such nonsense?
Wow, what a wonderful third president we got!
With him, the future of the Shinsen Family is secured!
Did you see those two, Shizuya?
Both Hijikata and Namakura were after the president's seat themselves.
They lost sleep over it.
Mom.
I hope they keep their word.
I quite enjoy my current "honest" life.
It's only to prevent those two from escalating it into an open conflict
that I've become the third president.
You should do as you like.
A position of power
or a cheap office worker's position—
you'll quickly find out
which one is more comfortable for you.
Well now, it turns out you know how to drink, don't you?
All right, let's keep it up!
Really, that's going too far!
You should stop, Kondo-kun.
Oh! That's good! Don't stop!
He finished the bottle in no time.
He doesn’t look the slightest bit tipsy!
Could he secretly be the biggest drinker known to man?
Tsk. You're no fun. I'm going home!
Thank you so much for the visit!
Yeah, sure thing! I'll come again!
Your bill.
Right...
Two... 279,000 yen?!
Are you kidding me?! Why does it cost so much for one bottle and some snacks, huh?
Ni-Nigeno-san!
Hey, mister.
In these parts, it is customary to pay the bill for what you’ve eaten and drunk.
Let me go, you twerp!
Pay up, wontcha?
Yeah, sure... But you see, that price is a bit steep for me right now...
Chief, please leave.
Let me deal with this.
After all, I ended up
drinking most of it myself.
O-Oh, really? W-Well, if you say so.
We'll leave you to it, then! Let's go now, okay?
Wait! Can Kondo-kun really pay for it?
Let's go already! Hurry up!
Oh? So you’re the walking treasury
for those dolts?
Yes, but you see...
I only have a couple of 100 yen coins on me.
Ya lookin' down on us?
Lookin' down, aintcha?
Therefore, I intend to pay you with labor.
What?
Allow me to help you with this scam.
Hey, show this twit our menu.
Aye.
A: You gang up on me and beat me up!
B: You take one of my fingers as payment!
C: You stick chopsticks all the way up my nostrils!
Which one'll it be?
They all look painful.
Then we'll call your home!
We'll have your family bring the money!
You phone number—say it!
Hello, is this the Kondo family house?
We have your son here, you see.
He thought it was a good idea to pig out at our restaurant without having any money on him.
Got it.
Yes, I'll be there in a moment.
They're coming already.
Until then, you stay here and behave.
Maybe we shouldn't have called them...
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Know your fucking place!
Shut up!
You'll never catch up with me!
Devotion
Hurry up damn it!
Oh, here they are.
Shinsen Family assault force leader Inokubi Koshiro is here!
Hey, everyone. I'd like you all to help this place with their scam.
Aye! Roger that, President.
President, why did you allow that scum
to treat you like trash?
They'd never lay a finger on you if you told them you were our President.
That's just not my preferred way to do things.
Even if they're just some scam artists?
Still, we should've at least compensated them for that bottle I drank...
Yes, what is it?
Yes, he's with me.
Got it.
President, Boss Hijikata is waiting for you.
Hijikata?
Why does it have to be
this late at night, Hijikata?
Because it's the only time
when you're available, President.
I see. That makes sense.
President.
We held a conference with the other underbosses today, and there's something we need to ask.
When are you going to exact revenge for your late father?
Those Choshu bastards are mocking our group in broad daylight at every occasion!
This is outrageous! We're being made into a laughing stock for all the other organizations!
If they want to laugh, then let them.
President...
In the underworld, we can't just brush it off like that!
The Shinsen Family is in crisis!
Hijikata, are you trying to order me around?
It is no order, it's a plea, sir!
What's the matter?
You're not usually like that, Hijikata.
President...
If you have time to make women’s panties,
couldn’t you spare a bit of it
to think about this organization's future?
Oh...
Huh? So you knew?
Namakura told me today.
Even after becoming president,
you refused to quit your honest job.
How come the president of the Shinsen Family works for a panty-making company by day?
This makes me feel so miserable...
So miserable!
Sorry, but...
I won't quit.
In any organization,
the word of the higher-ups is absolute.
I won’t tolerate you lecturing me ever again.
Night is a dangerous time.
You should go home.
I don't understand!
Why are you that hellbent on keeping your honest job?!
That's because...
I'm scared.
Scared?
Of living entirely in the yakuza world.
What's the point of being so timid if you're already the president?!
I didn't mean it that way.
You must prove yourself!
If you don't demonstrate that you have what it takes to be a leader, the people won't follow you!
You can't go places in the yakuza world
with your parent's reputation alone!
Hijikata.
Madam, did you hear what just happened?
What he truly meant was that he’s afraid of himself in this world.
Afraid of himself?
Hijikata, you probably think I’m a fool for elevating Shizuya to this position just because he’s my son.
Or perhaps you think that I did it
simply to prevent a succession war between you and Namakura?
You're wrong.
Huh?
Shizuya is a yakuza by nature.
He’s afraid of awakening the blood of a ferocious yakuza that lies dormant within him.
That's why he clings onto his honest job.
His father always said that only Shizuya could succeed him as the third president.
Boss did?
He saw through Shizuya's makings of a yakuza.
You think he's a placid man, right?
That’s because you don’t know what he’s truly like when you really stir him up.
Shit for brains!
These Kishu Family assholes said they can't send reinforcements!
That's not what we've settled on!
What the fuck did we even get the Shinsen president out of the way for?!
If all-out war broke out between Kishu and Shinsen, the cops would take down both of them!
Wasn't that our plan from the get-go?!
If he meant it, then why are we the only ones risking our necks now?
They even sent their best hitman after me!
Are we to wage this war against the Shinsen Family on our own?!
You're a moron, Setsuya!
Boss, if it came to this,
we have no choice but to prepare for the worst.
I've been prepared for ages!
Look at this, I have all fronts covered!
You never know when and where the Shinsen hitman will attack!
I doubt anyone is going to make an attempt at your hindquarters.
Don't you understand?
How do you know if their hitman is not some faggot
who likes to do
his victims from behind?!
You need to calm down, Boss.
Besides, the Shinsen Family has been eerily quiet lately.
Their ranks include over 260 groups,
10,000 members total.
In turn, our group numbers less than 100 members, even if we include the small fry.
What are you trying to say?
Tell me, Tamaki!
Are you saying that the killer might come from our own men, the Kishu Family?
Promise me that you won't let him get away with it!
Fine...
Boss!
Great news, Boss!
This guy overheard at a gambling den
that the Shinsen Family’s new Prez,
someone named Shizuya, is a cretin, sir! A cretin!
A cretin?
It seems, even after getting appointed as the president, he kept his honest job.
Oh, so he ain't a yakuza?!
Yeah. Hijikata and Namakura
are also paralyzed by his inaction.
The Shinsen Family
is falling apart at the seams!
It seems we can still win this battle.
Fighting is not about numbers,
it's about courage.
It all hinges on one's leader's qualities.
If their third Prez is such a pushover,
we have this in the bag.
Well said, Tamaki!
War is not a matter of numbers only.
As long as we have a leader who's a real man,
we can do just fine without help from Kishu!
We'll haunt and terrify him, and when he's scared shitless, I'll deal the final blow myself...
That's how it'll be!
Kondo-kun, I'm sorry about yesterday.
We shouldn’t have left you all alone at a shady place like that...
Are you mad?
Oh no, why should I be mad?
Anyway, what do you think about this design? Isn't it cute?
Man, you have zero sense of style.
I-I think it's cute.
Anyway, Kondo.
What does your family do for a living
where you can afford to pay 300,000 to a sham business?
Um... Well, our income is a bit above average.
Why are you dawdling
when your boss is waiting for a light?!
I-I apologize...
Pay attention, you dimwit!
Ow...
Are you okay, Kondo-kun?
Y-Yeah...
You shouldn't mention to the Chief
that you're rich.
He’s terribly resentful of the rich.
So he's a proletarian at heart?
Shinsen Family HQ
I can't wait any longer!
I'll do it myself!
Devotion
In a week, the Choshu Group
will be wiped out!
My Namakura Group would handle it much more deftly!
After all, we're the strongest battle formation in the Shinsen Family.
Namakura, how can your merry band
be considered a battle formation?
Oh, sorry, did you mean to say "ballet formation?"
What did you say, you chrome dome?!
Chrome dome? We'll see how bald you'll be when you're my age!
Please stop this nonsense, both of you.
The president will probably tell us
to stay away from it.
Okita! Where the hell have you ever seen a yakuza who lets his parent's murderers go unpunished?!
That's right! Damn right!
I’m sure the president is acting on his own endgame plan.
The Choshu Group from Chiba
is backed by the Kishu Family from the west.
The president won't be so rash as to attack them head-on.
The president is still young.
Which means we must rally him more actively!
What's all the yelling about, Hijikata?
President...
Good morning, sir!
Please allow my group
to avenge your late father!
Haven't I told you already
that we can't do that?
You just don't know when to give up, Hijikata.
President! Do you intend to leave your parent’s murder unpunished? To let them get away with it?
Isn't it only natural for children to avenge their parents?
You all keep calling him my parent.
But for me, it was my own
father who got killed.
Please understand the feelings I'm having to suppress.
Unauthorized actions
will put everyone in a fix.
Oh, my lunch break is already over.
Let us put a full stop to it here.
Keep up the good work.
Even in times like these,
he prioritizes making panties over the family!
You should watch your mouth, Hijikata.
If it came to this, we have no choice but to ask Uncle Okubo for help.
Yes...
Hey, everyone!
Everything in order?
W-Well, if it isn't Matsudaira-sama!
So nice of you to visit...
I'm just dropping by.
Yes, sir, of course.
Get lost, kid.
O-Okay...
Working hard, Akino-chan?
Oh, I like that design!
Are you wearing
something similar yourself, huh?
Hey, how about we take a breather
and go get some coffee together?
I'm working right now.
Say, does she have any urgent work?
Not at all! Actually, Akino is supposed to be on break right now!
OK! It's settled, then.
Come on, let's go.
I-I really can't!
Of course you can.
Come on, let's go now.
Manager, where should I put this?
Asshole! You did that on purpose!
Huh?
B-By no means, Matsudaira-sama!
He doesn’t have the brains or the guts
to do that on purpose!
Why aren't you apologizing yet, Kondo?!
I'm very sorry!
Oops, it popped off.
President's Office
For god's sake,
what were you three thinking?!
President, do you really want our company to stop dealing in Pretty's products?
I do hear people saying that underwear from European brands happens to be sturdier.
Let’s not allow this incident
to leave a sour taste in our mouths.
Apologize, Kondo-kun!
I'm very sorry!
Hey, you...
Don't you see your tie is crooked?
Look!
Please stop!
Remember!
For the small fry like you, I can terminate your employment whenever I feel like it!
So, how about dinner with me tonight?
Yes, that sounds good.
Akino-kun, why don't you and the manager
entertain Matsudaira-san tonight?
Sure!
President, I don't want the baldy.
Yes, I suppose you're right.
Kido-kun, you stay!
That means Akino-chan is in danger!
What can we do?
He's the top brass.
But man, what a pity—he is the only son of Matsudaira Genta of the Toto Distribution Group.
That brat!
If the Toto Department Store weren’t our primary wholesale retailer, I’d have torn him to pieces!
Manager, you seem quite salty about being left behind.
He's a big shot, all right...
Don't restrain yourself, Akino-chan!
O-Okay...
We're happy to see you here tonight, Matsudaira-sama.
You! What the hell happened today, huh?
You know that whenever I come, #1, Teresa, through #3, Kei, should already be here!
Get them here now!
Number three, Kei, is so in love with me,
she always suddenly starts smooching me!
Um... Matsudaira-sama,
unfortunately, all three are occupied for today...
What?! Are you saying there's a customer more important than me?
Y-Yes...
Ugh! You prick!
Hey, you there!
These three women
are always reserved for me.
Sorry, but I'm taking them.
Go ahead.
What are you doing?!
I-I'm from the Toto Group, the national monopolist!
What makes you think you can butt in and demand someone for yourself, huh?
N-No!
Please wait!
That person is important to our company.
Please forgive him!
See if I give a fuck!
Inokubi.
We shouldn't refuse the honest-working lady's request. Forgive him.
All right, but still...
Well, we must've scared you.
Oh? Your tie is all crooked.
Right... Appreciate it...
I think you shouldn't push your luck
when having fun with girls.
Because I can terminate your employment
whenever I feel like it...
Along with your life.
Let's go.
Aye, Boss.
Careful!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes...
Thank you very much...
I can terminate your life whenever I feel like it...
Terminate...
Where... Where have I heard that line before?
Welcome, sir!
Uncle Okubo, we welcome you.
Namakura and Hijikata,
if the third president really is as worthless as you make him out to be,
I'll kill him!
I don't remember becoming the guardian of an idiot!
G-Gotta be careful with him...
Brother, I never thought
I'd drink with you like this again.
I might have to sever
your own son from you this time.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Oh, President?
I called for you a while ago.
With a sword cane?
Did Boss Okumo really go to meet Shizuya
with a hidden blade?
Yes. He said if he doesn't find the new president capable enough, he'll kill him.
Madam, are you sure
the third president will make it through?
Idiot!
The one I'm worried about is Boss Okubo.
No, I'll pass.
Is that so?
By the way, I’m sure you have some plans regarding the Choshu Group.
Not really. I never thought about it.
Didn't they do away with your pops?!
If you keep letting people make fun of you,
I won't be able to remain the family's guardian!
I never really asked you to be one
in the first place.
Look, you're really trying my patience here!
Before, anyone who talked to me like that
would be dead by now!
You see, I'm busy today.
Could you come another time?
Today is inventory day,
and I'm going to be late because of you.
Bastard! So you really are still working at your honest job!
Yes. It seems someone told you already?
T-Then it's true that it's for a company
making women's panties...?!
Yes. Actually, you have a daughter about my age back home, don't you?
I could give you a discount.
I'll kill you!
If he flashes his sword in front of Shizuya...
Shizuya!
You are all here?
What's the matter?
Uncle seems to have had a bit too much.
Are you okay?
Boss!
Get lost, you two.
Y-Yessir...
I fucking told you to leave!
Y-Yessir!
Tae-san, I've got quite a lot of questions for you.
If it's about Shizuya,
it might take some time.
Ah, Manager? I got the fabric.
I also secured the silk delivery.
Oh, good. Maybe you're better suited for sales than design.
You can just go home
without stopping by today.
Huh? But there's a design meeting in the afternoon...
It'll go more smoothly without you here.
Huh? Are you serious?
Bull's eye!
Right, Tamaki?
Can this guy really be their president?
You did well, Boss.
This way, we can do it
without relying on Kishu.
Boss, the Shinsen Family is here...
Imbecile! What are you waiting for?!
We'll meet them guns blazing!
But it's just one guy...
Huh?
That's him!
What? Are you sure?
Boss, it's is Shizuya.
B-Boss!
Wow, did you come here alone?
You know what kinda place this is, don't you?
Yes, of course I do.
Today, I happened to in the vicinity for work.
So I thought I might drop by.
Because there’s a favor
I’d like to ask of Choshu-san.
What?! Are you serious?
They broke off from the Kishu Family?
Yes, I'm sure it's true.
All right, here's our chance!
Gather everyone, arm yourselves!
We'll crush Choshu once and for all!
What do you think?
Could you please dissolve your organization?
You do that, and we’ll both forget the past wounds.
Are you serious?
That'd be hella apropos!
President, that's unconditional surrender.
But in our position,
we actually have some leverage.
After all, their most valuable piece has fallen straight into our hands.
You're right.
Hey you, the amateur! How can we ever accept such conditions, you cretin?
Please take this seriously. My men will grumble again if I return empty-handed.
Let’s wrap this up quickly and go home.
At this rate, I’ll be late for work tomorrow...
He's manifesting disrespect.
H-Hey, you! Want us to slaughter you here and now, like we did with your daddy?
I knew you were coming, so I was waiting fully prepared! Wanna check for yourself?
Boss, it's okay.
No need to show it.
H-Hold it there!
Please, just consider it.
Please disband.
I beg you!
S-See it, people?
The president of the Shinsen Family
kneels down before me!
Huh? How'd you like that?
Remember, people!
It'll be the Namakura Group who arrives there first and puts Hijikata to shame!
We'll be the ones who takes Choshu's head!
You got that?!
Yeah!
Hey, what's wrong?
Did you really think things will go as you want if you just kneel down?!
If you want us to disband that badly,
you'll have to crawl under my groin!
Inokubi, did you let the president know?
He never showed up in his office.
I thought it was weird.
We need to hurry!
The Namakura Group is heading there too!
They left already?
You're a fool, Okita!
Rather than waiting for the president's permission, we'll do it under Uncle Okubo's orders!
We must get there, whatever it takes!
Prepare for some action, everyone!
He really crawled through it!
Did you see that, Tamaki?
That's what power allows you to do.
You're right! Yeah.
The powerful rule the world.
Hey! If you want us to disband, you're gonna have to lick my feet!
What's wrong? If you lick them, we'll disband.
You want it or not, fucker?
For real this time?
The Shinsen Family is on the move?
Yes, we just received a call from Tokyo.
How many troops are they going to use?
How do they plan to deal with Choshu?
Find out and report back.
Yessir! Roger that!
Kishu Family
He did it!
Did you see that, you slackers?
He licked my foot!
This means you'll disband from today on, right?
Huh?
Hey, what is this dunce talking about?
Are you stupid? Who'd disband a group
over something like this?
So you lied to me?
You stupid brat!
I'll make you lick my heels next!
Bastard!
Die!
Fuck...
You're a dead man!
H-He's strong...
What's with this guy?!
I can't wait to see Namakura's frustrated face.
Why the hell are the cops after us
at a time like this?!
Fine! We'll split into two groups!
Whoever shakes them off first
gets to kill Choshu!
Ow, ouch...
Ah? Huh? What happened?
Right! The Shinsen president!
Hey, stop it!
Show some mercy!
We'll disband! We'll disband, you hear?!
We'll disband! Please...
Shit, we're late after all?
Motherfuckers...
Hijikata, you bastard!
You were fucking lucky this time!
Who...
Who did this?
Huh? What's the matter?
Just try these on.
I knew I was wrong.
What's this about?
Akino-chan met a cool-as-a-cucumber yakuza the other day.
He's such a wonderful person!
What's more, he was about your height
and had a square face just like yours.
He must be some very important boss!
If their boss really looked like that,
that organization would fall apart in no time.
My face is not that bad?
RAW provider
Translator
Editor
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Darkcart