Produced by Osaka City Board of Education
Crap, the cops are here.
Start the maneuver!
All right!
They've seen us! Start moving!
It's them!
This way!
We got you!
Seriously!
It's been how many times this year?
You think this stuff is funny, or something?
Hah. Quite the opposite.
I'm doing this 'cause it's no fun.
The world is a dark place.
That's not what I asked!
By the way, what about that guy?
He just glares at us, silent and arrogant.
Him? Ah, Takeshi?
Takeshi? What's his full name?
Iba Takeshi.
New blood?
Well, something to that extent.
We use him to mess around sometimes.
'Cause he's a Buraku.
Buraku?
This is Takeshi's bike!
Yeah.
What are you doing with your life?
Now you even ended up at the police station!
You need to stop with the antisocial behavior.
I just want you to stay out of trouble,
is that too much to ask?!
I am staying out of trouble.
Joining a biker gang
is the definition of trouble!
This is so embarrassing—
I can't face our neighbors now!
That's not what's embarrassing.
What do you mean?
Being born in this city is.
What are you saying?!
Hello?
Coming!
Pardon the intrusion.
Not at all.
Please don't mind the mess.
Come on, Takeshi.
Your soccer club coach is here.
I went to the police,
but it seems I was just a bit late.
How are you, Takeshi?
We were worried.
I'm truly sorry for all the trouble
he gave you...
I've been raising him to the best of my ability,
but being on my own...
It looks like he bought that bike
with his savings from the part-time job.
Maybe it was my fault
for allowing him that...
Mom, stop talking nonsense.
It's time to go.
Right... Excuse me,
I need to go to my work now.
Thank you for looking after Takeshi so much.
Your mom is going to work in the evening.
It must be hard for her.
Yeah, she works night shifts at a convenience store.
Tell me, why did you mingle
with a biker gang?
No reason.
Is that so?
I don't think you'd do something like that for no reason.
He's right! What was it?
You're overthinking!
Something happened.
Why won't you tell us?
Is it about that scribble in the clubroom?
Buraku
Goalie
Leather scraps
at Takeshi's shop!
I've already forgotten about that.
Forgotten?
Of course! That stuff happens all the time.
They only ever call me "Leather Worker."
I understand your pain.
You understand?
Don't make me laugh.
Everyone says that to me.
I haven't done anything wrong!
They labeled me that just for being born here!
How can you understand
that kind of pain?!
Even if that's the case,
becoming a thug won't achieve anything!
What will it change?
That's right. By resorting to that
you'll only seal your fate.
So what? I was doomed from birth.
Cretin!
What was that?
Don't you know how much Yukari is worried for you?
I don't want your pity.
Just go home and leave me alone!
Please...
We're leaving for today,
but you'll have to promise me something.
Definitely come to school tomorrow.
Yoshimura-sensei insisted on that.
If they ever catch you doing it again,
they might suspend... No, they might expel you!
So what? Not like studying and getting good grades is gonna get me anywhere.
I'd be better off working and helping mom.
You still keep saying that?
Do you have any idea how hard your mother had to work to raise you up to this point?
If you study and become
a respectable person...
Teacher, give it to me straight.
Do you really think that I'll be able to become a good person if I study?
I think you will.
You're lying.
Huh?
My efforts never pay off.
No decent place will take me in anyhow.
Why are you so hellbent on that?
Unless you think that working
at some big company isn't a great thing?
I don't care if it's great or not.
I just want to be looked at
as an ordinary person, that's all.
Soccer Club
Hey, Takeshi!
Long time no see.
I hear you've been up to stuff
with your biker buddies.
You threw a stone at the cops?
Impressive!
I didn't throw no stone.
I'm not stupid.
Exactly! Takeshi just got caught up
in the confusion.
Is it true?
Yes! Aren't you supposed to be glad
that your goalkeeper is back?
Well, I suppose we could...
Yukari's the only one who's happy with it!
Hey! How long are you gonna be blowing hot air? Get on the field!
We only have four months
until the autumn tournament.
C'mon, let's go!
Catch this!
Look out!
Whoa!
A dirty ball!
Ugh!
Can't touch this!
Man, it stinks!
Takeshi, be careful not to get injured.
I know, I'll be fine.
This doesn't interfere
with your school, right?
I wouldn't mind if you only came to work here on weekends.
School will be all right.
I don't wanna go there anyway.
That ain't right.
Well, being a poor learner myself,
I have no right to tell you off, of course...
Are they bothering you a lot at school?
It's written on your face.
I've been through that too.
What do you mean?
Takeshi is your teammate!
If he was our teammate,
he wouldn't be skipping practice!
That's right. He's got no sense of responsibility as a goalkeeper.
Think he has some complex or something?
Soccer Club
Isn't that terrible? And it all happened with your tacit approval!
All that malicious gossip
and the clubroom graffiti!
Soccer Club
The scribble was Hayakawa's...
Bullshit! It was Moriya!
Dumbass! You scribbled it yourself!
I know nothing.
Maybe Mihara?
Don't try to frame me!
Soccer Club
Yeah, now I remember. Mihara wanted the keeper's position for himself!
That's not true!
Soccer Club
Mihara, Mihara! It was Mihara!
You guys think this is funny or something?
Soccer Club
No matter who wrote it,
preventing it was everyone's responsibility!
Soccer Club
Don't you feel ashamed as humans?
Coach, there's no need
to make a mountain out of this molehill.
Yeah, yeah!
Hold it!
You guys may think
that it's all fun and games.
But anyone you target is deeply hurt.
Why can't you understand how he feels?
Soccer Club
To be honest, I was really shocked
to see that scribble...
But if I'd blown the whistle,
they'd do something similar to me next.
Soccer Club
For me, it was middle school.
I dropped out midway.
Looking back now, it was a mistake.
All I ever did was run away.
What happened next?
I had enough.
I become defiant.
I thought I could change everyone's view of me by making good money.
I barely ate and was saving money
little by little, it wasn't a very humane life.
That's admirable.
Nothing is admirable about it.
Even if you manage
to save up some small sum,
people will keep looking at you
with the same contempt.
Hello!
Yeah...
It's Hiroko, the woman
my son recently married.
So it's her? The woman from Kobe?
Yeah. Despite her family's protests, she went ahead and married my son.
She's a hardworking lass.
They decided they want to work here together and returned.
My son had it tough too, but he never complained or abandoned our town.
Let's take your father, for example.
When he got drunk, he used to brag
that his Takeshi is strong at heart.
He wanted to use your scholarship to send you to university,
then come back to revitalize our town.
My father said that?
He was a skilled high-altitude worker—
just a bit too fond of drinking.
You're never coming back to school?
No. I haven't made up my mind yet.
The Coach is worried.
And the guys are too.
Because there's no goalie, right?
It's not just that!
We talked to everyone.
Coach was asking them
why can't they get along with you.
He even cried later.
He said it's his fault—
it's his responsibility to prevent things like this.
Why can't everyone just be honest?
What's Coach's responsibility here?
What does it mean?
It's because he's so worried for you!
What a funny thing.
People here look at me askance just because I was born on the other side of the river.
There!
Takeshi! You can't give up!
Yeah.
But sometimes I wonder,
"What kind of shitty life is this?"
Then I start hating this town and my parents for having me,
until I stop caring what happens to me.
If I'm honest, I don't understand myself.
I'm home.
Kazue!
You're back?
Yeah, Takeshi, and it seems
you're full of life too—
so much that you're starting to give your mom trouble.
Are you back for good?
No. I have to return tomorrow.
Oh, did something happen?
Kazue...
is getting married.
For real?
Yeah. We haven't decided
for sure yet, though...
Takeshi, before going back, Kazue is going to visit father's grave tomorrow.
Won't you come with her?
Sure.
Family
Tomb
It's been seven years already.
A pity that happened to dad.
Family
Tomb
Yeah. How did that accident happen if he was
as great a high-altitude worker as they say?
It was raining, and they were pressed for time,
so they made him work late.
Iba
Family
Tomb
He slipped on a high floor.
He often made it hard for mom
because of his drinking,
but I guess it was his way
of coping with a lot.
When I first went to Tokyo, he was supportive at first,
but after a few drinks, he suddenly got very angry, like he thought I was abandoning this town.
Now that I think about it,
I probably wasn't a model daughter either.
Say, Kazue, when you get married,
are you going to return to Osaka?
I wish I could do that,
but I'm afraid I can't.
I'm too shy for that.
But you do your best for both of us.
Dad was counting on you
to make the most of your life.
Okay? Won't you please
come to school, for me?
Hey, Kazue!
Long time no see.
What a surprise! It's been ages!
Really, Kazue?
You know Coach?
Oh, I'm sorry, but I gotta hurry.
Katayama transferred
to my class in high school.
Oh?
So he was your classmate?
I think he said he's from Kitakyushu...
Kitakyushu?
Yeah.
Where does he work now?
Helping out at his uncle's
sporting goods store.
So, he devoted his life to sports?
Is he pushing you hard in training?
It's manageable.
But I know Katayama is a good person.
Yeah. I don't know why,
but he looks after me a great deal.
Yikes...
Now she knows I'm cheating in English.
Cheating?
Yeah. That's what it was, right?
You're hopeless...
"Never give up."
It's an expression of encouragement when someone is about to give up.
Huh?! But I wrote it in the answers column!
You're such a dunce...
Well, practice makes perfect.
Fight!
Is Takeshi doing well?
Yeah, it seems like he's
much more motivated than before.
They should show more camaraderie
towards each other...
Teacher, he'll be fine now—
they went over it at the last briefing.
Glad to know.
I think it's a problem
that needs to be addressed
not only by the soccer team,
but by the school as a whole.
Hey, did you say something?
It wasn't about you.
For real?
You don't need to be so strung out.
Come on, keep running!
Takeshi, you haven't been coming to the meetings lately.
We're meeting on the embankment tonight.
I can't come tonight.
Why can't you come?
Break the rules,
and you'll face a world of pain!
Hey, wait a minute.
When did I become one of you?
We just rode together for a bit, that's all!
Hey, who allowed you to talk like that,
you fucking Buraku breed?
What?
Hey...
Hey, hey!
Huh?
Somebody's forgetting his place!
What? Not feeling so saucy anymore?
Come on! Say something!
Hey, what's wrong? Come on!
Takeshi, hey!
Oh!
What's that?
Watch out!
Wh-What the hell!
Hey! This is no place for kids!
Move it!
You'll regret it, you bitch!
Let's move out!
Okay.
Takeshi, don't you give in to it!
I'll be fine.
I don't care about them.
I'm not just talking about the bikers.
I know you've got a lot on your plate—
school and all.
Running away won't help!
You fight back!
Like that!
My husband also ran away
from this town and settled in Kobe.
When I learned about it,
I was beside myself:
"Are you forgetting who's in the right—
the discriminator, or the discriminated?"
Isn't that right?
If that is right,
then we can only fight back!
Since you can't fight a war alone,
I said I'd join him.
So we came to live here.
As they say, "A person born in the mountains is no different from one raised by the sea."
We're all the same.
Differentiating people
by birthplace is just stupid.
It's like saying some people deserve everything,
and others—nothing.
Whatcha gossiping about?
What? Gossiping?
Is it about our recycling factory?
Recycling?
Just look at him, Takeshi.
My husband's only accomplished in his dreams.
He wants to build a factory that makes new cars by recycling the ones in this junkyard.
Oh?
They were all only used once.
If we let such vast resources go to waste,
our Earth is doomed.
And that's what he's building a recycling factory for—though only in his dreams for now.
It's important for people to have dreams!
I never said I'm against it.
Hey, you slackers!
Better wrap up your work soon—
it looks like it's going to rain!
Sure, sure.
See? We're only getting scolded
by our scary boss for now.
I'm home!
What's up?
It's Kazue...
She quit her job and planned on leaving.
Huh? What?
She was supposed to be here
for a month already.
I don't know why,
but I have this uneasiness in my chest...
I'm going to Tokyo.
How are you going to do that?
It's okay, I saved up
some money from my part-time job.
I don't like the sound of that...
And how am I going to explain it to your coach?
Mom, please call him now.
ABC Trading Co., Ltd.
She quit about two months ago.
Don't you know why she decided to quit?
Who knows...
She didn't tell us why she decided to quit.
The record says it was
for personal reasons, though.
What personal reasons?
How should I know that?
Did something happen to her?
Like what?
You know the real reason
my sister quit, don't you?!
Why won't you say it, goddammit?
Kid, are you Kazue's brother?
Yeah.
Let's have a chat.
It's best that you try not to be
too inquisitive about your sister.
Why's that?
Why? Because those
are inconvenient questions.
Inconvenient?
Are you Kazue's groom?
No. Not me, someone else.
I just happen to be in the know.
In the know about what?
Her marriage?
Well, that too, I suppose.
But I heard your sister
hid something important from him.
In other words, he had a change of heart
after learning about her origin?
Surprise, surprise. You people just put on a front.
You're cowards—both you and him!
Your whole company
ganged up on my sister to drive her out!
Hotel "Cell"
Hello?
Huh? You're going
to the office tomorrow again?
Hotel "Cell"
It's time to stop. Please, Takeshi. Don't make me worry even more.
Kazue may seem docile,
but really, she's a strong girl.
Mother knows best.
Please. We'll talk to your coach and work something out. Just come home, you hear me?
ABC Trading Co., Ltd.
Kid...
Where are you going?
Huh? Well, this company, obviously.
Well, let's take a walk together, maybe I can
answer some of your questions myself.
What is it you want to know so badly?
Who are you?
Me? Let's just say
someone with ties to this company.
Listen. Your sister
wasn't forced into quitting.
The bottom line is that you should
leave this matter be.
No, more like everyone
will just forget about it.
Let sleeping dogs lie.
This is for the best—
for everyone, including you.
That's cowardly!
You're just trying to cover it up!
I'm a benevolent man.
But not everyone is like that.
Boys like you,
charging around like wild boars,
only end up hurting yourselves.
Hey!
Takeshi!
Coach?
You brought reinforcements?
Well, take care, young man.
Hmm... I wish we at least knew
the name of the town...
Coach, I think I'm going to give up.
Since they found out that Kazue is Buraku,
they couldn't keep her in the company.
I'm afraid, that how is it.
That's because she's so docile.
Still, I was able to grasp
something from this, Coach.
If we keep quiet,
discrimination will never go away!
It's a pain, but we have to give up for now. Tokyo is enormous.
We have to wait
for further developments, Takeshi.
I don't believe that Kazue forgot about you.
She might get in touch with you soon.
Okay? Let's go back to Osaka tomorrow.
Now that that's sorted,
I'm suddenly starving!
Let's find something to eat.
Oh!
Soba
Tempura
Welcome!
Kazue, we have customers!
Coming!
Kazue!
Takeshi!
I was looking for you!
I hope you forgive me
for doing that, Takeshi.
Now that I know, it's fine.
Still, why did you have to run away like that?
You didn't do anything wrong,
so why do you have to hide?
That's one thing that keeps bugging me.
Tell me, Kazue, do you hate our town?
Do you detest our people?
Not at all.
I've not forgotten it even for a moment.
Yes, our town.
Filled with kind and warm people.
A town to be proud of!
So why hide the fact
that you're Buraku?
I was scared.
But I kept asking myself all the time,
"What should I do?"
He's right!
Only a freak would hide who they really are.
A pushover! A coward!
No, I'm just speaking for myself.
Huh?
Actually, I was hiding it too.
My mother is also
a Buraku from Kitakyushu.
Seriously?!
I'm sorry. I should've told you after everything,
but I was feeling embarrassed too.
If it's true, why'd you wait so long to say it?
I'm sorry.
It was inexcusable of me.
My father married a woman from the assimilation district,
despite opposition from those around him.
It landed them in a world of trouble.
But my father told me once:
"It's not on you. Forget where you're from
and live your life to the max."
So that's why you moved to Osaka?
Yes. I came to live with my uncle.
That was how I intended
to cut ties with my past.
But meeting Takeshi forced me to face everything I've been hiding until now.
I'm nothing but a weak, lone man.
By supporting you in every way I could,
I quieted the voice of justice in my head.
But I was also ready to throw away
the most important thing
a person can have,
no matter how foolish that sounds.
It's something Takeshi
helped me understand.
Yes, it's the same for me.
Oh man... You make me sound so great...
I just thought it would be nice
if we could take pride in our birthplace, like Kaji does with his factory.
Yes! It's as you say.
I was willing to cast away
that important thing together with my parents.
The thing that needs to go
is the discrimination, not the Buraku!
Exactly! My father also liked our town!
Kazue, let's return to Osaka.
Come home and start over!
Okay.
Nice!
We're going home!
I hope your next interview goes well.
I've had three already...
But don't worry—I'm sure my skills
will secure me this next job.
I've gotten quite good with computers.
Oh? That's impressive.
You need to take practice seriously—
did you see how worried Katayama was for you?
Gotcha! I won't let him down.
Coach told me everything.
About what happened in Tokyo?
Yeah. And that he's from Kitakyushu himself.
He apologized for hiding it.
Huh? He told everyone?
Yeah. He gathered everyone in the clubroom
and explained everything to us.
We're the ones in the wrong—
not the Buraku people.
I lacked the courage too, but I feel I'll stand up
for the Buraku more assertively from now on.
Takeshi!
What's up?
Did something good happen?
That's not very nice of you.
Takeshi's finally taking school seriously—
why shouldn't we be happy?
Right, Mihara?
Tsk. You're just teasing me.
But I was also concerned about our soccer team.
The tournament is less than a month away.
All right!
But you need to take care, okay?
While you were away in Tokyo,
those bikers came to my place once.
Huh?
What did they do?
They grumbled that you've neglected their meetings lately or something.
It looks like they're scared to lose you.
They just want to use Takeshi.
Can you imagine it—
they also offered me to join them!
They call themselves fine fellas,
but deep down, they must be terribly lonely.
Takeshi, listen up! You've got to guard our goal like your life depends on it!
I'll handle all of them!
Get this!
Ugh!
Stop it, you guys!
You're not supposed
to be on the field, manager!
He missed so many practices,
so we're helping him get back in shape.
Get back!
The game is on!
I don't need anyone's pity!
I ain't gonna lose!
Come on, bring it on, people!
Come on, what's wrong?
All right, let's have two goalies for now.
Don't get in my way, Mihara!
Get back!
Why not? Just leave it to me.
I'll help too!
What's your deal?
We can't keep playing like this.
He's right, it's a bummer.
Let's call it a day.
Continue this game!
Move on to the next formation!
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
I'm home!
Welcome back
Oh, so you're back, Kazue?
So how did that interview go?
Really? So they took you in?
Yeah! I'm starting next week.
You've really done it, Kazue!
Right, mom?
Yeah. I'm sure your father would've been happy too. So let's have a feast tonight!
Really? Let me help too!
Sure.
What do you want?
Takeshi, we brought you some great news!
That girlfriend of yours... Yukari?
Boss is taking care of her!
What the hell?!
If you're worried for her,
come to the park by the pier.
Yukari is also waiting!
Takeshi! Where are you going?
So he's here!
Good to see you here, Takeshi.
You kept the lady waiting.
Yukari, are you okay?
Yeah, she's all right.
You'll have her back soon.
Even we wouldn't stoop so low
as to fool around with a Buraku woman.
What was that?
Takeshi, call the police immediately!
Don't let them pull you back in!
What the hell, you bitch?
Who said you can go?!
C'mon, get 'em!
Gotcha!
Hey, where you gonna run now?
Hey! Why won't you leave him alone?!
Coach!
Kazue told me!
You'll be fine now!
Who's that? A cop?
Whatever, just beat 'em both up!
Get this!
Come on, what's wrong?
Hey!
Takeshi!
Are you okay?
Who are these guys?
Scram!
We'll remember this!
Takeshi, are you okay?
Takeshi! How bad is it?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Hey...
Doesn't it hurt?
Hey, how are you?
Coach!
Are you hurt?
You'll play in the tournament, right?
He's important for the team.
I hope he's not hurt.
I'm sorry. I ended up
getting all of you involved...
What are you apologizing for?
We couldn't do it without you!
You're one of us.
Really?
You did this for me?
You gonna cry because
they whooped your ass?
No at all. It's because I'm happy!
Our hard-as-nails Takeshi is crying!
That his "Never Give Up" spirit!
There!
Raw by WOWmd
Translated & typeset by Perevodildo
Editing by Paul Geromini