Mayday! Mayday! May...
Blasphemboys present
Army?
"Top secret and urgent..."
This is code 404.
This is not a drill. Code 404.
This way, Major.
Even if the helicopter crash was deliberate,
they wouldn't have any means to steal it here.
My men can do it without leaving any footprints or traces.
Together, the two pods should weigh a ton and a half.
I've read the dossier.
Right...
But I mean...
Still...
We picked up the pilots two kilometers to the north.
We’ve given them both the truth serum
and are keeping them separate.
It seems to have been an engine failure.
Inform the soldiers.
Major, over here.
Call in the specialists.
What was inside?
I heard that robot weapons
have six legs in some countries.
Walk over there.
Don't talk. Act natural.
Is this...
The M-66 antipersonnel automated soldier
is supposed to be the perfect robot!
Why didn't they hide the pods?
Why didn't they erase their footprints?
We'll be the judge of that,
just tell us the facts.
The M-66s must be in the middle of a mission,
targeting someone specific.
They were en route
for experimental deployment.
The target program
wasn’t supposed to be loaded yet.
Maybe that's to our benefit.
Without a program,
M-66 would just hide somewhere endlessly.
In that case, unless you demolish
every structure within its mobility radius
and dig up every inch of ground,
finding them would be impossible.
Who are the M-66s after?
Who knows?
We've finished, sir.
Tell everyone to stay away
from the pods and the footprints.
You and Rico check it out.
Roger.
What's their mobility radius?
Since they're not carrying any coolant,
and have to rely on air cooling,
I'd say about that of a light vehicle.
Roger, evacuate all government officials,
foreign diplomats,
in short—all the possible VIPs from Central City and the surrounding forest area.
Employ the police if you have to.
Going after a story on the military?
You're nuts, you know that?
Feel free to stay behind.
Huh? Hey, wait!
Hello? Hello?!
Say, Sybel, did you break up with your husband again?
Don't worry. I won't propose to you, even by mistake.
Is being married to your work that much better?
It's worlds apart from the sight
of some boring man.
A wrecked military craft?
The armor plating is composed of 20,000 projectiles.
Even if we manage to catch them,
it's all for nothing if they just self-explode, shooting that stuff all around.
Rico, go with Doctor Slade
and bring the scientist
in charge of the project to the highway.
Use the high-speed craft.
We'll set a trap there.
This is bad, Sybel!
Really bad!
I'm not about to trade my life for a scoop!
Let me out!
I've got nothing to do with this!
Fine, get out if you want.
But then you'll have to walk
all the way to the city.
Might make tonight's news if you're fast.
Easy for you to say!
You haven't got a family!
What kind of family do you think you have,
sleeping in my car just to get some material?
The military is gonna fight some violent runaway armor on the main road!
We'll never have a better chance!
This is what's known as a "hot scoop!"
Matthew! Doctor Matthew,
there's trouble with M-66!
Come right away!
It's an emergency!
Ferris, go call your grandpa, and hurry!
Tell him there's trouble with his invention!
Sheesh!
Yes, Military Engineering.
Ah, it's Doctor Matthew's granddaughter.
One of those weird military things
broke the house again.
You'd better get it repaired today.
Grandpa.
Grandpa?
Failed again!
Why? Why can't the power panel handle it?!
With this method, a barrier always appears!
G-Grandpa, the military wants you.
Again? They've probably come for something trivial as always.
All they do is interfere with my research!
I thought they're paying
for your research and this house.
I don't recall selling my soul as well.
Ah, I'm going to town with some friends,
so take your key with you.
The whole system has to be rebuilt.
As it is, it burns out at once.
We're in a bit of a pickle here.
Not just you.
I've found a flaw in the system itself.
Good to know.
What are you saying, you idiot?!
Huh? Is that the sound of a military aircraft?
I thought it was a wood spirit playing his flute.
Is something wrong?
What the...
Wh-What could have done this to a bear?!
Claws... Its claws are broken!
Major.
We’ve tightened the encirclement to the designated area.
Hey, how are the troops?
Tense. They're speculating that we're about to make contact with a UFO.
Have you equipped them as instructed?
Yes, but the men aren't used to...
No matter. Keep it up.
Have you placed any men in the woods?
No, sir.
Major!
Three o'clock, five minutes, zero degrees.
Robots aren't that stupid.
It might be a trap. Use ten men.
If it's M-66, don't engage it just yet.
Yes, sir!
What's the situation?
The team back at the scene reported finding
the bodies of a bear
and a couple of hikers in the valley.
It seems to be the work of M-66.
Judging from their estimated time of death,
the M-66s should be here by now.
Then get outside.
It's dangerous to stay in here.
Yes, sir!
Why?! Why did you load the test target memory into the M-66?! That had...
Is it like a cruise missile or something?
I wonder what's gonna happen.
I wonder if my wife would worry if I disappeared now...
Hey, Sybel, is it even safe here?
It will be if you shut up and keep a lookout.
I can't get a good picture with you twitching like that.
A freelance reporter, huh?
What in the heck are you doing dropping M-66 in the first place?!
Good. Detain them.
That's why I didn't want to...
Should've kept quiet!
Didn't I tell you that program
was just an experimental deployment?!
Are you sure it can hold the robot?
If you position it properly.
What?
We've lost two life readings.
Pass the word to everyone, formation "C".
Yes, sir!
I'll leave it to you.
Major, we've made contact.
Pull back!
It got away, but we wired it!
So that's the M-66?
It's the enemy!
Wires!
To all groups:
the attacker is a diversion!
The other will cross the road.
Ready the nets!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and capture it already!
You'd never imagine this from the data sheets.
Over there!
Stay still!
There's the other one! Over there!
After it!
Good timing.
Don't let these two out of your sight.
Leakey! Leakey, this is our chance!
Hurry up! Open your eyes!
Here it comes!
Group Six, go around.
Group Eleven, back them up.
Group Four, hold your fire.
How is it. Roger?
All ready, sir.
Major, this...
Group Nine, spread out.
Spread out to hold it down!
It's self-destructing!
Bring the scientists here.
Yes, sir!
Put on your gas masks, everyone!
Major, take this.
Yes. You put yours on as well.
The other one!
Hurry up and do something!
Don't shoot! We'll hit each other!
What are you doing? Over there!
Here it comes!
There, up above!
Pursue it with the thermograph.
Major?
No, don't go into the woods.
Gather your men and come with me.
Yes, sir!
That's brutal... He was a friend of mine.
We'll make that monster pay!
Stop shooting! The enemy is gone!
All this because you rushed the delivery—
air-shipping the product
in bad weather with the test program still loaded!
It was an accident!
When it arrived at the destination,
the test program would've been overridden
with the real program.
I should have made you the test target!
M-66 can still find its target
without revealing itself even in the city.
Major! Major! Hurry up and catch it!
Just who did you select as the test target?
Who is M-66 after?
What?!
It's after my granddaughter?
You've got to stop it! Please!
I put in her data as the test target...
Is there a possibility that its program malfunctioned due to the crash and this battle?
There's a high probability, yes.
Got it. Let's go.
Yes, sir.
We're still suspecting this to be a Northern State plot.
It may not be after your granddaughter at all.
Oh... Come on...
How come you're so goddamned heavy with a diet like yours?!
It's because my head is packed so full.
Of garbage?
Yeah, raw garbage.
Oh, my back hurts.
Don't complain!
If I took a picture of you now,
I bet it'd come in handy later.
I wouldn't want my kid to see me like this.
Hey, are you still gonna go for it?
I've only just begun.
I feel like I've seen that scientist somewhere.
I wonder what it was.
It has a nice sound, though.
That model features an intercooler!
The way they treat the stylists is terrible!
But say, isn't it true that...
It doesn't look good from the recent news...
Hey, isn't that Ferris'...
It's Grandpa!
I always thought he looked like a criminal.
He's published a book on bipedal walking and its control.
Isn't he employed by the army?
He's just greedy.
The military is placing orders,
and Doctor Matthew just...
Can't get through here either.
You can't expect to find his exact address with just that clipping.
But talk about finding diamonds in leftovers...
Huh?
There's a boy with green eyes
at the reception desk of the PFT TV station.
Will you deliver this film
with the three stars on it to him?
So he's the reason you're on this story?
Make sure to give it to him, not anyone else!
How are you gonna find the Doctor's house?
Keep your voice down,
or the military will come.
If there’s a trench, there’s a house inside.
That means I can find it.
That woman is obsessed.
This film will probably be on Midnight News!
What is it?
There’s a spy in the technical division we’ve been letting feed the enemy misinformation...
Weren't you keeping tabs on him?
No. But one of the technicians was in contact with him...
A traitor?
They threatened his family.
So the spy teamed up with the technician
to stage this accident
and tip off his side about the M-66?
The family is protected, and the Foreign Ministry is now handling the investigation.
Very well. Initiate a level A-2 media control.
What's the technician's name?
His name!
Don't say it.
Keep the soldiers in the dark as well.
Y-Yes, sir.
Just as I thought! It's after my granddaughter. It wants to kill Ferris!
The robot I've created
is after Ferris!
The M-66 is humanoid,
so it's likely to cause a panic, and then...
Hold on a minute.
Major, we’re running out of fuel!
I'll give you a map showing the mobility radius
of the Doctor's granddaughter.
Land down within it.
Yes, sir!
Give it to him.
Doctor Matthew
Granddaughter Ferris
Hi, this is Ferris!
I'm dining out at Lumpring tonight,
so I'll be home late.
But don't worry, Grandpa—
I've programmed your dinner into Mayflower.
Hi, this is Ferris!
I'm dining out at Lumpring tonight,
so I'll be home late.
But don't worry, Grandpa—
I've programmed your dinner into Mayflower.
Wait a minute.
A robot?
A military robot is after its creator's granddaughter.
But there are no more battle robots or army here...
Oh, shit!
Other than the robot, I'm the only one
who knows the girl's location
from that answering machine message!
Robot or not, I'll show you!
Everybody, listen up.
When you locate the M-66, do not engage it.
Our best bet is the Lumpring restaurant on the 16th floor of this building.
Roger, you go and protect her.
Nakamura!
Hey now, why do I have to babysit?
Major!
Surely, you're not going to let it kill my granddaughter,
then wait for the evacuation signal from F6, are you?
From now on, we only communicate via the emergency channel.
Can't you send a spare robot after that runaway one?
No time for that!
How about using a dummy?
It'll only warn M-66!
Nakamura, booby-trap the building.
I don't want to lose any more men
to that rogue robot.
Yes, sir. We won't lose another man.
It's performing far better than during the test run...
C-1, evacuate the entire building.
My apologies for the inaccurate data.
C-2, gather at my position with equipment set "E."
This is top secret. Take covert action.
How about you and me...
I haven't had any time today.
C'mon, you've got nothing to lose...
Ah! A thief!
Ah! Hold it, you!
Hey, wait a minute!
That's mine!
Got it! You, make yourself more obvious!
You idiots! You don't shoot at people for no reason!
The police... I wonder if they'd believe me?
No way.
The girl could get killed in the meantime.
If I waste my time at the station,
my chance of saving her will slip away.
And if I just informed the military
and backed out now...?
No, they've already seen me,
so I'll take this as far as it goes.
Yes, sir, that's right.
All clear here.
We'll continue our surveillance.
What's going on?
Left at the next intersection.
We'll be at Lumpring in a moment.
It should be around here somewhere.
Ah, it's Grandpa's robot!
Hi, F6-402! What are you doing here?
It's here to kill you.
Huh?!
N-Now wait a minute! Who are you?
All right, I won't say this twice, so listen up.
Morris!
Listen to me!
The military robot is here to kill you.
We've got to run! Got it?
Major!
What are you doing? Hurry!
The Doctor's granddaughter is in our custody.
Take her to the roof.
Roger, pick up the girl on the roof.
Use the high-speed craft.
Yes, sir!
It's coming!
Okay, go back!
All right, do it!
Paco, go to the roof with these two.
We're going back to recover the robot.
It was a good idea to start setting up the traps from here.
It's the most obvious place.
Hey, I hear that the military's closed off this whole...
Hurry! When the temperature drops,
it'll start moving again!
I guess you're unfit to be a reporter
since you ended up doing this.
but I respect what you've done.
Hey, this way!
It's not here!
What?
What about the wires?
It used its heat ray on the meat hooks.
Group One, Group Two, code one.
The robot is on its way to you. Roger?
Code one?
Okay, I'm counting on you, partner.
Open up! It's Paco!
It'll be here soon.
We need to get to the roof.
Emergency stairs are there!
What did you guys do to the F6-402?
Grandpa...
Stop it. The soldiers are doing their best here.
Hurry up!
Come on.
Is there any other way out?!
Take the other elevator!
We'll buy you some time.
Turn on the donut.
I'll block all the robot's functions.
Damn it!
Did we do it? Whoa!
It's working now! Perfect!
Seal it in with the donut.
I'll call the recovery squad.
We did it!
Recovery squad,
Shut it down.
report to Major, we have F6 right here.
O-Okay.
Let's see...
"First, insert the tip of the red hair
into the back of the head..." Oh?
What? There's two of them!
Okay, done. "A signal should appear..."
"After that, just press the switch on the forehead to deactivate the target lock."
Okay, it's time for us to go to the roof for evacuation.
I-Is it over?
I leave the rest to...
The switch on the forehead!
The switch...
Don't stop!
We're almost there!
Run!
Nakamura, we've located the F6!
It's on the top floor, pursuing the object.
Evacuate the object.
The robot's almost caught up.
What was that?
Hey!
It's not the robot.
It's the object.
Isn't Paco with you?
Squad leader Nakamura, object is with us
in the hall leading up the roof.
Aid Roger in their evacuation.
We'll deal with the robot later.
Run!
Are you safe, Roger?
Yes, and so is the Doctor's granddaughter.
No one else is in sight.
Nakamura?
Four missing in action.
Eight lightly wounded. Over.
I don't see any remains of that thing.
Move it!
Over here! We'll pick you up!
We're dropping the cable—
grab on tight! Copy?
Hey, cover them with machine gun fire!
It could hit the girls.
What the hell! Get us closer, then!
Come on! Can't you do something?
No can do, sir. You saw what happened.
The cable! Lower me down there!
Sir, that's insane!
Do you expect me to just watch from here?!
This is our last chance.
Don't get swept off by the blast.
If we're lucky, only the robot will be blown up.
What's your name?
Sybel.
Sybel? Sybel!
Th-Thank you!
It's too early for that, silly.
It's blocked by debris!
Why... Why me?
What have we done to deserve this, God?!
Not bad. Should've used a smaller basket, though.
We're saved.
Hey, it's over here!
Second group, go back!
We lost 18 men today—and counting.
What can I say to their families to apologize?
Wanna grab a drink later?
I figured you might need company.
What is it?
We've recovered the robot.
Returning to base now.
Good.
Let's go.
Okay.
Major, can we land?
Don't get in the way of the vehicles.
Land to the west of the building.
Got it!
Is your work always this dangerous?
The real danger starts for me now.
After falling from such height,
the exoskeleton is largely intact.
Looks like continuous overheating
damaged the circuits.
There's still a lot of room for improvement.
Grandpa!
Ah, come here, child.
You must have been scared!
But you fought back well.
I'm so relieved!
Sybel!
No!
You're not taking her!
Wh-What do you mean I'm not?
Grandpa!
What? What's going on?
Look, Ferris, this really isn't something I can help with.
Then you're not trying hard enough!
That's not very scientific.
Oh, really?
So you’re gonna throw to the wolves the one who saved your precious granddaughter?!
Let her go.
Yes, sir!
Major!
I need your signature to arrange for a forensic expert to reconstruct the faces of the hikers.
They might have been spies from the North.
Keep your guard up.
I still don't know why he let me go.
This whole thing may have been an act
to promote anti-North feelings in the nation
and that little white robot
may not have been a secret at all.
Of course, the official statement was
"Northern Terrorists Bomb Building."
There were plenty of opposing voices, but it’s easy to cover them up with a smoke screen.
Later, I received three or so letters from Ferris,
but that was the end of it.
Frankly speaking, I myself am not sure any of it really happened to this day.
I can't even imagine that the Northern troops
might be fighting those dolls somewhere as we speak.
They confiscated my film and camera,
but the one precious roll
that made it to Midnight News
was enough to get me new gear right away.
Good evening.
As many of you may already know
due to the crowded train lines and overflowing parking lots,
there was an accident on the central highway tonight.
Midnight News has managed to obtain some rare footage of the accident.
Let's watch it with the cameraman who was there, Richard Leakey.
Mr. Leakey, it doesn't seem like a traffic accident, does it?
Yeah! Not at all!
Here you can see a massive buildup of troops.
I must say, obtaining this footage
was very hazardous!
Isn't that Special Forces?
And that made the actual fight
all the more dangerous!
I couldn't film it properly—
the soldiers were in the way.
Still, I felt that the world needed
to see this, even if it could cost me my life...
Huh?
Wha... Sybel!
A dream is bleeding like ink,
In Ceramic City
Down on their knees,
at a loss for what to do,
stray children
It's no one's fault
It's just my rusty heart creaking
From a printer that prints tomorrow,
Blue data is spilling out
You don't feign cheerfulness
You don't show me your plastic smile
You're not afraid to cry when you are sad,
and that's why I like you!
Pull up! I'll cherish you
Pull up! If you can go on
Pull up! You have nothing to fell sorry about
Pull up! I want to hear your voice more
We'll be finally free!
Original translation: R1 DVD (Yoshida & Ledoux)
Encoding: WOWmd (Batty's LD)
Translation check: Perevodildo
Quality check: Marty Mcflies (LonelyChaser)
Briareos, let's go!
Appleseed
The strongest mecha that will determine the fate of Olympus,
the multi-legged turret, was stolen by terrorists.
Me and Brio keep working to stop them constantly,
but we always get stopped just one step away from victory.
And this time,
even Gaia stopped functioning.
I feel like some huge power
just became active.
The long-awaited Super Battle Action Appleseed.
Don't miss it!
Why did you load the test target memory into the M-66?!
The beauty approaching you is the killing machine M-66
It's targeting someone specific.
What?
Who did you select as the test target?
Who is M-66 after?
Long awaited by anime fans!
The birth of the worst ever Crusher Police Squad!
I think there are many ways to go about doing this.
Thank you for your advice.
But here, we only do it our way.
Special Tank Police: Dominion
In the city of Newport, rife with crime,
no matter how much criticism flak we get,
I and Bonaparte
will protect the peace of the city!
D-Don't come close!
I'm gonna kill him!
If you kill the hostage,
you'll lose your trump card.
There are only two paths left for you:
give yourself in now and go to the detention center,
or end up at the police hospital.
If you behave, I won't shoot you.
Is that so?
Use the Vulcan!
It's got a laser?!
What is that thing?
What?!
A daily battle action hub with original stories
that you wouldn't expect to see in a dramatic comic.
The latest OVA series
is finally here, in 6 installments.
Don't you look down at the tank police!
Special Tank Police: Dominion.
A total of 900 people will be selected by lottery
from those who apply during the campaign period.
You will receive one free telephone card of your choice from Appleseed,
Mario 66, or Dominion.
The application deadline is the end of April 1994, so make up your mind.
Please don't hesitate.