N-Not working!
I see you on TV all the time.
Thank you.
Though whenever I do, I can't help thinking
that your acting is clumsy.
It'd probably be considered great for a school arts festival.
But you don’t have the attitude of a pro.
H-Hey, hold on a minute!
Who are you?!
Kumagai Ichiya.
Nice to meet you.
Please don't let my heart go astray
Handsome Girl
I wanted to show it to you first—
the white skirt I bought yesterday
But you're so insensitive,
you didn't even notice
When I get into a bad mood,
Please stop the time
Please change my mind
If you try to ask me why,
Please tell me why
The tears will fill my eyes
I understand, I'll turn my back on you
I’m running alone down a slope under the setting sun
Please chase after me
Don't let this love go astray
Clumsy?
Yes! He said it right to my face!
Of course, I don’t see myself as a great actress.
But it’s definitely not on the level
of an elementary school arts festival!
I didn't become a celebrity because I wanted to.
Why, then?
Why I did?
Let me think...
I've been on TV since I was little.
And before I knew it, I became famous.
I guess it just happened naturally.
Happened naturally?
I'm Hagiwara Mio, aged 15,
Sagittarius, blood type O.
I'm a charming girl who's
just entered high school this spring.
I told Aya I got into showbiz naturally and without trying,
but in truth, I really enjoy being in this world.
If possible, I'd like to make acting
my lifelong career.
That's what I have on my mind lately.
I'm home!
Being an actress is really interesting.
You get to play so many roles, live so many lives, experience so many different things.
I can't think of another job like this!
You're clumsy.
Bleh! I remembered him again!
Your plan definitely appeals to me
in several ways.
The main one being...
That you, the director,
are a high school student.
Your demo tape is extremely well done.
I can feel the young talent
radiating from the screen.
Thank you very much.
As for the actress you chose for the lead role…
Your choice showed sound judgment.
She has great potential.
Very well. We will sponsor you.
A-Are you serious?
In the current state of the film industry,
it’s difficult for Japanese films to become global hits.
But I dare say, I have high hopes
for you young talents.
I just need you to remember one thing.
Our Somy Group is a commercial enterprise.
We don't fund your hobbies or charities.
You must create a certified hit film.
On a page of a magazine I bought at a train station,
I was looking at the horoscopes
It seems, one day I started caring
Aya-san!
about your star sign
Even though I know we're just fooling around,
For some reason, I feel just a little embarrassed
You can see right through it—my poker face
As I pretend to be the same as always
She really is a little different
from all the other idols.
But this time, I'm feeling lovely
My smile is a poker face
Please accept this palpitation
that was born quietly over time...
Aya, congratulations!
That was really something!
Thanks, Mio.
Ah! I-It’s him! The guy who said I’m clumsy
and no better than an elementary school kid!
Hey! We meet again.
L-Look, you...!
It's Kumagai Ichiya-kun.
He spent two years in the US
studying film production.
He just came back this spring.
Aya, you know this guy?
He was my classmate in middle school
before my debut.
Classmate?
See ya.
Yeah.
Keep practicing,
and you’ll become a worthy actress.
Before you start filming,
you'll need to get the word around.
Get the word around?
Yes.
First, we need to build your profile.
To that end,
you'll shoot a promotional video.
Put your gift into it
and we'll broadcast it on TV.
We'll leave the novel imagery and the authors' names imprinted in people's minds.
Then we'll announce
the production of the film.
I'm putting my trust in you guys,
so please make it good.
After all, it will feature Sawaki Aya, Somy Records' top idol and pride.
Nice to meet you, Ichiya-kun.
Don't ask me why...
While you're waiting for a bus,
I'm sitting on your suitcase
and watching the endless sea
A white ship
gently sails away,
Taking away our golden summer
Again as my childhood friend,
You return to the big city
I hold unspoken words in my right hand
While waving lightly with my left hand
I'll keep your smiles in my heart
Hey, please shine on for me
Number 1 on the charts for five consecutive weeks, "The Summer to Remember" by Sawaki Aya.
You've got another big hit?
Yeah.
Maybe it's thanks to that promotional video?
It was nicely done.
It shows off all your good points.
Oh, that? Ichiya-kun filmed it.
Ichiya? That Ichiya...?
Hey!
I want your love that fills with sensation
Ichiya-kun!
Wanna celebrate with us?
Give you all my body tonight
Celebrate?
We're throwing a small party to celebrate
the success of your promotional video.
I need your love that follows your emotions
Wow! Thanks!
Every time it seems so without you
If we're going the same way,
we can share the ride.
Where do you live?
Seijo.
It's on the way, then. Get in.
O-Okay...
Your face is expressive enough.
The timings aren't bad either.
You have a good sense for acting.
But the delivery is unconvincing.
It will take some effort, but with a bit more practice,
you'll improve as an actress.
When I said you're clumsy,
I didn't mean any harm.
"But the delivery isn't quite there.
With a bit more practice,
you'll improve as an actress."
Seriously?
He's far too late to try
and make amends with me.
When I said you're clumsy,
I didn't mean any harm.
Maybe he's not such a bad guy after all.
Boy Genius Film Director
Kumagai Ishiya (16)
Spectacular Debut
Announcing the new movie - Private Aoi
Somy Group Provides
Financial Backing!
Coming!
The heroine played by
newcomer Hagiwara Mio!
Come on! Are you still sleeping?
Turn on the TV!
What is it?
Make sure you don't drop your jaw
when you see it, Mio.
You've been cast
in the lead role in a feature film!
President already signed the contract!
Mio, this is your chance to make it big!
At last, a star will be born
under our production!
Oh, it's you, Mio-chan?
I'm glad you came.
Come on in, hurry up.
U-Um...
My manager suddenly called me this morning,
but I didn't quite understand everything...
It's pretty straightforward.
We just want you to be the star of our movie.
B-But...
Sorry we didn't consult you beforehand.
But Okita-san suggested that announcing
the production this way would be more impactful.
Okita-san is one of Somy's head managers
that is backing us.
I'll introduce our staff.
Otomo Yasushi,
he's the producer for this one.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kani Osamu, the cameraman.
Mio-chan, I'll film you beautifully.
And this is Hosaka Minoru, art director.
Nice to meet you.
Lighting—Oda Shuji.
Recording, Fujii Daisuke.
Nice to meet you.
Finally, scriptwriter and director—
Kumagai Ichiya.
Nice to meet you.
Ah... Excuse me...
N-Nice to meet you.
Hooray! Mio-chan agreed to work with us!
We've got it!
That means you need
to speed up the script, Ichiya.
Yeah! I'm on it—almost finished.
I guess we'll start filming
during summer vacation.
We can't forget about the school.
What are you saying?
When making a movie,
we can't let school distract us.
Calm down, Osamu.
No need to be so extreme.
Their enthusiasm energized me as well.
They... love cinema with all their hearts.
It's so nice to love what you're doing.
Thanks.
Everyone was thrilled when you
agreed to work with us.
Everyone?
Well, of course, I'm happy about it too.
Do you want to go see a movie?
Wait a minute!
They call actresses such as Lauren Bacall
and Marlene Dietrich "handsome women".
"Handsome" is usually reserved for males.
Lately, it's been used for ladies too.
It means you're cool, intelligent and determined...
Or something to that effect.
It's like an ultimate compliment.
Making a captivating movie
with an overwhelmingly handsome heroine
alongside my friends and peers...
that's my dream.
When I first saw you on TV,
I felt you were that heroine.
We'll capture your beauty!
You can trust us with it.
I've never seen him like that...
Every time we meet,
I discover a new side of him.
He's confident... And stern.
Yet he's shy and gentle.
I want to get to know Ichiya better.
It's a good script. Let's roll with it.
Can you start filming immediately?
Yes, sir!
Cut!
Ichiya, you're devoting yourself
fully to this movie.
Completely oblivious to the outside world.
I like that about you.
But I wish you looked at me more...
Ready?
Start!
Mio!
Is the shoot going smoothly?
Yeah, it's going great.
I feel like we're about to wrap it up.
Mio, you've become so much more lively
since you started.
Oh, really?
Is something wrong?
You don't look like your usual self.
Aya...
This love is already over,
so I thought I'd forget about it.
But...
Ichiya-kun and I were dating
in the middle school.
My first kiss was with him too.
I made the first step
and confessed my love to him.
After that, we walked home together every day.
We went on dates several times a month.
And in the autumn...
We kissed.
Why did you break up?
Study abroad?
Yes. For two years, maybe more.
I'll be studying film-making in the US.
I see. I also got my debut arranged
through my singing teacher.
I see. Congratulations.
I guess this is goodbye, then?
Yes. So it seems.
So long.
Yes... Bye-bye.
I wanted him to tell me to wait three years.
But Ichiya left without a word.
I had no idea.
I envy you now.
You spend all your time with Ichiya.
Aya...
This love is already over,
so I thought I'd forget about it.
But... But...
Why won't you acknowledge
Mio-chan's feelings for you?
It's obvious if you look at it from the outside.
Whenever Mio-chan sees you, the love in her eyes burns so intensely that it's impossible to ignore!
I love her too.
Then why don't you ever say
a single kind word to her?
Osamu, make no mistake: when I said I love her,
I meant the actress, Hagiwara Mio.
When you say "the actress"...
you mean her as a movie asset?
Or as a girl?
Neither.
So you're not interested in her, after all?
The way I see Hagiwara is nothing like that
Mio-chan.
Ichiya! Mio-chan just overheard you.
I'm just an asset...
Merely a tool for Ichiya to make a movie with.
No!
It can't be...!
Cut!
Hagiwara! You call that acting?
I can't feel any emotion in it!
S-Sorry!
No, that won't do!
One more take!
Okay!
I'm just a tool for making movies.
Good... Looking great, Osamu.
Zoom out!
Ichiya's recent scripts are amazing.
Yeah, incredibly thrilling.
Mio-chan's doing great too.
She's totally believable!
Wh-What did you say?
The production was halted?
The order was given from above.
Okita-san, I thought you were the department head.
Who could be above you?
The president.
My own father.
O-Oh no...
"Film-making is a waste of time;
ready-made software is a better investment."
That's his judgment as an entrepreneur.
How could they do that? We've only got one scene left to film—the story's climax!
If we want to keep filming,
we'll need to secure additional funding.
Are you saying we have to give up?!
There's no other choice.
For the sake of this movie, I've already set aside
everything I had—school, family, and...
I won't let them stop us now.
Absolutely not!
We'll finish filming!
Ichiya!
Um... Excuse me...
Don't worry. We'll finish it.
But...
I borrowed money from the bank
using my apartment as collateral.
Everyone worked hard
to make it happen.
We can't give up now.
All that's left is a car chase scene, don't worry.
See ya.
Ichiya, are you sure you can manage?
You'll see.
I'll nail this scene.
Osamu-kun told me
that you're handling the stunt work.
You came to see my stunt?
What a curious audience I've got.
No!
I'm... worried.
Why's that?
Mio...
Good luck. Don't get hurt.
Bye.
Do you read me, Ichiya?
Are you ready?
Yeah. Good to go.
Start the camera!
Timing is crucial now!
Did it!
Got it!
We did it!
Now the bend.
N-Not working!
What are you doing, Ichiya?
Slow down!
That last stunt busted the bike.
This just got real!
Ichiya!
Ichiya, answer me!
Mio-chan, hang on! Mio-chan!
Why?
Why did this have to happen?!
I don't believe this...
Answer me, please!
Ichiya!
Osamu?
Ichiya? Is that you, Ichiya!
Ichiya! You're alive?!
Yeah... Made it out, barely.
The bike's burning right next to me,
what a thrilling sight!
Silly...
You're crying again.
Ichiya! Hang on, Ichiya!
What's wrong?
From the moment you're flung into the air until you hit the ground, time seems to slow down, strangely.
It was just like slow motion.
Then a thought flashed through my mind:
"Ah... so this is how I die."
It reminded me of all those past regrets.
Like turning my back on my true feelings,
or not letting myself respond to her.
I wanted to make a good movie
without making any compromises.
That's why I put everything
not related to the movie aside.
What's the point telling me that,
ya blockhead?
If you don't retell this to Mio-chan,
I'll make you regret it.
Good afternoon!
Wow, perfect timing!
Can you believe we were just gossiping about you, Mio-chan?
Eh?
Well, I'm sure Ichiya will be happy to fill you in.
O-Okay.
Osamu!
Don't hold anything back, Ichiya.
What is it?
Ah? Nothing.
Does it still hurt?
No, I'm fine now.
See?
No! Don't get up!
You need to stay in bed.
I love you, and I always have.
Don't cry anymore.
Ichiya...
So, Ichiya, what happened to our movie?
Well, there's still some work to do.
Probably only after I recover.
Tell me.
Will you use me again
when you make your next movie?
Of course!
Like I can let someone else have you!
Hagiwara Mio will always be
my exclusive heroine.
Please don't let my heart go astray
I want to be reflected more beautifully
Than anyone else in your pupils
I'm putting on a brave front again
Your kindness is not enough
Please understand
Please watch my hand
Which of us is going to say it?
Please take my heart
But for now, we just fight all the time
I understand, I'll turn my back on you
I’m running alone down a slope under the setting sun
Please chase after me
Don't let this love go astray
Based on 2011 script by LAkiba (Little Akihabara):
Translation: Yamazaki Masatomo
Editing: Karen Duffy
Additional Translations & Lyrics: Rumi
Editing, Timing & The Rest: Ba-chan
For this release:
Translation check: Perevodildo
Encoding: WOWmd
Quality checking: True Noobow Gamer