Alto
I can't lose my spirits
You'll win
My eyes are fixed
You are a special girl
Flashback
In that one moment,
Attention!
I'll drive you crazy,
my dear
Whatever will be, will be
No, no, no
I can feel this shining light,
bringing back memories
100%
And I keep chasing
My future all the time, no matter how far it is
100%
Catch me
I believe in tomorrow's myself,
that is the only real me there is
Blasphemboys Production
Keep your chin up.
And take care of your health
Give my regards to brother.
Sure. Well then, I'm off!
Hm?
Huh?
The one bound for Tokyo is over there.
That's so much like her, honestly...
Will she really manage
working at a TV station?
She sells seashells by the seashore.
She sells seashells—
Peter Piper picked
a peck of peckled—pickled—
I'm gonna tie my tongue in knots!
H-Hey, may I...?
Can I help you?
How can a clam clan—
Excuse me?
Cram in a cleam—Cl-Clean cream can?
Excuse me, ma'am?
Do you need some help?
Ah! I'm sorry. Oh no...
Huh? They hired you an as announcer
for a domestic television station?
Yes, I was surprised too!
I still can't believe it.
I see... Well, congratulations then...
You don't look too happy for me, Takagi.
No, it's not that...
What, then?
It's not that, but still...
I'm really happy to hear you'll be moving to Tokyo
and be by my side, just like old times.
But if you launch a career as a TV host and end up on every screen in the nation,
you'll be living in a world completely different from mine.
You'd only distance yourself from me instead...
At least that's how it feels.
Of course not!
I never imagined that someone as clumsy, slow,
and scatterbrained as me could ever be
a good announcer—let alone a host!
Do you really think of yourself that way?
Huh?
You're so charming and sharp,
and that's what allowed you to overcome countless predicaments so far.
Still, I'm relieved.
Knowing you've carried that pure soul with you all these years fills me with confidence, too.
I think Miyazaki Midori from NHK recently married a lawyer, didn't she?
Uh? Yeah...
So they're a news host
and a lawyer—just like us!
Y-Yeah, I suppose...
Wait! Wait a moment, Yoko!
You're so clingy, Akiyo.
What kind of man is he?
I demand that you at least tell me that!
He's middle-aged, with wife and kids.
Huh? Isn't it an affair, then?
I just can't feel good unless I'm with a man
who's a lot older than me.
Besides, you college students are still just kids.
Bye!
Yoko... Yoko!
I've just cut all ties with that infantile fool.
Now I'm all yours, dear!
We should celebrate your employment tonight.
You'll see, I'll become
the absolute best host ever.
A real host who is no match for anyone.
I always knew you had it in the bag.
I thought so too!
Once you start making appearances on TV,
we'll no longer be able to walk together like this.
What are you talking about?
To me, you'll always mean the world.
But I'm a married woman,
and you're a single announcer.
The magazines will be watching you closely.
I'm just an announcer, so there's no guarantee they'll even let me get on TV.
You should stop worrying so much.
Besides, once you divorce your stupid man and marry me, we'll have nothing to fear from them.
Shuu...
I'm home!
Welcome home.
I'll run you a bath right away.
Thank you, big bro.
So, how did meeting
Takagi after all this time go?
Huh? We only dated for three months
before he transferred, we're not really that close.
Have you at least kissed?
Of course not!
We haven't even held hands yet.
He's a pretty passive guy—
nothing like any of my other friends.
I don't have time for that right now either.
I need to focus on my work at a TV station.
She sells seashells...
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled p-peppers...
Kazuyo?
Wow!
Oh?
Wow! Is this it?
No! Stop! Only authorized personnel are allowed in!
Oh, but I'm with this TV station now.
Can't you hear me?
Only authorized personnel!
No, I mean I'm the new employee!
New employee?
Have you got any proof?
Ah... Yes! An acceptance notification.
Now, where was it...
My bag!
No! Don't step on it! Let me...
Please!
My bag...!
So, don't simply think of it
as one of the fields of mass media.
30TH INTERNAL MEETING
I want you to always remember
that you're directly connected to the people
on the other side of the screen.
Society's view of journalism is also understandably harsh.
Therefore, starting today,
I want you all to watch yourselves closely.
We expect you to carry yourself with the pride of being chosen from thousands.
Oversleeping or coming late is unacceptable!
We'll take our lunch break now.
Please come back in an hour.
Hey, would you like to eat with us
as three announcers of the 30th generation?
You haven't introduced yourself yet.
Let's go!
Okay.
I see. So you got caught up in that commotion?
That's awfully unfortunate.
Then my bag popped open,
and my acceptance letter got all crumpled!
I had nothing to prove my identity with,
so the security guards distrusted me.
By the time HR confirmed my domicile
and DOB via phone and the guards let me in,
it was already hopelessly late.
Hey!
Are you guys this year's new announcers?
So who was it that overslept
and missed the entrance ceremony?
Was it you?
I didn't oversleep!
Who are you, anyway?
Who am I?
You work on domestic TV,
and yet you don't know me?
Huh?
I know you.
Edogawa, right?
Huh?
A famous announcer
of the Incredible World talk show.
Oh, I expected no less from you guys.
Yes, I am that Edogawa. Nice to meet you.
I'm Kitamine Yoko.
I look forward to working with you.
Ah, so you're Kitamine?
Tokyo University graduate
fluent in four languages, right?
T-Tokyo University?
Four languages?
Make it five, sir.
I don't make much of it, though.
I'm Mukai Shuji from Waseda University.
Oh, you've seen the world, haven't you?
I hear you walked across the Sahara Desert.
Yes, once.
Traveled around the world?
Quite impressive for someone your age!
And what about you?
I'm Hata Kazuyo.
I came from Kumamoto.
I really ought to have known you by now.
I apologize!
Oh no, it's quite all right.
Everyone has to start somewhere.
We all have our weaknesses. Yes, yes.
In Hata's defense,
she didn't oversleep.
She just got caught up
in the commotion at the entrance.
The guard can confirm that for you.
It's all right, I believe you.
Well, I hope you three get along well. Good luck!
Thank you very much.
Boop.
Oh jeez...!
Speaking five languages… Traveling the world…
How will I measure up
working alongside such incredible people?
Why would they hire someone as plain as me?
All my confidence is gone.
Whatever! Cheer up, Kazuyo!
Okay, bring camera here!
OK!
Is lighting ready?
Are mics in standby?
All OK!
Let's start rehearsing, then!
This is the first studio.
We mainly record singing shows
and dramas here.
Wow! Look, it's the Shonentai!
Ah, Wink too!
Shh! You don't raise your voice here during rehearsals!
Sorry.
You're the new announcer, right?
You must learn to focus more on what
the director, host, and assistants are doing
rather than just reading the captions.
Got it. Thank you.
Good to know.
I'm counting on you to pay attention now.
Certainly.
Thank you very much.
Okay, the opening sequence is rolling!
8, 7, 6,
5, 4...
Good evening!
It's time for the Incredible World talk show!
If you haven't adjusted the channel yet,
better do it now!
Edogawa, today's plan is to treat
our viewers to a pretty rare film, right?
Precisely!
Good job, everyone!
Yeah, good job!
Wanna go have dinner with us?
Ah, sounds good!
Hey, how about we all
bring our partners to dinner next time?
A wonderful idea!
It'd be nice.
However, the time...
The time?
My girlfriend has her own family.
Huh?
Same here.
H-Huh?!
But we can manage
if we choose the right time.
How about you, Kazuyo?
Are you free this weekend?
But I'm not sure
I can really call him my partner...
More like my brother's best friend.
If you're planning a dinner, count me in.
Ah, it's you...
Allow me to finally introduce myself.
I'm Kuwata Kyosuke from the production department. I joined this year as well.
Hokkaido University graduate,
and the future influential director.
Nice to meet you.
So you were a newbie too?
That's right.
We met on the studio tour, remember?
But you talked to me so confidently,
I was sure you're a seasoned veteran here.
No harm was done. You were fangirling so hard, I could hardly stand it.
Jeez...
So, will you let me tag along?
No! Not happening!
Today's the announcer department newcomers' party, not the arrogance department.
Let's go, Yoko.
Okay...
Sorry. Maybe next time.
Tsk.
The plan is, starting this fall, we'll be airing our news bloc at 10 p.m. to directly compete
with the other stations' broadcasts and grab more viewership.
Oh, so we're finally doing it?
For that,
I think we should take the plunge this year and let one of our two new female announcers host it.
Make use of the new blood.
What do you think?
I see. However...
Is it no good? I hear this year's additions look rather promising.
No, there's no problem with that.
One is a beautiful polyglot
from the University of Tokyo.
But the other one
is your average provincial girl.
She's unpretentious and likeable.
And pretty too!
Oh?
Those two will definitely win over
living rooms across Japan in no time.
Isn't it great?
We should go for it, then!
Yes, but we'll have to train them...
Then start an intensive training course!
We need to be ready by autumn.
And then we'll make our pick
based on the results of it.
I'm not trying to exaggerate, but our company's success depends on this. It has to work, Katayama.
Understood, sir. Let's do it.
I'm Iyama. Starting today, I'll be your tutor for pronunciation and diction. Nice to meet you.
Now, without further ado,
please read the news in front of you.
Let's start with you, Mukai.
Okay, I'm reading it.
According to a report from our correspondent
Takami at Cape Canaveral...
So what do we have here...
Mukai has a few drawbacks in his speech,
but I'm sure we can fix that in no time.
But Kitamine's speech is simply wonderful!
With your abilities,
we could start filming right now.
Now, as for Hata...
Compared to her, you're a total failure!
It's a miracle you even landed a spot with us!
Alto
You'll win!
Compared to her, you're a total failure!
It's a miracle you even landed a spot with us!
You are a special girl
Flashback
Attention!
Hata! You're talking
with the wrong accent again!
And why do you constantly try to talk faster than you need to?
Why can't you pay attention for once?!
Even if you try to emulate Kitamine,
it's still night and day!
Come on, try again now.
Okay.
Why are you giving me that face?
How many times have I told you
to remember to smile?
We don't have to do it
if you don't want to, you know.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Now, read it again from the beginning, slowly.
You can't survive in this world
if you cower at every turn.
Okay.
Iyama doesn't really have to talk so harshly.
I guess there's an element of personal grudge to this.
We only have two weeks until the announcement, you just have to endure it until then.
Cheer up, Kazuyo.
I appreciate you worrying for me.
But when I think about it, she's right—I am a bungler.
It's my own fault.
Even when scolding you both for the same thing,
Iyama is clearly being too hard on you.
I'll excuse myself.
Tough love
Maybe
You are a special girl
The sky
The stars
Why am I crying over this?
Where will I be if I keep crying over this at every turn?
It's just foolish.
How well and truly foolish!
Good job, everyone!
Thanks!
Thank you for your work!
Hey. You look completely drained.
How about grabbing a meal together?
You were crying, weren't you?
I was actually seriously worried about you, you know.
If hazing pains you, just quit!
Quit... And become my wife!
Shove it!
I'll never be with the likes of you!
Humph!
Ah... I need a break!
Seriously? It hasn't even been a month yet,
and you're saying it already?
Gosh, you're hopeless.
Weren't you listening?
It's because there's that really mean old hag.
Rather than giving useful advice, she just berates me. It's as if she has something against me.
She just wants to help.
No, absolutely not.
It's something else.
You must indeed be hopeless, then.
She'll be scolding me again today.
Five more days...
But I'm already at my limit.
Yikes! I missed my stop.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Bye.
Planning Department
President's Office
Executive Office
Studio
What? While he's so young? No way!
Good morning!
Morning.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Wow! What's this?
Where did it come from?
Who knows.
It was already there when I came.
Someone must've brought you a present.
A present?
The janitor lady told me that a very handsome man apparently left this flower this morning.
What a childish act.
He's a weakling!
Handsome?
He left a note too.
"It looks like you're having it hard.
I'm rooting for you from the shadows.
I hope even this single flower
can cheer you up a bit.
PS: You can't afford losing your temper."
I wonder who it is.
It was apparently
a tall and good-looking man!
A flower from such a wimp
is only good for eating!
Hey! Cut it out, Edogawa!
I'm sorry.
Please stop, Edogawa-san.
Our training is over for today.
Kitamine and Mukai can face the camera
with sufficient confidence.
I'll approve your nomination.
Okay.
Hata.
Y-Yes?
You need to keep refining your technique.
Record this transcript onto a tape
and repeatedly compare it
with the correct pronunciation on mine.
Sounds good?
Yes.
Well then, I wish you all luck
in your endeavors.
Thank you very much!
It's over!
Banzai! Banzai!
I forgot to mention something.
Chief's office monitors everything that happened in this room.
Goodbye.
Cheers!
It's great!
The beer tastes the best today!
What's more, you did well hanging in there.
That's true!
You're tough, Kazuyo.
If I were you, I'd have lost my spirit by now.
It's all thanks to your continued support.
Not again!
B-But that's true!
This, and that flower...
That's right...
I still wonder who brought it.
What are you smiling at?
N-Nothing at all!
That's suspicious!
Nothing means nothing!
That's nice!
Hiding under the desk—
once again, quite a charming quirk.
As ever, thanks for your hard work, Iyama.
You're welcome.
So what is your verdict
about the training results?
Will we make it in time
for the autumn news show?
Yes. Kitamine is a perfect candidate.
That's what it looks like.
And what about Hata,
the problem child?
She's totally unsuited for this job.
I see...
That said, she's shown some outstanding strengths over the past two weeks.
Oh? Like what?
I'm sure you were also
watching her on this screen.
She has this mysterious charm
that draws people in,
which can be a powerful weapon
in the hands of an announcer.
Really, that was so typical of you!
Yeah, we drank like fish today!
Hold it, you.
Huh? You mean me?
Asshole...
Wha... Hey, what are you doing?
Getting handsy with another's wife, you prick...!
Huh? It's you...?
I am Tae's husband!
Jackass!
Watch out!
I wonder what'll happen to Mukai now.
Who knows. In the end,
it'll be for the HR Department to decide.
Um... They're not going to fire him, are they?
Well, I wouldn't expect that.
And even if he brings me his resignation letter,
I'm not going to accept it.
It'd be a shame to lose such a good
and promising young man over this.
Well, it must have certainly been
a huge hit for him.
But who knows—maybe it'll give him a nudge
in the right direction in the long run.
Now then, as for your assignment...
Huh? Already, sir?
Of course. What do you think
you trained so hard for?
Right... Still, hosting a program all of a sudden...
Believe in yourself.
Directors from various programs
are counting on you.
Okay...
Now then...
Kitamine.
You'll host an afternoon talk show from 3 to 4:30 p.m., Monday to Friday.
Okay!
You did it!
You're getting your own regular show!
We'll begin with a short-term show set for one quarter, so don't get too happy too soon.
As for Hata..
You'll host a show called Variety Day from noon to 1:30 p.m., Monday through Friday.
Wow, sounds interesting!
I'll do my best!
Good. Here's a rundown
of each of your programs.
We'll start working our way through these tomorrow.
Okay!
Ouch!
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow, it finally starts.
Good morning!
Good morning, Toi.
Good morning.
It's today, right? Good luck!
Yes.
Morning!
Good morning, Yoko.
Wow, you look gorgeous!
It suits you so well.
Thank you. I picked the one
that I liked the most.
The first day like this
is worth commemorating.
Your clothes are lovely too!
You look charming.
Thank you.
Hey Kazuyo, did you have any sleep?
I couldn't sleep a wink!
Really? I slept like a log!
What a tough girl you are!
That's true! So tough!
N-Not at all!
It's not that.
I'm just insensitive.
Maybe a bit of an idiot too...
Ah, this is the one.
CONFERENCE ROOM E
Found it!
Hey. We've been waiting for you. We really can't afford newcomers coming late, you know!
Ah... It's you! Are you...
Yes. I was assigned to the same program as you
as the new assistant director.
We'll be working closely from now on.
Maybe we were bound
by a red thread all along?
Don't decide that on your own!
Enough chattering at the doorstep!
Hurry up and come in!
Ah...
Edogawa...
We've been waiting, Kazu!
Come on in now.
Um... Were you also assigned
to this program this time, Edogawa?
Huh?
Listen, you! I'll have you know
I'm the main host of this show!
I've been one for three years, in fact!
Yikes...
Have you really never seen
our insanely popular show?!
All right, you get a kiss as the punishment!
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry!
Ah, Edogawa, please stop!
Good morning.
I see you're hard at work.
The Chief Director is here!
Good morning, sir!
Good morning!
Morning!
And it looks like our newcomers are here too.
Kazu, he's the show's chief director, Ijuuin!
Kazu?
Kazu...
Um... I'm Hata.
Glad to be working with you.
You're welcome.
Let's introduce you two to everyone, then.
This is Kuwata Kyosuke, a new production team member joining the show today.
And our new announcer Hata Kazuyo.
I look forward to working with you!
Both are outstanding professionals
assigned to our program at my personal request.
Please guide them with care.
He said, "my personal request."
Well then, allow me to kick off
the welcome party for the newcomers.
First, let's raise a glass
to the journey ahead with Kuwata and Hata.
Cheers!
Allow me?
Thank you.
Ijuuin-san...
Hm?
Thank you for that flower.
Huh? Flower?
N-No, never mind it.
By the way, Hata, what do you think?
Now that you're involved in Variety Day,
is there anything you feel could be improved?
R-Right...
I've been too busy just getting through
each day—I had no time...
I see. At the next meeting, don't hesitate
to comment more often on what we're doing.
We need to hear
more opinions from the youth.
Okay!
This complicates things...
Would you like another drink?
Kuwata.
Yes?
Take a good look—a fierce clash
between women is taking place.
Huh?
You need to pick up on these subtleties
to win over the ladies.
Look at Terakawa over there.
She finally decided to act.
Chief Director, let me...
Right... Thanks.
Hey, could you move?
I need to sit next to the chief director for a bit.
Huh? O-Okay...
I'm still not done talking to Hata.
You sit on the other side, Terakawa.
O-Okay...
Oh? Looks like our Kazu is quite smitten with the Chief Director.
I'm going to enter the fray.
Hm?
For a clash between men.
What? H-Hey, Kuwata!
Oh, Kuwata?
We were just talking about you.
Sir?
We're preparing a segment called
Visiting a Millionaire for the next Variety Day.
I'd like to ask you and Hata to take care of it.
Huh?
Hata will cover the scene as a reporter,
and you'll be the overall director.
How about that?
Y-Yessir! I'll do my best!
Hata, we're counting on you.
Okay.
A reporter, huh?
Ugh, enough!
I need to go to sleep.
Good night.
Hey, now that we're working together,
we need to ease this tension.
Let's talk about something.
Wanna sing together?
Can you be quiet for a moment?
I'm on edge, trying not to embarrass myself.
It won't be live, and we can always re-record it as many times as you need.
Take it easy.
I know that, but it's not that simple.
I dreamed that I failed last night.
You'll never be a good host
if you're so timid.
Maybe I'm not cut out for it, after all?
It's too late for such thoughts!
We can't have you lose your confidence now.
The Chief Director is counting on us.
Give it your all.
You're right. Nothing ventured,
nothing gained. Yes!
Is the camera ready?
OK!
Reflector?
Here, ready!
All right, Hata. Let's roll it.
Okay... Ready? Start!
Dear viewers, g-goodmow...
Good morning!
I flubbed it, didn't I?
Th-That was probably awful. I'm sorry.
J-Just relax, all right?
Look, we'll try once more.
W-Wait a minute!
Okay. We can start.
Ready... Start!
Dear viewers, good morning.
Today we're visiting
Kanaya Manjiro's house.
It's a wonderful mansion, surrounded by countryside as far as the eye can see.
Take a look. It's a 100-meter walk from the gate
to the house—pretty impressive, right?
Okay, cut!
It went OK!
Good job.
Thanks.
You have a smile to die for.
Just be confident.
Thank you.
Now, let's check out the room the owner
is most proud of in his home.
Wow! Would you look at that, dear viewers!
The floor here is made of glass!
Below that—a pond full of carps!
I bet you've never seen
a house like that.
Kanaya-san, have you ever
broken this glass floor?
It's tempered glass—strong enough to hold an adult jumping on it.
It won't break even if you
strike it with a hammer.
Is that true?
Certainly! Why don't you try
jumping on it yourself?
Huh?
Go ahead!
Then, please stay tuned
as I jump on that glass.
Yes, yes!
It's true! The glass doesn't budge at all.
But I guess I'm too scared to jump on it.
It'll be fine, just try to jog on it. Go ahead!
Okay. Let's jump together, dear viewers.
But you see, I can't shake my fear of glass,
so I'm still scared to jump on it.
But when that happens,
I gather my courage and...
That hurt!
But look—the glass still wouldn't budge!
Didn't I tell you?
Yes. However, the carps were so startled by that sound just now, they all swam off!
Now that glass is also butt-tempered!
Oh, geez!
I'm sorry. I flubbed it again.
Let's retake this one.
It was good.
Huh?
Yeah, you showed off the strength of that glass,
and then nailed the sexy appeal!
Huh?!
That won't do! It was too embarrassing!
We have to retake it!
If I say it's good, then it's good!
I'm the director here and I approve it.
If we air me messing up like that...
My parents and siblings will be watching too, you know! Spare me!
I'm sure they'll love it.
That cut was so refreshing.
Kanaya's comment on butt-tempering and your smile. It was all great.
It was outstanding.
Let's keep it. It's perfect!
Oh, whatever!
But when that happens,
I gather my courage and...
It hurt...
Hey.
Ah... Wait a minute!
That report was a smash hit.
What do you want?
Don't be mad.
I'll treat you to dinner tonight.
I'll pass!
I-I'm sorry... Ah!
You'll fall again.
Oh geez...
All right, I'm sorry.
Thanks to you, we've received
a great response from the audience.
Plus, a glass company offered to sponsor us.
How about dining with me tonight?
Y-Yes! Thank you.
Thank you for being you
For all the things you say and do
For all the mountains you helped me climb
And most of all—
for being mine...
Good morning.
Can we talk, Hata?
Yes?
Did you go out to eat
with the Chief Director last night?
Huh?
Yes, he treated me to French cuisine.
Nothing more?
Huh?
Hata, can you help me here?
O-Okay!
I still don't know anything.
Well, whatever.
I'll never forgive you for this!
What did you want to talk about?
If I were you, I'd stop making advances
on the Chief Director.
You don't know
Chief Director's nickname, do you?
Huh?
We call him Junior.
Junior?
He's the esteemed heir to the president of KTS,
our biggest domestic TV station.
Huh? No way!
Why would I lie about this?
He'll never see you as his equal.
Before it's too late, you should quit
and spare yourself the pain.
That's all I wanted to say.
I'm always here
to offer advice if you need it.
Ah, Hata?
Yes?
I've been waiting.
We need to talk about work.
I want you to go to Niigata.
Okay.
It'll be a two-day trip.
Terakawa will cover for you
at your Variety Day job.
It's best to experience life
while you're young.
Will you do it?
Yes, I'll do my best.
Kuwata, we're in trouble!
It's about Kazu!
Did something happen to Hata?
She and Aburai went
on an overnight assignment this morning!
Huh? Aburai...
You mean that shameless rake?!
Yes, Aburai, who'd use any trick in the book to harass a woman if he gets the chance.
This ain't good!
Then we only have time until tonight...
Hey, Kuwata!
It's impossible to recall her now.
She went on that assignment
for legitimate reasons.
I'm sorry, but my hands are tied.
All right, I see.
It seems I severely overestimated you,
Chief Director!
Welcome.
Hello, we're from the TV...
Yes, Aburai-sama,
we're glad to have you here.
Guide our guests to the Plum Room!
Huh? Wait, we're sharing the room?
Yes! This way, please.
I-I'm sorry. Huh?
Ah...!
Madam, you told her
all the other rooms are taken, right?
Sure, sure, that's what I said.
And you're gleaming with excitement.
Oh? You're so generous!
That hits the spot!
But is this inn really chock-full?
I'm sure all the other rooms looked vacant.
Should I look for another inn?
Damn it all!
This would've been an ideal trip
if I didn't have to share a room with Aburai!
Oh, I think it's this way!
No, it's here!
Damn, we'll have to wait
at least half an hour to catch one!
We have to do something, lest Hata...
Kuwata, look at that!
Huh?
Chief Director!
So he also rushed here.
Well, you sure took your sweet time.
Why, you're not wearing a yukata?
Oh well. How about a drink?
They say there's another hot springs inn
about a 40-minute walk from here.
I'll be staying there.
Oh? Really? Fine, then.
But does that mean you're refusing to meet your Director for tonight's prep meeting?
It's not that...
I won't make light of you neglecting your work like that. We can fire you too!
Now then, what'll it be?
Aburai.
Hm?
You're disgusting.
Sure, whatever you say.
Now let's drink!
There is a 4.5 tatami room in the back,
so you can sleep there if you're that worried.
It has a lock inside too.
Is that true?
Of course! Just take a peek.
Wh-What's the meaning of this?
Ouch!
What do you think you're doing?!
C'mon, let's do it!
What the hell?!
No! Never! Let go!
Let go, you idiot! Idiot!
No!
Stop it!
Don't resist!
You creep!
Pervert!
Back off, you creep!
Randy old fart!
Just be a good girl and enjoy yourself!
Let go, you're not getting it!
What are you doing?
No! Stop it! You're gross!
Don't get near me!
Let go!
N-No! You're never getting it!
Help me, someone!
Somebody, help!
No!
Oh? The TV people?
They are staying here,
but should we bother them?
They both went to bed early
in the Plum Room.
W-Went to bed together?!
How can a large inn like yours
have no spare rooms?!
My...
Aren't you brash,
asking things like that...
It's an emergency—
please take us there.
This is the room.
I'll leave you to it, then.
I'm opening it.
There's another room in the back.
I wonder where Hata went on her own.
Let's wake him up and ask!
Hey, wake up!
Hey!
What is it? You're goddamn noisy...
Edogawa, Kuwata... And Ijuuin-sama too!
What in the world has happened?
That's what we should be asking.
Where's Hata?
Huh? Oh, her?
Well, she really took the cake!
She refused a prep meeting with me
and went somewhere on her own!
What flagrant negligence!
And your face is all scratched up.
That was some rough negligence, wasn't it?
No! No, n-no, th-that's...
Yes. Yes, that's right. Yes.
Why were you sharing the room?
I'm sure there's a
workplace regulation, stating
that female employees
can't share a room with their male escort.
Oh... No. No, I know that, but...
None of the inns had any single women
staying there tonight.
I see.
Where could she possibly go?
Let's wait until daybreak
and search for her again.
Okay.
Tell me where you and Hata
have been to yesterday.
Chances are, we'll find some leads there.
Okay...
Good morning!
We're from TV!
Coming!
Good morning!
Chief Director! Kuwata and Edogawa?
Why are you here?
Wh-What about you?
Me? I stayed here last night to have more time
to prepare for today's reportage.
Kimi!
Kazuyo! Hold me again!
Sure, sure.
Well, Aburai, shall we start the prep meeting?
Not at the 4.5 tatami room, but here.
What's the matter with that mister's nose?
Ah, you're wearing glasses!
100%
And I keep chasing
My future all the time, no matter how far it is
Raw
Translation & TS
Quality check
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Anonymous
100%
Catch me
I believe...