He's so miserable!
That's true.
Is he really a baseball club member?
Hey, I was wondering
what you think about that.
He's a scarecrow.
Not a scarecrow!
A traffic cone.
You said it!
They're not even training with him!
They should've called him "a nuisance" on last year's memorial calendar!
I'm so glad I wasn't born
a nature's freak like him.
What's even the point of living like that?
True, true!
By the way, what's that scarecrow's name?
You don't know?
Yamashita Taro.
Yamashita Taro?
Umisora Prefectural High School
Baseball Team Member
Yamashita Taro
The dreams I threw
into the blue sky are like birds
They spread their wings
and flew into the future
Don't cry, hero
You can fly too
Stretch out your hands
and try to catch your courage
The scars on our hearts
will shine one day
Like diamonds, (diamonds)
the symbol of youth
Don't cover your own weakness with tears,
Just run straight ahead,
without worrying about the past
Don't give up
I'll keep you safe
Don't forget that you're loved
And don't forget that you love me
Don't give up
Someday you'll hold up the flag of victory
I want to embrace you as you smile
Pretty ordinary name.
Hey, Taro!
If you can make it here before
I count to 10, we’ll let you train with us!
All right!
1, 2, 3,
4, 5,
How stupid...
6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11!
Too bad.
He was late to slip in.
And now it's too late to slip in anyway.
W-What about...
the training?
You can start by catching this.
Sure.
There!
Right! Right! Right! Right! Right!
Ah, left! Left! Left! Left!
Ah, look, it's to the right again!
Hey! Okamura, Shinkai.
Spend less time mocking Taro
and more time training!
The preliminaries are coming up.
Got it, captain!
We're done!
What for, if we'll lose in the first round anyway?
Training.
It's over, you dunce. We need to clean up
the field and collect the equipment now.
Man, oh man...
I wonder why I keep clinging to this
baseball club if they don't even let me train.
I could do just fine without them!
I shouldn't let them take me for an idiot!
Hey! Quit disgracing
baseball with your shitty playing!
A klutz such as you should stay quiet
and let the real men do the playing!
If you don't do anything,
at least you won't be a laughing stock.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?!
Dumbass!
Remember this!
Hey, isn't that Tatsumi?
Tatsumi?
You know, he was a star pitcher
when he was in middle school.
It's not all fun and games, you cretin!
He had to quit after he left the team manager
half-dead in a post-match brawl...
So it's that Tatsumi?
It’s people like him who push Japan
toward a future of darkness and violence!
I wish he never joined the baseball club!
Scary...
Does your tiny brain at least
know the rules of baseball?
What rules?
You absolute moron!
Read this book.
If you can't read, you should've just said so!
Listen.
For example, let's break down this position.
When the runner is at the base, the pitcher...
Look!
You do it like this.
While holding the runner on base...
Cool!
I didn't ask for your opinion!
Why do I even have to do this?
What a bunch of bullshit.
This... Teach me! This! Hey, can you...?
Teach me this!
Piss off!
T-T-This!
Did you get used to my punches or what?!
This...
Teach me!
This... Please, teach me... Teach me this!
How long do you plan on following me?
If you don't leave me alone,
I'll fuck you up.
Go pester some other sucker
about teaching you!
There's nothing I hate more than baseball!
Got it?
When you're facing a batter,
you have to give him a walk!
When hitting, you have to bunt!
Following the orders...
To hell with it!
Not being able to do what one wants
is the worst thing a man can do!
Why did you have a baseball guidebook?
Stop asking stupid questions!
Tsk. Pathetic.
If he had followed me a bit longer,
I would’ve told him.
Teach me.
Imbecile!
You can’t hit hard if you hold the bat like that!
It's too long for someone your height!
Cretin! It's too short now!
Here I go!
Where're you swinging at, you dunce?!
Listen up! Keep your eyes wide open and
focused on the ball! Never take your eyes off it!
Got it?!
You idiot. I'll be pitching now!
Let's go!
You're looking at it too much, you dunce!
You see the ball from 5 meters away,
then predict its trajectory!
All right!
Shit...
What am I even doing here?
That cretin's completely engrossed in it.
Why are you like that, you scarecrow?
Preliminaries
Round 1
Aonuma High School
Lucky day
Listen!
Your hands and feel must work in sync!
You start moving the moment I hit!
Dumbass! How many times do I have to say it?
Today as well...
We do this every day now.
Before I knew it,
I too have become invested in it.
Just like before...
If I have to look like an idiot,
then I'm gonna be doing it as hard as I can!
Training...!
Lucky day
Preliminaries
Round 1
Aonuma High School
Huh? Yamashita Taro?!
The preliminaries start tomorrow.
Of course, Taro is one of the club regulars.
T-That's ridiculous...
Huh? Isn't he a regular?
What will it be?
B-But number 9
is the right fielder​, you see.
9th is not a right fielder​!
What do you want me to do?
No... Not that...!
Umisora High School,
1st turn: second baseman Sunaga-kun.
2nd turn: catcher Tanaka-kun.
We're with you, Umisora!
3rd turn: pitcher Tatsumi-kun.
Huh? Did she say Tatsumi?
What? 3rd?
What does that mean?
Tatsumi?
4th turn: third baseman Yamashita Taro-kun.
Whaaa... Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Captain! I know we're playing Aonuma,
who are the favorites of the championship...
A-And you know just as well
as I do that we’re going to lose.
But that doesn't mean we can field whoever.
Unless... Tatsumi threatened you?
Eek...!
Shut up!
He's the member
I'm pinning my own hopes on!
Batting first: Aonuma High School.
Fly ball!
1st turn at bat: second baseman Kato-kun.
Strike!
Strike! Batter out!
Wow, he starts with a strikeout.
Tatsumi is serious about it.
Isn't Taro feeling a bit stiff?
Taro!
Timeout!
Hey!
H-Hold up, what are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Stop this! I'll cancel the match!
Shut up!
Stop commenting on everything I do!
You're a fucking eyesore!
What's going on?
So? Have you calmed down?
Yeah.
All right! Sorry for the delay!
Fly!
Taro! Don't worry!
I'll take care of the rest!
If we keep hitting to 3rd base,
we can have all the points in the world!
He's starting to feel it...
Strike! Batter out!
The first inning
goes to Umisora High School.
1st turn: second baseman Sunaga-kun.
Batter out!
3rd turn: pitcher Tatsumi-kun.
Bring it on!
Shit!
All right, I got it!
Out!
Strike! Batter out!
4th turn: third baseman Yamashita Taro-kun.
Taro! Time to prove yourself. Go!
Yessir!
Wait, you forgot your helmet!
Idiot! You did everything
the wrong way around!
Strike!
This is hopeless...
Batter out!
Out!
Good job stopping the ball. That was a great face catch. That's good enough.
Dammit, I haven't played in a year.
After pitching for nine innings,
my shoulders and back are starting to sore.
What is it?
Fight!
Don't worry about me!
Defend your base!
Okay.
We've got two outs in the 9th inning.
We must take a point now, no matter what.
Safe!
Dammit...
Are you serious?
Taro! We haven't lost yet!
Shit!
Out!
Last one! Let's get started!
Batter out!
Out!
3rd turn: pitcher Tatsumi-kun.
We need to steal the base, no matter what!
Dammit!
Okay, I got it!
Don't catch it!
Wow!
Safe!
4th turn: third baseman Yamashita-kun.
This will be our last turn.
Timeout!
What's wrong?
Can I bat from that square on the left?
Left-handed batting?
Yeah.
Why?
That's closer to 1st base.
Huh?
All right. That's one option
I actually haven't considered. Let's try it.
Okay.
When you get there—the moment the pitcher raises his foot... start counting, "one, two,"
then swing the bat as hard as you can.
Got it.
"One, two."
"One, two..."
That idiot needs to switch hands!
One, two...
swing!
I hit it! Hit it!
For the first time ever!
Huh?
The game is concluded.
A-Am I outed?
Good bye.
Good bye...
Good bye!
Cretin! Hurry up to finish your winning run!
It's your farewell home run!
I love Taro-kun!
There's more to him than meets the eye!
I thought so too!
You've done it, kid!
Taro!
Not too shabby.
Was this good enough?
Yeah. It was great.
Our developing team, Umisora High School,
barely won the first round.
Can you believe how lucky we were after that?
We ran ourselves ragged through all those grueling matches until,
by sheer luck or chance,
we miraculously made it to the finals.
The clouds covering the sky seem ready to burst,
as if waiting for the final match
between our Umisora and Egawara High School from the Hyogo prefecture
to begin here at the prefectural stadium.
That's unfair, Tokumitsu-kun!
Broadcasting Club
You only came to cover the finals!
We were here to support them
from the very first match!
The support of our lovely female students must
have been a great boost to the baseball team.
Well, it certainly is true...
He said "lovely!" You think he means it?
Egawara High School...
Huh? What’s this?
I thought you were an elementary schooler,
but you have a proper uniform.
Are you in middle school?
I-I’m in high school, for your information!
Yeah, sure. Don't get so worked up, little guy.
You're a little guy yourself!
Then you're a tiny guy!
Then you're the one-inch boy!
Then you're a microscopic guy!
You're a molecular guy!
Did you come here to support
those weaklings at Umisora?
Umisora are the best of all time!
Even the best of all time cannot compete
with Egawara, the strongest of all time.
Strongest of all time?
The best of all time is better!
Cretin!
Egawara will go to Koshien and win!
What's a Koshien?
The best of all time is way greater
than the strongest of all time.
The finals are now just several minutes away!
The prefectural stadium is packed.
Both teams finally appear on their respective benches.
The microscopic guy!
You bastard...
Who's that?
Pitcher, first-year, Yoshida. Left arm.
A first-year?
Taro, you're pitching today.
Huh?!
T-That's absurd!
Didn't you say we'll lose anyway?
I'll pitch! Let's do it!
The game starts at 1 pm sharp.
Our Umisora High School bats first!
Play ball!
Egawara's pitcher is Yoshida, position one.
And he throws!
Whoa, it's a dead ball!
Dead ball!
Suddenly, he throws a dead ball!
My bad, chum!
He's sorry.
Batter is Tanaka, position two.
Whoa! It's another dead ball!
That dickhead did it on purpose!
Shut up!
No outs, 1st and 2nd base taken.
Yoshida is already in a tough spot.
The replacement batter is Tatsumi,
position three.
What's with his cold-blooded demeanor?
What's with that guy?
Take that!
Tatsumi hits!
Home run!
It's a home run!
Tree run home run!
Nice home run!
Umisora start strong with 3 points.
Egawara will be on the offensive, now.
Their first batter is Murata-kun,
second baseman.
I'll do it!
Taro! Calm down!
Damn it, he's fast.
Suddenly, Murata goes for a safety bunt
and reaches 1st base.
The next batter is Yoshida-kun, the pitcher.
Taro-kun... threw it!
He hits! Murata runs!
Suddenly, there are no outs,
and 1st and 3rd bases are in trouble.
And the next batter is also the giant first-year
Otawara-kun, third baseman.
He's the same age as me?!
Dead ball!
Taro!
Fight!
Don't worry 'bout me!
Defend your base!
Now, no outs, bases loaded.
And the next batter is second baseman Kitano-kun, known as the strongest of all time.
This guy has no weak points.
Is it in?!
Strike! Batter out!
The first inning ends with a tie, 3-3.
Taro, are you feeling better already?
Takakura, show me the data we have on Egawara so far.
Okay.
Just as I thought...
They keep the score even,
only winning in the last inning.
What a team...
Our Umisora School is still hanging in there.
The game went into overtime, still tied at 3-3.
In the 11th inning, Umisora's on
the offensive with two outs already.
The third batter is Tatsumi-kun.
Whoa! Yoshida-kun was hit in the leg.
Will he be all right?
Hey, are you okay?
T-They won't get me that easily!
Taro, bunt and let Yoshida take it.
No!
Who do you think you are...
Taro-kun, doing this is not a cowardly move.
It's a smart tactic, in fact.
Two outs, two outs!
Strike!
I told him to bunt,
but that bastard keeps opposing me!
Well fought.
He hits! The ball is in the center field!
Whoa! It's still in the center field!
Runner is on 3rd base!
Will he make it?!
Out!
No, safe!
Nice!
Keep it up!
The 3-3 status quo is finally interrupted in the top of 11th inning!
Finally, Egawara is on the offensive in the bottom of 11th inning.
If Umisora manages to defend its position,
it'll be our first victory!
However, Egawara's batting order
starts with Hirayama-kun, the right fielder.
Taro! Only one more game.
All we have to do is out
three more of their guys.
Everyone! Give it your best
in this inning, all right?
Let's go!
Hit! The ball is at 1st base!
Oh no, he fumbles it!
Safe! Safe!
This is not looking good!
The replacement runner reaches the base!
The batter is once again Murata-kun,
the fast-footed one!
And he goes for a bunt!
Safe! Safe!
That guy is quite something!
Now, no outs, bases one and two loaded.
We need a long hit, or it's all over!
And the second batter is Yoshida!
Strike!
Are you kidding me?!
Did you hope for a life-or-death battle with me
with a lifeless ball like that?!
The battle of the best
against the strongest of all time!
Get this!
Yoshida hits! The ball flies high!
It's in the left field! Will we catch it?
Yes! It's a hit!
Second runner runs!
He throws to the third base!
O-Out!
One out! Yoshida on 1st base,
quick Murata on 2nd base!
And the third batter enters the box!
Egawara's cannon, Otawara.
Taro-kun, who shows signs of fatigue,
is in big trouble!
And now... He throws the first ball!
Otawara hits!
Is it in? Is it out?
It's in!
Taro, this is our last chance.
Can't be helped. I'll throw it.
No way! I still have my left hand.
Mind your fucking place!
I'll throw with my left.
I don't wanna lose
to the strongest of all time!
I don't wanna lose to him!
You can use this.
Yoshida's right hand glove.
Right? You don't mind, Yoshida?
Yeah. Seems like a fitting way to wave goodbye to Umisora.
I'll borrow it, but I won't lose!
Play!
Suddenly, it's a dead ball!
Dead ball!
Taro-kun worsened their position himself!
One out, all bases loaded!
And the fourth batter
is the fast Kitano-kun!
Damn it, everything went exactly according to his plan.
But Taro’s unwavering confidence
might just be our ticket to getting out of this.
If they manage even a single hit now,
we can kiss victory goodbye!
Fault!
This is a serious predicament!
No strike, three ball!
Is this the end of our dream
to break the tie?
He'll definitely hit the next ball.
No matter what you throw...
I totally will...
become the best of all time!
Let's settle this!
Get back!
Out!
Game set!
That was damn impressive,
"the best of all time."
I'm... the best?
I'm... the best of all time?
Yeah, much more than me.
You're the strongest!
When you do your best
You live your youth to the fullest
When I was troubled,
You were always there for me
Smiling gently
from deep inside my heart
A round of applause for the fine play,
A round of warm applause
But the game continues into the eternity
Oh...
You look dazzling as you swear to never lose again
I'm sure of it—you can get your super life
Hey! Yamashita Taro!
Next time we meet, it'll be an even more
amazing match of the strongest against the best!
Ripped and encoded by WOWmd
Translated by Perevodildo
Quality checked by MartyMcflies