"Eiji"
Make it!
Your soft lips—
don't let anyone but me see them!
Just a few kind words
I whisper them gently to your ears!
Our hearts are in direct opposition.
We're lovers for one night!
Let's dance
our last dance
There's only you tonight
When you doze off,
entrust your dreams and sighs
to the changing time
Make it!
Your soft lips—
don't let anyone but me see them!
A gentle kiss,
your hair is so unruly when it's near my mouth
Our last dance—
when it's over,
There's only you tonight
When you doze off,
entrust your dreams,
entrust your sighs too
to the changing time!
Make it! Before the thread is reeled in,
don't let anyone but me see you!
Make it! Your soft lips—
don't let anyone but me see them!
C'mon, you punks! Bring it on!
Akagi Eiji, you are suspended for a week!
Next time, you're out of here!
Musashi Academy
Why should I care if they expel me?
Hey! Akagi!
What the hell are you doing there?!
Today has come
I gotcha!
Like hell you did, you idiot!
as a sequel to yesterday,
Let's see...
Aren't you afraid I'll rape you?
Jeez!
And tomorrow will come
Give the ticket back.
as a sequel to today
Sorry.
I've given you tickets how many times now?
And yet you only came once.
Yesterday it was cloudy,
Fine. I'm not giving you a ticket ever again.
today it's pouring rain,
But it wasn't any fun...
But tomorrow
And now I'm getting expelled too.
D-Don't lie. I heard you were just suspended.
it will surely be sunny
They said they've had enough of my shit.
"One day it rains,
I'm no longer welcome in this town.
the next day it clears up,"
Maybe I should go somewhere far away
and never see you again.
Liar.
you said while getting wet
So, for the last time...
Hey, won't you give me just a little kiss, Marina-chan?
I loved walking
W-Wait, I don't wanna!
Oh, come on! What do you have to lose?
on rainy days with you,
Hold it, Akagi!
What the hell are you doing there?!
Don't move an inch! I'm coming right now...
even though you hated carrying an umbrella
Not a chance!
See ya later!
Akagi-kun!
Is he even serious?
When you laugh...
One-two! One-two!
What are you staring at?
Your fly is down.
Must have done it unconsciously...
...will come
as a sequel to today
Captain, this is the guy.
Akagi Keijiro's son.
I don't know
I see, so you're...
what the future holds,
the son of the late, great boxer Akagi Keijiro...
but if I can walk with you
Jeez, why did I even bother trying to console him?
then that's good enough for now
Kusanagi-san...
A rainbow in my heart
Kids, kids, kids, kids, kids on street
He saw them...
When the rain stops
Kusanagi-senpai of the boxing club, of all people...!
I like watching rainbows together
Is he your boyfriend? Eiji.
No! Not at all. I don't even know him.
Really. E-Excuse me!
What a lovely girl...
I want to write her a letter.
Oh yes, I've heard some nasty rumors about you
The latest news about you
You had a jolly good time yesterday,
Holding hands and grinning with a fabulously cute girl
This town's turned into a rather gaudy place since I've been gone.
It was lollipop, Lolita, lonely day
I called you right away
I did it! I finally spoke to him.
Huh?
I spoke to Kusanagi-senpai from the boxing club!
Lollipop, Lolita, lonely day
I'm alone in my world
That all? Good, I guess.
You sound spiteful. Why's that?
I can't help feeling awfully deserted
What's with them still doing primitive sports like boxing in high school in this day and age?
That's what happens when you're not around
You say that, but how does your family make a living, again?
I wanna see you, I can't wait to see you
I won't ask for anything extra this time
Move it, gramps! Don't just crawl along!
Do you have a death wish?
I can't sleep alone! I'm too scared to sleep alone,
we have to stick together tonight, baby hold me tight!
You moron! What are you thinking,
riding a bike together on this narrow street?!
It's crowded enough as it is!
Think about other people!
I've got those crazy paisleys in my head
How can I respect the elderly when they're so nasty?
So showy, but so sad, what a pain!
Oh? You got something against me?
I told you off for being a jerk,
is that what angers you, huh?
Lollipop, Lolita, lonely day
So you're one of those who don't know how to admit their guilt?
Lollipop, Lolita
Geezer... I hope you have your will written!
Lonely day, lonely day
I'm stronger and more enduring now
Akagi-kun, you must cherish the elderly!
Akagi? Hey, punk, could you be by any chance related to the Akagi Gym?
But the limits are getting loose
It's my home!
Boom, you're knocked out!
Who the hell is he?
Oh boy, Keijiro must be turning in his grave
knowing his son is a good-for-nothing.
Caught you. And now...
Corkscrew!
Oh God, he did it...
Think about other people and try not to live too long, pops!
That punk... is the son
of the greatest boxer of all time,
the unparalleled genius puncher,
Akagi Keijiro...!
Ah! How regrettable... And painful.
Annoying...! And painful.
But still regrettable!
Ah, Eiji-chan!
Welcome back.
Sir!
Sup, Kojiro. Looking good.
Cut your blabber when I'm training.
You distract me.
Ooh! Scary.
Ah, Eiji!
No thanks, I get enough lecturing at school.
It's not that.
I wanted you to go meet our guest.
Guest?
Nogi-san, a remarkable man who trained your father...
Or rather, the man who raised him.
He should've been here by now...
Maybe he got lost on the way?
Could you go look for him at the station?
I-It was him...
Huh?
He's fine. Probably looking for some soothing suppository right now.
I wanna have something fun to do...
So, you're going to the Olympics?
Yes, I'll start by winning gold at the next Olympics in Barcelona,
then go pro and aim for the world championship.
He's so cool...
I guess I'm also one of the groupies now...
I hope he doesn't dislike the fickle girls.
He smiled at me!
No way! It was me!
Phew, he sure has a big mouth.
That guy is a prodigy, all right.
I've seen his match once,
and he's a natural technician.
Yeah, I heard that no one has ever landed a clear punch on him throughout his entire boxing career.
Wow, that's incredible.
Yeah, his boxing style reminds me of Akagi Keijiro's back in the day.
Who's that?
How could you be in this business if you don't know of Akagi?
Well, maybe he was a thing so long ago I can't remember it?
Akagi Keijiro,
he was a boxer like none other...
He hit, but was never hit back.
There's never been anybody else who's epitomized the ideal of boxing so perfectly.
Neither before, nor after him.
Nogi-san, it sounds to me like you still live for boxing.
I do. Go ahead and laugh at me for sticking with it this long.
But I want to see it
just one more time before I die...
Some genuine, blood-pumping boxing.
The times have changed a lot, Nogi-san.
A door that's about to close
A breath that's about to stop
L-Look, take it easy, okay?
What do you mean,
"I don't have to come anymore?"
And I have to take that subway
We're not some street thugs,
we're musicians!
No matter what it takes!
R-Right! Whenever the crowd boos or heckles us,
you jump in and start a brawl!
He's sleeping by the stairs again this morning
Besides, the owner doesn't like the idea of having a high-schooler in the band, you know.
A blissful smile on his scruffy face
So, no hard feelings,
that's just the way things are.
It's like he's mocking me
I get it. You don't want to have anything to do with me ever again.
Hey, hey, where is the exit?
I wonder where I'm going
Fine, but make sure you don't regret it.
Hey, hey, why is it so tight in here?
Make a sound, someone!
Moron! Who gives a damn?!
Everyone was fed up with his lousy guitar playing!
That's right! It's all power and no technique!
He only used the guitar for fighting.
The audience is sure to appreciate it. We'll have a real shot at landing a TV show audition!
What the hell is wrong with Tokyo
where you can't even buy a house?
Oops... You're still here, Eiji-chan?
"Oops?"
I'm just a...
Seriously! You guys have no spunk in you, outside of your hairstyles.
I've had enough of dealing with you too.
Hi.
You're cool, you know that?
You're posing with your long legs
But I saw the heels of your elevator shoes
I should've put my tongue in...
Just this once, I'll pretend I didn't see it
Senpai...
W-Wait... A-Aren't you rushing things?
It's a small favor I'm willing to give you
I love you, Senpai!
Stop that! It's outrageous!
Did you really become the Boxing Club manager to do something like this?!
My cool darlin', oh, my cool darlin'
No! Not just that!
My feelings for you are true!
Spreading playboy rumors,
you're just trying to impress me
This is not what high-school students should do!
My cool darlin', oh, my cool darlin'
What a pity... Young women these days
only want you for sex, sex, sex, before anything else!
I praised him once for his manly profile
and he's been looking to the side ever since
The gold medal and platonic love are my goals!
He looks pretty worked up for that title match.
Japan's champion finally accepted a challenge from him,
he's working himself harder than needed.
Hey! Don't stop there!
You need to follow that up with a left jab!
Well, in any case,
he's a gifted boxer—no more, no less.
Aren't you supposed to be suspended?
What are you playing at, you punk?
All while your big brother is busting his butt to reach his goal—don't you have any shame?!
No...
How long will you stay, pops?
Until I die!
Then hurry up and die.
I'm full of energy, no time to think about others
You just kiss me, and I'll punch anyone for you
Bad man...
It's still nothing!
Get crazy!
chance, chance, go crazy!
Move her to the bed!
On your knees!
Paint over the clock!!
No need to be so wasteful...
I'm bored. Damn it.
Summer's coming up...
I'd like to know your address.
M-My address?
Yes, your address. With the correct house number.
And don't forget the zip code.
I could do that, but...
You gonna write her a letter or what?
Akagi-kun!
That guy acts like a fossil!
Your fly's not down today, you idiot.
Marina is my woman.
Stop making passes at her.
D-Don't believe it!
I'm not!
Shut up! Come!
Why don't you smooch some punching bags?
I thought you loved them.
Hey! Akagi-kun!
Akagi Eiji... He is the first underclassman
to ever address me so disrespectfully.
I'll remember that.
I can feel it flowing, on this freezing night
I want to tell you, to engrave it in stone
your graceful coup d'etat
Into the Winterland
Where are you going, Eiji?
To Shigeyuki's.
Would you look at that!
All he does is fool around.
If you have nothing better to do,
why not help your brother spar?
You're the one who has nothing better to do—
picking on my every move!
Good evening.
K-Kusanagi?
We're only dreaming of a different life
Oh? This gym is nicer than I thought.
Oh, aren't you Kusanagi Naoya,
the high-school champion?
Like a notebook that you can't use up
What, Kusanagi?
You're right, it's him!
What's with all of you?
Is he really so famous?
Ah, and there's your older brother,
The video that plays on the CRT is a picture search
#3 lightweight in Japan,
Akagi Kojiro-san.
I saw your fight on TV once.
I got the impression that you were
a mediocre boxer for someone touted
I can't fast forward through this boring everyday
as the eldest son of the legendary Akagi Keijiro.
Oh no, I didn't mean any offense.
Hey boys, what you need is toughness
Hey, did you come here to start a fight?!
By no means! The other third-years have already retired from the club for exams.
I'm getting out of shape,
so I was hoping for a sparring session.
Hey girls, I'm not the same person I was yesterday, am I?
I'll spar with you if that's what you want,
Mr. High-School Champion.
But you have a title match coming up.
We wouldn't want you to get hurt now, do we?
I can feel it flowing...
T-That punk...
He's been fooling me all along!
Barging into someone's house and talking shit about them...?!
I can't stand bastards who don't know any manners!
You think you have any right to be saying that?!
Doesn't matter if you're competing inter-school or whatever,
you're still just a high-school amateur champion.
No reason to get all high-and-mighty!
There's no reason I couldn't beat the shit out of you if I wanted to. You got that?
Eiji! That's enough!
Boxing is not a street fight.
You need to know the rules and theory.
Tsk! Who said anything about boxing?
A street fight or whatever, bring it on!
No, I'll excuse myself.
It's embarrassing for a high-school student
to engage in uncivilized fighting.
You prick!
Eiji, cut it out!
I apologize again for my rude demeanor, Kojiro-san.
Good luck with your match.
Ah, Akagi-kun.
I won't forget that you knocked me down.
Oh? Did it hurt that much?
See you tomorrow at school.
I'd really prefer to never see you again!
Wh-What?! What, what, what, wha...
Get changed, punk.
We're going for road training.
W-What time is it? 5:30!
I'm going to sleep.
W-What are you doing? Get lost!
I'm not your plaything.
Don't fuck with me, you punk! You're going to be a boxer and that's it! No turning back now!
Wh-Who are you to decide what I'll do with my life? I'm not a boxer, and will never...
Don't you wanna become the world champion?
W-World champion?
That's right.
You've got the makings of one.
And I'm prepared to spend what's left of my life
to make you a champion.
Humph! You can keep that life to yourself.
I will never be a boxer.
What will you be, then?! You got anything else you wanna do, punk? What can you do at all?
I don't know, all right?!
But definitely not this!
I wouldn't be able to eat what I want,
drink booze, or go out with girls.
And I'll be dirt poor until I make it as world champion.
Even if I do start making good money,
I'll have to retire before I'm 30.
What am I supposed to do for the rest of my life?
Cut my hair short and run a ramen shop?
Gimme a break, will you?
Thanks for the offer,
but I'll pass on that kinda life!
Don't you have a dream?!
Akagi Eiji
Hey, Akagi!
Wake up!
Akagi! Go run 10 laps in the yard!
That'll wake you up!
The melody at the end sounds a little sad
Shit, this is all the old fart's fault...
I think I might be getting
a little bored with him
But I don't really
Hey, look! Can you believe it?
Need love to be
Ugh. The freshmen girls are laughing at me. I'm so pathetic!
eternal
Next, Kusanagi-san!
Okay!
The bed springs creak
like in a TV drama
I can't give up on this thrill
Of playing games with you
Deep inside,
I'm just a bit
nervous
For a little bit,
So, what do you say?
I hesitate
Oh, right... Well...
Love is sweet, exciting, tearful,
You feel guilty towards Akagi-kun?
No! He's nothing more than a childhood friend. It's the truth.
an elusive fantasy...
So... Does it really have to be pen friendship?
I mean, I get it when the people
who live far away are doing it...
But if we go to the same school,
exchanging letters is kinda... funny.
Kinda weird.
Why?
Huh?
First, you exchange letters,
and eventually, perhaps, diaries...
After that, the first date happens.
Isn't that the natural course of a relationship between a man and a woman?
Ah, so that's how you see it?
What do you say? Do you agree?
I-I do. For now.
That's a delight to hear.
By the way, would you like to come
to the boxing club room after school today?
There'd be something for you to see.
Huh? For me?
Akagi-kun. Won't you come with us for a moment?
Boxing
Club
Room
So you've gathered everyone
to take revenge on me for yesterday?
So much for the athletic honor.
Revenge? Nonsense.We'll settle it with a match. You wouldn't deny me that honor, would you?
How many times do I have to say
that I despise boxing?
What the fuck is wrong with you people?
Well, seeing as the audience is already here...
I don't need
Don't disappoint me.
Just let me be clear,
I'm gonna fight a street fight.
any explanations from you
Very well. As you wish.
But I'll make your heart race
Hm. Anyone here to put this glove on me?
Stop that, Akagi-kun!
Do you even know who you're up against?!
If it's just a coincidence,
if there was no special reason
What are you doing here?
You too, Kusanagi-san! Why do you have to do this, knowing he's an amateur?
For us to meet, well, that's fine too
Challenging someone to a duel—
I thought you were better than that!
I drink the rose wine
With those massive gloves,
he can't kill Eiji.
that tastes like
Huh?
cherry blossoms on your lips,
You old fart!
Where the fuck did you come from?!
No man can run away from his fate.
And then I start talking to you,
Listen, you!
Shut up and gimme your arm.
but we can never reach a deal
Better get used to seeing me around now.
We'll be together until either of us dies.
For the rest of our lives!
What then?
To hell with it!
I don't need anything from you!
I'm just fine
You and your jokes are nauseating!
This is the last time
Yet I keep going in circles
Akagi-kun, you don't have to do this.
Don't stop night
Just watch me, Marina-chan.
I've waited long enough!
Akagi-kun, what about your headgear and mouthpiece?
Didn't I tell you this is a street fight?
I don't need them.
Go for it, Akagi-kun! Good luck!
How's this for a start?!
Your legwork is a complete mess.
They call you a natural technician.
No wonder you're good at escaping.
Whoa! Scary!
Doesn't hurt much, does it?
These are 16 oz gloves.
Not much...
Yours are normal 10 oz gloves for tournament use.
Those do hurt. Try to hit me!
What? Who asked you to give me a handicap?!
This handicap was my own doing,
out of consideration.
With your cold eyes,
Damn you!
...And also confidence.
you humbly refuse to give in to my kindness
Come on, Akagi-kun!
This ain't a game of tag!
Shit...
There is something else
I wanted to tell you.
If you wipe away your lipstick,
I'll give you a passionate kiss
The other day,
I asked Takasugi Marina-kun to go out with me.
And she said yes.
What the hell?!
Marina! How could you do that while you're with me?!
If whimsy is also a charm,
B-But I'm not with you!
Let me get this straight now.
then love is a game
Starting today, Marina-kun and I
are in a lifelong relationship!
What then?
To hell with it!
Now you're only going to address her respectfully!
I don't need anything from you!
Wow, Akagi can't even catch his breath...
This is the last time!
I've got to stop this!
Don't.
Yet I keep going in circles
Once more!
A woman mustn't interfere with a man's affairs.
This is the last time
Wh-Who is this girl?
I don't need anything from you!
I'm just fine
To hell with it!
It's been 3 minutes.
Why no bell, Tamura?
Yet I keep going in circles
Oh, my bad. Want me to ring it now?
This is the last time
He needs a rest.
To hell with it!
You jackass!
Pretty sure I told you
I was gonna fight street style!
Those are 10 oz blows...
Isn't it getting a bit dangerous?
Yes! Go for it, Eiji!
Keep hitting, give him no quarter!
Remember that feeling of hitting someone hard with your glove!
Mister! Don't be so irresponsible!
We have to stop him, or Naoya will die!
That's it! Go to hell!
Don't get cocky, you brat!
I was trying to act gentlemanly, and this is what I get?
You street thug!
Do you even realize who I am?
I'm the future world champion!
I won't tolerate bratty kids like you
talking to me disrespectfully!
Are you listening?
Huh? Did I make myself clear?
Now, it's your turn—go straight to hell!
Akagi-kun...
Shit, gotta stop Naoya!
I heard he's lost again!
Eiji's daddy loses all the time!
He's a failure of a boxer!
No! He used to be very strong once!
What does it matter if he's a worthless boxer now?
Yes! Worthless! Ha-ha!
Don't make fun of daddy!
Akagi-kun, stop!
He's awake.
I see. So Kusanagi took me for a ride...
With 16 oz gloves the size of a cushion!
Shut it, geezer!
When we left the movie theater,
I'm sorry.
Losing his temper like that
is uncharacteristic of my big bro.
it started pouring and we got soaked
Big bro?
Looks like we have Kusanagi's little sister here.
The four of us ran to the entrance
I appreciate that last time!
Oh, you know each other?
of the underground mall
Only if having kissed once counts. Am I right?
As we started to pack up to go home,
Oh, is that so? I see now.
Please don't let me interrupt you any longer, then.
tired from swimming, you said to me,
"If this town is the sea,
Here, your textbooks!
God! Can't believe I've been worried
for someone like him!
then let's become the pirates in it"
Well, take care, then.
We are the pirates
H-Hey, wait!
The selfish pirates
How was it?
Why is it that I always have to be
What?
How did it feel to fight on the ring for the first time?
with someone to feel safe?
Damn it!
I was just a punching bag for him.
Why can't things go the way I want them to?
I've been boxing since elementary school.
Always fighting with a cool head.
Mindful of how much damage I'd done,
or how many more punches I needed to deal to defeat my opponent.
Never before had I lost my cool in a match or miscalculated.
But today, for the first time,
I fought mindlessly.
Heedless of the audience,
with no calculation...
All I knew was that I had to beat up the guy in front of me, and my body moved on its own.
I can now see clearly that each punch I landed on him made me feel better.
It was the first time something so disgraceful happened to me. I'm ashamed.
He's exactly the man I pictured him to be.
When I first saw his gig,
I was more moved by his passion than his playing.
After that, more than anything,
I wanted to see him box.
I knew he was going to be up-and-coming boxer material.
But instead, you ended up with a beaten-up one.
Boxing magazines
I took interest in him because he was the son of Akagi Keijiro.
So, I decided to give your idea a shot
and let him try boxing with me.
But it's no good.
He's just a rabid dog.
He doesn't have the makings of a boxer.
Naoya, could you take this order over to Tokita-san at the office center?
Sure.
So sorry to make a future champion
work at food delivery...
Don't mention it, Mother.
It's my job. Later!
Looks like things are heating up...
A TV show just for boredom,
A magazine just for laughs
A love that comes through force,
An ordinary melody,
but something's missing
After God knows how many sad movies you've watched
you still expect a happy ending?
Alas, that's not possible
Yeah!
Akagi-kun, you can drive, right?
What was that?
A driver's license—you have one, right?
Way, now you're riding on a wind
Why would I?
What?! S-Stop the bike! It's brand new!
I just bought it! Stop!
that won't carry you to tomorrow
Please, stop!
Way, now you should embrace
dreams that are bigger than they seem
Kojiro, tomorrow's the big day.
Are you nervous?
No, somehow, I feel very calm today.
I've done everything I had to do.
No matter what happens now, I won't regret it.
What will you eat after the fight?
A steak this big!
That is, if you want to be a man
I'm not joking anymore!
The city is a money game that is all smoke and mirrors
Stop I said!
If your keep your eyes closed, even love will become crooked
Ah! Watch forward! Forward!
Way, now you're riding on a wind
that won't carry you to tomorrow
Way, now you
should embrace
dreams that are bigger than they seem
Dreams that are bigger than they seem!
I'm sorry. I was going to tell you, eventually.
But you have boxing now, don't you?
Sounds like you had it all planned.
Why do you want me to box so badly?
I want to see your true self,
burning on the ring.
You weird woman,
stop sticking your nose into others' business!
No training today
Really, Kojiro and the others left already?
I'm dragging my baggage from yesterday,
waiting for things to get even worse today
Japan Title
Winner
All the fancy gatherings and threads that adorn the streets,
and we're just a bunch of bums
This atmosphere, this smell—
like in the good old days!
Hello.
You've come to see the match too, Marina-chan?
Are you alone?
No, I'm with him.
Run around on the street all day long
Oh, you're here with Kusanagi-kun?
You'd make a good couple.
Please don't tease me like that.
By the way, where's Eiji-kun?
Run around on the street all day long
He never comes to these.
He could at least come
to a match that's so important for his brother...
If I open my eyes, I'll no longer be able to see the dreams
What's with that guy, seriously?
Hey Dad, if I'd grown up watching you in your prime like Kojiro did,
I don't want to say it, because I don't want to live in the memories
maybe I'd have wanted to be a boxer all along.
But when I was growing up,
We only want the heat
I'll always be the same, Baby
you were already on the wane and couldn't win a single match anymore.
The way you always looked—
so gloomy and intimidating—
sparked a resolve in my young heart
to never become a boxer.
We only want the heat
I'm still asking for the very same thing
It's the only thing that keeps my dreams alive
It connected! He did it again!
The challenger, Akagi keeps landing
perfect body blows!
Tonight's title match for Japan's Lightweight Champion exceeded all expectations!
I walk the streets with a cold face,
The challenger, Akagi Kojiro, is giving the champion,
the crowd favorite Taba Takeshi,
also known as the K.O. King, a serious run for his money right now!
always trying to reach the same place
Stop!
Akagi was downed in the 1st and 3rd rounds, but he held his ground well after that.
And now, midway through the 6th round,
he knocked the champion down with a combo of right and left hooks!
The champion's aides can't hide their frustration
with the unexpected struggle.
It was an intense and thrilling match
that defied all pre-fight predictions of an early KO victory.
A straight from Taba!
And now a counter from Akagi!
Neither side is willing to budge!
Wow, you're not bad, brother.
Round 8!
Round 8    Time Left: 2:59
Whoa! Akagi throws a punch as the bell still rings!
Akagi, known for simply outboxing his opponents,
must go all-out on the offensive tonight!
Two more punches!
Taba's fighting back!
Do it! Hit him hard, Kojiro!
The fighters shower each other in punches— Ah!
We all felt this one!
Taba's down! Taba's down!
He did it!
1,
2,
3,
4...
Fight!
Akagi unleashes a flurry of punches on Taba!
The champion is on the ropes!
That's it! Wipe the floor with him!
Yes! Show no mercy!
Goddammit! So close!
E-Eiji-chan...
Eiji...
You're doing great, Ko-chan!
Thanks.
Hey, big bro.
Knock him out, won't you?
Look who's come to see one of my fights for the first time.
Yeah. You're looking super-cool!
What's wrong?
C'mon, sit down.
Yeah...
I have to make sure I don't regret anything...
You got this, bro!
Do your best, Kojiro!
I have to make sure I don't regret anything...
No regrets...
I said some rude things to Kojiro earlier.
I can't go meet him in person now.
Please tell him that it was a great fight.
See you later.
Senpai...
Retire?
N-No way!
He has a detached retina now...
If he told us earlier,
I wouldn't have let him fight.
You still have a whole life to live
after you retire from boxing...
Only a man can truly grasp the drive to chase his dreams,
even if it means risking his eyesight.
Who are you to tell us that?
Well, we don't know for certain that I'll go blind, and even if I do, I'll get by with my other eye.
Hey! Did you come to see me?
It's over now.
Huh? Uh-huh?!
R-Right... Allow me to introduce
Imaizumi Reiko-san.
Nice to meet you.
Look at that! He pretended to be disinterested in girls, but really,
he's been doing his homework too, right?
Come on, Eiji!
He's been living his youth to the fullest!
One youth ends here.
But another one begins...
The second I look away, you try to act cool.
Take care, then.
I'll be leaving soon.
Hey, geezer...
What is it?
I'm so damn bored right now...
Maybe I should give boxing a shot, after all?
What? I didn't quite hear that, Eiji!
It's so bright...
If you ever need a little giggle, why don't you come with me
to an amusement park in the middle of the day?
In the weekday afternoon, I'm sure it'll be just the two of us
I want you to listen to my troubles under the Ferris wheel
I'll sit down on the grass and listen to you for a while
Without even changing out of our uniforms,
we'll always come here right on time
Ah, even if I had wings,
I wouldn't fly in the sky
I still haven't said even half
of what I wanted to say
I'm riding on a merry-go-round
When I do that, I love you
That's when I feel that I'm alive
Do you remember what you once said to me?
"You can't live your life as carefree as a kangaroo"
I laughed at you that day,
but for some reason I can't laugh today
Sometimes you seem to me like a philosopher
Sometimes, I seem like one myself
Even if I don't have any luck being sentimental,
I'm fine just being with you
You know, even if I had wings,
I wouldn't fly in the sky
I want to talk to you like this for some more
I'm riding on a merry-go-round
When I do that, I love you
Maybe we're dreaming too much
I'm riding on a merry-go-round
When I do that, I love you
B
Be
Bec
Beca
Becau
Becaus
Because
Because I
Because I'
Because I'm
Because I'm r
Because I'm ri
Because I'm rid
Because I'm ridi
Because I'm ridin
Because I'm riding
Because I'm riding i
Because I'm riding it
Because I'm riding it t
Because I'm riding it to
Because I'm riding it too
I do that to save you
Because I'm riding it too!
Everybody's riding on the merry-go-round
Theatrical Trailer
From the author of "Susume!! Pirates" and "Stop, Hibari-kun"
Hisashi Eguchi
(published by Shueisha Jump Comics)
I'm riding on a merry-go-round
Directed by Nishikubo Mizuho
("Red Photon Zillion" and "Heaven Wars Shurato")
Theme song by Kawamura Kaori
(Pony Canyon)
When I do that, I love you
Original translation
Translation check, songs
Encoding
QC
Special thanks
Random Masters
Perevodildo
WOWmd
Eternal_Blizzard, WOWmd
Unowen
I'm riding on a merry-go-round
I want to see your true self, burning on the ring.
"Eiji"