Those guys are total morons!
Picking a fight with Matsugoro of all people.
He’s the kind of guy
who doesn’t know how to hold back.
Oh man... Guess it's our cue already.
Ogami Matsugoro
This place's gonna be haunted for ages now.
Hey, offer them a prayer
so they can pass on in peace.
Oyako High School
'Sup.
'Morn.
Height: 188 cm.
Weight: 96 kg.
Special skill: Praying over the half-dead to help them move on.
Ogami Matsugoro.
Also known as "Praying Matsugoro."
We're really charging down the Victory Road.
Yeah, we’re a newly established school​,
but thanks to Matsugoro, our rep’s skyrocketing.
Exactly—just hearing the name "Oyako High"
is enough to make people flinch.
But hey, Matsugoro,
you better keep your guard up.
Yeah, around here, “Take down Matsugoro”
has become the rallying cry.
Seriously, watch out
for sneak attacks and cheap shots.
They can come at me from any direction.
I'll pray over every last one of them.
Uh, sorry to kill
an entertaining discussion, boys,
but you do realize we're in the middle
of morning assembly?
Oyako High School
Oh? Our bad, we’ll be eating real quiet-like.
Just go on about your thing.
Dammit... If it wasn't for the quota,
they'd long be out of here!
Principal! Your speech! Speech!
So you're Matsugoro, huh?
We’re with Nanko High.
We hear you’ve got quite the attitude
for a first-year punk.
Don't forget that you're just an upstart
from a new school!
Less talk—
More fists!
You punks! This ain’t over yet!
That’s awful...
Just as we finally fixed it up!
S-Sorry about that,
but it wasn’t on purpose...
Go away!
You’re in the yakuza, aren’t you?
I don’t care what cowardly tactics you use, I won't give in!
Hold on a minute, I’m a student!
A first-year high schooler.
Liar.
No way a high schooler
has a face that weathered.
L-Leave it alone.
It seems you had
a good reason to think so.
Yes... No, I mean...
Sorry I said something so rude earlier.
You really aren’t with the yakuza, are you?
Nah.
I’m Nagasaki Koume.
First year at Yowa Girls’ School.
I’m the daycare director’s daughter.
Oh, I’m Ogami Matsugoro from Oyako High.
It was me who punched through your wall.
Punched?
Yeah. It’s kind of my specialty—
when I fight, my punches always swoosh!
Just go home.
You really aren’t yakuza,
but I still hate people who think
they can force everything through violence.
I absolutely hate them!
Oyako High School
Yo, Matsugoro, I heard you got hassled by some Nanko guys yesterday.
We should head over there today
and settle the score.
Gotta make sure it ends clean.
Yeah.
Do you guys know
the Misono Daycare Center?
Yeah, totally! I used to go there.
Same here, that’s where I went too.
Yeah, but apparently, the land under that area has shot up in value,
and the Kodan Family yakuza are moving in.
They’re ordering the daycare to shut down
and hand over the property.
It’s outrageous of course,
but that’s how those thugs work—
they’re using intimidation and daily harassment to force them out.
The director’s now too scared to come to work,
and I heard she was hospitalized
from the stress.
That’s messed up.
I hate violence! I hate it!
Matsugoro!
What’s up, Sato?
Actually, I need a favor...
From me?
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
Here, take a look.
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
New store opening
Arm wrestling competition
Free ramen for a whole year
Huh? Sato, didn’t you already run some kind of grand reopening campaign recently?
Yeah, that’s the one! "Finish our Monster Ramen and it’s free" deal.
Well, that’s where the trouble started.
Once we launched it,
a bunch of maniacs showed up.
They kept asking for seconds and thirds.
And now they come every day
because they’re hooked.
But if we shut it down, we might get harassed—
plus, we’re already barely scraping by.
Oh? So you’re changing the campaign?
But won’t that backfire?
Giving out free ramen for a whole year—
if you lose, you’re finished.
But we’ve got him, don’t we?
The man with the golden arm.
Please, Matsugoro!
Win this thing for us!
I don’t wanna live in a world where the shop shuts down and I can’t eat ramen anymore.
All right, leave it to me!
Heck yeah, he said yes!
Now I can look forward
to lunch every day again!
Okay, but first, let’s work up an appetite.
Go grab the tools from the workshop!
All right, let’s do this!
Time to return the favor!
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
Misono
Daycare
Center
How did it come to this?
Why do punks like us
hafta do some community service?
Let’s shape up and get this battle started!
I mean, look at this chair—
got some nerve, right?
So here’s what we do:
like this, and this, and then—this!
Ogami-san!
Um… what exactly are you—
Yo, you guys better get pumped up!
This is merely our warm-up
before the real deal!
That goddamn swing set
over there’s looking cocky too!
Ogami-san…
Really? Is this all for that girl?
Lovesickness turns people into idiots.
But he's already an idiot!
Big sis!
You guys came after all?
Come inside—come on!
It's so clean and nice!
All right! Classroom's all done, then.
Thank you so much, Ogami-san.
What you're actually doing
is fixing my dream.
This place means everything to me.
My mom’s the director, so I’ve been here since I was little—playing, learning.
I love kids,
so I want to become a nursery teacher
and spend my days here with everyone.
That’s my dream.
Then you'd better stand fast.
Seriously, you just need to turn everything into a fistfight, don’t you?
I wish I had a larger vocabulary...
Ogami-san, why do you like fighting so much?
It’s not that I like it.
It’s just the only thing I've ever done.
Take fighting away,
and I’m just some idiot.
That’s not true at all!
Kodan Family?!
What do you want?! Get out of here!
No, you get out!
You’re the ones who need to scram.
This land ain’t yours anymore.
The director agreed to sign it away,
here's her seal—see?
No way…
That can't be right!
You threatened my mother at the hospital, didn’t you?!
Once we’ve got that stamped form,
the place is as good as ours.
And anyway, what’s the point of keeping
some failing daycare running?
Exactly. So what if it’s all bulldozed?
It doesn’t matter.
You bastards—
Stop it!
Koume-san?
Stop it! I hate violence!
I absolutely hate it!
Violence just tears apart everything—
people, things... Dreams!
Don't shiver,
I'll fix this as well.
Matsugoro-kun...
Hey, let me see that paper again.
Huh?
Look at it all you want—
it’s got the stamp, plain as day.
You idiot!
What the hell are you doing
to a legal document?!
Matsugoro-kun!
Stop! We’ll leave and send you
the replacement paper! Please!
No way!
You can’t do that, Koume-san.
It’s your dream, right? Then you don’t just throw it away like it’s nothing.
Matsugoro-kun…
You jerk...
Kid’s got some real guts!
Hurry up and spit out our paper!
Stop! Please, I’m begging you!
Stupid bitch!
Get the hell outta here!
Koume-san!
Come on!
You like to endure it, huh?!
If you want me to vomit,
do it like this!
What the hell’s your problem?!
I’m the Praying Matsugoro!
I'll offer a prayer
for you all to go to hell!
Don’t mess with us!
Flank him!
Why don’t you just die already?!
Koume-san, are you okay?!
No…
Stay away from me…
Koume-san…
Stay away!
You're just like them!
You're no different from those guys!
You hate violence, right...
Sis
It's all messy again...
But the big brothers
will fix it up again, right?
They’ll come back, right?
That big brother—
he’s not like those Yakuza guys.
Because he didn’t
break anything—he fixed it!
He’s not the same, right?
I guess...
He’s not the same after all.
Kodan      Family
You nitwit!
You let him destroy that important document,
got your ass handed to you by one guy,
and you call yourself yakuza?!
We’re sorry, Boss. But that guy was
a total monster—he was crazy strong.
Big build, terrifying punch,
and those bloodthirsty eyes…
I’m telling you,
he’s definitely from a rival gang.
He fought back like a beast—
no ordinary man can do that!
Tch. Thinks he’s hot shit, huh…
Boss,
perhaps it’s best if we take
a step back and feel things out.
Would you mind letting me handle this one?
Fine. Go ahead.
Much obliged.
Sato's Ramen
Ready—Go!
Damn, that’s the 60th one today!
Sorry to dump this on you.
Don’t sweat it. Just treat me to some ramen afterward and we're even.
He's here. That’s the guy.
Word is, this shop’s not long for this world.
Matsugoro, be careful.
From what I dug up, this Hasegawa guy
competed at the national level in judo.
If you’re gonna back out, now’s the time.
Ready...
Go!
Bastard...
Matsugoro!
Persistent bastard.
But let’s see if you can handle my secret weapon.
Quit stalling and show me what you’ve got!
Alright, then—this is it!
Now!
Matsugoro!
Damn, this guy just won’t go down!
Matsugoro, that’s enough!
I’m sorry for dragging you into this.
Don’t be an idiot!
If I lost to a clown like that, I’d be the laughingstock for the next three years!
That big mouth of yours is still running, huh?
Because of him, I...
I...
I angered her again!
Man, Matsugoro really
wiped the floor with that guy.
No way I’m ever going up against him.
Not in a million years.
What is it?
Wha?
Koume-san?
This Sunday’s our school’s cultural festival.
I was wondering if maybe
you would like to come?
S-Sure!
Koume-san!
Let’s dance together, okay?
Dance...
Hooray!
All right, step forward with your left,
shift your weight back to the right.
Good—left foot to the side, a little to the back.
Now shift your weight back to the left.
Next! Who's next?
Come on! Come forth, don't dawdle!
Want me to "pray" for you?!
Move! It was you who said
only western and ballroom dancing counts!
You take responsibility!
Education is dead!
Tsk. Weaklings...
I can make do without help
from losers like you!
I wish he'd just said that
from the start!
Not bad, huh?
And finish!
My cha-cha-cha is impeccable!
Yowa School Cultural Festival
Matsugoro-kun, welcome!
Thanks for coming.
No, it’s nothing.
My, Nagasaki-san, you brought your father?
Want me to "pray" you, you old hag?!
E-Excuse me?
Please, just promise
you won’t use any violence today.
Pinky promise!
Be quiet
in the hall
Confectionery
Free handmade cookies
Saburo Kitajima
Classical Music Club
The dance party will start soon.
Those who want to participate,
please move to the venue.
Wow! Finally, the dances!
Ah, right. Matsugoro-kun, you probably don't know ant ballroom dancing?
No, just leave it all to me,
whether it’s Jitterbug or Tango!
Phew, that’s a relief.
Matsugoro-kun, I’ll be at the hall.
Guess all I can manage is the cha-cha-cha.
Can’t help it. I’ll just wiggle
my way out of the rest somehow.
Really?
Hey, how many girls did you pick up?
Hmm? About four or five.
Lame. That’s why I hate girls’ schools.
If it were another girls’ school,
I’d be swimming in dates.
Well, well, no need to rush.
The main event is still the dance party.
I see.
Yeah, gotta set the mood
and then take them out for a walk all at once.
Exactly, gotta polish up for that.
Wh-What's up with these guys?
Yowa Girls’ School Dance Hall
All right, Jitterbug time! Let’s dance.
J-Jitterbug?
U-Uh, my stomach suddenly hurts...
Huh, you okay?
It's Cha-cha-cha!
I’m going to shine in the Cha-cha-cha!
Come on... Come on, put it on fast!
The hunt is on!
Now, which girl should I pick?
Next up is the Square Rumba.
Matsugoro-kun?
Uh, my foot hurts now...
Really?
Next is the Waltz.
Uh... My head...
Next is the Rumba.
Uh... My neck...
Next is the Blues.
My nose!
Cha-cha-cha, Cha-cha-cha!
Next up is the Cha-cha-cha.
All right, Koume-san!
Koume-san!
Where does it hurt this time?
Matsugoro-kun, you idiot.
All right, it’s Cha-cha-cha time.
Let’s go all out and keep it bright!
I hate you, Matsugoro-kun.
You promised we'd dance together!
What’s wrong?
No, nothing at all.
If you’re sad,
I’d be the one to comfort you.
Ah, uh...
Please stop!
That douchebag!
Violence is absolutely
forbidden, remember?
Be more honest with your feelings.
L-Let me go!
Come on, why resist it?
Kyaa! Hey, hey!
Whoa there!
Violence is not allowed!
Matsugoro-kun!
I-I remember!
Next is the Tango! It’s up-tempo,
so beginners, please sit this one out!
Won't you please be my dance partner?
Huh?
What...
What's this...
Your steps are all over the place!
No doubt about it!
I've only come here
to "pray" you down!
Koume-san, are you mad?
Of course I am!
I told you violence is a no-go!
That was just dancing.
Lies! You totally messed up the venue!
You broke both promises.
If you didn’t want to dance,
you should have said so from the start!
I was so worked up,
really looking forward to it.
I was all excited,
and now I feel like an idiot.
If you hated it,
you should’ve told me so!
Huh?
Zoinks...
Is this...?
Sorry. The truth is I don’t know
the first thing about ballroom dances.
I tried, but Cha-cha-cha
was all I could manage.
I'm sorry.
Then let’s practice now for next year!
All right, starting with the Cha-cha-cha.
Look, no matter what,
my heart is with "Pro Golfer Tokiko."
Sato's Ramen
She’s amazing! She’s out there wailing on folks with a 5-iron, no joke.
No, no, if we’re talking preferences,
mine's with "Commando Girl Akemi!"
If you get hit by the bazooka,
you’re flying for sure.
Hm... Feels like they’ve
used up all their tricks.
What will they come at us with next?
Matsugoro.
Who’s this Ogami Matsugoro?
Come out!
What, scared stiff and can’t even speak?
I’m Matsugoro, but who are you?
I’m Rolling Okyo,
the leader of the Purple Division
of the Nanko Ladies Eight-Wheel Rampage Gang.
Ogami Matsugoro,
you’re marked for death!
I don’t fight women.
And I don't remember having a beef with you,
a stranger from nowhere.
You don’t remember?
Don’t make me laugh!
It was exactly two weeks ago,
at this spot, at this hour,
when you ruined my little brother’s life!
Two weeks ago?
That was the day we did arm wrestling.
Don’t tell me you forgot this face.
My brother had an important
judo match the next day,
but you broke his arm
and he got kicked off the team!
Since then, he went downhill and became a delinquent.
Even if he’s a screw-up,
he’s my one and only dear brother.
Matsugoro, I’m gonna cut you to pieces!
What’s this?
Not again...
What should I say to get them to leave?
Purple Division, line up!
Matsugoro, it’s time to pay your dues!
Combat technique number one:
Dancing Phantoms!
Let’s go!
Yeah!
Charge!
Hey, you’re going too far with the pranks!
I warned you,
we're not kidding!
Matsugoro, what are you doing?
Give 'em hell!
Don’t be stupid!
You think I’d fight a woman?
Where will they attack next?
I can see it!
Leader!
Yoshie!
Ahead is the main street!
It’s dangerous!
Sorry, I need to borrow this!
Help!
Fucking idiots!
You all right?
Look, if you’re a girl,
use the knives for cooking.
Matsugoro...
If you’re a girl,
use knives for cooking.
Sis, you look happy today.
Huh?
You must’ve found someone you like.
Is it true you’re in love with Matsugoro?
Just rumors, right?
It’s not true, is it?
No, it’s true.
Sis...
Hiromi, I feel bad about you,
but I'm serious.
I've fallen for his manliness.
I like guys who are manly.
Come on, you must be hungry, right?
Let’s eat.
'Sup!
Oh? That’s rare—
short jacket in this weather?
My stomach’s cold; I don’t like it.
But my long jacket is in tatters right now.
Yeah, figures.
But at least those ladies
gave me the first good laugh in a while.
And the reason is...
Purple Division is here!
Yeah, this!
We’re the Purple Division messengers,
here to deliver Sister Kyoko’s message.
Huh?
"Hey, Matsugoro!
Thanks for saving me the other day.
To thank you, I'll be waiting
at the "Apple Forest" at 5.
If you’re a man, don’t run away.
That’s all."
Over and out!
Now your short jacket
is going to be in tatters too!
Apple Forest
Ogami Matsugoro, first generation leader
of the Oyako High gang.
From elementary school to now,
many gang incidents.
The most notable one is the Misono Daycare Center incident, involving the Kodan Family.
All three gang members
were out for three months.
Misono Daycare Center?
Nagasaki Koume, first year at Yowa Girls’ High,
the daycare director’s daughter.
Met Matsugoro over the turf war
between the Kodan Family and the daycare.
The incident with the Kodan Family seems to be Matsugoro showing his feelings for his girlfriend,
Nagasaki Koume?
Hey.
What’s with that outfit?
It’s the only winter uniform I have left.
If you’re gonna pick a fight,
aim for my face, up here.
Huh?
Who said this was a street fight?
I sent my messengers to you, didn't I?
So it wasn't a call for a duel?
Here.
A custom-tailored winter jacket.
With Carver Zenbei's masterpiece
"Pine Tree and Dragon."
This is a thank you for the other day.
Please accept it.
Matsugoro, I’m sorry!
Hey.
I heard that it was actually
my brother who was at fault.
But I misunderstood and caused a big mess.
I don’t expect you to forgive me just like that,
but could you please at least accept this?
Look up.
I can’t accept this.
No good, after all?
It’s not about that.
Then, what about my feelings?
If someone hurts a person important to me,
I’d fight back too.
What you did wasn’t dishonorable at all.
That’s the sister of the guy
who lost the arm wrestling match?
Yeah, she came for revenge,
but couldn’t bring herself to hate me.
She said I'm a good guy.
A good guy?
A good guy, huh?
All right.
Matsugoro.
Hey!
What’s up? What are you doing here?
Let me introduce you:
Nagasaki Koume.
Nice to meet you.
I’m Nagasaki Koume,
first year at Yowa Girls’ High.
I’m Hasegawa Kyoko.
She's cute!
Matsugoro, I need to talk to you for a bit.
Apple Forest
What’s this about?
I felt bad about what I did to you,
so I looked into the incident
at Misono Nursery with the Kodan Family.
You did it for that girl, right?
You told me the other day:
if someone hurts someone important to you, you’d fight back.
Is she that "someone important?"
I see.
Matsugoro!
Huh?
You’re the Praying Matsugoro, right?
What the hell do you want?
Asshole! You'll pay now!
Get him!
Now we're square.
Not bad!
Golden Yasha
Golden Yasha?
These guys suddenly started throwing their weight around lately.
They do everything—
extortion, bookmaking, even selling drugs.
They’re just punks.
But there are rumors they’re connected to a yakuza gang behind the scenes.
Thanks for helping me deal with them.
Would you let me be your friend?
Of course.
I’m home. Huh?
Sis, you're not here?
What’s wrong, Sis?
It’s unusual to see you cry.
It’s nothing.
Report on Matsugoro
Is it Matsugoro?
Did he do something to you?
It was so inconsiderate of me!
I gave myself false hopes
when he already had a girlfriend that lovely.
Girlfriend?
When you really fall for someone,
refusal is the hardest to take.
Report on Matsugoro
It’s the most painful!
Sis, I’m heading out for a bit.
I just remembered something important.
Hiromi? No way...
Yes, that’s right.
We’ve uncovered the background
of that amateur Matsugoro,
and we know his main weakness too.
Surprisingly, he’s connected
to the nursery girl.
This is killing two birds with one stone.
Yes.
Yeah.
Understood.
Leave the rest to me, Boss.
By the way, Hasegawa Hiromi, right?
You've said before that you've got a score to settle with Matsugoro.
Isn't that why you joined our group?
Well then, let’s shake things up
for your Matsugoro.
Sis, do you still need help carrying stuff?
Yeah, still more to carry.
You understand the plan, right?
Leave it to us.
Here.
Nagasaki-san, there’s a delivery for you.
Coming! Take it upstairs, okay?
Sure.
Okay. Now for your part, as planned.
With this, both Matsugoro
and the nursery are done for.
I wonder if my eyes are still red.
Sis!
What is it, messenger squad?
Kyoko, I thought you were
better than this!
No matter how much
you love Matsugoro...
Sis... You've really
crossed the line this time!
Hey, what's this about?
Don’t play dumb!
We know Hiromi-kun together with the Golden Yasha snatched that girl Koume!
Didn't you orchestrate it?
Hold on, tell me the full story.
Kyoko, you didn’t know?
Then why would Hiromi-kun
do such a thing?
Sis, I’m heading out for a bit.
I just remembered something important.
That dumbfuck!
How could he!
Kyoko!
Matsugoro absolutely mustn't find out!
Whoa! Awesome!
This is tank-level stuff!
This is gonna be a record breaker!
It’s serious, people!
The daycare is burning!
What?
Move, move!
Big bro!
Is everyone safe?
Yeah! It was real scary!
Koume-san—what about her?
Someone came!
After that, she disappeared
and the fire broke out!
So Koume-san is not here?
Matsugoro!
What?!
Koume-san was taken by the gang?!
Kyoko said not to tell anyone!
She went there all on her own!
Those guys aren’t the kind of people
she can take down by herself!
Matsugoro, please! Hurry!
You...
You idiot!
Sis...
This is the one
who’s Matsugoro’s girl, huh?
She’s kinda cute, actually.
Too good for a guy like him.
When Matsugoro comes,
tear him apart, okay?
Yeah.
We might as well use her
to kill time while she's out cold.
Let’s enjoy ourselves until he shows up.
Hold it right there!
If you so much as touch that girl,
Rolling Okyo will make you pay for it!
You...!
Sis!
Sis, why...? Ouch!
You cretin!
I never thought you’d be this stupid.
Did you really think doing this
would make me happy?
Kyoko-san?
Hold that broad!
Kyoko-san!
You bitch...
Run!
But what about you?
Forget about me, run!
If anything happens to you,
I’ll never be able to face Matsugoro again.
Kyoko-san...
Don't just watch!
Get her, you cretins!
I swear on my life,
you won’t step a foot out of here alive!
We'll see about that.
What’re you going to do?!
It’s obvious.
We'll pay her back instead of Matsugoro.
S-Sis has nothing to do with this!
Bring it on.
Koume-san!
Matsugoro-kun!
Koume-san? You’re safe...
What about Okyo-san?
I don’t know... Kyoko-san stayed behind
as a decoy to help me.
Got it. I’ll handle the rest.
Right now, the daycare is a scene from hell.
The kids are worried. You must go there.
Wait! You can’t do this alone!
They’ve got numbers, Matsugoro-kun!
Matsugoro-kun...
What a sight to see.
Screw you!
Ah! He's strong...
Sis!
All right, playtime’s over.
Do what you want with her!
Now, where to start—
nose or ears?
Better yet, let’s strip her down.
Matsugoro...
Matsugoro!
Why are you here?
What about Koume-san?
Matsugoro... Did you come here for me?
So you’re Matsugoro, huh?
And you’re the leader, huh?
Hm. You figured this place out well.
Made our job easier.
Plus, now we get
to take revenge for the gang.
Revenge?
Yeah.
I’m the former lieutenant of the Kodan Family
who used to cause trouble at the daycare.
I once had to back off because you interfered, but now I formed the Golden Yasha
to take back that land and take down
anyone who gets in the way!
So it was you who started
that fire at the daycare?
That's right, we torched it real nice.
With that, the daycare
and you are finished!
What you're actually doing
is fixing my dream.
I'm gonna pray all of you the fuck away!
Bring it on!
That's as far as you'll go, Matsugoro!
Of course, if you don’t care what happens
to this girl, then you can go on.
S-Sis...
Matsugoro, it’s fine!
Forget about me!
Have it your way.
Matsugoro...
You’ve caused me so much trouble...
You scumbag!
Matsugoro!
How does it feel to be a loser?
What’s with that look?
Don’t stick your nose
in grown-up business!
This'll teach you
to stay in school and behave!
Matsugoro! Why?
Why would you do this
for someone like me? You idiot!
Don’t cry...
We’re friends, aren’t we?
If so, I can’t just leave you alone!
L-Leader, you’re gonna kill him!
Shut up, all of you!
If you’re scared, get out!
You damn half-dead dog!
Just drop dead!
Matsugoro!
Kyoko!
You fool! Why did you—
We’re friends, aren’t we?
So I can’t just leave you alone!
S-Sis!
Asshole...
I’ll never forgive you.
What you did can never be forgiven.
I'll pray you to death!
Hey, call an ambulance.
Yes... Right away!
I still have things to do.
The rest is up to you.
Kodan      Family
Wh-What's going on?
Another group's attack?!
Hey, you! What the hell—
I brought you a can of whoop-ass.
Who the hell are you?
Praying Matsugoro.
Don't fuck with us!
Gasoline!
Hands off the daycare center!
For a school student,
you're something else.
Well, go ahead and try.
You’ll become a human torch too.
Seeing that girl's sad face
hurts way more than burning alive.
All right.
Hold it!
Guys like him are the most dangerous—
not because of money or greed,
but because they fight with their hearts.
Tanaka Surgical Hospital
Hasegawa Kyoko
You’re lucky, the wounds weren’t deep.
Yeah, this protected me.
Your brother’s pendant, huh?
Yeah.
More than that—
you’re really tough yourself.
It’s all in how you train.
Damn, you’re on another level.
Hey, Matsugoro-kun,
don’t think badly of me, okay?
You risked everything, including your life,
to protect Kyoko-san.
I'm a little jealous.
Huh? Why is that?
Ugh!
You’re so dense. I hate that!
Koume-san!
H-Hey!
Koume-san, what’s wrong?
Koume-san!
Raw provider
Translation & Typesetting
WOWmd
Perevodildo