A country that neglects its agriculture will invite the collapse of its people, just as Rome once fell...
The American train is coming
American
Train
Arriving
soon
American
Train
Arriving
soon
Big America!
Blissful America!
The American Train in Harajuku
Entrance to the fair
Your favorite America!
The newest American train is being received at this station.
The American Fair is being held here!
The American Train is coming
Once you eat this,
there won't be turning back!
Come with us, you!
The Land of Anger
Early summer of 1988
Ah! It's that late already? I gotta leave!
You'll be at your best today as well!
Next—Shinjuku! Shinjuku!
American Train?
That's right.
"Big America. Delicious America. Your favorite America," they made that their catchphrase.
It'll run through Harajuku Station on July 4th,
and other places across the country where fairs for American products are held.
50 of them countrywide, it seems.
I see...
This is a major project to promote imports of American products.
So maybe we should also cover it with a major special article in our city.
I wanted to put you in charge of that.
Me?
Yeah.
You've long been wanting
to cover something big, right?
Well, here's something worth covering!
T-Thank you, editor-in-chief.
Will you help her with the photos, Ishida-kun?
Yes. Pleased to work with you, Yokozawa-san.
The pleasure is mine.
Good. Get to work starting tomorrow, you two.
Okay!
I'm very excited about this assignment.
I admire America with all my heart!
I plan to go to California someday to study photography there.
I was dreaming of New York.
Broadway, Times Square, Wall Street...
I'd love to report from the center of world culture and economy.
I sure hope they send me to the US for the next assignment.
That'd be good. I hope so too.
I have a premonition of something.
I feel like the American Train will bring about a major change in us both.
Yes.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Over there.
Got it.
Okay, look this way now! Good!
So what exactly is the American Train?
Well, to put it simply, it's a program to express the goodness of America and American products
in a way that everyone would be able to understand.
I see. Could you explain more specifically?
Starting on July 4th, US Independence Day,
a train converted into a pavilion will travel
through approximately 50 stations, linking sister cities in Japan and the US
We hope everyone will enjoy the pavilions and the events they bring.
Furthermore, there are American fairs held on station platforms and plazas.
These focus specifically
on activities encouraging everyone to purchase various specialty American products.
Regulated paddy fields
So what exactly is the purpose
of this American Train?
That's quite simple! Its goal is deepening the friendship between Japan and the US.
By means of this campaign, we hope to encourage the imports and resolve the current trade frictions.
I'm getting a bit tired here.
That's true...
I understand the meaning of American Train,
but the whole thing honestly feels too gaudy.
Well, that's what happens when a private project
takes the form of a national sales pitch.
It feels like these American products are just being blatantly pushed on me.
I suppose.
Can't say I don't feel the same way about it.
This stuff is poisonous!
Eating this is like tying
a noose around your own neck!
Why can't you see?!
Stop it, grandpa!
Stop, you're embarrassing me!
This whole "American Train"
is just a gimmicky "kitchen car" stunt.
A pompous kitchen car, you hear?!
Kitchen car?
Cool down, gramps!
Quit yelling weird things!
Ugh! Let go!
Grandpa!
Hey! Aren't you being a bit too harsh to him?
Who are you?
Are you with this geezer?
No, I'm not.
There are some weirdos out there pulling stunts
in protest against the American Train.
You need a permission to take pictures!
I have that permission.
I said no!
Are you okay, grandpa?
Are you hurt?
No, I'll be fine.
Some brutes they are.
Treating the elderly this way!
It’s nothing. I’ve got a strong body from years of working in the fields.
Can't hurt me that easily.
Excuse me, but what made you say those things?
Well, I came to see this touted American Train
because my grandson urged me to.
But the way they mocked the Japanese
fired me up like nothing else.
I couldn't help getting mad.
Um, one more thing.
What is that "kitchen car" you mentioned earlier?
Hm. Don't you know what a kitchen car is?
Yes. It was actually the first time I heard it.
I've never heard of it either.
Hm. I see, that's understandable.
This term goes back
to before you guys were even born.
But even if you haven't heard it with your ears,
your body should be well acquainted with it.
Huh?
Look, there's one. Right there.
From about 1956 to 1961,
those foreign kitchen cars traveled all over Japan,
teaching the housewives "nutritious cooking."
Nutritious cooking?
What does that mean?
Hm?
As the name suggests, they cooked nutritious food
in those cars to teach the people how to do it.
It was funded from the US, with cooperation from the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
Does the name of Kaya Okinobu
ring any bell to you?
Kaya Okinobu?
Is that the former Class-A war criminal?
Yes. He was the chairman at Japan Dietetic Association,
which put this nutritional guidance program into action.
They said if you only eat rice,
you'll be stupid.
No way!
Well, they did believe it and launched the kitchen cars back then.
It was advertised on every corner.
Let us all eat bread!
Bread diet is good for your mind and body!
If you only eat rice,
your body will stop developing.
Let us all eat bread!
Bread is good for your mind and body!
If you only eat rice,
your body will stop developing.
Let us all eat bread!
Okay, let's eat.
Hey, don't feed us the rice alone.
Huh?
They say you turn stupid
from eating nothing but rice.
What are you saying?
Did you forget how much we treasured
even a handful of white rice
during and after the war,
when there were food shortages?
See for yourself.
You should read the newspaper too, sometimes.
At least to keep up with the news!
Huh? "Eating rice inhibits brain development.
Bread diet is recommended, especially for children?"
Oh my...
The adoption of bread diet and its effects
Higashimachi Community Center
And therefore,
as I've been explaining for all this time,
Rice weighs heavily on the stomach and is nutritionally unbalanced.
Bread and its benefits
Nutrition and culture
It is harmful to the body
and inhibits the work of the brain cells.
And this is how you sandwich the fried flavor between slices of bread coated with ginger miso.
You cut it into pieces
and serve it with apples or other side dishes.
And... you can serve it on a fish pan.
With it, they gradually changed the public mindset in regards to eating habits.
The Kitchen Car program was the first concrete program we undertook in Japan.
1978 NHK interview responds to the questions
Our next plans include expansion of school lunches,
and development of domestic bread industry.
We focused all of our early market development efforts on Japan.
We specifically targeted Japan and concentrated the US Department of Agriculture aid funds here.
As a result, wheat imports
from the US increased dramatically.
2.5 million tons in 1960
became 5.5 million tons this year.
The share of American wheat has increased from 30% to 60%.
Therefore, according to the policy of the Ministry of Education,
we've decided to provide bread-centered lunches to elementary school students first.
PTA regular meeting
Bread lunch and its benefits
Eventually, we plan to extend it
to junior high schools as well.
So, the new school lunches came as an extension of the kitchen car program? I didn't expect that.
Yes.
That man they interviewed, Baum,
later did not hesitate to say that Japanese bread
companies were developed by America.
Kizaki Bread Company
Eat bread!
Now! Come, come!
Newspapers, radio, magazines, specialized books,
and even prominent scholars and critics, such as Professor Hayashi Takashi of Keio University,
claim that eating rice makes you stupid, while eating bread makes you smarter!
Yes, you heard me right! Please, please!
Starting tomorrow... No, starting today already!
Replace the rice in your ration fully with bread!
Don't hesitate to ask us how!
Now, let’s continue with the trending topic
on the dangers of a rice-based diet.
We'll hear from a prominent
critic Sawada Koichi-sensei.
To bring the average physique
of Japanese people up to par with Westerners,
switching from rice to bread is essential!
We need to shift towards a more refined food culture, focusing on health-enhancing foods like meat and eggs.
Evidence of this can be seen in the low levels
of civilization among many rice-centered societies,
mainly those situated in Southeast Asia.
What is this imbecile talking about?
Japan is the land of the rice ears!
Tossing out all the rice is the same
as asking for divine punishment, goddammit!
But dad, my son also eats bread for school lunch.
Silence! Let's all settle down now!
Both this bread and skim milk powder
are American-made.
They say eating bread makes you smarter.
Let's eat well and leave nothing on the plate.
Okay!
It seems, the connection between the kitchen cars
and school lunches is undeniable.
Yeah, but all I remember about school lunches
is that they were never any good.
You're right, they're bad, actually.
Still, before we knew it, we fell in love with bread
and forgot the rice. Isn't that right?
Yeah...
Come to think about it, you're right.
When I said that your body remembers what a kitchen car is, that's what I meant.
By the way, do you guys know
about that old movie called Weasel Children?
"Weasel Children?" Don't think so...
I've never heard of it either.
Figures. It is actually one crappy movie.
But at the time, it was screened extensively throughout the country to promote school lunches.
Screening of the movie "Weasel Children"
Sponsored by the National School Lunch Association
Weasel
Children
There were two elementary schools
in two neighboring rural towns.
Yama Town's Elementary hadn’t started serving bread lunches yet, so the kids were still eating nothing but rice.
It gave them protruding bellies
and a weasel-like body.
Meanwhile, kids in town schools where lunches are already provided
have shown impressive improvement in their academic performance.
Whenever they met the children of the Yama Town,
they made fun of them, calling them weasels.
In this case...
The effects
of bread diet
The elementary school teacher in Yama Town
explained the importance of adding bread to school lunches.
Don't you understand?
But many of the parents were rice farmers, who didn't even attend the school lunch information sessions.
You need to have a healthy and balanced diet...
A-san, a traditional father,
I don't care!
held firmly to his belief that food prepared by parents can't be bad for their child.
One day, A-san's eldest son, who had just moved to Tokyo to get a job, collapsed due to low blood pressure.
A-san was worried that it may have happened
due to unbalanced nutrition.
Inter-town marathon
Then came the day of the inter-town marathon.
And the runners took off!
A-san's second son started off strong, but halfway through the marathon,
he ran out of breath and crouched on the ground, despite his father's heated encouragement.
This was enough to convince the stubborn A-san.
Rice and plum bento was no longer good enough.
As a result, the Yama Town school also began serving bread lunches,
and the kids were no longer teased as weasels.
The End
I don't believe it!
There's no way such a stupid movie exists!
Oh no, it really did happen.
National School Lunch Association
The National School Lunch Association was behind all of that.
Hello, Mister Yoshikawa.
Yes... Hello, Mister John Baum.
Mister Baum, cinema—OK.
Thank you for the produce money.
By the way, next kitchen car money please?
Would you like 100 more cars?
Yes, advertising... Getting better! Right...
OK, sure!
They screened it like that for quite some time.
Goodness...
Now I wanna watch it too!
That would be impossible, I'm afraid.
Even if there were film reels,
they were never released for public.
They must be mighty embarrassed about it, I imagine.
But was it truly necessary to go to such lengths
to aggressively promote bread-based meals and school lunches?
They were bound by the
MSA Wheat Import Agreement.
MSA Wheat Import Agreement?
What is that?
MSA Agreement
(Mutual Security Agreement)
Foreign military assistance agreement
between the US and its friendly nations.
The aim is to strengthen rearmament through military and economic assistance.
In 1954, Japan became the 46th country to sign the agreement.
Well, to put it simply, it was a promise that Japan will buy the surplus of American wheat.
At that time, Japan was essentially the US's backyard, making it impossible for us to refuse that imposition.
More like we gladly accepted it.
Unbelievable!
No matter how much we try to dress it up with claims of improving nutrition or refining eating habits,
in the end, the kitchen car program was just a ploy by the US to get rid of surplus wheat.
Changes in wheat imports and domestic production
tons, kk
Then the government-sponsored scientists and the media also jumped on the bandwagon,
Imported amount
MSA Agreement
Kitchen cars
Domestic production
despite the dubious nutritional evidence.
The people, who knew nothing of this,
started asking for more bread themselves.
At some point, the eating habits and tastes of the Japanese people changed for the US's convenience.
Yep. That's what I mean.
Japanese school lunches will improve your nutritional standards and prepare you for your future adulthood.
Summary of speech by the US Secretary of Agriculture Benson after inspecting school lunches in 1957
They are intended to help children cultivate better eating habits.
Welcome, Secretary of Agriculture Benson
It will also help promote trade between Japan and the United States.
Thanks to the nutritional value of the wheat and milk kindly sent to us from the USA,
Omiya City, Saitama Prefecture
Highjacking of child representative addresses
our bodies have become much stronger than those of children before the war.
It's not just us who's become happier.
Our families have grown to like bread just as much.
I will continue to train my body and work hard with our American friends to build a peaceful world for us all.
Thus, the Japanese wheat
was "euthanized,"
as some put it.
I can hardly control my rage!
That's true. So do I.
Hm. If you say so, telling all that to you
was worth my while.
Grandpa!
Let's go home. I'm hungry.
Well, I guess I'll go home then. Good bye!
Ah... Please wait.
Now I know what a kitchen car was.
But why did you call the American Train the second kitchen car?
And why did you call all the foods on display there poisonous?
Could you please explain that to me?
You guys are journalists, aren't you?
Why don't you do a little research on your own,
instead of just writing what you're told as it is?
B-But I...
Post-harvest application.
Post-harvest application?
What is that thing?
Post-harve... something.
After being harvested, agricultural products are sprayed with pesticides again to disinfect them.
They use pesticides
even after the crops are harvested?
It is to prevent mold and spoilage during long transportation and storage.
You guys should investigate what happens after that.
I'm sure a lot of interesting stuff will come to your attention.
Maybe even some other hidden things
that you don't expect.
Things we don't expect?
American Train, huh?
Let's go home now.
Yeah.
Oh?
Whoa!
1,2, rice!
Rice!
Don't let them take away Japan's staple food!
We don't want your train!
Yes! Go to hell!
We don't want their crops, covered in chemicals!
We don't want!
It seems, today was only
the beginning of our coverage.
Post-harvest application.
A system when crops are treated with pesticides again after harvesting for disinfection.
This is done to prevent mold and rot during long transportation and storage.
Mariko-san, look what I got.
Thank you! Come on in.
There it is! List of post-harvest pesticides!
More than a few of them!
Let's see.
Ethylene, nitrogen,
combustion gases, and so forth...
A total of 57 products are permitted for post-harvest use in the United States.
Among them, 15 chemicals are treated as food additives or natural products in Japan.
And six other items are registered in Japan as pesticides allowed for use on imported agricultural products.
This means, 36 items from here
cannot be used in Japan.
In other words, it is clearly illegal
to use these for post-harvest treatment.
And seven of these pesticides have been proven carcinogenic.
Benomyl
Thiophanate
methyl
Formaldehyde
Ethylene oxide
Captan
I believe the 2,4-D was one of the ingredients in the infamous Agent Orange used in the Vietnam War.
Hanoi bombing continues
US planes fire missiles at city
Guerrilla offensive expands: 21 "liberated areas"
Fighting intensifies in South Vietnam as government launches retaliatory bombings
So it's actually "Cheap, delicious, dangerous"?
But how come such a serious matter
was never brought up before?
Good question. The use of pesticides is supposed to be strictly regulated by food laws and standards.
Say, what if they don't thoroughly check
whether the products meet pesticide and post-harvest treatment standards at the time of import?
Let's see. Pesticides regulated in Japan upon import...
Ah, there are some for imported cherries.
Post-harvest and pesticide regulations
(Cherries)
Now, if we select pesticides from that previous list...
Pesticides,
restricted in Japan
Parathion
Dieldrin
Endrin
Diazinon
Dicofol
Chlorbenzilate
Fenitrothion
They're not testing it for pesticides used in the US?!
Post-harvest (USA)
Captan
Allethrin
Methyl catabolite
Piperonyl butoxide
Bilethrin
Dichloronitroaniline
Benomyl
Thiophanate methyl
Iprodione
What is wrong with this country's
checking regulations?!
Let's go to the port ourselves, Ishida-kun.
In 1980, Japan's food imports totaled over 3,388,300,000,000 yen,
making it the world's largest importer of food.
Food
Crude oil
Approximately one-third of those imported products come to the port of Yokohama.
We process all sorts of stuff
from different countries.
For starters—grapefruit, orange, kiwi, and banana.
Beef, pork, vegetables, wheat, soybeans, buckwheat, potatoes, pumpkins.
Even mountain herbs, sometimes.
Wow, you've got everything
and the kitchen sink here.
I guess that means
tofu and miso are somewhere here too.
Even the staple Japanese foods like soba
have to be imported!
What happens to the food that arrives at the port?
First, we let the Ministry of Agriculture's men inspect them.
It would be a problem if any pathogens get imported with the products.
A surge in quarantined agricultural and livestock products
It is also necessary
to protect Japan's flora and fauna.
The Mediterranean fruit fly controversy
is still fresh in my memory.
In 1981, a large outbreak of Mediterranean fruit fly, which lays eggs in fruit,
Japanese Agricultural News
caused extensive damage to American agricultural products,
Mediterranean fruit fly damage expands; agricultural product shipping restrictions
especially grapefruit, mainly in California.
The fumigation agent EDB used at that time contains diaphoretic substances.
What happened to the eradication declaration?
Although discontinued in the US, it was used as a disinfectant on fruit destined for Japan.
Large quantities were imported into Japan,
causing a scandal.
And if pests are found, we disinfect again.
By fumigation, right?
Yes.
Well, you could say pests, diseases, and fungal rot
are the fate of any agricultural product that spends a long time crossing the ocean.
Fumigation in progress
No trespassing
Here.
Thanks.
Fumigation in progress
Some are fumigated before coming to Japan,
but a lot more only do it after they get here.
Probably 30% for vegetables, 50% for grains.
70% of beans.
But the first place goes to fruits with 90%.
What chemicals do you use for it?
Combustion gases and methyl bromide.
Do you have any concerns about the chemicals,
working in a place like this?
Yeah, that's scary stuff, all right.
We have to work amidst the sea of chemicals here, you know.
So we have to take a lot of precautions,
especially for stuff coming from the US.
If the container's from Florida,
it's likely that the concentration of EDB inside is still strong from the treatment over there.
Yeah, it's not that easy.
Arriving at the destination
takes from two weeks to two months,
depending on the item.
Of course, it’s hardly fresh after all that time in transit.
This is salted bracken from China.
Look how rusty the drums are!
It's been accumulating rust here for at least half a year, I imagine.
I wonder if bracken can really hold up
that long, even if it's pickled.
This will probably be turned into a local specialty.
Yokohama 2nd Port Government Building
How many quarantine stations are there checking imported foods, at the moment?
Food Surveillance Division
We have about 20 locations nationwide.
Quarantine Station
How many of your people are engaged in this work?
We have 75 employees total.
And here, at Yokohama Quarantine Station?
Seven.
I was informed that approximately one-third of imported goods come through port of Yokohama.
Yet only seven people
are supposed to check all of it?
Yes, that's right.
Look at them one by one sounds like a lot of work.
Well, that's kind of why most of it is conducted through a document review, you know.
Just the documents?
That's about 90% of work.
After checking the documents, we go there to actually look at it and conduct a sampling inspection.
Are there any deficiencies
in the current inspection system?
Well, we're doing it according to the law, and we have a lot of knowledgeable and experienced specialists,
so I think it's fine.
That port official seemed quite confident,
but really, he was worried too.
It seems there are many more things happening that we have no idea about.
That's true. Things that would be too shocking
for anyone to see or learn about.
Yes. We can't just ignore this hunch.
We have to dig deeper.
Yeah... Come to think of it, people carefully browse through
various catalogs for electrical appliances and computers they don't even truly need,
yet remain indifferent to issues that impact their daily lives and could even be life-threatening.
Yes, we seek gratification
in being called a savvy consumer.
Oh man, this is so wrong.
I feel ashamed of myself.
But having seen it with your own eyes, you realized there's more to it than you can imagine, right?
Thank you for waiting.
L-Look!
It's gotten a little hard to eat, hasn't it?
I cried out subconsciously.
Let’s talk to a few more people to get a fresh perspective on this.
Health Research Institute
What exactly is the problem with imported food products?
Well, mostly it's pests,
pesticide residues, and food additives.
And it's not just chemicals that are dangerous.
Mycotoxins are also a major concern.
To combat this, they have to disinfect and fumigate the products several times over.
Examples of foods contaminated with aflatoxin, a carcinogenic mycotoxin not found in Japan:
Maize, buckwheat, buckwheat flour, wheat, rye flour, peanuts, peanut meal, millet, cottonseed, fresh bean paste, copra meal, peanut butter, pistachios, cheese, almonds, chili peppers, nutmeg, white pepper, peanut oil...
And more recently, there's also the radiation from the Chernobyl accident, and so on and so forth.
American scholar predicts
1 million cases of cancer, thousands of deaths
Even radioactivity?
Yes.
There is always the risk of radioactive contamination when it comes to imports from Europe.
To they conduct tests to detect radioactivity?
Yes. The government has announced that it will test all lots
Inspection equipment installed at Kanagawa Co-op
for 17 products from 12 countries, including the Soviet Union, for possible contamination.
Inspection Report
Were there any results?
Yes. As of June of 1988,
Imported foods exceeding the provisional radioactivity limit
1st announcement (1/9/87) Hazelnuts (Turkey)
2nd announcement (2/6) Bay leaves (Turkey)
Sage (Turkey)
Beef tripe (Finland)
3rd announcement (2/13) Reindeer meat (Sweden)
4th announcement (3/27) Thyme (from France)
Sage leaves (Turkey)
5th announcement (5/8) Bay leaves (Turkey)
Sage extract (Greece)
Heather flowers (France)
6th announcement (5/23) Almonds (Italy)
Herb tea (Spain)
7th announcement (6/12) Herb tea (Yugoslavia)
Sage (Yugoslavia)
Black currant puree (France)
Sage (Albania)
8th announcement (7/24) Raw hazelnut (Italy)
Hazelnut paste (Turkey)
9th announcement (8/20) Dried herbs (France)
10th announcement (9/11) Bay leaves (Turkey)
11th announcement (10/21) Beef extract (Brazil,
Ireland,
France)
12th announcement (10/28) Ice cream paste (Italy) Dried herbs (Yugoslavia)
13th announcement (12/22) Hazelnut paste (Turkey)
Sage extract (Albania)
14th announcement (1/20/88) Mushroom ferns (France)
15th announcement (2/15) Dried herb:
St. John's wort (Yugoslavia)
Herbal tea rose hips (Romania)
Mushroom: black trumpet mushroom(France)
16th announcement (6/2) Dried herb: Juniper berries (Yugoslavia)
Dried herb:
honeysuckle (France)
17th announcement (6/...) Sage leaves (France)
32 food items have been found to have radioactivity levels above the threshold,
and their importation has been halted.
Doesn't that mean we can feel safe now?
No, what we are concerned about
is the standard value itself,
the 370 becquerels,
and whether or not it is really safe.
As a result, an increasing number of citizen groups
are conducting their own inspections.
Civic organization office
This means we cannot leave the matter
to the government, doesn't it?
Indeed, in times like these,
we have no one to rely on but ourselves.
Civic organization official
What do you mean by that?
To give you an example,
let us remember the March of 1988.
Antibiotics have been detected in pork
imported from Taiwan and the United States.
Japan's Economic News
March 20th of 1988 issue
It was an antibiotic called sulfadimidine,
which causes excessive sweating.
No checks on "certificates":
growing anxiety over Japan-US agreement
Yet they just continued to import it?
No, financial measures have been taken,
but the real problem came after.
What do you mean?
A high-ranking government official came from the US
and said that from now on the US government will be responsible for the inspections,
and if you have their certificate you will get a free pass in Japan.
The same goes for products from Taiwan.
Although it's us, the Japanese,
who will actually have to eat it,
you need a certificate from a foreign country
to have a free hand?
The seller’s interests outweigh those of the buyer.
We can't leave something like this to a third party; history has plenty of examples to back that up.
With the liberalization of imports,
regulations on additives are being eased year by year.
Previous cases of deregulation
1972 Biphenyl
1977 OPP
1978 T.B.Z
1983 Aspartame, ferrous gluconate,
titanium dioxide, adipic acid,
isopropyl citrate, copper salts,
disodium EDTA,
calcium disodium EDTA,
silicon dioxide
This is absolutely unacceptable.
If it came to this, we must collect our own data
and conduct the checks ourselves.
This has been particularly closely related to the issue of trade friction in recent years.
Agrarian critic
The biggest example of that is the major deregulation of 1983, implemented
March 22nd, 1983
The Japan Business Federation requests the government to amend 43 laws, including the Food Sanitation Law, the Agricultural Chemicals Control Law, and the Pharmaceutical Affairs Law, to significantly relax regulations on food additives.
immediately after a request from the Japan Business Federation.
Could the current issues with importing agricultural products also be a sign of trade frictions?
I believe, the certain connection is undeniable.
However, when we talk about food specifically,
I think the question is whether or not it's acceptable to look at it from the economic point of view.
It is difficult to balance
economy and safety, isn't it?
But then, what do the people who actually produce the crops think?
Their view of agriculture
is nothing like anyone else's.
Although we call it large-scale farming, it may be more appropriate to call it a factory rather than a farmhouse.
That's because agriculture is an important industry that focuses on export.
Consider the United States, where agriculture alone offsets the trade deficit caused by large oil imports.
They favor large areas of land,
highly productive and economical management,
and the competitiveness to conquer the international market.
This requires a large amount of agricultural machinery.
Even chemicals that are prohibited in Japan
can be used on rice and grass there.
At this farm, feeding etc.
are managed by computers.
We can't afford to have someone look after each particular animal.
Of course, it's crucial to stop diseases
before they can take hold.
For that, large amounts of antibiotics
are mixed into the fodder.
Half of the antibiotics used annually in the United States go toward livestock farming.
And in 1987, beef from Australia was found to contain residues of carcinogenic chlordane.
Japanese Agricultural News
It was used as a termite control agent
in Japan until a few years ago.
Even the most common fruit,
bananas, have a similar problem.
The workers on the plantation have to work under pesticides falling from the sky.
This is inevitable for major banana plantations
run by large capitalists.
The locals won't even touch the bananas
that are discarded due to shipping regulations.
Not even when near starvation, with extremely low wages and exploited through peonizing loan-advance systems.
Because they are fully aware of the harmful health effects of those fruits.
These stemming from prioritizing productivity and cost-cutting in crop cultivation.
So what it boils down to is a fundamental difference in how we see agriculture?
The mindset of prioritizing cost-cutting
is what has led us to our current situation.
I'm absolutely shocked that we keep filling our bodies with products made in such an unscrupulous way.
Even the people who grow these bananas won’t eat them, and the origin of the growing site is hidden from us.
But we keep eating them without knowing or even trying to know...
No, we're being fed, rather.
Don’t you find it odd that our bodies hasn’t shown any abnormalities yet?
Yes.
Indeed, a major concern is preventing any abnormalities from developing in our bodies.
Health Research Institute
However, the truly frightening part would be if that toxicity seeped into our genes.
In that case, it would be our children and grandchildren who suffer the effects.
It begins with plankton and eventually finds its way into the human body,
by which point the toxicity
reaches alarming levels.
Miyamae Safari Park
The number of monkeys born without limbs started to rise after imported grains were added to their diet.
It seemed to suddenly appear
as a phenomenon one day.
It’s undeniable proof that the disease was inherited from a contaminated body.
I don't think we have any guarantee that the same won’t happen to humans.
I discovered that the number of children with atopic eczema is actually rising.
Pediatrics
As well as children with food allergies.
Atopic dermatitis is on the rise year after year
We can't separate this from the increase in imported crops and food additives.
Lemon
Special offer!
Can you believe it? We eat this stuff every day,
yet they’re so careless about regulating it!
I don't even know
what I can really eat or drink anymore.
Tofu beans, minced hamburger meat,
bread flour wheat,
chicken food and eggs, milk, cheese—
we import everything!
What's worse, all that stuff is harmful.
It seems, the rice is the only thing we still produce domestically.
But how did Japan become like this?
We've left our own stomachs in someone else's hands without a second thought!
I think I understand now—
what that old man was trying to tell us.
Good grief... Where is this country really headed?
It seems, the MSA Wheat Import Agreement that he mentioned was the beginning of it all.
Come on, Ishida-kun.
Don't lose your spirits.
We still have a lot of research to do.
Like we still don't know what the old man meant when he talked about "things that we don't expect."
M-Mariko-san, wait for me!
MSA—the Mutual Security Act with the USA, enacted in 1951.
In 1954, the Japan-US Mutual Defense Assistance Agreement was signed, building on the previous act.
Mutual Defense Assistance Agreement
Foreign Minister Okazaki
and US Ambassador Allison signing the agreement
Based on the situation on the Korean Peninsula at the time,
this became the basis for Japan's rearmament.
At the same time, they signed a surplus produce agreement.
The section relating to wheat trade became commonly known as the MSA Wheat Import Agreement.
The main contents of this agreement are as follows:
First, the US government sells $50 million worth of American wheat and barley to Japan annually,
which amounts to 18 billion yen.
Next, 80% of the 18 billion yen, equaling 14.4 billion yen, is allocated
How MSA Agricultural Purchasing Agreement works
The US
Not paid in dollars
$50 million
worth of wheat
80%—14.4 billion yen
Japan
20%—3.6 billion yen
Paying for US military bases in yen
Gifted to Japan
Most: Buying weapons
for the Self-Defense Forces
Part: American
agricultural produce
advertising expenses, etc.
by the Japanese government to pay the US military stationed in Japan in yen.
In other words, it will be deducted from the costs of stationing the US military in Japan.
The remaining 20% would be provided
to Japan by the US government as a bonus.
However, the proceeds will be used to produce and purchase weapons.
A portion of that money will be used to develop markets for American agricultural products.
That's an incredibly sweet deal.
It didn't require Japan
to use any foreign currency at all.
Yes, this was a wish come true
for Japan at the time.
We were able to redirect all foreign currency towards industrialization. However...
However?
However, this brought about
a major pivot in Japan's food policy.
At that time, Japan was in the midst of a five-year plan to boost food production from 1953 to 1957.
They swiftly shifted its focus to importing food.
First, they introduced wheat and launched various campaigns to enhance its image.
Such as kitchen car?
Yes, it was an effort to alter the foundation of our eating habits.
But in fact, it was to increase the wheat consumption, and by extension the wheat imports.
Over time, that movement led to so-called euthanization of Japan's wheat industry.
Come to think of it, you don't see anyone treading on wheat plants anymore.
In 1956, the New Comprehensive Measures for Rural Construction were put forward.
tons, kk
Wheat
Imports
Domestic production volume
In the name of "right production in the right place," there was a push
to shift from grain farming to fruit, vegetable, and livestock farming.
Soybeans
As a result, we became less self-sufficient in grains
Imports
Domestic production
and increasingly reliant on imports for soybeans and even fodder grains.
And before we knew it, we became only about 10% self-reliant for wheat.
Changes in self-sufficiency rates for major products
Wheat
Soybean
For soybeans, it's even less.
Beef
Now even traditional Japanese flavors
are produced abroad.
There's an interesting detail
in that previous graph.
Please pay close attention to the year 1960.
Wheat
Imports
Domestic production
tons, kk
The graphs show the most change in the '60s.
Soybean
Imports
Domestic production
Do you remember anything about the year 1960?
Beef
Wheat
Soybean
Changes in self-sufficiency rates for major products
1960s... Was that when the Security Treaty​ was extended?
Yes, a new mutual security treaty
to replace the MSA accords.
The New Treaty, also known
as the 1960 Security Treaty.
Liberal Democratic Party welcomes the signing of the security treaty
Protest the treaty!
Death before enslavement!
If the MSA agreement marked the first step, the signing of the new security treaty—
which split the nation into supporters and opponents—
became a decisive second step.
What do you mean?
This treaty entailed our commitment to cooperation with the US not only militarily but also economically.
It was fixed in the so-called economic cooperation clause in Article 2 of the Security Treaty.
Article 2: The Parties will contribute toward the further development
of peaceful and friendly international relations by strengthening their free institutions,
by bringing about a better understanding of the principles upon which these institutions are founded,
and by promoting conditions of stability and well-being.
They will seek to eliminate conflict
in their international economic policies
and will encourage economic collaboration between them.
The Japan Poultry Association signed a contract
with the American Dekalb Company.
New York, 1960
Our Association will not handle foreign egg-laying hens
or egg-laying systems other than those of Dekalb.
Dekalb HQ
Thank you, Mister Yoshimura!
Yes, thank you, sir.
Chairman Yoshimura, here are the points of the contract.
Highline Co.
Highline will slaughter its hens within the next 18 months, and its roosters within 7 days of the last breeding.
Sounds good to you?
Soon, large shipments of Dekalb chicks would begin
departing for Japan from airports across the US.
Dekalb Chicks
The similarly, Highline's fertilized eggs were shipped throughout the country from various airports.
Highline's fertilized eggs
Haneda Airport
Osaka International Airport
Naturally, these changes change the poultry farming in Japan on a very fundamental level.
Yes, traditional free-range chickens
like White Leghorns,
Nagoya Cochins, and others have disappeared altogether from Japanese farmers' gardens.
Instead, more and more facilities were built
for large-scale growing of Dekalb and Highline breeds imported from the US.
Of course, it wasn't just poultry farming.
Livestock farming, including pigs and dairy cows,
went through a similar process.
Alongside this, imports for livestock fodder also skyrocketed.
Japan Fodder
Relying almost entirely on imports for resources led to various issues along the way.
Something's wrong!
This is the Newcastle disease,
which is spreading throughout Japan!
How did this happen?
Through the food.
The bird food is infected.
Can't we help it somehow?
No, there's nothing you can do.
N-No way!
Japanese agriculture was gradually choked off, one sector at a time.
And then the process was complemented by the Basic Agricultural Law.
The two pillars of the Basic Agricultural Law were structural improvement and selective expansion.
Basic Agricultural Law (enacted in 1961)
A law that lays out the basic policy for agricultural structural improvement projects. In order to adjust the demand for food and correct the income disparity of agriculture in relation to other industries, the law stipulates that the government should modernize agriculture, improve agricultural structure, i.e., develop family farming, foster self-reliant management, encourage cooperatives, promote farmer independence, and secure the necessary budget.
Structural improvement meant promoting land readjustment
and large-scale mechanization.
Selective expansion meant linking agricultural production to the rising demand.
You cut back on producing crops with declining demand or those that can be easily imported.
In other words, it was like reverse protectionism, where imported products took priority.
These changes accelerated Japan's industrialization, propelling it into an era of explosive economic growth.
Kanna Junior High School Graduation Ceremony
We're having a very meaningful graduation ceremony today.
13th Graduation Ceremony
It marks the end of your compulsory education
and your entry into society.
Japan is currently undergoing rapid economic growth, with our industries developing by leaps and bounds.
That's the kind of cutting-edge workplace where you'll soon find yourselves working.
My hope is that when you go to Tokyo,
you'll all become valuable pillars of our society.
As farms underwent restructuring,
surplus labor
shifted to Tokyo and other
major industrial cities,
which were chronically short of workers during the high economic growth period.
It’s no exaggeration to say that migrant farmers and children
who went through mass employment were the backbone of what would become the Japanese economic miracle.
1964, Tokaido Shinkansen begins service
In 1964, Tokaido Shinkansen begins service.
Also in 1964, the Tokyo Olympics were held.
Then, in 1969,
Rice Acreage-Reduction Policy began.
World Expo opens to the public today, with a variety of events running until September 13th
In 1970, the Japan World Expo was held.
Its slogan was
"Progress and Harmony for Mankind."
But the reality
of that progress and harmony was...
Dear me, is that what you call
progress and harmony?
Natural archipelago destroyed for oil
The period of high economic growth turned out to be a fleeting 12-year dream, cut short by the 1973 oil crisis.
Toilet paper shortage and price hikes
No more books in schools!
Abnormal inflation, company downsizing, massive layoffs, and widespread bankruptcies
Orders are not fulfilled
among small and medium-sized businesses.
How much have we really gained from high economic growth, and how much have we lost?
Meanwhile, Japan's agriculture is caught between part-time farming and full mechanization.
Large-scale livestock farming is endangered by American-made fodder.
And then also...
Wetland rice situation in Tohoku worsens
Rice crop deteriorates further
In rice-growing areas, for the first time since the end of the war,
Cold-weather damage
rice production dropped by 140,000 tons compared to the previous year.
The rice-crop index is at 87.
At the same time, the rising exports
units, kk
12.27 million units
11.04 million units
(#1 in the world)
Changes in automobile production in Japan
of industrial products like automobiles to the US
sparked strong opposition from Congress.
Japan's trade balance with the United States
(non-agricultural products)
$ millions
Exports
Imports
Trade
balance
As previously discussed, the Japan Federation of Employers' Associations is convinced
Computer prices also drop sharply
Difficulties in agricultural exports explained
Japan complies with the US demands?!
Federation of Employers
that the solution to US-Japan trade friction lies in working closely with the government
to fully liberalize agricultural products
and reduce subsidies,
Chairman
ending the excessive protection
of the domestic agricultural sector.
The Labor Union Federation Preparatory Committee,
aspiring to become a national center, believes that
Labor Union Federation
Preparatory Committee
agriculture is excessively protected,
and subsidies should be cut significantly.
Additionally, we must fully liberalize agricultural products and increase imports
Secretary
Chairman
of cheaper goods to safeguard workers' livelihoods.
This will help resolve the trade frictions.
This is one aspect where we can work together with the company in a cooperative manner.
Labor Union Confederation
House of Representatives Committee on Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries
So... After careful deliberation, we've decided...
We've decided to launch the second phase
of measures, restructuring the use of paddy field.
We will take decisive action to reduce fallow land,
setting a target of 677,000 hectares.
If you support it, please vote "yes!"
It was around this time when the media started jumping on the bandwagon.
Japanese agriculture is overprotected
They were abuzz with talk of trade liberalization, acreage reduction, and agricultural overprotection—all at once.
More than half of the salaried worker's taxes
go to the agricultural budget?!
This is another one of those unexpected things
that the old man was talking about.
They slowly eroded every root.
But does the main trunk still hold firm?
Oh! Yes, good!
Thank you, good cat.
Yes! America and Japan share a common destiny, Cat!
The Japanese archipelago is America's unsinkable aircraft carrier!
Blockade the Soviet Union in four straits
and fight alongside the United States!
Yes! Well said! Good! Good!
In other words, we said that if we die,
we die together.
Protest the South Korean imports!
Yeah!
Protest the agricultural imports liberalization!
Japan's crops has suffered cold weather damage
for four consecutive years since 1980!
Chagawa Prefecture Farmers' Union Against Korean Rice Imports
Importing foreign rice? Don't make us laugh!
Black rice is endangered by the autumn frost sheen,
and we're close to having to import it from South Korea!
But South Korea itself
hasn't yet reached full self-sufficiency in rice!
Association for the Protection of Japanese Agriculture
Rice is the lifeblood of the Japanese people
So they’re importing rice from America first,
then selling it to Japan!
The political and financial worlds, along with sympathetic factory workers and the media, are all in sync!
They say Japan doesn’t need
to produce its own food!
They say it’s fine to import rice, fruits, meat, and vegetables—everything but the kitchen sink!
Protect agriculture                Protest rice imports
Do you agree with that, everyone?!
As a result, Japan’s food self-sufficiency rate
steadily declined over the years.
France
The USA
The UK
West Germany
Japan
Grain self-sufficiency rates in major developed countries
Among all developed countries, Japan was the only one
with a food self-sufficiency rate in the red.
1986.
That was when the US pushed Japan
to make a decisive choice.
Namely—uncompromised liberalization of agricultural products.
Well, as you likely know,
Japan is one of the world's largest economies.
We now have a trade surplus of $82 billion.
A staggering number!
This is thanks to Japan's exports of automobiles and home appliances.
Japan compensated for its lack
of natural resources by developing
Kanichi Takemura's Public Commentary on the State of Affairs
advanced technology and exporting high-quality industrial products.
It’s only natural that our American partners are now pushing for the full liberalization of agricultural products.
Only natural!
After all, the US is Japan's
most valued customer.
Most valued!
And they also need some assurance of cooperation from Japan.
If we want to stay on good terms with our most valued customer, we need to liberalize agricultural products.
For a country as small as Japan, there's nothing wrong with abandoning farming altogether.
Fruits, beef, rice—
we can import anything from abroad!
There's nothing wrong
with importing it! Absolutely!
In fact, it would allow us to enjoy products that are both cheaper and tastier than what we have now.
As you can see, agricultural liberalization
brings only advantages.
I guess I got carried away a bit.
With sincere regret, I have to inform you that
Prefectural Governor's Emergency Press Conference
there are only two days left until the Prime Minister leaves for America.
We found ourselves unable to stop the expansion of Cargill Inc. into Shibushi Bay in Kagoshima.
Cargill is one of the six largest grain trading companies in the USA, the so-called Big League.
Cargill Inc. (USA)
Grain Trading
Commodity Trading Division, Sugar Division, Molasses Division, Flax & Sunflower Division, Cobra Division, Produce Trading Division, Sylvania Peanut Company, Heynold Elevator Company, Owen Park Brothers, Pan America Division
Grain Processing
Feed Soybeans Domestic Division, Feed Soybeans International Division, Flour Milling Division, Seaboard Allied Milling Corporation, Ballas Flour Milling Division, Ross Industries, Protein Products Division, Scryabin Oil Mill
Home and Livestock Division
Home and Livestock Products Division, Scheuber-Poultrybury, Deing Farms, Dean Farms, Cave Rock Industries, MBPXL Corporation
Home and Farm Supplies Division
Seed Division, Feed Division, International Feed Division, Fertilizer Division, Wake Close Corporation
Finance and Taxation
Cargill Investors Service, Punk of Ellsworth, Cargill Leasing, Horizons N.A. Agency, Inc., Summit National Life Insurance, Cargill Americas Inc., Cargill Export Inc., Tennant Americas Trading, Tennant International Sales
Transportation
Transportation Division, B&M Towing, Barbco Inc., Gulftaw Inc., Cargo Carriers Inc., Greenwich Marine Inc., Midwest Towing Co., Tri-State Marine Services, Marine Barchasers Inc., Rogers Terminal & Shipping Co.
Other
Chemical Products Division, North Star Steel Co., Zellrich Steel Co., C, Tennant Sons Co., Tennant Strapping Division, Aenco Inc., Salt Division, Watkins Salt Co., Silent Night Security Systems Inc., Venture Sprinkler Inc., Cargill Lampar Co.
The company's sphere of interests spans all grain-related operations,
from trading to processing, production, and financing.
It has a presence in most countries
except the communist bloc.
Shibushi Bay
It is truly nothing short of a trading company giant.
The actions of Cargill Inc. in Shibushi Bay epitomize America's grain strategy toward Japan.
Cargill USA
Cargill Worldwide Asia
They already have feed mills and fertilizer plants in the area.
Dealing Room
Will Japan's agriculture become just another asset in this capitalist web?
We can look at Taiwan for answers.
Cargill is the leader of Taiwan's feed industry.
In particular, pig farming has been transformed into an export-oriented business, where everything
from feed supply to management structure
is primarily focused on Japan.
Of course, their mainstay is beef and broilers.
Is that the future that awaits Japan too?
White House, 1986
Japan must make a historical transition.
I intend to stand up to this challenge.
To resolve current trade tensions with the US, I pledge to my good friend President Reagan that I will strive
to shift Japan's industrial structure from a major exporter to a major importer.
Prime Minister's Office
Prime minister
Then came the so-called Maekawa Report, put together by Prime Minister Nakasone's advisory panel.
Economic Structural Adjustment Research Fund Report Recommendations
○ Opening up the agricultural market by lifting import restrictions
○ Rationalizing imports by simplifying inspection and trade systems
○ Structural policies cutting off part-time farmers!
1986 Tokyo Summit
The Maekawa report
was submitted to the Tokyo Summit.
Tokyo Economic Declaration
As a result, the Maekawa Report's call for agricultural product liberalization
Report of the Provisional Council for Administrative Reform
became an official commitment of the Japanese government.
We should expand agricultural imports,
cut the agricultural budget,
and further shrink Japanese agriculture!!
And finally, in September, voices demanding the liberalization of rice came out in force.
United States Capitol
RMA—American Rice Millers' Association
files lawsuit against the US government
However, it seems this was also influenced
by someone pulling the strings.
This was their new feint to eliminate Japanese agriculture once and for all.
Wheat import dependence is at 86%.
Soybean import dependence—92%.
Soybeans
Wheat
Import Dependency Rate
And if we liberalize the rice as well...
Lemme tell you something,
Japanese rice is already ridiculously expensive.
The only way forward now is to lift import restrictions
and set prices on an international level
to make it available to consumers.
The Japanese people will also feel their consumer basket getting cheaper.
What's more, we'll be able to spend more money on other products.
We'll enter the era of splurging,
and it won't be a dream!
That's what I want to scream to all of you!
But I guess I got carried away again.
If rice is liberalized, will it really become cheaper as the critics say?
Only 4% of the world's rice production is exported
and available on international markets.
World total
Rice production by country
Exported (in 1986)
China
Japan
Thailand
USA
Others
Moreover, if we look at Thailand, the world's largest rice exporter,
there has been a 17% fluctuation
in harvests over the past decade.
Highest and lowest rice production in Thailand over the past 10 years (per 10 ares)
Highest
Lowest
If Japan, whose staple food is rice, were to step in to buy rice in such an unstable market,
$/ton
Fluctuations in rice export prices from 1965 to 1982
Sources:
that would obvious drive the international price up.
The rice liberalization will be achieved at all costs!
Summary of RMA Vice President Garbert's address
RMA (Rice Millers' Association)
The US now has a surplus of rice.
While I can't guarantee that the supply will remain steady in the future,
as I am merely the vice president of a private organization,
even if exports from the US were to halt,
Japan could purchase rice from other countries like China, Taiwan, South Korea, and Australia!
However, only the USA produces Japonica rice,
favored by the Japanese.
Japonica species
Indica species
Distribution of Indica and Japonica species (diagram)
Furthermore, other Asian countries are not self-sufficient in rice either.
In the end, this so-called liberalization essentially just means importing from the USA.
And only the few grain majors
control nearly 90% of US grain exports.
Chicago Board of Trade
Ultimately, the price of the rice we purchase
is simply manipulated by the whims of big capital.
International price fluctuations of major agricultural products (1972-74)
Wheat
Soybeans
Maize
Year
Month
What's worse, American agriculture is now stuck in a perpetual crisis that's nothing short of a depression.
Continuous drought, soil desertification,
and rising debts from failed economic policies
Nebraska
South Dakota
Iowa
Illinois
Kansas
Texas
are now reportedly causing up to 2,000 farming families to go bankrupt each day.
That's likely why they had to pivot to rice,
the backbone of Japanese agriculture.
The US share of world wheat exports
The US share of world rice exports
The US share of world maize exports
The US share of world soybeans exports
The US share of total grain exports (%)
It's incredibly foolish to rely entirely on a country like that to feed the Japanese people.
1986, Ministry of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries
I would like to announce the results of the deliberations
of the Agricultural Policy Council.
First: lower domestic food self-sufficiency
to ease trade friction.
Second: cut the rice-producing area by 770,000 hectares next year.
The self-destruction of Japanese agriculture was happening with small steps like that.
If agriculture dies, nature also dies.
Paddy fields don’t just produce rice;
they also play an irreplaceable role in flood control.
If Japan fully opened its market to the US, one-third of its rice paddies would vanish.
We will also have to endure the consequences of soil erosion
and water shortages impacting our countryside.
How can they be that foolish?!
It's not just them.
We were the ones who chose those people
and entrusted them with Japan's future.
We did ourselves.
A-Are you sure?
I welcome our many guests,
you can call me Noboru!
To everyone's delight,
the Beef-Orange issue has been resolved.
I made the decision and put it into action.
Thank you.
Beef-Orange: Agreed on for the next three years
You can call me Ron, I am also very happy with this development.
If fully liberalized, the Japan-US negotiations will be over in two years
I am pleased to see the resolution of three key issues: the opening of the construction market,
the scientific and technological
cooperation agreement,
and the liberalization of beef and orange imports. Thank you.
Thank you very much for taking the time out of your busy schedule to come here today.
Japan-U.S. Joint Committee
The Toronto Summit was a great success,
and the challenging issue of liberalizing beef and orange imports was resolved.
The Ron-Noboru union
is now entering its honeymoon season.
Therefore, with the full cooperation of JR East,
we can now discuss the American Train program, an express train filled with American dreams.
A word to Okita-sensei,
the Chairman of the Committee.
The project was initiated
at the urging of prominent figures concerned about the rising trade friction between the US and Japan.
It will be a jointly-funded endeavor.
A 12-car pavilion train
loaded with American produce.
It will depart from Tokyo and travel through various regions of eastern Japan and Hokkaido for one year.
We must make this a great success and eventually expand it to JR West.
But the problem is this tape, distributed by some individuals "Would you still eat it?"
This infuriated the American political and business circles, including Agriculture Minister Lyng.
Would you still eat it?
Dangerous imported food floods the country
Is it really safe?
Its content sharply criticizes the toxicity of American agricultural products.
For that reason, we need the media on our side.
Avoid topics of safety and freshness
whenever you can.
Center the promotion around
"cheap and delicious" as the key theme
to alleviate trade friction, all while celebrating Japan's status as having the world's largest trade surplus.
So our investigation
finally reached the American Train.
I can now see through the unscrupulous trick of the American Train.
Ishida-kun, I'll do it.
Huh? What?
I'll write the truth
about the American Train.
Editor-in-Chief.
Oh!
The American Train article is finished.
Oh! You sure took your time
with it, didn't you? Let's see.
Wh-What is this nonsense?!
"American Train is the Second Kitchen Car,
the Vanguard of Rice-Crushing?!"
Are you out of your mind?!
Yes, you heard me right.
I am confident that we
have done our best job.
Ugh, fine.
I'll read it just in case.
Did you really think
we could print something like this?
Rewrite it!
Without any of this bullshit!
Why's that?!
We faithfully and accurately compiled the information
that emerged during our investigation.
Yet you can's accept it?
If you're gonna reject it,
at least tell us the reason!
What can't you understand?!
What I asked you to write was a showcase
of the abundant products that the American Train
introduces and demonstrates,
not this deranged rambling!
Why didn't you say it clearly, then?!
What you really wanted was just a puff piece for the American Train!
Wh-Whadja say?
Just like all the other media, riding on the government’s and financial world’s coattails,
churning out sycophantic articles.
Meanwhile, no one realizes just how toxic the imported products and food additives really are.
What's worse, it's reached the point where they're even importing rice—our staple food—and trying
to wipe out our agriculture entirely!
Isn't that the great duty of the media...
Fine! Enough!
Don't rewrite it!
We'll just get someone else to write this article!
Very well.
I have no intention of rewriting it either.
Excuse me.
M-Mariko-san!
What insolence!
Mariko-san!
Mariko-san, what are you going to do now?
Don't know yet.
But it's definitely not working here.
God!
The American Train in Harajuku
Entrance to the fair
Once you eat this,
there won't be turning back!
I wonder where this country is headed?
Living in darkness,
intoxicated by fleeting prosperity...
Quite right—this country is finished, and it's not only politicians and big businesses that deserve the blame.
This situation stems from the choices we've made ourselves.
We’ve had numerous chances
to say “no” until now.
However, our obsession with the prospect of quick gains has caused us to forget what truly matters along the way.
It's them... Without people like them,
the world would be a better place.
Who are you?
Disgusting humans,
who don't even grow their own food,
who destroy the mountains, pollute the sea,
and neglect nature—you've brought about your own ruin!
Mountain God,
the other mountain is also collapsing!
Mountain God?
There's no longer any way
we can coexist with these idiotic humans!
It's the end for them and for Japan!
Wait, Mountain God!
Is there really, really no hope left for us?
Is it decided already?
Farewell.
Wait! Don’t leave me behind!
Ah! The house!
Our house!
No, this is hopeless.
It just wouldn't stand straight.
Tohoku region suffers worst harvest since the Meiji era
1988 Extreme Weather in Japan
Dad, these are rotten to the core!
Yeah...
Anxiety spreading around the world
Keep the fire burning!
The temperature is still dropping!
Skin diseases are spreading
Please line up!
One full bucket per person!
Don't be so stingy!
One dam has dried up
One full bucket per person!
It's drying up
Hey, don't jump the line!
Please line up!
No more water in the dams
Strategic stockpiling resumes in October,
to be increased to 100,000 per day
Huge ripples throughout Japan:
major bankruptcy hits ceiling
Chicago Grain Price Skyrockets
Spinach 800 yen
Radish 1000 yen
What? How is it this expensive?!
It can't be helped!
The weather is bad and the crops are failing.
Soybean prices
rise due to spike
House special
Miso soup
Rice
Small         Big
All the ingredients have hiked in price.
I'll just have miso soup.
I'm sorry, but all soybean imports
have come to a halt.
Price control for agricultural products
Food battle has begun
Please line up!
Only those with rationing tickets!
Okay, that's all for today!
What do you mean?!
A dream...
No, this isn't just a dream.
In a few years, it will be our reality.
And that'll be the end of Japan.
Weekly issue
American Train that carries the dreams
"American Train that carries dreams?"
Don't make me laugh!
Hello.
Oh, the young lady I met the other day?
Um...
I don't mean to make excuses,
but I wasn't the one who wrote that.
I know.
I never thought you'd write
such a disgusting article.
Well, why don’t you stop
being so shy and take a seat?
Sure.
But I still feel guilty.
Ultimately, only subjective articles get approved.
I nearly feel embarrassed to be in the media.
Hm. Can't argue with that.
Um...
Yes?
Is Japan done for?
Is there no way to divert it
from self-destruction?
If things keep going the way they are,
its fate is sealed.
So there's no future for us anymore...?
No, there is a future.
Oh?
No matter how dire the situation becomes,
as long as there are people
working hard everywhere to overcome it,
and even a glimmer of conscience to reflect on the past and seek to make amends, there is hope for the future.
Is that true?
Yes.
Follow me, I'll show you the future.
The future?
Yes.
Ah, wait!
This is the future.
Looks like just an ordinary agricultural plant.
Hard to tell from the looks of it, isn't it?
Y-Yes...
Hm. Well, let me give you a tour,
and then you can decide.
Young lady, do you know
what they are doing?
Yes...
That's the same as making the soil.
Make soil?
Yes.
Hey, Gen-san!
Oh, Yamazawa-san?
Could you please teach this young lady
how to make soil?
Oh, it's nothing difficult, really.
Organic farming is all about
letting nature take its course. Yah.
Nature's course?
What I mean is, crops grow in the fields
by absorbing nutrients from the soil.
And then the animals eat them.
Circulation of elements
Solar Energy
Plants
Dead tree
Animals
Grass
Fertilizer
Fossils
Withered grass
Earth elements
But crops pull nutrients from the soil,
so if left unchecked, the land will soon be depleted.
That's why we humans use fertilizer.
It nourishes the soil.
In other words, we create the humus. Yah.
And that's how we sustain the natural cycle.
Take a look at this. There are billions of microorganisms even in this handful of soil.
What we're doing is breathing life into it.
Living soil?
Yeah, that's what makes
all these crops grow for us.
Those are nothing like
the ones churned out in factories.
There are microorganisms
and minerals in the soil.
Destroying these is a no-no.
What pesticides and chemical fertilizers do is killing the soil.
Usually, you can finish the harvesting cycle in less then 100 days with pesticide farming.
Of course, the natural cycle should be longer.
That's why we also set up square-shaped compost bins to replenish the soil. Yah.
Compost?
Compost is created by packing and fermenting rice straw,
dried grass, and other plant and animal waste.
Yes, mixing that into the ground
and watering it makes the soil as good as new.
That also lets you make use
of livestock waste and rice straw.
The rest could be used for chicken feed,
and chicken droppings make excellent compost.
It's easy to disrupt the ecosystem if you're not careful with it.
Selling surplus compost can, in turn,
become a valuable source of income.
Work with nature,
and it will reward you in return.
That mindset is essential, yah.
We are the producers.
Work with nature
and it will reward you back?
Yeah, it's really that simple.
All you need is a genuine desire to produce something good. Right, Gen-san?
Absolutely! Grow real food and eat real food. That’s all there is to it.
Organic farming, which relies on compost, utilizes the natural balance of the soil, making it a safe method.
In contrast, farming practices that employ chemical fertilizers and pesticides are "deadly farming methods" that jeopardize not just the soil but also crops and human health.
The number of farmers like him is gradually increasing across the country.
Yes, we keep in touch and hold study sessions, among other things.
Thank you.
I caught a glimpse of the future.
This is also future.
Organic farming?
You've learned a lot more now,
but that's not all.
Here, they are restarting rice cultivation
from the ground up.
From the ground up?
Exactly!
If it isn't Tome-san!
Long time no see.
Well said! Tome-san, please show us
the future of rice cultivation.
Sure.
Japanese rice cultivation has suffered great setbacks over the past 25 years.
Over-mechanization, excessive pesticide use, and mono-cropping have led to a decline in the soil's quality.
Excessive enlargement and mechanization will lead to the degradation of rice paddies...
After all, those are also
important for our imports.
Number of fallow fields expected to increase
For years, we pretended that those are helping both the farmer and the customer.
A rice-centered agricultural policy
does not find support within the LDP
So what we did was,
persuading them that the rice farmers are the basis of Japan's food production.
Lawsuit to be filed against import restrictions on rice
Rice needs to be opened up too
Well, if you just think about it,
it sounds confusing at first.
US takes lead in agriculture negotiations
But let's try.
Rice cultivation has roots in the Tohoku region: a new discovery
1,300-year-old tree unearthed: vital clue
Japan cultivated rice for thousands of years.
Rice cultivation, namely paddy fields,
was where the Japanese culture was born.
Ritual rice dance at the time of rice planting
Performed to accompany the planting of the seedlings by Sootome girls
(Taharakasane Farming Scroll)
That's not all. Take, for example,
"Let's build a rice field."
It's not just about growing rice.
It is used to say "let's protect our land."
Protect the land?
Yes.
Tome-san refers to this.
Paddy fields are also a water storage.
In times of flood, they contain the water as well as dams do.
Like dams?
Yeah.
The amount of water stored in Japanese paddy fields is approximately 8.1 billion tons.
This is about three times the amount of water in all the dams in Japan.
Correct. They make the water seep into the ground and become groundwater, also useful for other plants.
Since ancient times, we covered the mountains in rice fields.
Every farmer understands their usefulness through a close connection with nature.
The forests on the hills
also receive additional water.
Groundwater plays a crucial role in maintaining natural circulation.
Groundwater helps alleviate
the effects of drought.
Forests absorb solar heat and evaporate water, regulate temperature and prevent wind from running rampant.
The flash floods and landslides weren't nearly as frequent in the past.
But we've all but forgotten
to appreciate it nowadays.
Leveling rice fields
to build golf courses is reckless!
So we must take an active stance
for a return to the mountains.
18 holes spread across a course
Now is the time to learn golf
Rice paddies filled with water shield the nutrient-rich soil from being swept away by the wind.
Oxygen                                                                                      Oxygen
Principal water insulation effect
Soil
Groundwater (dam effect)
So they're protecting the earth as well.
The greenery of the rice fields also helps provide fresh air.
Do you really think American and Thai rice will protect Japan's
greenery or take the place of dams?
Whadja say?
Unlike conventional fields,
paddy fields aren't affected by mono-cropping.
And you can grow wheat as a secondary crop.
But wheat isn't much good
for anything besides milling.
Meanwhile, any excess rice
can easily be used as animal feed.
I want to eliminate pesticide-laden agriculture.
My dad has cancer;
I’m sure it’s also because of pesticides.
If it kills bugs and weeds,
surely enough, it kill people too.
We'd be better off without it.
Debts are increasing because of forced mechanization,
and migrant farmers are losing their jobs.
Blinded by subsidies, we've lost sight
of the true essence of agriculture and forestry.
Originally, we grew rice
by managing the water temperature.
We also began using it as a method
to combat pests and diseases.
This means that every rice farmer
is a self-sufficient farmer.
These people aspire to become the foundation of this new culture of rice farming.
So you want every farmer to be self-sufficient?
Independent distribution
is still a tough challenge, though.
Especially with the new food regulations.
But we, simple farmers, still persevere.
You showed me one more future for Japan.
I feel a little better already.
Now then, let me tell you a story
that will cheer you up even more.
Yes, please do.
Well, here you can see another future.
Grandpa!
Oh, hey there!
Helping your parents, I see?
Yeah!
Ah, hello!
Hello.
Is he doing well?
Yeah, he's working hard!
But dad still says he's just a layabout.
Excuse me, who is he talking about?
Him, of course.
You took your sweet time,
didn’t you, Mariko-san?
I-Ishida-kun! Why are you here?
Why, gathering material, of course!
But lately I've also been
helping people out a lot more.
Come on, let me show you the future!
The products harvested at this farm
are delivered directly to consumers.
Consumers also help in transporting the goods.
With fewer middlemen involved, the products avoid any added costs.
It's very cheap.
And the products are still fresh
when they are delivered.
Ah, and here comes the representative from the consumer group.
Hello.
Are you always here?
No, not all the time,
but I make an effort to visit whenever I can.
I enjoy meeting the people
at the production site.
Firstly, here, producers and consumers can connect, letting us cook and eat with peace of mind.
When I know it’s going to be eaten
by an anonymous someone I don’t know,
I end up thinking that as long as it sells,
it’s good enough.
People often buy it simply because it looks appealing and is cheap.
That's right.
I believe it’s time for us as consumers
to be more conscious about what we eat.
Our dining table is full of imported foods!
Is it really all right to just mindlessly consume everything?
They say those vegetables and fruits can last two to three weeks in the refrigerator.
Checklist for a safe dining experience!
1. Always read the labels carefully before purchasing.
2. Avoid produce from radioactively contaminated areas.
3. Enjoy seasonal Japanese foods at your table!
4. Wash fruits and other foods thoroughly with water.
We deliver quality products from all over the world.
Is it really safe to eat such products?
Can we really take it for granted that seasonal fruits and vegetables can be eaten year-round?
Organic farming from Narita Farm
(Living soil)
American Cherry
Star player of decoration
If we consumers keep consuming carelessly, why wouldn't the producers do the same?
The Japanese flag is only for rice.
It seems we need to reconsider our dietary habits,
which currently focus on being
"rich, beautiful, and all-you-can-eat year-round."
Both production and consumption should align with nature.
It's up to humans to rebuild the nature
that they have destroyed.
We believe that living in harmony with nature is the key to true happiness for humanity.
Yes, I understand.
All across the country, farmers, rural areas,
and consumer groups like our friend here that embrace this mindset are slowly gaining traction.
Oh my, Ishida-kun, you're beginning to sound
like one of the farmers yourself!
Huh?
By working with the producers, lobbying the government,
and expanding the circle of our groups,
Protest the agricultural liberalization
Safe things come from Japanese soil!
we've been making steady progress, although still little by little.
Food critic Junichi Kowaka is giving a lecture
on pesticides added to imported foods
The drive to make and eat only real food
is still very strong in people.
I want to eat the real thing!
Citizens' Association
What do you say, young lady?
Won't you lend us a hand?
Huh?
Although the number of people who understand is growing,
we are still just a small speck
scattered across the country.
That's where people like you
and Ishida-kun come in.
I understand. I will be happy to help.
Actually, I would be honored to.
Just a little while ago,
I felt so powerless it made me nauseous.
But now, I can clearly
see the future with my own eyes.
Hey, lady!
Lady, please eat this tomato!
I grew it myself.
Thank you!
His tomatoes really are something else.
Wow, it's so good!
It has thick flesh and a strong aroma!
Now I realize that the tomatoes I've been eating until now weren't the real deal.
We've finally found something
we can eat without worry.
You're absolutely right!
But it's still a long way to go...
Mountain God!
Are you back to normal, Mountain God?
It's up to us to rebuild
the nature we've destroyed.
Reportage
"The Land of Anger"
To calm the land's anger,
to regain the lifestyle where humans live in harmony with nature...
Our journey only begins now.
RAW provider
Translation
Editing
Quality checking
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
True Noobow Gamer
Safe and
stable food
from
Japan's soil...
Safe and
stable food
from
Japan's soil...