Cream Lemon
Special issue
Translation from Japanese: Alexmalkavian, Niidou, Sevotart
Translation check & adaptation: Perevodildo
Quality check: JmePenseBon
Yokohama Deez '25
Episode 38
(Release date 06/25/1987)
After this opened Job his mouth, and cursed his day:
Let the day perish wherein I was born, and the night in which it was said.
Let that day be darkness; let not God regard it from above.
As for that night, let darkness seize upon it.
Lo, let that night be solitary, let no joyful voice come therein.
Let the stars of the twilight thereof be dark; let it look for light, but have none.
Why died I not from the womb? why did I not give up the ghost when I came out of the belly?
For now should I have lain still and been quiet, I should have slept: then had I been at rest,
As an hidden untimely birth I had not been; as infants which never saw light.
There the wicked cease from troubling; and there the weary be at rest.
There the prisoners rest together; they hear not the voice of the oppressor.
Wherefore is light given to him that is in misery, and life unto the bitter in soul;
Which long for death, but it cometh not;
Why is light given to a man whose way is hid, and whom God hath hedged in?
For the thing which I greatly feared is come upon me, and that which I was afraid of is come unto me.
The Latin Vulgate Old Testament Bible
Job - Chapter 3, verse 1-26
I don't like this forest.
What's up? A breakdown?
Yeah. I tore the chain apart.
Are you from the seminary?
Yeah.
It seems God
has turned away from you today.
Yeah.
You really saved me!
If you hadn’t picked me up,
I'd have had to spend the night stranded in the woods.
Are you serious?
If you try to spend the night in such a place,
you'll get eaten by demons.
Huh? What do you mean?
They call these woods "The Demons' Forest."
Once, there was a castle in this area.
And, one day, the only son of its lord
went hunting alone in this forest.
He was never seen again.
Grief-stricken, the lord
decided to burn this forest to the ground.
But when he did, all the men in the country
fell ill with a mysterious disease and died.
Ever since then, they say if you enter this forest you won't come out,
so most people take
the long route around it.
I-Is that true?
It's just an ancient myth.
If a demon showed up in the age of SDI,
that’d be a hell of a sight.
Still, I'm truly thankful you didn't leave me
to camp out the night here.
You've helped me too.
Huh?
I mean, I got a chance to help a servant of God in need, right?
Surely Jesus will take this into account and send me to Heaven when the time comes.
You hungry?
Yes, thanks.
I'm Ned.
Student at the St. Mark's Seminary.
I'm Neil.
I'm a traveling artist.
It's burning!
We were saved by a hair's breadth,
but the car is bust.
Are we gonna have to spend
the night here, after all?
You're joking right?
Where, "here?"
Is this area still part
of the Demons' Forest?
That's just hearsay, remember?
But it sure is dark.
Now the fog’s rolling in too...
Like we’re in some B-grade horror flick.
Oh?
A coach?
Is there something wrong?
Your clothes, please.
Ah, no, there's no need.
Make yourselves comfortable, then.
Not bad.
It's my first time getting greeted
by antique dolls.
Kestner, Armand, Bru, Jumeau.
There's even Thuillier!
Enough to last you a lifetime.
You sure know a lot about these.
Just bits here and there.
Still, whose mansion is this?
We'll learn soon.
Yes.
You will learn soon.
Who said that?
I did. Right here.
Where?
Here. Right here.
Where is it?
O-Over there!
Welcome, gentlemen.
She's not a doll!
Did you mistake me for a doll?
Yes. You were so gorgeous, after all.
My, you flatter me.
So, are you in charge here?
Yes. My name is Maria.
There are only three living in this house: myself, Khayyam, whom you've met already, and one more person.
After all, we don't even have
a phone line around here.
Although our place is somewhat lacking,
please make yourselves at home.
Thank you.
My name is Neil.
And this is Ned.
Are you a seminary student?
Yes.
Did you come here on a trip?
No. Our principal tasked me with delivering this
to the Archbishop, who will be coming to Munich.
What's this?
One of God's miracles.
God's?
Yes. From what the principal has told me...
It is rumored that after Jesus was crucified,
his students hid his body, wrapped in a shroud.
Of course, this theory
is not recognized officially.
But the cloth that Jesus' body was wrapped in
was stored in our school all this time.
So it's up to the archbishop to confirm
whether it's a genuine miracle of God—
no matter how many times you wash it off,
Jesus' face appears on it.
Is that a real thing?
Of course, there's no telling
how much of it is true.
Hey now, as a seminary student,
you should at least show some confidence.
But it's really hard to believe.
Come in.
I beg your pardon.
This is our maid, Beth.
Nice to meet you. I'm Beth.
Yeah, th-the pleasure is mine.
Let’s start with some tea—
dinner’s still a ways off.
When we're done here,
it'll be completely dark.
Still, these are rather tasteless decorations.
This place is creepy.
"Paradise Lost?"
Too fitting for a creepy mansion
in the Demons' Forest.
"The angel Gabriel was sent by God to a city of Galilee named Nazareth,
to a virgin betrothed to a man
whose name was Joseph, of the house of David.
The virgin’s name was Maria.
The angel said to her,
“Rejoice, highly favored one, the Lord is with you!”
Beth...
She looks like a wonderful person.
Madam Maria is beautiful,
but a little intimidating.
My Lord, I've let an indecent thought
slip into my mind.
Please forgive my sin.
What, just some wind?
Tonight for sure... I must...
Really, what an intricate mansion.
Mr. Khayyam!
What, just an armor?
This way to the hall.
Who's there?
It'S me, Maria.
Please open.
M-Madam Maria...
Wh-What's the matter?
You're my guest
and I'm sorry to trouble you...
But you see, I wanted to take a shower before dinner, but the bath seems broken.
Could you perhaps take a look at it?
You'd be wiser to ask Mr. Neil
about something like that.
Mr. Neil went out, it seems.
Could you at least take a look?
A-All right...
I'll see what I can do.
Which way to the bathroom?
Down the corridor.
Not here...
Where could it be?
Excuse me, Madam Maria, where...
Madam Maria!
Just for one night, won't you turn your faith in God into love for me?
M-Madam Maria, what are you...
Don't be shy, fall into my arms...
Go ahead.
I-I...
I don't...
You've never seen a naked woman up close,
have you, student Ned?
Let me give you a full demonstration.
I mustn’t look... This is wrong...
Please stop, Lady Maria.
Take a look, Ned.
This is a woman's body.
They suck you in...
The doll's eyes...
It begins.
Come on, embrace me...
Hurry!
That's right. Be honest with yourself.
Isn't it foolish to suppress your desires
because some god said so?
Go ahead, use your tongue down there.
Yes...
That's good.
You are magnificent, Ned.
Yes... Like this.
It's you...
It seems I startled you. I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
Did you get burned?
No, I'm fine.
Good to know.
Yes, like that.
You're getting good at it.
God's servant eating me out
is a supreme pleasure!
That kind of life seems nice.
My wife cooking for me,
and me, always by her side, watching her.
Don't you think so, Beth?
Surely you jest, but I appreciate it.
Who's jesting?
I mean it!
It may be difficult to believe
when I say it so suddenly,
but I mean it.
I fell in love at first sight.
Would you like to run away with me?
I want to make you happy.
No!
Why not?
Do you dislike me?
I like you...
But we've just met, and when you say so,
you must think I'm an indecent woman.
How could I ever think that?
I'm happy, Beth.
Will you come with me?
No!
I can't do that.
Why?
It's impossible for me to leave this mansion, to leave Lady Maria.
I'll talk to Lady Maria myself.
No! You mustn’t!
Don't worry. I'll explain everything to her,
so that even Lady Maria will gladly let you go.
It's hopeless!
Lady Maria won't let me go!
Why's that?
Because...
You have no idea what the real her is like.
Real her?
No! I misspoke!
It's nothing... Forget about it!
I beg you, forget it
and don't bring this up again!
Beth...
I understand, Beth.
I heard you.
Come on, stop crying now.
Mr. Neil...
Just "Neil" is enough.
Neil...
Yes!
Give me more...
Yes! That's good!
Yes!
You...
So deep...
So good!
You're really good at this...
Y-Yes!
Like this...
Like this!
Maria, who'd think...
Who'd think you were that kind of girl...
Gave up already? Good...
Maria...
I'm falling into Hell...
I'm falling into Hell!
I love you, Beth.
Neil...
I will definitely make you mine one day.
Of course, I'll wait until you say "yes" first.
For as long as it takes.
Neil!
Ned!
You belong to me now, all of you!
A seminary student...
God's child...
The Antichrist will be born from your semen!
What?!
Our child will bring the Armageddon on earth
for the upcoming battle with God—
you will sire him, and I will carry him!
You're destined to die when we're done here,
but before that, let's savor the pleasure to the fullest.
No! You can't reach it either!
Sweet dreams, Ned!
Madam Maria!
Lady Maria!
Beth, what are you...
I'm sorry!
Know your place!
I am terribly sorry! I...
Lady Maria, please wait!
It's my fault.
Beth only followed my lead...
Mr. Neil, each house has its own customs—
please keep your foolish thoughts to yourself.
Madam Maria!
I'm sorry! Please, Madam Maria!
Beth!
Please stop.
Those human males are not good enough.
The dong of that guy Ned
couldn't reach my womb either.
This makes five of them.
The reason I feel this way
is because it's my seed as well!
I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
No, I can't forgive you.
And I'll make sure you learn this lesson
so that it never happens again!
Please forgive me!
You are at my service.
Did you forget?
Disobey me one more time,
and I won't stop at this!
Is that clear?!
I'm sorry! I won't...
Who's there?
Khayyam! Quit fooling around and get rid of it!
This meat is fresh and tasty.
Why won't you eat any?
Oh? Yes, I was just wondering
where Ned went.
That's true.
But your meat is growing cold.
I'm sure he'll be back soon.
Right, Beth?
Y-Yes...
That's strange...
What's wrong, Beth?
No, nothing.
Good.
What happened to Beth?
The meat really is good, though.
It's still dark in Ned’s room.
You can no longer call it slightly late. Ned...
Beth?
This is Maria.
Come in.
I wonder where Mr. Ned went—
he didn't even show up for dinner.
Yeah... It bothers me too.
You don't suppose he got eaten
by the forest demons?
Wh-What are you doing, Lady Maria?
It's not my fault Ned was no good.
No matter how hard I tried,
his thing just couldn't reach it...
Lady Maria, what are you talking about?!
Wasn't he delicious?
I guess all seminary studs are like that.
And he was also so tender, still a child...
Didn't you enjoy eating it—Ned's meat?
I'm gonna puke!
Oh no, are you unwell?
Then try licking this!
I wonder if you're better than he was.
Why... did you kill Ned...
His sperm was weak,
completely unfit for my child.
And he was so close
to fathering the Antichrist...
Then, are you...
Yes, Satan.
Well, let's see what you're made of.
Let go!
It's no use trying to resist it.
At the end of the day, you're the same as Ned.
Now, let's have some fun.
I said let go!
Wh-Why, you...
Neil, I'll fill you with lust!
No mere human can resist me!
Wh-What...
What? I can't move?
I'll let you get a good taste
of the Demon Messiah's semen.
That's a good boy, Neil.
Now, why don't you lose those boring clothes
and have some fun with me?
Wonderful, Neil!
Shit!
Think I'll let you lead me a merry dance?!
Didn't I say that it's no use trying to resist?
Stop!
M-My body can't move!
How can I get a hard-on?!
Can you feel it now?
I-Impossible!
It's as simple as that for me.
Ah! You look much more robust than Ned!
With this kind of manhood,
you might just be able to reach it!
Tens of thousands of maggots are swarming in excitement deep inside my womb!
You can't be serious!
I’d rather kill myself than fuck you!
Didn't I tell you it's no use trying to resist?
Besides, I'm ready for you now.
Ugh! You still don't get it?!
Neil!
Run!
Beth!
Beth, you...
Beth, come on, hurry!
Wait, Beth!
I won't let you get away!
Rise up, my servants!
Rise up and bring both Neil and Beth back to me!
Where should we go?
To Ned's room.
I've got an idea.
Watch out!
This way!
Almost there! It's at the end of this corridor!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
Come on, hurry!
That way!
What now, Neil?
I'm not sure, but Ned is supposed to be a seminary student.
So he should have with him a cross
or something else to scare the demons away.
Here!
But if it had any effect,
Mr. Ned wouldn't have died...
That's a fair point, though...
I know!
What is it?
It's here!
In here should be the cloth Ned told us about.
Maybe that'll save us.
It has a hard clasp!
They're here again...
Neil, here!
Thank you, Beth!
Let's see how you handle fire!
Beth!
Let go, you monster!
Hide in here, all right?
Neil...
Maybe this is our last meeting,
so I'll say it again: I love you, Beth.
I love you too.
Hide!
Neil!
Where is Beth?!
Like Hell I'll tell you!
There, perhaps?
Well, doesn't matter.
It only changes which one of you will die first.
Resistance is futile!
I believe...
Quick, run!
How come?! The Demons' Messiah, I, who was meant to become the Mother, would die here?!
Why? Why must I die here?!
I will survive...
No matter what...
I will survive!
It's all over now.
That's right. And you are free.
No—you are mine!
I'm so glad!
You're this wet already?
Oh no, don't tease me!
Well, here I come.
Does it hurt?
I'm happy!
It's incredible, Beth.
I can get so deep. It's sucking me in!
Neil!
I'm coming!
Me too.
You reached it...
B-Beth...
Time to say goodbye.
Wh-What do you mean, Beth?
You know what.
And I saw a beast rising out of the sea, with ten horns and seven heads, with ten diadems on its horns and blasphemous names on its heads.
One of its heads seemed to have a mortal wound, but its mortal wound was healed, and the whole earth marveled as they followed the beast.
And the beast was given a mouth uttering haughty and blasphemous words, and it was allowed to exercise authority for forty-two months.
Also it was allowed to make war on the saints and to conquer them. And authority was given it over every tribe and people and language and nation.
If anyone has an ear, let him hear:
If anyone is to be taken captive, to captivity he goes; if anyone is to be slain with the sword, with the sword must he be slain.
The Sacred Bible
The Apocalypse of St. John