In the near future, robotics have advanced
at a remarkable rate,
and robots can be found in all sorts of fields.
Among them, battles between small robots
called custom robots have captured people's hearts,
and people of all ages, from children to adults,
are thrilled by those battles.
The man standing at the top of these battles,
this consecutive winner
in the world of robot battles,
is reverently called by people...
the Custom Robo Master!
And one day...
Today, new robot models have been announced
by the Custom Robo maker Noise Factory.
Reporter Thomas Feynman
Noise Factory Stadium
The eye contact registration process with Robo Master
is scheduled to take place today.
Well, I made it myself, so I'm not sure what to say,
but Rei is a great model!
This will surely help Robo Master
extend his winning streak!
No way!
So that's a new Robo model?
Looks badass!
Hey, Koji, remind me, do you have
a Custom Robo of your own yet?
He scored poorly on his test, and it doesn't seem like he'll be allowed to own a Robo ever again.
Really? What a loser!
Don't laugh!
And now, the long-awaited moment
has finally come!
The new Robo, Rei, will soon be handed over
to the Robo Master!
Now's our chance! Do it!
Now's our time to snatch
that new Robo model for ourselves!
What? What's going on here?!
B-Bastard... Where is it?
Huh? What's this?
I-It's a Custom Robo!
Eye contact registration initiated!
Genes, personality, strong and weak sides...
80%.
90%.
Registration completed!
Hey! This Robo just scanned my face!
Wh-What does this mean?!
Koji-kun! Don't you even know
what the eye contact registration is?
Huh?
Eye contact registration is like
an initiation ceremony for your Robo.
The first person to make eye contact
with the robot becomes its one and only owner,
and once the owner's data is entered
into the robot's system, it cannot be changed.
Stupid brats... You snatched the Robo we were after… You'll pay for this!
Robo-dive!
Then I'll deal with you!
What are you gonna do?
You're still too inexperienced to fight with it…
Shut up!
Then please listen to the rules, at least.
First, the Robo owner
commands the dive to initiate the battle.
The match ends when the opponent
is forced to admit defeat or is unable to fight.
When you win, the opponent's parts data will be automatically recorded on the IC card
of the winning robot, and you can take it to a shop to get custom parts.
Got it?
He wasn't even listening.
C'mon! Bring it on! What are you, afraid? I'm right here!
Koji-kun...
Let's go! Robo-dive!
Huh? What's going on? My body can't move!
Huh? I'm standing on my head?
Is this what they call dive?
Feels more like I took over the Robo's body.
You'll regret coming here!
You won't like what comes next!
Koji-kun! You can't let you guard down for even a second during a battle! Get a grip!
Easier said than done!
Come on! Where'd all your bravado go?!
I just jumped in after him on a spur,
but how the hell am I supposed to fight a monster like that?!
You can't beat me in a thousand years!
What do I do?!
Look at that Robo. It's supposed to be
a new model, but he's ridiculously weak.
That's the commander, not the Robo.
I... I never thought Robo battles
could be this intense.
Playing hide and seek now?
You're an embarrassment to that new model!
I'm sick of running away!
Koji!
What's wrong?
Come on, grow a pair!
It's the heart that matters!
You're asking for too much!
There's no way you can win with just your heart!
No one was born strong!
Even the Robo Master only got there
thanks to his determination and hard work!
The most important thing in a Custom Robo
is the commander's heart!
Commander's heart?
Right...
I've become a commander too.
Now that I'm a commander, I can't lose!
Seems you've finally given up!
Commander and Custom Robo fight together.
And share the joy of winning!
You're that desperate already?
Then I'll turn you
into Swiss cheese as you wish!
He's too reckless!
What is he doing, getting closer?!
I have to commend your guts,
but only after I blast you in half!
Die!
Genocide bomb...
It's flying to his face!
I believe...
What? He caught the bomb?!
in the commander's heart!
A... A gap in my armor?
Bastard! We'll make you regret it!
Go ahead and face me again anytime!
That was amazing, Koji-kun!
Not at all like a rookie!
You fought well.
I'm impressed.
R-Robo Master!
I'm so sorry! I was only saved thanks to this Robo! I'll return it at once!
What are you saying?
This Custom Robo, Rei, is yours now.
That's right! I liked you too, kid.
Take care of it for me.
R-Really?!
Sure!
M-My Robo...
Rei!
Since you understand the commander's heart now,
you're a full-fledged Robo commander too starting today.
Grow stronger.
I will!
Yay! I got myself an amazing Robo!
Koji suddenly became the owner of the Custom Robo Rei, meant for the Robo Master.
His heart is now filled with a burning determination; to become an invincible Robo Master one day!
Now,  together with Koji and Rei, it's time for you guys to head into the fierce battle and to Robot-dive!
RAW by Mr.Robotics (YouTube)
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by JmePenseBon