Ah, a roller coaster!
Scary!
Coward! Chicken!
She was stung and she was bitten!
Sniff...
It's not that scary.
You'll be fine.
I'll try my best!
It actually wasn't that scary.
Amazing!
Yeah, you're great!
What about you, Tsuneko?
If Nono-chan can ride it just fine,
why wouldn't I be fine too?
I wanna ride an even scarier one!
Whew, that was scary!
Coward.
Enough for me.
I'm feeling sick.
Coward.
Tsuneko-chan, didn't you shriek on this one?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
I was just ya-w-ning!
Let's ride the Fighting Pirates next!
I'll take a break.
Me too.
You guys are no good!
Let's go by ourselves.
What now?
I mustn’t let myself scream again.
I'm starving.
You're right.
Let's grab something to eat.
You're not eating?
In your dreams!
When you're done,
let's hit the star attraction.
I'll ride it!
I feel that I'll be fine.
Yeah!
Tsuneko-chan.
Are you okay?
I'm good!
Let's get in already.
That was so fun!
Tsuneko-chan?
I didn't even feel it.
I'll ride it again!
Awesome!
She let go of her hands!
Tsunta-kun... is actually a punk!
Our reserved Tsunta-kun?
Ain't no way!
He's so quiet all the time.
For a moment there,
I thought it's true.
But his hairstyle is normal.
Miyo's sporting a London-style bob.
But Tsunta's hairdo is too plain.
Hey, what's a punk?
Ugh!
It’s annoying when a kid like that joins in—
she doesn’t even know what a punk is.
I don't understand
why you can't explain it! Tell me!
Nothing’s more pathetic than trying to explain
a lie someone tossed out as a joke.
Why should I tell you if you're constantly teasing me? Aren't we enemies?
Wasn't that Tsunta-kun just now?
Huh? Where?
He ran over that way,
wearing sunglasses and a sleeveless shirt.
Hah! She really did it.
Ignorance is a scary thing!
You probably don't even realize that lie
you just made up repeats what I've heard.
Huh? When did I copy anyone?
That's just what I said earlier,
that Tsunta-kun is a punk.
Really? So being a punk is about
wearing sunglasses and sleeveless shirts?
No, now that I think of it...
What is wrong with me, really!
To think I'd forget my all-important abacus!
I'm positive it was Tsunta-kun.
But Tsunta-kun should be
at his abacus class by now.
Once a week, Tsunta dressed up as a punk
and took the train to a nearby town
to attend an abacus class.
The reason he dressed up as a punk
was because he wanted to stand out.
The reason he went to the nearby town
was because he felt embarrassed.
The reason he chose an abacus class
was because he tried to go to the London Night at Tsubaki House,
but of course they wouldn't let him in.
But if Tsunta went to an abacus class,
his parents would pay for the tickets.
Abacus
Class
Camden
Palace
Get seated already.
Okay.
If we take...
185 yen, plus 125 yen,
plus 820 yen, plus 821 yen,
plus 119 yen, plus 780 yen...
Tsunta-kun?
Yes!
It's 1,850 yen!
Wrong.
What about you, Michio-chan?
Yes.
It's 2,850 yen
Splendid!
Let's try a double neck.
Wow! Tsunta-kun is so cool!
280 yen, 150 yen, 591 yen,
356 yen, 305 yen, and 290 yen.
Ankichi-kun?
It's 3,858 yen.
Splendid.
Wrong again...
All right, let's reset.
All I have is an abacus!
Tsunta-kun threw his abacus.
Awesome!
He's so radical!
He's a true punk!
U-Um, I mean... Uhh...
You're that kid...
What was it? Sakuramochi...
Sakuramochi Ankichi!
I'm so happy! I can't believe
you even remembered me by my name.
W-Well, goodbye now!
I ended up catering to the public again...
I have to be more frugal.
Let's walk one station.
There was a girl who was put to sleep
every night at 9 o'clock.
She was forced to sleep
at 9 o'clock sharp no matter what.
There must be something interesting
happening at night after 9 o'clock.
That's how she felt.
Hey.
Have you ever stayed up late at night?
Hm? Yeah.
I sometimes stay up late to watch TV.
The shows they play at night
are way more fun.
Hmm, I see.
I'm tellin' you,
midnight ramen is the best thing ever.
Yeah, a beef bowl
also tastes better at nighttime.
What is it about sorting books at night that causes night to turn into morning?
Oh, it’s true! I just start reading one
by accident and forget all about sorting.
It happens to me too, whenever I try
to sort records. It really does!
I'm home!
I said, "I'm home!" Hello?
Sister.
Ah, Suneo, where's mom?
Mom went to visit our aunt in Yokohama
and will stay overnight.
She told us two to watch over the house.
What about dad?
Went on a business trip.
He said he'll be back tomorrow.
He told me to "Fully close the gas valve,
turn off all the lights, and go to bed at 9 o'clock."
Hooray! I'm staying up all night today!
Ah, you can't do that!
Mom wants us to go to sleep at 9.
She told me.
You're so daft, Suneo!
Staying up late is fun!
The ramen you eat at midnight
is a great deal tastier!
You know how to make ramen, sister?
Come to think of it...
You've never even made it before!
You make it.
Huh?!
No deal!
You're better with your hands than me.
By the way, what's for dinner today?
Ah, it's shrimp gratin!
You're so easygoing!
I need to eat a lot to build up stamina
and stay up all night!
Okay, it's done.
I'm going to sleep, Sister.
Don't forget to do your dishes.
Yeah, I remember!
The night is long.
He doesn't know how to enjoy life.
How about sorting some books?
I have fewer books than I thought.
Let's sort the records too!
They're even fewer than the books.
Kiriko-chan lied to me—
this nighttime TV is totally boring!
Maybe a ramen would cheer me up!
Suneo! Suneo!
Make me some ramen.
I'm going to tell mom.
I'm going to sleep.
It wasn't any better.
But now I’m stuffed and feel sick.
Maybe I should’ve asked him
to make me a beef bowl…
It's still only 2.
Let's go to the bathroom.
Hey, Tsuneko-chan.
Did you know?
When the night slips past 2 a.m....
Suneo!
I already made ramen for you!
C'mon, get up!
Ow!
Don't you leave without me!
I'll definitely tell mom.
Jeez! I'll never stay up late again.
If you're gonna do it, do it alone!
My favorite things...
Ice cream!
Chocolate!
Favorite... Things...
Biscuits!
Favorite things...
It sure is a pain...
That music homework they gave us today.
It's a breeze!
Songwriting is easy.
Th-That's a strong statement to make.
That's 'cause I do it all the time!
Eh?
You got a problem with that?
Uh? No, not at all...
You just need to let the song
flow naturally out of your mouth.
Just repeat after me!
I think I'm one of those people
they call a natural musician.
What? You got something to say?
No, it's just too sudden.
So how do you write lyrics and music?
All at once!
A-Amazing!
For example, when I get home...
We’re probably having
my favorite for dinner, right?
Don't you run around the house
at times like that?
Why should we?
To work up an appetite, obviously!
At times like that,
a song comes out nice and easy...
Today, it's rice with curry!
Hold up!
Maybe curry rice would rhyme better?
"It's curry rice..."
Today, it's rice with curry!
I see. So it's a poem!
My talent is almost frightening sometimes.
What's for dinner today?
Yakiniku.
I'll be bass.
I'm tenor.
Yakiniku!
Brother is bass.
Michiko is tenor.
Yakiniku...
Tsunta, go buy some eggs.
Okay.
Mother...
Excuse me, teacher,
where is the song supposed to start?
Mother!
We can't have you lose
to your peasant friends.
Brazil, Brazil, they have samba.
Maybe I'll get to eat a juicy mango?
This smell...
It's an onion!
Doesn't matter if you hate it.
You need to eat onions to grow smarter.
I need to write a song.
On-on-onion...
Ion...
I can't stand that smell!
If Tsuneko can do it,
there's no way I can't.
I don't have to think of it as an onion.
Imagine... Imagine...
That it's a chestnut!
Yes, that's better.
Chestnuts​, chestnuts,
chestnuts, chestnuts,
chest...
Ah, it's onions!
No good.
I can't make a song.
I'm so hungry...
You finished your song?
Omelet today...
Red ketchup!
That's terrible!
Well, do your best.
Hya! Omelet today!
With the yellow of the egg!
Mi-Mi-Mix it with flour!
Hamburger, hamburger.
Woohoo! Another great song
is already coming along!
I'm a genius!
I love hamburgers.
I like hamburgers too.
So we're happy together—
me and hamburger!
Encoding: Piyo-Piyo Productions
Translation: Perevodildo
Editing: Paul Geromini
Quality check: Muzussawa