School Ghost Stories That Truly Happened
Hi there.
The story you're about to watch
is a strange tale that happened at a school.
The ones who'll run into this mystery
are three close friends—
Ryota, Mina, and Manabu.
Ryota loves sports.
He's not too fond of studying, though.
Mina's a lively girl who can
hold her own against the boys.
But she's got a kind heart, too.
And Manabu-kun may not be great at sports,
but he's a top student and the class rep.
This is the story of those three as they face strange happenings at their elementary school.
So stick around for School Ghost Stories.
Now, Episode 1,
The Tale of the Poison Spider, begins.
This mysterious event started on the day of the closing ceremony, right before summer break.
All right, everyone, your long-awaited
summer vacation starts tomorrow!
We won't see each other for a little while,
so make sure you stay healthy
and keep a good routine.
Before we finish, there's
something important you need to know.
You might've heard it on the news
or read about it in the paper,
but last week a poisonous spider was found
at an elementary school in the neighboring town.
Thankfully, there haven't been any reports
of one near Midori Elementary yet.
Caution:
Redback spider
But if you see one,
don't ever try to touch it.
Tell your mom or dad right away.
Poisonous Spider at School
Closing ceremony
Summer vacation
All right, everyone, let's start cleaning up the classroom and the teachers' room before the break.
Class reps, come see me after your room's done.
Okay!
You can't run away like usual
when we clean the staff room, can you?
Shut up.
All right, now wipe down these desks.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, I heard the kid at that other school, the one who got bitten by the spider, is still in the hospital!
Ew, no way.
Oh right, I didn't hear it directly,
but they say one showed up at our school too.
For real?
A girl from Class 6-2 said she saw a huge
spider shadow in the corridor after club practice.
That's kinda creepy.
Is it? If one that big really existed,
that'd be awesome!
What was it called again,
that poisonous spider?
Something… "back-spider"?
Oh yeah, "Backstabbing Spider" or something?
It was "Redback Spider."
It's "Redback Spider."
They live in hot regions
like Australia, India, and Southeast Asia.
They're venomous—if you get bitten,
you might convulse, but you'll recover in a few weeks.
They're not aggressive, and they don't bite unless you grab them with your bare hands.
Spoken like a true professor's kid.
But could they ever grow over a meter long?
No way.
No spider species that big
has ever been found.
Hey, guys, I've got an idea.
An idea?
The Poison Spider Investigation Team?
Listen up. Starting today,
the school's on summer break.
But what if a giant poisonous spider
is hiding somewhere in the school right now,
and multiplies while nobody's around?
Who knows how many there'll be
when the next term starts!
So we're gonna find it before that happens.
How about it?
Yeah, sounds kinda fun.
Yes, let's do it!
All right, it's settled!
Eh, we can come out already?
Yeah, the janitor just finished
his rounds anyway.
Okay, let's move out.
Phew, that room was so stuffy.
We had to stay still for hours, after all.
What's with all that gear anyway?
What'd you bring?
That's a secret.
All right then, time to hunt some spiders.
Nothing weird so far.
Yeah, see? There aren't any poisonous spiders.
We just started looking!
It's so bright with the full moon tonight,
it's not even scary—boring, rather.
Ryota always comes up
with such childish ideas.
Poison Spider Investigation Team or not,
what's the point if nothing shows up?
Mina-Chan, that's a bit harsh.
Damn it, she sure likes to run her mouth.
I know!
All right...
Hey Ryota, isn't this the hallway
they were talking about?
Yeah.
Ryota, I'm sorry about earlier.
Oh, it's nothing. Don't mention it.
Hold on, I need to hit the bathroom.
Ryota?
Ryota, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine...
See?
C-Calm down, Mina-Chan.
Gotcha like that!
They're all toy spiders!
Man, I love seeing you jump like that!
Got your heart racing, didn't I?
No, Manabu, seriously, that was no fair at all!
That was your own fault.
You idiot, Ryota!
Idiot, idiot, idiot, idiot!
I'm done with you!
Hey, she stormed off first.
Let her be.
What poison spiders?
What monsters?
If you're here to scare us,
then come on out already!
Mina!
What's wrong?
What happened?
S-Spider, inside there!
S-Spider!
So it's here...
No way that thing's that big!
Hey, let's just call it quits.
No way, not after coming this far!
Then I'm waiting here.
Fine, but don't leave without us.
Jeez, she's so worked up she's seeing things.
Hey Mina, there's nothing here.
Look, Ryota!
What?
Run, you two!
Ryota!
Whoa, awesome!
That's huge!
N-Never seen a spider that big before!
Ryota, hurry!
Hang on, let me get a picture first!
Oh right, Ryota's a total monster geek.
Now's not the time for that!
I know!
Bug spray?
Ryota, get back!
Just one more shot!
Oh! They're scared!
All right...
Take this!
Stop!
Wh-What?
Please, don't kill the spiders!
Don't hurt them! Please!
Come to think of it,
they haven't attacked Ryota at all.
Yeah.
I-I'm Sekiguchi Ryota.
Nice to meet you.
Huh?
W-Wait, is she a ghost?
Ryota!
Ryota?
Huh?
Where am I?
Under the ginkgo tree.
Ginkgo tree?
Ah, right!
That woman!
You mean me?
Ah! She's here!
Come on, calm down!
You're not scared of giant spiders,
but ghosts freak you out? You're weird.
Sorry for scaring you earlier.
She's not a ghost, you know.
But...
Come on, just hear her out.
She's the spirit of the ginkgo tree?
She says showing herself to people in this form
is something really special.
I just... really wanted to save those spiders.
And what were those giant spiders?
I-I'm sorry.
It was just an illusion—
I made them appear big with my power.
See, the real ones are right here.
Redback spider!
This one?
These spider didn't come to Japan
because they wanted to.
The truth is...
According to the ginkgo tree spirit,
who appeared before us in her human form,
the redback spiders in this school came all the way from Australia,
hidden in shipping cargo bound for Japan.
But just because they're poisonous,
people see them as dangerous and kill them.
The ginkgo tree felt sorry for them,
so she used illusions to hide them from people,
and keep us from getting too close.
But that kinda backfired with Ryota,
since he loves monsters so much.
So what are you going to do now?
With my power,
I can't send them back to Australia.
All I can do is try to keep people away.
Hey, Ryota, can't you think of something?
We can't just leave them like this.
It's too sad.
Even if you say that...
Wait, maybe...
You got an idea, Manabu?
I'll ask my dad for help.
Maybe he can find a way to send the spiders home.
Yeah, your dad might actually
be able to do something.
Hey, Ginkgo Tree, I can't promise anything concrete,
but I'll do my best to ask him.
I'll ask too.
Me too.
So, can I tell my dad about the spiders here?
Please do.
Yay!
That's great!
Right!
Let's take a commemorative photo together!
You sure have a lot of cameras.
Oh no, oh no...
Guess it broke when you collapsed.
Geez, you're always like this.
Hey, that's not true!
It's already been two months
since that strange night.
With Manabu's dad's help, the redback spiders
were safely returned to Australia.
In the end, we couldn't really explain
what happened that night.
But we believe it.
We believe it really happened.
We've never seen the ginkgo tree take
human form again.
But maybe someday,
when something voiceless
is drowning in sorrow,
she'll appear before us once more.
I just have a feeling about that.
Hey, so how was it?
The spider story.
Huh? You weren't scared? Really?
Then next story is about meeting Hanako-san!
And now, Episode 2,
The Story About Hanako-san, begins!
And then, you do it like this...
I see.
And then this part goes here.
Done! All set!
Wow, Manabu-kun,
you really know how to use a computer!
I just watched my dad use one for work
and thought it looked fun,
so I started messing around with it and picked it up.
Hey, Ryota, you're being obnoxious.
Come on, class is finally over,
so why are we still studying? That's boring!
What's that supposed to mean?
This isn't studying!
Then what is it?
It's online communication!
You can use the phone line
to talk to all sorts of people
and see tons of information!
I wanted to look up stuff about music.
See? That's still studying.
There's sports info too,
like your favorite soccer and baseball.
Really?
And anime and games too.
Seriously?
You should've said that sooner!
Then, for today, let's choose...
Blue Sky Network
Cyber Feng Shui Plaza
Cat Net
Dynamic Van
Blue Sky Network?
Yeah, it's a network made
for elementary school kids like us.
All right, we're connected!
So, where should we go first?
Yes! Sports, sports!
Let's check out music!
Why's that?
What's your problem?
Okay, now.
How about a compromise: sci-fi!
Fine by me.
What's this "Mystery Club"?
Hm... I've never been there before either.
Then let's go check it out!
I wanna see too!
Okay.
Welcome to the Mystery Club
The purpose of this club is for everyone to share the strange experiences and rumors they've encountered.
If you're ever stumped by something mysterious, this place might be helpful.
Wait, is this a scary story thing?
What? Ryota, you scared?
Idiot! Of course not!
Oh really?
All right then, let's go.
How to Follow Hanako-san
The Legend of the Slit-Mouthed Woman
The Legend of the Slit-Mouthed Woman?
The Curse of the Human-Faced Dog
The Curse of the Human-Faced Dog?
Mystery of the Science Lab
Mystery of the Science Lab?
Ryota.
Ryota!
Wh-What?
You okay? You look pale.
Of course I'm fine!
Where are we going?
The Legend of the Slit-Mouthed Woman
The Curse of the Human-Faced Dog Hanako's past
The ghost in the music room
The wheelchair that chases you
The Past of Hanako-san?
What's that?
Oh, that's Hanako-san who appears if you knock on the bathroom door three times.
You wanna see that one, Mina-chan?
Yeah.
"It happened more than ten years ago.
A certain incident at a school in northern Japan
was the start of the Hanako-san rumor.
A girl who went to that school
was bullied over and over by her classmates.
One winter day, while she
was locked in the bathroom,
snow piled up so high that the roof collapsed.
Trapped underneath
the snow and debris, the girl died.
That girl became Hanako-san,
and to take revenge on those who bullied her,
she began appearing in school bathrooms,
dragging anyone she met
into the world of the dead."
That's kind of a sad story.
Yeah, but remember what it said later on?
There was a boy named Jiro
who always stood up for her.
Yeah, but he transferred away
soon after, right?
So what about it?
Maybe Hanako-san still appears in the bathroom
because she wants to see Jiro again?
Come on, it's just a rumor.
Who cares?
Still, if it's true, it's kind of sad.
And what if it's revenge instead? Then what?
Ryota...
But...
It's over.
So, Ryota, what are we doing today?
Wanna keep going with the online thing?
Sure, sounds good.
It's Saturday anyway, we've got plenty of time.
Looks like you're hooked now too, huh?
Huh?
Mina-chan?
Ah, sorry, I've got some
family stuff to take care of.
What's with that attitude?
Let it go. It's just family stuff.
Today was kind of dull.
It just doesn't feel right without Mina.
I wonder what's up with her.
She was acting strange earlier.
Ah...
I know—let's stop by her place.
Good idea.
Conditions for meeting Hanako-san
But she said she had errands, didn't she?
And now she's going back to school
to get something she forgot?
Don't be stupid.
Mina went back to meet Hanako-san.
What? But that's just an old rumor!
I don't know, I've got a bad feeling about this.
Someone logged into
Blue Sky Network right after us.
It's gotta be Mina.
Can you tell where she went?
Wait a second...
"On a day of red sunset,
in the second-floor girls' restroom
bathed in the evening light, open the door as the school's closing melody plays."
That's it!
The school's closing melody...
just started!
Let's hurry!
Yeah.
Hanako-san?
Hanako-san, can you hear me?
You're looking for a boy, right?
That boy's name... it's Jiro, isn't it?
Jiro...
You know Jiro-kun?
Yeah. I learned all sorts of stuff about you
through the computer network.
Listen, Hanako-san...
Your death happened a long time ago.
So even if Jiro's still alive,
he'd be an adult by now, and you...
I want to see Jiro-kun.
Where's Jiro-kun?
I'm telling you, Jiro-kun's already...
Why?
Why won't you let me see Jiro-kun?!
No, that's not what I meant!
You're all terrible!
You bullied me and laughed about it!
I'll never forgive you!
I'll never forgive anyone who hurt me!
Mina!
Ryota!
Mina, hurry!
You too!
You came here to bully me too!
Hanako...
Mina!
Hey, Mina, are you okay?!
D-Damn it!
What do we do, Ryota?!
Don't just panic—think of something!
You're a professor's kid, aren't you?
That's got nothing to do with this!
I know!
You can just die for all I care.
I'll send anyone who bullies me
straight to the other world!
Jiro is an idiot!
Jiro is a coward!
Jiro is a dimwit!
Jiro is a dummy!
Jiro is a blockhead!
Jiro is a crybaby!
Jiro is a mommy's boy!
Jiro is a coward!
Jiro is a cheat!
Jiro is a weakling!
Jiro's... uh...
You.
You're the one who badmouthed Jiro-kun.
It's you.
I won't forgive that.
I won't forgive anyone who speaks ill of Jiro.
I'll take you too—
to the other side with that girl.
Y-You've got it all backward!
Th-That girl, Mina wasn't mocking you!
She was trying to help you find Jiro!
Don't lump her in with the ones who hurt you!
I mean it! Don't you dare take her away, ever!
I won't ever let you!
You like that girl, don't you?
I-It's not like that.
It's just that I can't stand seeing
someone innocent suffer for nothing, that's all.
I see.
You're that girl's Jiro-kun.
Do you want to protect her?
Yeah.
No matter what?
No matter what!
All right.
Then I won't be taking her.
Really?
Yes.
But promise me
that you'll keep protecting her.
Sure! I promise.
Thank you.
Ryota...
Ryota!
You okay?
Yeah...
And that's how our strange encounter with Hanako-san came to an end.
Since that day, none of us...
No, rather, not a single person
at school has seen her again.
Let's check out the soccer network today!
No way—music!
Soccer!
Music!
It's gotta be soccer!
It's music, obviously!
Would you two give it a rest already?
Snow!
Why is it snowing in here?
Oh, I bet it's Hanako-san.
Maybe she's telling us not to fight.
I wonder if she ever found Jiro-kun.
Yeah, I'm sure she did.
Aren't you glad that Mina-chan
wasn't taken away?
And Ryota, for someone who hates ghosts,
he sure held his ground.
I hope Hanako-san gets to see
Jiro-kun again someday.
And that wraps up today's story.
Thanks for watching till the end, everyone.
I hope we can all meet again someday, somewhere.
Until then, be careful
about what you encounter at school.
Because that strange rumor everyone's whispering about
might just be true, like the one we've just seen.
But that's all for now. Bye bye!
Translation: Perevodildo (of Blasphemboys)
Raw: hazel
The End