Hotaru Kagayaku
Shining Fireflies
Teacher!
Oh, it's Takashi and the others?
The fireflies are flying, right? They'll fly today, right?
Of course they'll fly! We in the Firefly Club
have raised larvae for a year!
It's already June though.
They're already flying everywhere else.
Perhaps they won't fly this year...
I wonder what went wrong...
You all worked so hard.
Maybe they'll fly if we wait a little bit longer!
Waiting any longer isn't gonna do no good!
Playing catch-ball is more fun than fireflies!
Let's go, Takashi!
Sure!
Wait, you two!
We're out of here!
Jeez!
Here it comes!
Okay!
Catch!
Nice ball!
Oh?
There!
Here!
Fine!
Taka-kun, Akira-kun!
Isn't it the Firefly Club day?
Ah! Welcome back, mom!
We're done with the whole Firefly Club thing.
Hup!
See ya!
You see, the teacher said the fireflies
may not fly this year.
Is that so?
And I so wanted to see the fireflies you raised fly about.
You know, when I was about your age,
the fireflies actually saved my life.
Fireflies saved you?
That's right.
You see, Japan was waging war against China back then.
And so, a country called Manchukuo was forcibly created
in what is now the northeastern region of China,
where a great many of Japanese families were living.
But Japan lost the war.
So a lot of children got separated from their families
and were left behind in China.
I was myself on the verge of not being able to return to Japan.
You too?
Back then, me and my family
lived in a Chinese city called Dalian.
AUGUST 1945
AUGUST 1942
Me, my younger brother Hiroshi and my mother,
took a train from Dalian to Rason, where my father was.
SHINKYO
b
Tumen
F
Rason
a
Japan
c
Dalian
E
Are we there yet?
Hey, sit quiet now, will you?
I wish I could see dad sooner...
We're almost there.
Almost!
However, on the day we arrived at Rason,
the Soviet-Japanese war broke out.
Rason
a
SOVIET
b
And because the Soviet army was in the immediate vicinity,
We had to immediately turn back to Dalian
without ever getting a chance to see father.
Mom, are we going all the way to Dalian on this freight car?
We were lucky to catch any ride at all.
You should bear with it.
You hang in there too, Hiro-chan.
Okay...
Mom, I'm hungry...
Just a little more. Bear with it.
I can't, I can't! I'm so hungry!
Hiroshi...
It's the enemy!
The enemy is gone!
There's no telling if it doesn't come back...
Either way, let's try going outside!
Now, Chisato and Hiroshi,
hold tight to mom, will you?
It's alright!
Why...
Hey, mom! Why did this happen?
This is just what war is like...
The train kept going for another two days towards Dalian.
Mom, are we there yet?
Just a bit more. Stay strong.
When we get do Dalian, I can meet up
with my friends again, right?
That's right, so—
What now?
What's going on?
The railway track is busted!
There's no hope of fixing it now...
Alright, let's walk!
Fine.
Fine...
Hey, be careful!
Hey, take my hand!
There!
Dalian shouldn't be all that far by now.
You guys want to get home soon, right?
Yes.
Then let's keep our chins up
and push through.
Yeah!
However, even after we walked for two days straight,
the city of Dalian still wasn't in sight.
People camped on the ground as it became dark,
and then started walking again at dawn.
It was a repetition of that.
Mom!
Seems like we're borrowing
this place's hospitality for tonight.
A watermelon!
A farmer agreed to share it with us.
I'll split it now.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I'm starving already!
Here, Hiro-chan.
Thank you!
Here, Chi-chan.
What about you, mom?
This is your share for tomorrow.
Mom...
What's the matter? Eat up now, dear.
I saw something over there!
My, what are you doing out there?
Come over here.
You must be hungry, right?
Come on! Sit with us and eat some.
Mom, that's...
Wait!
Being all alone out here in the night...
It must be very difficult for you, right?
Feel free to rest here with us for tonight.
You're Shibata Yoshikazu-kun, right?
You did well to come this far all by yourself.
A commendable feat.
My father was killed by the enemy airplane attack.
Your father?
Mother also got wounded. Later...
A Chinese lady was looking after my mother and me.
But I...
I left mother behind and ran away.
My...
Your mother must be awfully worried.
Like she'd ever worry about me!
She's not even my real mom!
But she was the one who raised you, right?
In any case, you're welcome to stay and rest here tonight.
Okay.
Thank you, ma'am!
Aren't you glad?
I hope this rekindles your determination
to keep doing your best, together with your mother.
I think Yoshikazu-kun should return to Dalian with us.
But you know, his poor mother is injured and can't travel now.
She only has Yoshikazu-kun to rely upon.
Cheer up, Yoshikazu-kun.
Ma'am... Thank you... I... I'm...
Yoshikazu-kun?
I'm going back to where mother is!
I'm sure you'll manage to return to Japan, Yoshikazu-kun.
Let's meet up someday!
Sure. I'll never forget you all!
Oh, right!
Here, take this!
What?
A marble!
So pretty!
Thank you!
Bye!
Be careful!
Goodbye!
Goodbye! Stay safe, everyone!
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Now, we should get going too.
Yeah!
Mom?
Everyone started crossing over.
Come on! Just a bit further! You can do it!
Come on, let's cross over too.
We'll be at Dalian as soon as we cross.
I'm scared!
Mom!
It's all right. If you muster all of your courage, we can cross.
Don't you want to return home soon?
Yeah...
Mom...
Hang in there, we're almost through.
Hang in there, sis!
Come on.
Mo—
Chi-chan!
Sis!
Please! Help!
Chi-chan!
What is this place?
What happened to mom and Hiroshi?
Dad!
Dad... Mom...
I don't want to die out here all alone.
I don't want to!
A firefly!
My, how pretty it is!
It's so gentle, so warm. Feels nice!
Hiroshi! Mom!
Yoshikazu-kun!
Yoshikazu-kun?
Maybe he can't hear me?
Chi-chan.
Huh?
Chi-chan. Can you hear me?
Who's there?
I'm the Forest of Life.
The Forest of Life?
No need to be so surprised.
This place is a gathering spot
for all the kind souls that value life.
Wrapped in a kind soul,
any and all things can be restored.
And then, just like this forest, they can all live in peace.
In peace?
Then there's no war in this forest, right?
Yes, precisely so!
Look here.
Such a small firefly, for example.
Be it even just for a short spell, until the very-very end,
it'll shine the light of its life as best it can.
As best it can... The light of life?
Wow! Beautiful!
As long as the light of my life shines,
I must keep doing my best too, just like the fireflies!
I'm never alone!
Then, I...
Came to my senses in a hospital.
If it wasn't for the fireflies coming to the riverside back then...
I'd have died.
So the fireflies saved you, huh?
The fireflies granted me the strength to live.
That's how I realized that the Forest of Life
always exists in our hearts.
If you have a kind heart,
you can live in peace anywhere in the world.
In my heart too?
Yes.
The Forest of Life is a stunningly beautiful forest,
brimming with fireflies!
Hey, mom, now I wanna go to that forest too.
You can go there!
If kind hearts come together to protect all the life,
the whole world will be transformed
into a Forest of Life where everyone can live in peace.
The fireflies won't fly this year!
Didn't I tell you it's pointless?
Don't worry about that, just come!
I don't wanna! I quit the Firefly club, remember?
You can't quit! You worked hard with everyone.
Whatever it takes, I gotta show it to my mom!
To my late father too.
Akira, fireflies!
Fireflies are flying. They flew!
Mom!
The fireflies flew!
In my heart too,
there is the Forest of Life!
Translation / timing / typesetting
TLC
Raw provider
Glenn
Perevodildo
WOWmd