This work is a doujin anime, an attempt at new forms of expression.
Additionally, this work is fiction and has no relation to any real people, groups, or existing works.
Furthermore, this work was created for private viewing purposes only.
Reproduction or public screening without the author's permission is prohibited by law.
Those under 18 are forbidden from purchasing or viewing.
I'm coming in, Dad.
Humanity
Complementary
Fornication
Plan
Encoding
Translation
Editing
Lain32
Perevodildo
imatu
The year is 20XX AD.
Humanity was struggling with an abnormally low birth rate.
In response, a certain organization proposed a project: the “Humanity Complementary Fornication Plan.”
Everything was entrusted to this plan...
D-Dad...
Oh, you're late.
What took you so long?
What the...
What on earth is going on here?
The Humanity Complementary Fornication Plan.
This is your father's job.
This... is Dad's job?
Come on, stroke it properly.
Come in.
Okay.
What are you...
Put it in.
If your hands are free,
stroke this one too.
It's a little yellow.
Do it, son.
I can't do it right away, Dad.
Do it.
I can't!
Then get lost.
Chief?
I don't care.
If you can't do it, we don't need you here.
Jeez, are you really that feeble?
Come on, just embrace it and enjoy yourself.
He's cumming inside!
Filling me up completely!
Come on, let's get it done.
You have nothing to worry about.
They're cumming inside both my holes
at the same time!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Wow, so many cocks!
Yes, that's good...
Your dick is so hard and perky!
It's amazing!
Push it deeper inside me.
It's coming out!
Do it! Fill me up good!
You can still shoot such thick stuff!
Come on, let's go for another round.
Now it's our turn to play with you.
I'll show you how grown-ups fuck.
Come on, eat it.
Hey, why don't you try it with us next?
Whoa, it's happening again!
I'll give you lots of fanservice!
Here, I'll teach you the taste of a grown-up.
Ah! You've got a really nice, thick penis,
just like your father.
The liquid keeps dripping out of you.
Ah! That's good.
Alright, I'm putting it in!
Whoa, I felt it!
It's like I was born just for this moment!
Use your tongue to serve us properly.
Whoa, to think that I got to fuck a babe this cute.
How's that? Feels good, right?
The taste of an adult cock is on another level, huh?
Amazing... It's amazing!
It's so thick and wonderful!
Your sync rate is dropping.
Well... you girls prefer
adult men too, don't you?
Pull yourself together!
Are you trying to run away again?
Look at these two.
They're all kids the same age as you.
Are you even a man?
I can't hold back.
I'm gonna cum inside you right now.
No! Don't cum inside, pull out, please!
Too late. I just creampied this cutie real good.
So much came out...
now who would take me as their bride?!
I'm still gonna pump plenty more inside you!
If you cum inside me today,
I'll get pregnant.
Ugh... I can't hold back.
I'm gonna blow my load all over your cute face!
Alright, a massive creampie is coming up.
Get pregnant, take it all inside!
They're cumming inside me!
I mustn't... run away!
Mustn't... run away!
Mustn't run away!
Mustn't...
run away!
Look, I'm gonna fill your womb
with plenty of my seed!
More... put it all inside my vagina!
Here it comes, take it all inside.
Alright, more fanservice for you!
Don't cum so much!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Here comes the creampie!
I just unloaded everything deep inside you.
This should guarantee pregnancy.
Congratulations.
THE END