First Friend
Good evening, everyone.
I am Ernest Thompson Seton, the
author of the Animal Chronicles.
Starting tonight, I will tell you a
story about Jackie the Bear.
Around 100 years ago, barely 100 years after
the independence of the
United States of America.
Right in the middle of the Sierra
Nevada Mountains, which rise
to the east of California on
the border with Nevada.
A boy lived near a beautiful lake called Lake Taho.
This story is about the wonderful friendship between the
boy and a bear cub living in the nearby Tallac Mountains.
Of all the cedars in the world, the American variant grows the biggest.
Among them, under the tallest
cedar tree on Mount Tallac,
lived a large grizzly bear
nicknamed Pinto.
During her long winter hibernation, Pinto had twin cubs.
They were siblings, an older brother bear and a younger sister bear.
Come on, it's okay.
Come on out, kids.
It's too bright!
What's wrong? It's all right.
Hurry up and come out.
This place is so bright...
Yeah...
Come on, kids. From now on, you're free to play here all you like.
Be careful.
Can we really play in such a big place?
Oh, it's cold!
What's this stuff?
It dosen't smell like anything.
Son, this is snow, you know.
Wow, this is snow?
It's snow! It's snow!
Brother, it's cold!
Wait!
Stay away from me, brother!
Help!
?
Son!
Come on, you just came out.
You have to be more careful.
Wow! That was a shock...
Huh?
Oh, Mother!
What's that shiny thing?
That thing? It's called a lake.
It's pretty...
Hey, Mother, let's go to it!
Calm down, son.
This is your first time outside.
Besides, there are humans around there, so you have to be careful.
Humans?
What's a human?
Humans walk around on two legs,
and are very scary enemies to us.
They're scary?
Hey, why are they scary?
I can't tell you right now.
Come on, let's go find
something to eat instead.
Your mom's already really hungry.
Yes, Pinto was hungry and dazed.
And it was no wonder.
Before going into her long winter sleep,
she had to eat as much as she could.
Five months later,
she hadn't eaten a thing,
and had been feeding her cubs
milk the entire time.
Can we really eat this stuff?
I wanna try it too.
Right, I'll get it out.
?
Hey!
Hey, wait!
Stop it!
Wait up!
Cut it out!
Hey!
Stop it!
- What's wrong?
- Look.
What's that?
It must be one of those
humans Mother told us about.
No way! It dosen't look that scary.
Let's go after it.
I don't want to. I'm scared.
I'll go alone, then!
Stop!
Brother...
Where's it going?
?
Wait up!
Where did it go?
It's in there!
That was a surprise!
That's where Mother said humans live.
But what kind of animal is this scary
thing that walks on two legs?
Right, I'm gonna check it out!
Ow!
Ah, it must be Lan.
He's hiding, right?
Okay, let's get 'em.
Gotcha!
Huh? He's not here...
Grandpa Rocky!
Ah, so that's were you've been hiding.
You got me again this time.
Hello, Grandpa Rocky.
Did you get any work done today?
Nope. I haven't found a single nugget in three weeks.
Huh?
Really?
Hey, don't worry about it.
When you look for gold,
you can do it as much as you want.
This river was the start of an amazing
gold rush thirty years ago.
But those people gave up on
finding gold and left a long time ago.
Grandpa Rocky's the only one
still going at it, right?
Huh?
Oh, they were just a bunch of
bad people with no patience.
These days, everyone runs away from hard work when they can't make a profit.
I guess they didn't want to do such a hard job.
So why do you keep doing it?
Let's see... The road ahead isn't
about making money.
This is a job a man could spend
the rest of his life doing and not regret it.
Whether I get out of debt or not, it doesn't matter.
It all depends on God's will.
Anyway, it's important to work in the river until you die.
I don't really get it.
Maybe it's still a bit hard for you to understand.
You'll figure it out in time.
By the way, it's about this time that the bears come out of their dens looking for food.
You need to be careful when you play alone.
It's okay, Grandpa Rocky.
I have this bow!
My dad taught me how to use it, and I'm really good at it.
Oh, I don't doubt it,
based on what I saw earlier,
but you can't go up
against a bear with it.
I was born and raised in these woods and by this lake.
There's nothing to be scared of. Well, see ya!
Oh, come back!
Watch out, watch out!
I'll be fine!
Wait up!
That's it!
Here goes!
Ow...
Wait up!
That's it!
It has two legs...
I see. So that's a human. But it's so small.
It's a bear cub!
You've just been born, haven't you?
There's no need to be scared. Come on, come here.
Oh, right.
You're scared of this, right?
See? You're not scared anymore, right?
You see?
I'm a friend.
Yo.
Kellyan, how are you doing?
Hi, Grandpa Rocky.
Found any of God's dried rice?
It's no good. I think God
still dosen't approve of me.
But the cold water from the
melting ice takes a toll on me.
So could I come in and warm myself by your fire?
Of course. I'll add some wood to it now.
I feel like I've come back to life.
By the way, Kellyan, I just saw Lan.
Yes, he said he was going out to play.
But Kellyan, this is the time when bears come out to roam.
If he runs into one...
What? I told him not to go far, so he'll be fine.
Oh well. That boy's got a lot of energy, and that's what worries me.
So this is a human...
Something smells good.
Oh, yeah. Do you like the way this smells?
What do you think? Tasty, isn't it?
That candy was given to me by Alice,
a girl who lives on the ranch.
Alice is a friend of mine.
Let's be friends, too.
I guess it can't be helped. You can eat
them all as a sign of our friendship.
It's delicious, don't you think?
Hey, don't tear it!
Look, it's empty.
Look, look! This way, This way!
You can't catch me!
Come on!
Yeah, this way!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Look!
Come on, come on!
Don't be scared! Scaredy-cat!
Come on, come here.
That tickles!
Brother, where are you?
Hurry up!
Come on, come on!
What are you waiting for?
Something got caught!
Maybe a rabbit or a fox?
Well, that's it then.
Sometimes deer fall in by mistake.
Oh, that would be great!
Well then, I'm coming with you.
Don't be scared, it'll be okay.
My dad will be here soon.
Calm down.
You still haven't gotten over the habit
of sucking on your mother.
By the way, what's your name?
Ah, that's right.
You don't have a name, do you?
I'll give you a name, then.
Let's see...
Jack!
Jack is a nice name.
Since you're little, I'll call you Jackie.
Jack was the name of my grandpa,
chief of the Motok tribe.
It's Captain Jack's name!
From today onward, you're Jackie.
Hooray for Jackie!
Oh, Kellyan!
Could you please go a little more slowly?
I'm good at water.
But I'm too old for this mountain road...
What happened to Jackie,
a bear cub who made friends
with Lan, a human,
for the first time?
They accidentally fell into a trap.
But Lan's father and Grandpa Rocky didn't know that.
And the mother bear, Pinto,
was rushing madly to the trap.
I'll see you next week for the rest of this story.
Lan's father and Grandpa Rocky went to the trap and saw Pinto, the mother bear.
They couldn't move at all.
Suddenly, Pinto felt their presence and stood up on her hind legs.
Next time, on Jackie the Bear Cub,
"The Dangers of the Forest" Look forward to it.