Animated film commemorating the 30th anniversary of his death:
The Life of Kagawa Toyohiko: I Die Daily
I Die Daily
The Biography of Toyohiko Kagawa, the Father of Agricultural Cooperative Mutual Aid
Original story by Kiyoshi Usui, Adaptation and illustrations by Hikaru Ichijoji
This movie is an animated version of the original story.
Kagawa Toyohiko, the father
of the cooperative movement,
was a great religious man, thinker,
novelist, scientist, and social activist.
Until his death at the age of 72 in 1960,
at his home in Kamikitazawa, Setagaya Ward, Tokyo, his life was marked by great turmoil.
His is a history befitting
a world-renowned figure born in Japan.
Kagawa Toyohiko was born on July 10, 1888,
in the port city of Kobe, Hyogo Prefecture,
to a concubine mother.
He spent his youth in hardship, burdened
by his father’s demise and his family’s downfall.
Until April 1900,
when he met Dr. Harry W. Myers,
Tokushima Middle School
an American Christian missionary teacher,
while attending Tokushima Middle School.
This fateful encounter with Dr. Harry W. Myers
determined the whole life of Kagawa Toyohiko.
Dr. H.W. Myers
Brother, can I move to live with
an American missionary to learn English?
A missionary?! No way!
He'll convert you to Christianity!
Is something wrong with Christianity?
We have Buddhism right here in Japan!
I can’t let my kin become Christian—
it goes against our national identity!
Japan doesn't have a monopoly on salvation!
Who do you think you are?!
Shortly thereafter, the Kagawa family
went bankrupt due to his brother's reckless business ambitions and lavish lifestyle.
The creditors pounced on them,
and even the family estate had to be auctioned off.
Ultimately his older sister and younger brothers
were all sent into apprenticeship.
Having lost everything,
Toyohiko embarked on a spiritual quest
and asked Dr. Myers
to baptize him at his parish.
It was February of 1904,
when Kagawa was 16 years old.
In March 1905, he graduated
from Tokushima Middle School.
Congratulations, Toyohiko.
So what are you going to do
after middle school?
I want to join the Meiji Gakuin University in Tokyo
and become an evangelist.
An evangelist? Are you stupid?!
We won’t tolerate deranged Christian fanatics under this roof! Get out!
Now that even his uncle’s kicked him out,
he’s been left utterly alone in the world.
He had nowhere to turn
but Missionary Meyers’s place.
That's regrettable.
But I don't want you to worry,
you can stay here from today on.
T-Teacher!
In April 1905, Kagawa moved to Tokyo.
Extra Edition!
The Baltic Fleet is coming to the rescue
At the time, Japan was in the second year
of the Russo-Japanese War.
Tokyo, the capital,
was steeped in militaristic fervor.
When Kagawa entered Meiji Gakuin University in Shiba-Shirogane,
his passion for life was rekindled in his heart.
Jesus, please cleanse those corrupt souls
and set the world straight again. Amen.
Kagawa holed himself up in the library
and read through thousands of books,
one volume a day, without fail.
There were many untranslated works,
but Kagawa could digest even them without trouble.
Kagawa, you’ve got to attend
at least a few lectures—
you won’t graduate
if your attendance is too low.
I don’t need to sit through those lectures—
everything they teach there,
I’ve already learned from Dr. Myers.
The following year, Kagawa transferred from Meiji Gakuin University to Kobe New School.
He then helped out with missionary work
in Aichi Prefecture for six months.
There he met Pastor Nagao of the Toyohashi Church,
who fought for peasants and the poor.
In later years, Kagawa said this about Nagao:
"Until the day he died,
he kept crying out in prayer
that the gospel might reach
the poor and the peasants.
It was from Nagao that I inherited
my love for the peasants."
Kagawa was staying in Nagao's rundown hut,
and spent the days preaching passionately.
God is love!
I'm not saying love is some invisible deity,
but love is the manifestation of the divine in us.
God is love!
During this period, a lung disease
undermined Kagawa's health.
His slight fever never subsided
and it seemed to everyone like an incurable disease.
Eventually, he started coughing blood badly.
His breathing was labored,
and his fever climbed past 40 degrees—
eventually, even the doctor gave up on him.
But Kagawa was not
in the slightest afraid of death.
Rather, he remained completely still,
as if he had returned to his mother's womb.
Suddenly, spiritual light
enveloped his whole body.
Mysteriously, his breathing gradually improved,
his fever subsided,
and his complexion returned to normal.
Kagawa sought a quiet place
to recuperate from his tuberculosis,
and he found it in the fishing village
of Gamagori, Aichi Prefecture.
It was January 1908.
While he continued
to recuperate here in poverty,
he began writing a novel that depicted his lonely life—"Mimicking the Pigeon."
By the time the cherry blossoms were falling,
the novel was completed.
Kagawa then traveled to Tokyo for the first time
in a year to have Shimazaki Touson read his novel.
By then Touson had already published his "Broken Commandment," taking the literary world by storm,
and was serializing "Spring"
in Asahi Shinbun newspaper.
This is a novel I wrote, please read it.
Look, you can't write a novel
by straight-up describing life.
Shimazaki Touson
Novels are art, so they must have
a spark of emotion to them.
Touson rejected his "Mimicking the Pigeon."
Mimicking the Pigeon
Across the Death-line
Later, in 1920, "Mimicking the Pigeon"
would still be published by Kaizosha,
retitled as "Across the Death-line."
It became an unprecedented bestseller, going through 50, then 100, and eventually 150 printings.
The day before Christmas in December 1909,
Kagawa became a resident of the slums
of Shinkawa, Fukiai, in Kobe.
He believed the damage from tuberculosis
had left him with no more than three years to live.
Figuring he was going to die anyway,
Kagawa chose to live among those
with no food, no clothes, and nowhere to sleep.
He had resolved to keep preaching on their behalf until his life burned out—and to die doing just that.
A new life begins for me.
I understand God bestowed it unto me.
God, give me strength to keep doing my best for the poor. Amen.
Life in the Kobe slums taught Kagawa Toyohiko the many different ways people struggle to live.
For Kagawa—who would later become a leading voice in labor and peasant movements—
this way of life was a formative experience in his struggle against social injustice.
Soon, together with the people who gathered around him,
Kagawa established a church
in a six-tatami room he was renting.
It became the base for the
Kobe Jesus Society, organized later.
In the summer of 1911, Kagawa began working at the Fukuin Printing Company as a hymns teacher.
There Kagawa met
his lifelong partner Shibata Haru.
They got married on May 22nd, 1913,
at Kobe Church on Shimoyamate Street.
On August 2nd of the following year, 1914,
Kagawa departed for America.
The purpose was to raise funds to create
a settlement in the slums of Shinkawa, Kobe.
What is a settlement?
It is a social institution that seeks to improve
the lives of workers living in slums.
What is a settlement?
It is a social institution that seeks to improve
the lives of workers living in slums.
Haru, I'm going to America to earn money.
There, I'll get my doctorate
and earn some money.
With that funding, we’ll build a state-of-the-art hospital right here in Shinkawa.
To cover his travel expenses, he borrowed money from Dr. Myers and his acquaintances,
and took on translation work.
America
At Princeton University in the US,
Kagawa studied experimental psychology,
mathematics and natural sciences.
He thus spent his days
at Princeton University studying hard.
During his second year at university,
Kagawa completed Princeton Theological Seminary’s four-year coursework in only two years.
He was granted a Bachelor of Divinity degree in theology.
Kagawa went to see Water Street,
the slum district of New York.
This is no different
from the Shinkawa Slum City in Kobe!
What is a worker?
Is worker synonymous to "pauper" now?!
If workers are unemployed,
they can only end up in poverty!
All the relief efforts so far will never truly solve the problem of poverty in the long run.
The key to solving this problem
lies in addressing the workers’ plight.
The workers' poverty—that's it!
Unless the proletariat join forces and rise up to free themselves,
who’s going to help them?!
The workers must unite!
Each one of them is weak alone, but once they band together as a union, they become a powerful force—
strong enough to win their own freedom!
In May 1917, Kagawa returned from the US
to the slums of Shinkawa, Kobe
Kobe Jesus Society
Let's build our own factory—
for workers, by workers!
Buying daily necessities cheaply is another way
to protect workers' livelihoods.
Consumer Cooperative Headquarters
To do that, we need to link consumers and producers directly—
cutting out the leech of the middlemen.
Consumers will form a cooperative
and buy from the producers—personally.
Common Benefit
Kagawa also drew on his Christian connections to launch a consumer cooperative in Osaka.
Kobe Consumer Cooperative Headquarters
The following year, the Kobe Consumer Cooperative was born.
It would become the predecessor of the Nada Cooperative,
a pioneer of the consumer movement in Japan.
In April of the following year, 1918,
Kagawa gave a passionate speech
Lecturer
5th Fraternity Association General Rally
at the 5th Fraternity Association's General Rally
at the Tennoji Public Hall in Osaka.
Why are workers usually poor?
The first cause is drinking—
most of them do physically demanding work.
The second cause is illness—once they get sick, they lose their jobs and fall into destitution.
The third cause is injury—workers who operate machinery can’t avoid getting hurt.
The fourth cause is the lack of social security—
economic tides can shift at any moment,
and you'll lose your job.
Fifth: workers are not slaves—they’re free!
And the very fact that, despite their freedom,
they still can’t make a living points to a major flaw
in the social system. Let’s not forget that!
He strongly advocated for a mutual aid system
and the cooperative movement.
Kagawa Toyohiko, the father
of the farmers’ cooperative movement,
was already convinced of that
when he gave this speech.
Two full years have passed
since he joined the labor movement.
At the age of 32, Kagawa Toyohiko
became the leader
of the Japanese Federation of Labor
in the Kansai region.
The worker is a human person,
not a commodity.
Kagawa’s ideas gave workers a sense of pride
and struck a chord with many of them.
It was also around this time that a conference of Christian clergy was held in Japan.
A new religious movement organization,
the Friends of Jesus movement, was formed.
Is this also the Lord’s guidance?
I must return to the spiritual movement
and to evangelism.
When Kagawa saw that the labor movement
could now stand on its own, he felt an increasing pull back toward the spiritual movement—
and a certain thought kept returning to him.
Namely, the sight of rural areas
and the faces of farmers
that he saw in his childhood
in Tokushima Prefecture.
We must save the farmers!
Extend to them the loving grace.
We can build an ideal society
with the hands of farmers.
The Japan Agricultural Cooperative
was born on April 9th, 1922,
at the Christian Youth Hall in Kobe.
Agricultural Cooperative Founding
The day before, 120 farmer representatives from rural areas across the country had rushed to Kobe.
In every sun-weathered face held high,
you could see the yearning for Sakura Sogoro,
the folk hero of the Taisho era.
The founding meeting
ended in a great success.
The farmers' movement also helped strengthen industrial cooperatives,
which eventually expanded to include sales, purchasing, credit, and even medical care divisions.
This general meeting laid the first cornerstone in Kagawa Toyohiko's grand vision
to cultivate mutual aid organizations and create an ideal society in rural Japan.
The founding of the Japan Agricultural Cooperative marked a turning point,
Tenants Farmers' Cooperative
igniting the farmers' movement
as it swept across the countryside like wildfire.
At the same time, Kagawa Toyohiko was more active than ever.
He gave Bible lectures, taught at a workers' school,
supported a consumer cooperative,
and, finally, as a man of letters,
toiled endlessly with pen in hand.
In December 1922,
Kagawa's first son Sumimoto is born.
But one day in January of the following year, 1923,
he suddenly lost his sight due to repeated overwork.
Lecturer
But even so, he didn't stop giving lectures.
Kagawa's eyesight kept deteriorating,
to the point where he was on the verge of going blind.
At last, he was forced into hospitalization.
His wife Haru carefully read the Bible
and the Philosophical Books newspaper for him.
Kagawa was determined to keep up
with the changing tides of the world.
Job was hit with seven disasters,
but he endured it and never gave up on his faith.
He didn't run away from pain,
but happily accepted all the pain in life.
In August, his eyes began improving.
Universal Suffrage Law Passed
The Universal Suffrage Law
was enacted in March 1925.
That means we workers and farmers
were given the right to vote too!
In March 1926,
the Labor-Farmer Party was founded.
Sugiyama Motojiro was appointed chairman
with Kagawa as the executive committee member.
I've founded this party, but I'm not going
to run for the Diet myself.
With the spirit of Jesus Christ in my heart, I intend to serve the proletarian party from behind the scenes.
Having said that, Kagawa continued
to live by those words for the rest of his life.
Both before and after the war, there was a fervent push to get Kagawa Toyohiko elected to the Diet,
but he never took office.
The Japan Agricultural Cooperative, which had now become the largest such organization in the country,
gave birth to the Labor-Farmer Party,
the first unified proletarian party in Japan—
Labor-Farmer Party Headquarters
Representative of the proletariat: Japan Labor-Farmer Party
a groundbreaking achievement
in the history of political parties.
However, even the
Labor-Farmer Party soon became
a battleground for internal strife between left and right factions.
On February 1st, 1927, the Japan Agricultural Cooperative ultimately split
due to infighting among the proletarian parties.
Sugiyama-kun, let’s start a new farmers’ union.
One free of violence, free of internal feuds—
one that is grounded in political ethics.
Thus, with Sugiyama Motojiro as its chair,
the All-Japan Farmers’ Union was established.
But Kagawa’s hope for this
new farmers’ union was short-lived.
Leftist extremism began to seep in.
Even the All-Japan Farmers’ Union
turned into a combative, militant organization.
This is troubling.
My struggle has also been derailed by these insane political movements.
I must withdraw
from the proletarian party.
But I am still a disciple of Jesus.
I will never surrender like this!
The new battle Kagawa sought to fight against social evils
would now be through
the Kingdom of God movement
rooted in the consumer
cooperative movement.
He aimed to liberate workers and farmers
through the teachings of God.
He prayed that by disseminating the idea of Jesus saving farmers, he'd rouse them to action.
Kagawa Toyohiko, now distancing himself
from the proletarian party
to pursue the Kingdom of God,
established a Danish-style
folk high school for farmers in Japan,
hoping to foster an agriculture
strong enough to overcome hardship
through new forms of rural education.
That approach was called
three-dimensional forestry.
Kagawa Toyohiko’s concept
of three-dimensional forestry
aimed to make use of Japan’s mountainous terrain—
which makes up 80% of the country and is one of the root causes of rural poverty—for food production.
On January 9th, 1931, Kurokawa Taiichi
received a telegram from Kagawa Toyohiko.
Kurokawa Taiichi
Kurokawa, who would later
serve as executive director
of the National Federation of Consumers' Cooperatives
and head the Tokyo Medical Cooperative,
was 29 years old at the time.
Kurokawa-kun, I’m glad you could make it.
I’ve decided to start a medical cooperative.
I’d like you to work on it together with Kidachi-kun.
A medical cooperative, Kidachi-san?
It's a hospital, modeled
after a cooperative, it seems.
First, I’d like everyone to hear why I believe such a medical cooperative is necessary.
If we compare cities to the countryside,
data shows that the mortality rate in rural areas
is nearly double that of urban areas.
This means that poor laborers and farmers
are being abandoned by the medical system.
Rural areas in particular
have become medical hellscapes.
My aim for this medical cooperative is to rescue these rural communities from that medical hell.
Since the Taisho era and throughout Showa, the number of villages with no doctor only increased.
And with that,
the rural mortality rate kept rising.
How can such a thing be allowed
to transpire in a civilized nation?
There is only one way to save
rural Japan from its medical hell:
build healthcare facilities under the
Industrial Cooperative Act in farming villages.
The farmers themselves must create hospitals
through medical cooperatives.
A medical system based
on cooperative principles
is different from a state-imposed system—
members and doctors alike share responsibility.
Everyone will strive
to fulfill their duties ethically—
that'll allow the medical services
to remain affordable.
Farmers will be able see doctors at low cost, and doctors will have no reason to flee the rural areas.
The way to banish medical hell from rural Japan
is to build medical cooperatives.
On May 11th, 1931,
Founding Meeting
a founding meeting for the Tokyo Medical Cooperative was held at the YMCA Hall in Kanda, Tokyo.
150 people attended.
There, Kagawa passionately spoke on the goals
of the medical cooperative movement.
Medical treatment must be available
to protect the sanctity of human life,
regardless of wealth or social standing—
that goes without saying.
Tokyo Medical Cooperative General Assembly
On April 25th, 1932,
the first general assembly
of the Tokyo Medical Cooperative
was held at the YMCA Hall in Kanda, Tokyo.
That very same day,
at Osaka’s Central Public Hall,
the 28th National Industrial Cooperative Conference was held,
and a five-year action plan
for the cooperative was formulated.
On May 15th, 1932,
Prime Minister Inukai was assassinated—
Prime Minister Assassinated By A Violent Attack
that would be called the May 15th Incident.
On July 9th, 1932, an inn was rented
in the 3rd Block of Shinjuku, Yotsuya Ward,
Shinjuku Clinic
and so the Shinjuku Clinic was born.
Though small, it was a general hospital
with departments for surgery, internal medicine,
pediatrics, obstetrics
gynecology, and dentistry.
From this modest base, we'll expand our network of cooperative hospitals in Japan's farming villages
through the industrial cooperatives.
Then, on December 17th, 1933,
the Nakano Cooperative Hospital
Nakano Cooperative Hospital
was completed on Miyazono-dori's
4th Block in Nakano.
Dr. Hirose became the hospital director, and Kurokawa Taiichi took up the role of administrative director.
The cooperative already had
1,500 members in it.
In September 1935,
Nakano Cooperative Hospital expanded,
Outpatient Ward
Gynecology Ward
and in November 1938, it became the first
of all cooperative medical institutions nationwide to build a maternity ward.
Maternity Ward
Despite persecution from the medical association, it made great strides.
Kagawa’s vision of creating a model cooperative hospital and promoting it nationwide
had come to fruition.
Next, Kagawa Toyohiko
felt the need to establish a strong mutual aid system for medical expenses,
and began laying the groundwork for it.
One for all, and all for one—
everyone would pool money together,
and in case of need, draw from that fund
to cover medical costs.
This is the mutual aid system
we seek to implement.
Mutual aid associations and insurance systems
are well developed in Europe,
but we're not simply going
to copy those foreign models.
Our ancestors have had excellent
mutual aid systems since ancient times.
In Japan’s villages, there were traditional systems
such as a mutual financing association​.
These were also forms of mutual aid.
In 1839, Ohara Yugaku founded the Ancestral Shareholding Cooperative in Katori, Chiba,
and in Odawara, Kanagawa, Ninomiya Sontoku
established the Hotoku Movement.
Both were homegrown mutual aid systems
pioneered by local farmers.
Pooling cash is not the only way
to do mutual aid.
You can also generate funds
through joint use of fields,
by contributing rice or wheat in kind,
or by making straw crafts to earn income.
There are countless ways
to build a mutual aid fund.
Kagawa further argued
that cooperative health insurance
should not only protect farmers' health
through comprehensive support,
but also serve as a source of capital to invigorate rural economies.
It's for the farmers...
My cry for medical cooperatives as part of a 100-year national framework stems from this belief.
Tokyo Medical Association Founding Meeting
It's impossible to implement national health insurance
without raising enough medical cooperatives first.
Kagawa wrote a social novel
centered around this conviction.
He titled it "The Land Where Milk
and Honey are Flowing."
Light in Home
It was serialized in the "Light in Home" magazine from January 1934 for two years.
It is said that the novel played a key role
in propelling "Light in Home"
to reach one million copies in circulation.
The government too,
influenced by Kagawa’s activities,
began deliberating on the National Health Insurance System.
However, the government was only interested
in exerting ideological control on the rural areas,
and not in implementing the constitutional reforms
proposed by the cooperative movement.
Kagawa and other medical cooperative leaders insisted that the cooperative model be incorporated
into the proposed state health insurance plan,
and lobbied the Social Bureau
of the Home Ministry for it.
As a result, the draft version of the National Health Insurance Law
Non-profit associations may obtain permission to carry out the business of national health insurance.
compiled by the Social Bureau reflected Kagawa’s proposal in Article 9.
However, in Seiyoken in Ueno,
Medical Association officials from all over the country
convened an emergency National Physicians’ Congress.
We will firmly crush any cooperatives' attempts
to run national health insurance!
The Medical Association's pressure on the government was enormous.
Let’s hold our own congress
with industrial cooperatives!
If the Medical Association
applies political pressure,
then the farmers will fight back
with political power too!
Absolute Support For The National Health Insurance Bill
On March 15th, 1937, a National Rally to Absolutely Support the National Health Insurance Bill
was held in Akasaka, Tokyo, organized by the Central Association of Industrial Cooperatives.
All problems facing rural areas
must be resolved through industrial cooperatives!
Sengoku Kotaro
The association's ambitions for rural healthcare are an unacceptable overreach!
After the rally concluded, the cooperative representatives
carrying a resolutions in support of the government’s original bill
stormed the government
and two other ministries.
However, just before the bill was to be submitted
to the House of Representatives,
Prime Minister Hayashi's cabinet
suddenly dissolved the House.
The bill ultimately failed to pass.
Following the resignation of the Hayashi Cabinet,
Konoe Fumimaro
The succeeding administration
was that of Prime Minister Konoe Fumimaro.
The new Minister of Agriculture and Forestry
was Arima Yoriyasu, the president
of the Industrial Cooperatives Association.
Because Arima had joined the cabinet,
the medical cooperatives' advocates firmly believed that industrial cooperatives
Arima Yoriyasu
would take over national
health insurance operations.
However, on July 7th, the second Sino-Japanese war
broke out in Lugouqiao, a suburb of Beijing.
With this sudden turn of events, even this council
postponed the re-submission of the bill.
It wasn’t until January 27th, 1938—
when the flames of war on the continent
were intensifying by the day—
that the revised bill,
following coordination within the government,
was finally submitted to the 73rd Diet.
The jurisdiction over the bill was transferred from the Ministry of Home Affairs
to the newly-established Ministry of Health and Welfare.
With that, the industrial cooperatives
were officially recognized by the law
as representatives of health insurance unions.
Japan Industrial Cooperative
The realization of a cooperative society supported by love for humanity
was rapidly brought closer
by this becoming a state-funded project.
The number of industrial cooperatives acting as agents for the national health insurance business
reached 2,554 across the country.
At last, Kagawa secured industrial cooperative management of the national health insurance system.
It had been a struggle
against illness and persecution,
but Kagawa seemed to be steadily ascending the stairway to realizing an ideal society.
Japan is now trying to force its way through,
but that is not the fellowship of true Christians.
Even when we are subjected to violence
by force, we must endure it.
That is the path to saving the world
from the destruction of war.
The next day, Kagawa was arrested
and detained by the Shibuya Military Police
for violating the Military Penal Code.
This was due to the government’s outrage
over an antiwar commentary he had published in a calendar
issued by an American religious organization.
Kagawa was sent to Sugamo Prison.
What awaited him there
was the harsh life of a criminal.
Kagawa endured it by praying to God.
He recalled the words of Saint Paul:
“If I think of my life as dying anew every day
through a life of suffering,
then pain and sorrow become a joy.”
Ah, I die daily...
In 1941, Japan-US relations
grew worse than ever.
Foreign Minister Matsuoka Yosuke had already concluded the Tripartite Pact with Germany and Italy,
and also signed
the Japan-Soviet Neutrality Pact.
Just as storm clouds
gathered on the horizon,
Kagawa set out for America
as a member of a Christian peace mission.
Though facilitating Japan–U.S. dialogue
was also part of their mission,
it was mostly aimed to explain the wartime position of the United Church of Christ in Japan.
In late June, he visited New York,
and at the Roosevelt Hotel, a welcome banquet
for Toyohiko Kagawa was held.
But the atmosphere was heavy.
Even with such fine hospitality,
I cannot feel at peace.
Everyone, Japan and the United States
are on the brink of war.
Why are we not praying for peace between Japan and the United States?
Now is the time to pray—
for everlasting peace, true peace!
Let us not forget the love of Christ.
Kagawa’s voice trembled with tears,
and the audience, moved beyond national and ethnic borders, was deeply touched.
Let us pray from today, for one week,
so that war will not break out
and that peace between Japan and the United States will endure.
Kagawa gathered fellow church members and began an all-night prayer vigil.
A candle lit on December 1st continued to burn for a full week.
On the morning of December 8th,
when that flame finally went out...
A statement from Imperial Headquarters, for December 8th, 6 o'clock in the morning,
the Imperial Army and Navy are engaged in combat with...
Hiroshima and Nagasaki were eventually
struck with atomic bombs,
and the nightmare of war came to an end.
August 15, 1945—peace had returned,
but at a tremendous cost.
Japan's major cities were reduced to ashes,
and ten million of its people had lost their livelihoods
and were left wandering the streets.
On August 28th,
Kagawa was invited by Prime Minister Higashikuni
to the Prime Minister’s residence.
This is a national crisis—defeat, occupation,
chaos, and deprivation.
Higashikuni Naruhiko
We need a force capable of saving the souls
of the Japanese people.
That force lies with you, Reverend Kagawa.
The current cabinet alone
cannot convince the Americans.
We need someone
who truly understands America.
Reverend Kagawa, please accept a position as advisor to the Higashikuni Cabinet.
I understand your intentions well.
Please allow me some time to think it over.
Kagawa then consulted
with leaders of the Christian community
on what his role as cabinet advisor should be.
He proposed that Japan’s defeat
stemmed from the fact that its people,
both Christians and the general public alike,
have been ignorant, indifferent,
and overzealous in the past,
and now was the time to launch a nationwide “Movement for National Repentance.”
On August 30, General MacArthur arrived at Atsugi Airfield.
That very day, Kagawa’s open letter to MacArthur was published in the Yomiuri Hochi newspaper.
To Supreme Commander MacArthur:
On August 15, Japan accepted defeat and fell under the shadow of loss.
Now, the victorious nations must act
with great magnanimity and compassion.
Japan stands ready to embark on a new path
as a responsible member of the world community.
To confine her within narrow limits without cause
will only produce results
far removed from your noble ideals.
I ask you, sir, to bring out
the best of the Japanese character
and spur Japan forward
toward a new culture and a new world—
with a kind heart and not a sword.
With the return of peace, Kagawa Toyohiko found himself in the national spotlight.
On October 5, 1945,
the Higashikuni Cabinet resigned in full.
The following day, a secretary to elder statesman Ozaki Yukio
visited Kagawa’s home in Kamikitazawa
with three candidacies for the next prime minister:
Shidehara Kijuro, Yoshida Shigeru,
and Kagawa Toyohiko.
I already have work that serves God,
and I am committed to the cooperative movement.
I have no desire to become prime minister.
In 1946, he was appointed to the House of Peers,
Let's widely recruit comrades and form a socialist party
but there’s an anecdote that he never once
stepped foot in the Diet building.
One must also remember Kagawa’s key role
in the founding of the Japan Socialist Party.
In the fall of 1945, socialist leaders such as Abe Isoo
and Takano Iwasaburo joined Kagawa
in rallying former members
of the Labor and Social Democratic parties.
At the Kuramae Industrial Hall in Shinbashi,
Matsuoka Komakichi, Katayama Tetsu,
Kawakami Jotaro, Sugiyama Motojiro,
and Nishio Suehiro—around 200 figures total,
gathered to discuss the party’s formation.
The founding ceremony was held
on November 2, 1945, at Hibiya Public Hall.
Katayama Tetsu
Tetsu Katayama was chosen as the first party leader.
Now in the political spotlight, Kagawa
stepped down from his advisory role in the cabinet
and threw himself into leading the Movement for National Repentance.
He also served a crucial role as a mediator between the Japanese public and GHQ.
Though the country was broken,
its people remained,
Japan’s cities lay in ruin,
and the countryside fared little better.
The war had devastated the agricultural technology
that sustained food production,
and defeat had left farmers
in a state of total bewilderment.
At that time, men who had once
poured their hearts
into farmers’ movements, health co-ops,
and consumer cooperatives
began gathering at the United Church
of Christ in Japan in Kanda.
Let’s rebuild Japan on the foundation
of the cooperative movement!
We Will Unite!
I’ve visited several
European countries over the years,
and wherever a defeated nation was rebuilt,
it was through the power
of the cooperative movement.
From these talks, an organizational framework began to take shape,
Alliance Of Japan's Cooperatives
and on November 18th, 1945,
the Japan Cooperative League
was officially established
at the Kuramae Industrial Hall in Shimbashi.
Meanwhile, in November 1947,
the Diet passed the Agricultural Cooperatives Act.
This law formally allowed cooperative insurance programs.
In the years that followed, 28,500 agricultural cooperatives sprang up in rural areas across Japan.
Kagawa’s long-held dream
of cooperative insurance
began to take form
as agricultural cooperative insurance.
But opposition from the insurance industry
came as no surprise.
Insurance salesmen
began scrambling to rural households.
Additionally, some voices from within
the rural sector pushed back.
The existing Agricultural Mutual Relief Associations were far from quiet.
We’re the senior organization in agri-insurance!
There’s no reason
for the new co-ops to go that far!
We have the backing
of the national government!
The newborn agricultural cooperative insurance program found itself surrounded—
boxed in by the commercial insurance sector,
the Mutual Relief Associations,
and government ministries aligned with them.
Its very survival hung by a thread.
Then—on May 9th, 1948,
at the Matsuzawa Church in Kamikitazawa,
a ceremony was held marking 40 years since Kagawa Toyohiko
began his ministry,
as well as his 60th birthday.
And after a solemn prayer...
On this occasion,
I’d like to leave you all with my will.
Among the dozen or so wishes in his will, one stood out:
I ask you—make cooperative insurance a reality.
For cooperatives to demonstrate
their true strength,
we must establish life insurance programs that build long-term, stable reserves.
Although the Agricultural Cooperatives Act had passed and the way was clear for cooperative insurance,
even the co-op members—let alone officials at the Ministry of Agriculture and Forestry—
had only a vague understanding
of what co-op insurance actually meant.
In this environment,
it was Hokkaido that took the initiative
in agricultural cooperative mutual aid.
The Hokkaido Federation of Agricultural Cooperative Insurance Associations was the first to be established.
The national federation didn’t come into being
until much later—January 31, 1951.
Even then, the newly formed
national federation lacked its own offices
and was crammed into a corner of a building in Nishi-Ginza,
sharing space with other national agricultural cooperative federations.
Its first president was Okamura Bunshiro,
head of Hokkaido’s agricultural federation.
Yamanaka Ryozo, head of the Hokkaido insurance federation, was appointed executive director.
How were they to nurture
this besieged initiative?
The leadership fought desperately
to keep it alive.
From July 14th, 1952,
the first leadership seminar for agricultural cooperative insurance
was held in Koganei City, Tokyo.
Most participants were prefectural staffers with no knowledge even of the insurance program’s basics.
Kagawa Toyohiko drilled his cooperative insurance philosophy into their heads:
Private insurers operate for profit!
That’s why they avoid insuring people
or regions with high risk—
say, farmers living under
dilapidated thatched roofs.
Cooperative insurance is different.
It exists to protect everyone.
Its aim is to reinvest profits back into society
and function as a safeguard
that prevents disaster before it strikes.
This social reinvestment
is what benefits the members.
In other words, whether cooperatives
can help solve the root of society’s problems
depends on how insurance profits
are returned to the public.
To put it differently—Japan is still reeling
from the devastation of war,
and countless social problems
remain unsolved.
So I say this: Cooperative insurance
is the fundamental path to saving Japan.
Kagawa once again traveled from one agricultural cooperative to another,
explaining to the members that cooperative insurance was a national salvation movement.
My friends, if life insurance through cooperatives reaches farming families across Japan,
this nation will rise again with dignity.
Even if Japan should face
devastation again someday,
as long as life insurance exists,
it will rise from the ashes like a phoenix.
I’ve seen this firsthand
in countries around the world.
Kagawa’s impassioned appeals resonated deeply
with the cooperative members,
instilling courage and hope in farmers and villages still reeling from the war.
He also explained the essence of cooperatives and mutual aid in his own distinct style:
Cooperatives are the backbone of a nation.
And life insurance
is the spine of those cooperatives.
If we think of a nation as a human body,
the brain is the government.
But the heart, stomach, liver, and muscles are all different types of cooperatives.
The stomach is the consumer cooperative; the muscles are the producer cooperative.
In other words, production, sales, purchasing,
and credit cooperatives together
make up the nation which is a human body.
With the addition of life insurance,
the body finally stands upright.
A cooperative without life insurance
is like a jellyfish—spineless and shapeless.
And a nation without cooperatives is the same.
Life insurance gives cooperatives their backbone—
it turns them into vertebrates.
Excellent Life Insurance Record
In June 1954, an awards ceremony was held in the hall of the Norinchukin Bank in Marunouchi, Tokyo,
honoring agricultural cooperatives
with outstanding records in life insurance.
If you all continue this cooperative insurance movement,
poverty will vanish
from Japan’s farming villages.
Japan is the only country in the world that once banned cooperative insurance.
Our rural areas suffered under the burden
of high taxes and fees, while private insurers siphoned off cash from the countryside.
But this agricultural cooperative insurance program,
finally permitted after the war,
will become a mighty force for rural revival.
I earnestly hope all of you will join this movement across the nation.
Kagawa’s passion stirred agricultural leaders
and members alike nationwide,
Number of long-term
mutual aid policies held
4.76 million
250,000
Fiscal
year
1954       1955        1956       1957       1958        1959       1960
and the cooperative insurance program
experienced explosive growth.
By the end of fiscal year 1954,
there were 250,000 long-term policies in force.
By 1960, that number had ballooned to 4.76 million—
a 19-fold increase in just six years.
Long-term mutual aid holdings
668.7 billion yen
960 billion yen
1 trillion yen
500 billion yen
Fiscal
year
1959               1960               1961
And the growth didn’t stop there.
At the end of fiscal year 1959, the combined value of long-term policies stood at 668.7 billion yen;
by the end of 1960, it reached 960 billion yen;
and by June of the following year,
it had surpassed the 1 trillion yen mark.
In January 1956, the National Mutual Insurance Federation of Agricultural Cooperatives
launched a five-year plan
for cooperative insurance:
Enroll farming households nationwide and reach 400 billion yen in total life insurance coverage.
Ahead of the campaign, Kurokawa Daichi,
director of the Federation’s operations department,
decided a powerful poster
was needed to promote the initiative.
He planned to print a slogan in Kagawa’s own handwriting and distribute it to co-ops nationwide.
On New Year’s Day, 1956, Kurokawa visited Kagawa’s home in Kamikitazawa:
Sensei, would you give us some words to serve
as the backbone of the co-op insurance program?
Certainly! I'd be happy to write it for you.
“Japan’s recovery
begins with life insurance...”
The slogan was printed and sent to co-ops and prefectural unions across the country.
"Rural revitalization begins with long-term financing
by cooperative auxiliary organizations."
The original writing is still displayed today
in the Federation’s boardroom.
The first signs of Kagawa Toyohiko’s
fatal illness appeared
while he was traveling on a ship
from Kobe to Takamatsu.
He had set out for his hometown of Tokushima
to preach and give lectures,
but just before reaching Tokushima,
he collapsed and was rushed
to St. Luke’s Hospital in Takamatsu.
The date was January 6th, 1959.
He was diagnosed with myocardial infarction,
pleural thickening, cardiac hypertrophy—
seven serious conditions in all.
In the spring, when he stabilized,
he returned to his home in Kamikitazawa.
About a month into his home care,
Nakano Cooperative Hospital
he developed pneumonia and was admitted
to Nakano Cooperative Hospital.
I'd like to try going to a hot spring sanatorium in Izu-Nagaoka...
At 9:10 p.m. on April 23rd, 1960,
Kagawa Toyohiko passed away at his home in Kamikitazawa,
concluding his 72-year life on earth
and ascending to heaven.
The giant's final testament—
"Bring cooperative insurance into reality"—
was already realized,
and he ascended
while witnessing its dramatic progress.
For God so loved the world that he gave his one and only Son,
that whoever believes in him shall not perish but have eternal life.
For God did not send his Son into the world to condemn the world,
but to save the world through him.
(John 3.16-17)
Agriculture nurtures nature and the environment
Water, greenery, and earth for the next generation!
-National Federation of Agricultural Cooperative Associations
For peace and a better life
-Japanese Consumers' Co-operative Union
Raw
Translation & TS
Editing
Science Film Museum
(ripped by R-Raws)
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
The End