Are you all right? Come on, get up!
Well, well.
So the only place the Gabia Empire hadn't
bothered to invade yet is this dump of a town?
Even so, it's still quite a find.
Before long, this place will go to hell as well.
That's why I prefer the ocean more, Ben.
'Course you do! Ain't no bothersome
rules in the ocean. That's where we can be free.
Besides, there's a whole lot of
forgotten ancient ruins for you to plunder.
Life's tough enough as is, Ricky.
That's why I'm helping you realize your dream.
All right. Then we'll find them for sure!
Hey! The hell are you doing?
My bad!
Be more careful!
Run for your life! Gabia's here!
Gabia!
That's it. Gabia's finally here!
I'm fed up with this rotten town!
The sea is calling out to us!
Let's go, Ben!
All right!
People of Berulia, surrender immediately!
Or else I'll squash your country in one fell swoop.
With the exception of Africa and a part of Asia,
the whole world is already under my control.
I am the emperor of Earth, Darius!
Glory to the Emperor Darius!
Long live Emperor Darius!
Crap!
Halt!
Stop running!
You there!
-Halt!
-Stop!
Don't let them escape!
Capture and hang the both of them!
A dead end!
-Let's jump, Ben!
-Yeah. Ain't got much choice.
Hey, Ricky!
Ben!
Bathyscaphe XIII, this is Ricky!
Bathyscaphe XIII, surface at the point 353, ASAP!
All right... Now!
The Great Undersea War
20,000 Miles Of Love
Now, let's start rowing
all the way to the seven seas,
Where those we love
are snoozing on the shore
Like pirates with wind in our hair,
Let's set the sails to
catch the southern wind!
Until my endless journey brings
me into the depths of your heart...
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
I just want to caress the
cheek of your blissful sleeping face
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
Eventually, all of us become a
part of that ephemeral myth...
The legendary continent of Atlantis...
By now, I'm already getting close to it.
Both Grandpa and Dad failed to
discover these ruins, but I'll definitely find them.
As the ancient Greek philosopher Plato wrote,
the Temple of Atlantis is elaborately
constructed from white, black and red stones.
Yeah. I've heard an earful about it already.
About that lovely continent that sunk to the ocean
floor overnight because of a volcano eruption.
Atlantis wasn't the only ancient
civilization to disappear in the ocean.
There was also Lemuria in the
Indian Ocean, as well as Mu in the Pacific.
Both Grandpa and Dad devoted
their lives to those ancient civilizations.
Sure, sure!
As long as I have an excuse
to dive, I've got zero complaints—
What is it?!
The engine room's destroyed!
What?
This is bad! The airway is busted!
Really?
Surface immediately! We're low on oxygen!
O-Oxygen...
Hey, can you hang on...?
I'm suffocating...!
What in the world is that?
Ben. Hey, Ben! Wake up!
Ricky... What is this place?
Are we at the pearly gates?
What are you talking about?
Seems like we got saved, somehow.
What?
Well I'll be! You're absolutely right!
Ben!
But still... What could this place be?
Beats me.
Almost as if we're in a prison cell, ain't it?
Hey! Is anyone out there?
Don't be reckless!
You fool! I can't relax until I know exactly where we are.
Could it be that we're on a Gabian submarine?
It can't be... We'd have long breathed our last if so.
All right...
If you're up and running already, you'll be fine.
Let me check your pulse now...
My, isn't it great to be young?
Hey, old man! What is this place?
I'm no "old man" to you!
My name is Smith, thank you very much.
You're this ship's doctor, right?
When you ask others something,
you should be like this—duly polite!
Shut it! I'm used to talking like this.
Listen here, grandpa Smith.
It looks like we're inside of a submarine.
So what's it called, and which country is it from?
Well, you see... I mean...
As you have guessed, we're inside a submarine.
Perhaps, this is a nuclear submarine?
Ain't you a clever boy. Exactly so.
This here is a nuclear submarine.
The Nautilus.
This is the Nautilus, a nuclear
submarine that belongs to my father.
My, oh my...
With a pretty girl like you on board,
it doesn't look like a bad ship at all. Well met!
It is all the more apparent to me
that you have a pea-sized brain.
Excuse me?!
You eggheaded quack...
Thanks a lot for saving us.
My name is Rick Mudai. You can call me Ricky.
My name is Sophia. Nice to meet you.
What happened to my
Bathyscaphe, as well as our crew?
This way.
Well then, I'll take my leave.
It's the Bathyscaphe!
You're right... How the...
Holy crap!
It's been restored to mint condition!
True that! I can't believe my eyes...
Now that's impressive!
Thank you, Sophia!
By the way, our crewmates are
nowhere to be seen. What about them?
No need to worry. They're all fine.
Ouch!
Miss Sophia! We finished the
internal repairs! It's as good as new!
Oh! Captain Ricky! You made it through?
Bastard... You'll pay for that! I'll snap your neck—
Ah... Huh?
What? It's just you? Glad to see you're fine.
I was worried about you guys!
Hey, Ben! So you're fine too?
-I'm so glad!
What a touching reunion! Glad to see all of you!
It should be good to go now!
Hey, Ricky! Now when we're all here,
let's pack up and take our leave!
Yeah. But we gotta thank their Captain first.
No, there's no need for you to meet my father.
W-What?
Please, take me with you!
Um...
I mean...
Hey, Ricky! Hurry up!
Yeah! On my way!
Don't you dare act without my permission!
Father!
Hey, Ricky. Maybe this
submarine isn't as great as we thought.
Anyhow, let's get outta here!
I am Nemo, the captain of the Nautilus.
Those who set foot on my ship once
aren't allowed to leave it ever again.
What?!
Father!
Sophia! That goes for you, too!
W-What are you getting at?
Are we your prisoners or something now?!
You gotta be kidding!
Ben, was it?
I require your and Ricky's help.
Your other crew members will also work with my men.
If you accept those terms,
I will let you move freely on board.
If you refuse, you will rot in the bilge.
Come, Sophia!
Hey, wait a minute!
Get back here, you son of a...
What's his problem?
Has the power gone to his head?!
Depth—100. Speed—30 knots.
Good! Maintain that speed. Course—37 degrees!
Dammit...
Ben, calm down already.
Ricky, do you expect me to
put up with his rotten attitude?!
Besides, how can I calm down when
I'm forced to wear this wacky outfit?!
Now, now. Don't get so worked up.
It's no use panicking in the middle of the ocean.
Plus, this whole Nautilus thing kinda piqued my curiosity.
Huh? Don't tell me you fancy that gal Sophia...
H-Hey! Where are you going? Hey!
To see if we're really guaranteed
the freedom to roam this submarine.
S-So this is the nuclear engine room?
It's huge! It makes me dizzy!
Here's the nuclear cannons compartment! Amazing...
This must be where the miscellaneous data converges.
The computer room?
Here's the torpedo room.
A missile room, too!
Welcome!
I knew it was you playing the piano.
Hey. Sorry I let myself into your room.
I got drawn in by your melody.
Please forgive my father.
Now that you're stuck here, I'm not sure
if me saving you was for better or worse.
Then it was you who...
I was hoping that maybe I'd also be able to break out...
But I now see that it's impossible.
But isn't this your father's ship?
I want to meet my mother.
But I don't know where she is.
I want to go looking for her.
Your mother?
Which means your mother is still ashore?
I know she's still alive somewhere. However...
I don't know why, but my father won't let me leave.
It's been a year already.
My poor mother...
Poor? What do you mean?
I was raised in a small
village at the bottom of the Alps.
With my kind mother, and
cheerful villagers, I was truly happy there.
But my father wasn't around.
Whenever she talked about him,
Mother would always get sad.
Once or twice a year, Father would visit us there,
but then quietly leave again.
On such days, Mother would
always look way sadder than usual.
When I was a child, I'd been told that my father
did important research in some laboratory far away.
One year ago...
Mother set out to see him.
Then, 10 days later, Father suddenly reappeared
and said that we were running away together.
I cried and begged him to wait for Mother.
But he claimed we'd meet her later.
Then we boarded this submarine and set out to sea.
I've been living here ever since.
And for some reason, Father always
gets mad when I mention Mother.
So that's how it is?
I hope you understand why I hate my father.
But you've got no reason to.
I mean, think of it.
She may not be with you right now, but she's
out there somewhere. You'll meet her eventually.
Although my mother died right after giving birth to me...
Unlike you, I've got not a single memory of my mother.
Ricky...
Even if you've been apart,
you can still hope to meet her in the future.
We humans have a knack for optimism.
Even so, I miss her!
I want to get closer to her, if only just a bit.
I understand, Sophia. Trust me with this.
I'll make sure you get to see your mother someday.
Really, Ricky?
Yeah, I promise.
Now, now...
I'm Jim, the cook.
I did my best to prepare these special dishes.
A sublimely delicious green
turtle soup, monkfish marinated in oil,
as well as meuniere sauce from
sea anemones and fish eyeballs.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
I bid you bon appétit. Don't hold back.
With all due respect, Captain, I appreciate the meal.
Restraining our freedom like
this doesn't sit well with me, though.
But weren't you also diving
the seven seas in your Bathyscaphe?
How is my Nautilus any different?
On my ship, I have my freedom.
I can dive the seas of the world freely,
in search of lost ancient civilizations.
What's wrong with it?
Come on!
The same applies to my submarine, Ricky.
Why, you...
Because I'm also on a search for ancient civilizations.
What? For real?
Just ask Sophia.
Is it true?
It's true.
Up until now, we've been looking for Lemuria,
said to have sunk in the Indian Ocean.
It's true! It's true!
And then, we were on our way to look for Atlantis,
when we rammed your Bathyscaphe.
Well? If you want to realize your dream,
don't you think my Nautilus is more
convenient than your antiquated Bathyscaphe?
Are you really a fellow pursuer of ancient civilizations?
Are you willing to cooperate now?
Yeah, you got me interested.
However, I'm still allergic to being a prisoner.
Glad to know that. And if you make good
friends with Sophia, she'll stop trying to go ashore.
But, Captain...
Why aren't you letting Sophia see her mother?
That is no subject to be discussed with outsiders!
I mean, don't you pity Sophia at all?
Damn this thing!
Get your act together!
But I couldn't cut it...
No matter how many shining
stars I could line up before you,
All of them would pale before your beauty
Your shadow wanders along
the distant reaches of the galaxy
The longer I keep chasing it,
The more tears I see in your eyes,
the more you begin to doubt me,
And the more you distance yourself...
Shadow in the moonlight beach...
I love you
Even if you leave me,
I will keep loving you
Gabian submarines!
The Nautilus is no match for this many of them.
Let's go tell Captain Nemo!
Okay!
You idiot!
What was that for?
I thought I explicitly forbade you to go outside!
Father!
Break my rules one more time
and I'll send you to the bilge there and then!
Is this clear, Ricky?
What are you all doing? Get back to your posts!
Roger!
Please forgive him, Ricky!
It's okay, Sophia.
Back in the day, my own dad used to rough me up a lot.
Dammit, it's almost as if I met
him again for the first time in ages.
Captain on the line.
We've detected a submarine
2 km behind our stern! It's closing in!
Crap! Those Gabian nuclear subs caught up with us...
It's clearly following us!
Captain! What are your orders?
What's going on?
Nuclear cannons are standing by!
Wait!
Captain, we're not going to fight them?
Submerge to the maximum depth!
Captain! What are you saying? We have to fight!
If we don't fight them off here,
they'll conquer even the oceans!
Shut up! We're diving to the sea floor.
But why, Captain? Why won't you fight?!
Captain, there's only a few of them!
We should be able to take them on!
So why aren't you fighting back?
Behold this sea.
See how the sea is awakened
by the love of the sun? Do you understand?
The sea is alive.
The sea that went to sleep together
with us last night is waking up as we speak.
Behold this sea!
Don't you think this is what life is all about?
Right now, the sea is smiling at us.
But at times, the sea gets angry.
Just like us humans.
Submerging in 5 seconds!
4...
3...
2...
1...
0...
Submerging now.
Depth—26.
27.
Depth—30!
Good. Keep diving until we're at 50.
Is that...
All ahead at 20 knots.
There's a road at the bottom of the ocean?
Who in the world could've built this?
Humans had nothing to do with it.
It was created by the ocean.
It's made of manganese, oxidized in the sediments.
Do you understand now?
Just like the land, the sea is home to all kinds of
things. Some things are also unique to the seabed.
Among those things,
ancient cities and civilizations lay hidden.
Captain, when and where did you learn all that?
Also, where was the Nautilus built?
Ricky! Don't ask things you don't want to know!
What's going on?!
Activate the backup generators!
Control room speaking! Control room speaking!
Report, officer!
This is serious! All instruments are
malfunctioning because of electrical interference!
Even the compass is out of order!
What the hell?
At this rate, the bottom current will sweep us away!
Promptly identify the cause of the malfunction!
What does that mean, Captain?
You heard everything.
If we can't fix it, we'll end
up helplessly drifting along the seabed.
Sophia!
Perhaps I'll never get to meet my mother ever again...
Mother...
Sophia... Don't worry!
You can trust Captain Nemo to take care of it all.
My dad?
I wonder if he ever truly loved my mother.
He did!
You know, at times men are
too shy to express their feelings.
I believe we're around Puerto Rico's northern coast now.
No, we're likely nearing the Dominican Republic.
Captain, let me speak from my experience here.
This area should be 100% clear of any electromagnetic
anomalies which could affect our submarine.
Ben, what are you trying to say?
Ah... Well, I mean, this looks
like some very special case... And...
Could someone be doing this on purpose—
Huh? What's that?
It's an underwater base!
Captain, do you suppose that may
be the source of those magnetic disturbances?
Which is to say it's a Gabian base...
Captain, why aren't you saying anything?
Sharp turn to port!
No! Wait a minute there.
What if that base hasn't been
captured by the Gabian forces just yet?
Wait, you! Ricky! Ben!
Maybe it's a hideout for people who oppose Gabia?
Amazing! I've never seen an
underwater base this magnificent!
W-What are those? Mutants?
It doesn't look like they're on our side!
Halt!
We've been monitoring every step of yours!
Crap!
Struggle as you may, you can't escape!
What is this place?
-Bastard!
-What are you doing?
Experiments on humans!
Experiments on humans?
That's right. Emperor Darius of the Gabia Empire
tasked us with creation of an amphibious human,
capable of roaming the ocean floor freely!
And you will be my test subjects!
So that's what you did to the people in those vats?
Johnson, don't fail me this time.
In the name of Emperor Darius!
May his cause prosper!
Johnson, wasn't it?
You call yourself a scientist?!
You're a devil who sold his soul to Darius!
Are you the crew members of that nuclear submarine?
Maybe. What's it to you?!
I'll help you, but I need you to take me along.
What...?
Listen closely! I was an American scientist, but the
Gabian secret police kidnapped me and brought me here.
Day and night, I've been forced to
conduct horrible experiments on humans!
Johnson, does that mean you
know your way around this base?
What's that?
That part is cleared.
Oh no!
Johnson... I noticed your attitude
towards the experiments changed recently.
I'll send you to hell along with these brats!
Ben, we've got no choice. Let's go!
Okay! I ain't getting turned into a mutant today.
Ricky!
Sophia... I'm a little tired.
Ah, where am I...
Smith! Quickly, take them to the sickbay!
It seems they're totally exhausted...
25 degrees to the starboard.
Prepare to fire nuclear cannons!
You made it out safely, Ricky?
Yeah. I owe you one for saving us.
Spare your gratitude for Sophia.
She kept bugging me to help you.
So this is the man you told me about?
The man named Johnson?
He's just an unfortunate scientist.
He's an American, but Gabia forced
him to work on their horrible inventions.
What? Did you say scientist?
I hope you'll get along well, Captain.
Because you destroyed the
magnetic interference generator,
the Nautilus' equipment is back to normal.
However, now that we've put up some real
resistance to Gabia, they're not letting it slide.
Our main priority now is reaching
the continent of Mu as soon as possible.
If only we could go to Mu...
Captain, what did you just say?
No, I'm just talking to myself.
Johnson, what happened?
Hey, Pops, what's the matter with him?
Looks like the poor guy got
amnesia from the shock of the battle.
Johnson!
I've had enough of that Nemo!
I subjugated the land and the sky,
and the whole universe submitted to my will!
Having Nemo roam the ocean floor
freely under my nose is unacceptable!
Presently, Nemo is cruising south
along the coast of South America.
Having turned around the Horn Cape,
he plans to enter the Pacific Ocean.
So he's aiming for the
continent of Mu, just as I thought.
We can't let Nemo discover Mu!
Kill him before that happens!
Yes, Emperor Darius!
From Earth and all the way to space,
Nemo is the only one who ever dared to defy me.
Anyone who interferes with my dream of world
conquest, be it even a single thorn, or a single pest,
must be exterminated without mercy!
Hail Emperor Darius!
How are you feeling now?
What's wrong, Johnson?
It's no use... My head hurts!
Johnson...
Take good care of him.
Have you met Captain Nemo before?
N-Nemo...
What are you doing?!
Sorry about that. I've heard that amnesia
can be cured by inflicting another shock on him.
Acting like a brute as usual, I see.
Hey, you quack!
What do you suggest will cure him?
I'd have won the Nobel Prize if I knew that!
Memory loss is still a largely unexplored field.
We've had it pretty rough.
Yeah, this ain't looking well.
Mu isn't so far now.
Finish the repairs as soon as possible.
Okay!
Hold up! Where are you going?
Let us get ashore once in a while, will you?
Besides, looking at the landscape
could help Johnson restore his memory.
Now, off we go!
Yeah!
Stop!
Come back!
I forbid you to step ashore! Get back!
Come back! I will not tolerate this insubordination!
Father, please! Let them off the hook just this once!
From time to time, I've also had the urge to walk on
real land. I'm sure Ricky and the others feel the same way.
I've endured countless storms,
To spread the tale of my manly endeavors
Here and now, I swear to
never make you cry ever again
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
In pursuit of their dreams,
people cross the flow of time in tiny boats
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
Eventually, all of us become a
part of that ephemeral myth...
In the end, the food from the land is the best!
Hey, Ricky, look! What's that?
Oh no! Let's run for it!
It's a Gabian antisubmarine patrol plane!
Damn it all...
Hurry up with the repairs!
We'll buy you some time with a counter-attack.
Ricky!
I warned these idiots...
You still aren't done with the repairs?
We're done here!
Father!
Repairs are finished!
Good! Help the wounded men board!
Let me do that!
Jim!
Our boys are all exhausted. Lemme help 'em!
Jim! Jim!
Ricky!
All right! The moment all our men get inside,
commence the emergency dive!
Jim...
Forgive us. If we hadn't gone to that island...
Goodbye, Jim. I won't forget
your cooking for the rest of my life.
Jim, goodbye.
Hey... What is that?
If I had to guess, I'd say it's a grave.
Amazing. That's one beautiful cross.
But it's strange.
There's no inscription on this cross.
Captain Nemo, whose grave is this?
-Come on, we need to return.
-Captain! Whom does this grave belong to?
Be quiet!
We all need to hurry back to the ship.
Father!
Didn't you hear me?
Remember about Gabia. They'll catch up with
us soon enough. Now, let's get going, Sophia!
Father!
We've just received a transmission.
The Nautilus is heading towards the Mariana Islands.
So, is Nemo that determined
to find the continent of Mu?
All right, pursue him!
We must kill Nemo before he discovers Mu!
Yes, sir!
They're finally here...?
All right! Prepare to fight back.
Until we start drawing from Mu's ancient
energy, we need to hold out, no matter what.
Nautilus, 30 degrees to the
port bow! Distance: 2000 meters!
All ships, prepare to fire torpedoes!
Fire!
In hell's name!
Heh! They aren't holding back today!
Hey, what is it? You remembered something?
Commence the attack!
Captain!
What is it?
Ben?
Nemo? That's right, it's you. It's definitely you!
Excuse me?
Ricky, looks like Johnson
somehow got all his memory back.
What did you say?
I remember now, Captain Nemo!
No, the former chairman
of the Gabian Academy of Science!
Wh-What?
That's right! It is you!
You were the one who invented all
of those horrible chemical weapons!
Th-That can't be!
Finally, you were the one who
came up with the idea to modify humans.
Nemo had lost his fear of God...
People called him the devil incarnate!
This can't be!
Wait a minute! If Captain Nemo was a
chairman of the Gabian Academy of Science,
why is Gabia so hot on his trail now?!
Nemo is on the run.
He's on the run after betraying Gabia.
That's right! It all happened a year ago.
That day, a single woman showed up at the
doorstep of the Gabian Academy of Science.
The woman was none other than Captain Nemo's wife.
My mother?
My mother was a Gabian...?
The woman that introduced herself as Nemo's wife
begged him to return home for the
sake of their only daughter, Sophia.
I remember. That day,
my mother went to see my father.
But then, Darius came to tear them apart.
Darling, please, let's escape Gabia!
Darling!
Forgive me, Sophia.
Your mother did it for me...
She tried to free me from Gabian clutches...
Just as I thought, that cross on the ocean floor...
Your mother's death brought me to my senses.
Mother...
Sophia!
Forgive me, Sophia.
So you really are running
away to hide from Gabia's wrath?
I fully realize how frightening Gabian weapons are.
After all, I was the one who invented them all.
That's why I've been avoiding Gabian forces up until today.
So the Nautilus isn't powerful enough to win against them?
Indeed, for the time being.
But there's no need to despair.
The nuclear fusion reactor my
Nautilus has is not just a propulsion device.
The tremendous energy
that sank Mu to the ocean floor
can be harnessed from particles with
much higher energy density than uranium ore.
Once we tap into that energy,
we could instantly obliterate the Gabia Empire.
Sophia, I'm sorry to have
kept you in the dark up until now.
However, using the ancient
energy of Mu, we'll overthrow Darius!
I was going to tell you the truth
after your mother had been avenged.
Enough of that!
Ricky, nothing personal, but I can't stomach
working together with this former Gabian stooge.
-Ben!
-Think about it!
He built all those weapons that
Gabia used to subjugate the entire world!
I can't stand looking at him any longer!
Adios!
Wait! I'm going with you!
Ben!
I'm fed up! I've had enough of your submarine!
I'm leaving! Wait for me, Ben!
Sophi—
Sophia!
Sophia, would you really abandon your father?
Now that the Nautilus is coming under attack
from Gabia, I just can't leave it to its fate.
Ricky...
Try to forgive your dad.
He sent her off with such a beautiful grave!
No... More importantly, thanks to her,
your dad decided to put up a fight against Gabia...
...because they loved each other.
Your father and mother really did,
from the bottom of their hearts.
Deploy the Denkiran Special Forces!
Aqua Commandos, sortie!
Underwater Fighters, take off!
That bastard, Nemo, is about to breathe his last!
The third nuclear fusion
engine has been destroyed!
The second bulkhead has been breached!
The second living compartment's in flames!
Captain Nemo, it's hopeless!
The Nautilus is going straight to hell!
Is that...?
The Temple of Mu!
Mu's...
So that's the Temple of Mu?
There's gotta be something in there
that's emitting this tremendous heat.
I finally found it! That's right!
The secret of Mu is right there!
The source of the immense energy
that sunk the continent of mu.
My victory over Darius is already predestined!
Now then, we must get to the temple
and find that ancient high-energy fuel!
Get on with it!
H-Hey, what's that thing?
What? Th-That's...!
The core of the Temple of Mu...
That must be the secret of Mu's prosperity.
That could also be the reason of their demise...
What do you mean?
Their ancient civilization
prospered all thanks to that energy.
However, they likely misused it and destroyed themselves.
Just like the atomic and
hydrogen bombs we developed.
Ben, I wish Ricky could see this too!
He's likely been killed
by the Sea Crime by now.
D-Damn it!
Ben...
Ricky! Come see this amazing thing
we found! It's just what you were looking for.
A staggering source of ancient energy,
all hidden within the Temple of Mu!
Just as I thought!
Go now, Sophia!
Father...
Go! It's already over for my Nautilus.
I allow you to leave with Ricky!
Captain Nemo...
Ricky!
When people who create a civilization misuse such
tremendous energy, they bring their own downfall.
Mu has met that fate.
And so, it'll happen to me.
Now, let me die peacefully here.
Let me sleep at the
ocean floor, next to your mother.
Sophia! Watch out!
Hurry up and go!
My Nautilus is about to sink!
Ricky...
Yes?
Take good care of Sophia.
Captain Nemo...
Father...!
My life has been long and depressing...
I'm glad that I've been able to
spend these last moments with you.
Thank you.
Father!
Go now, Sophia! Hurry!
Let's go, Sophia!
Father!
Sophia...
This is bad! Those bastards managed
to find even our tiny Bathyscaphe!
They're coming after us!
That's right. I've got an idea.
It's now or never. Let's give it a shot!
What the hell? You say there's a way
we can stand up to the Sea Crime?
We'll blow up the ancient
Mu reactor with a time bomb.
Dammit, they're getting closer and closer!
Can't you accelerate?
Don't be unreasonable!
Accelerating any further will fry the engine!
-Ricky, hurry up and get inside!
-Ricky...
Ben, full speed ahead! Descend!
Okay!
Ascend!
It's the Temple of Mu, without a doubt,
Yes...
Beginning countdown:
10... 9... 8...
7... 6... 5...
4... 3... 2... 1...
0!
Wh-What is it? What's going on?
Wh-What...?
M-My Emperor...
Damn it...
S-Somebody...
We did it! The Sea Crime is defeated!
Captain Nemo, we avenged you!
Damn it! Ouch!
What's going on? It hurts...
Ricky!
Sophia!
Johnson, are you okay?
Barely!
Ben, just look at yourself!
Idiot!
You're the one to talk, for sure!
I've endured countless storms,
To spread the tale of my manly endeavors
Here and now, I swear to
never make you cry ever again
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
In pursuit of their dreams, people
cross the flow of time in tiny boats
Ah, Atlantis, my love...
Eventually, all of us become a
part of that ephemeral myth...
Translation:
GANGO
Translation Checking:
Perevodildo
Yume
Editing:
MartyMcFlies
Raw Provider:
Japanese Hoarder
VHS Audio Stitching:
w0wmd