The final lap of the Novice 250cc class championship is underway!
Leading the pack are bike #70—Jeff Anemos
and bike #88—Ichimonji’s machine.
These two are neck and neck, gunning for the win—and they fly out side-by-side!
They both got off to strong starts—
Jeff Anemos and Ichimonji Ken,
chasing him beautifully.
An incredible dogfight has been unfolding in the Novice 250cc class.
In the final stretch, they’ve completely shut out the rest of the racers.
Truly outstanding riding from both of them!
Yeah, no doubt—you won this one.
You had me by maybe half a tire length.
No, more like 20 centimeters.
Doesn’t matter—
lose by a centimeter, still a loss.
But next time we race,
I’m taking you down.
Too bad for you, though—
I just got special approval
to move up to the Junior class.
Huh? Say what?
Is that true, Jeff?
Yes. From now on, I’ll be racing in the All-Japan Junior series.
Kei, that means we won’t be
riding together anymore.
Yo, what’s up, Kei?
Were you dreaming about Jeff passing you again?
Nah, it’s nothing.
Go back to sleep.
We’ve still got a long way to Suzuka.
Outrun the Wind!
He's sixteen too, same age as Kei.
Just one race—that’s all it took
for them to clash head-on.
And Jeff Anemos got special promotion
into the Junior class.
The one left behind kept chasing Jeff’s shadow, riding like a madman.
No matter the race, the only thing driving him was the dream of riding with Jeff again.
Then came twelve races in the Novice class.
Two divisions—perfect wins.
Before the final round, he’d already locked in his promotion to Junior.
Even in the All-Japan series, Jeff dominates without equal.
Ichimonji Ken, who earned
a special promotion chasing after Jeff,
will finally face him in this Grand Prix.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Hey Pops, this place is nuts!
The track’s huge, and they’ve got full stands and control towers too.
Only Suzuka could pull this off.
Yeah, it’s impressive.
Oh crap—look at the time.
Alright, let’s move.
Time to get ready for race day.
Don’t doze off, old man—
this is what we’ve been working for!
You little punk...
How about you put some guts
into your training?!
You better win or I’ll kill you!
Relax, I've got this.
What the hell are you doing with my bike?
I’m surprised you made it this far
with a machine like this.
What?
Listen, from now on, leave your setup to me.
I’ve got the skills to back it up.
The hell are you saying? No way.
Do you seriously think you can beat Jeff like this? Not a chance.
I mean, sure, if you were just some average rider, this setup would be fine.
But with the way you were riding out there earlier, you need a proper tune-up.
Wait—you’re a girl!
Me? Yeah, I’m a girl.
Then quit calling yourself "boku!"
That crap gives me the creeps!
It’s gross. Got it?
Wow, what a letdown. Your big bro said you were worth respecting, so I had high hopes.
But your brain’s rigid, your heart’s small,
and your face is ugly—pathetic!
Wh-What’d you say?!
I can’t believe her, big bro.
Just barging in like that…
Hey Kei, this is your first time
in All-Japan, right?
No matter how fast you are,
that alone’s not enough anymore.
You need a machine set up just for you—
and a mechanic who understands you.
Even if you say so, I still
don’t want her touching my bike!
Jeff’s raced at Suzuka a bunch of times in the All-Japan series.
He’s a factory-backed rider.
Jun used to be my mechanic
before I moved up to A-class.
I vouch for her skills.
Our team’s got full support—
so you can focus solely on your riding.
That’s the only way you’ll ever stand a chance against Jeff.
Still, all that “boku this, boku that”—
what’s with that girl-boy?
Girl-boy? You talking about me?
Hey, relax.
We’ll all get along, eventually.
Jun.
Kei.
Kiryu Jun. Nice to meet you.
Ichimonji Kei!
Listen, Kei. This time, ride
with your head a little more, okay?
We’re giving you a machine
that’s dialed in to perfection.
Now it’s up to the rider to give it their all.
We’re doing everything we can to support you. That’s why I said—
Shut it. You’re damn good, I’ll give you that.
But say one more thing and I’ll kill you. Got it?
Don’t let it get to you, Jun.
It’s fine.
It’s not like I want to fight with him or anything.
But when I see the way Kei rides,
I can’t help but butt in.
I really think he can get way, way faster.
But Kei isn’t like Kazamatsuri-san.
You're a natural-born talent.
Still… Kei might even be
better than you someday.
Kei!
Are you all right?!
Dammit! Bike #17 slammed right into me outta nowhere!
The machine mostly just has cosmetic damage—nothing serious.
Hey, number 55.
Huh? You—
You were crawling out there
like you were in some backwoods amateur race.
Say that again, you bastard.
Kei!
Go on, I dare you—say that again!
No fighting!
Let me go!
Sorry! He just got bumped up
and doesn’t know how things work yet.
Just got promoted? A special promotion?
So you're Ichimonji!
A special promotion, huh?
Don’t think you’ll cut it in All-Japan that easily.
Shimazaki-san, is something wrong?
Nah, it’s nothing.
Though, with riding like that,
he’ll be out in no time.
Shimazaki?
He was the champ before Jeff
moved up to Junior class.
You really don’t know anything
except Jeff, huh?
Still, you did leapfrog
over a whole crowd of riders.
It’s only natural they’d resent you.
That’s fine by me—
if they all hate me,
I can go full throttle with no regrets.
That’ll make for some hell of a race.
I like that attitude!
I saw a foreigner in the hotel lobby earlier.
Could be Jeff.
All right, sounds great.
The engine and frame are both in top shape.
We just need to swap out
the fairings and we’re done.
Kei, leave the rest to us.
You should get some rest.
Jeff?
Kei?
Kei, first time since the Novice race, huh?
Didn’t expect we’d get to race
together again this soon.
Congrats on the special promotion.
You came all the way just to say that?
Well, I’m not thanking you.
I made it to the Grand Prix just to beat you.
Don’t think I’m the same rider I was back then.
I’m not finishing behind you ever again.
That’s a shame, Kei.
After this race,
I’m heading back to California.
What?
So in this race, I’ll make sure
to completely crush you.
Good luck, Kei.
Forget it.
We’ll shake hands after the race—
only if I’m first and you’re second.
87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100...
I’ve gotta be smoother with partial throttle through the corners.
And the washboard section...
Turn six.
What now?
You’re tweaking it again?
It’s good enough to qualify as-is,
but you won’t get a good position in the finals.
Besides, you’ve noticed it too, haven’t you?
The wobble on landing after the long jump.
Wait—you figured that out just by watching?
That’s a really subtle feeling.
Thank you.
That much I can tell.
I’m your mechanic, remember?
Mickey, raise the front tire
pressure by one level.
Tch. That Jun...
You were right on the money, Jun.
The bike's charging harder every lap.
Once I take the lead, there’s hardly anyone out there who can catch me.
We’re seeing an incredible qualifying round unfold!
Now in the lead is bike #55, Ichimonji Kei!
He crosses the finish line first in the Junior Class qualifier!
You did it!
Hey, well? How’d it feel?
Yeah, the bike’s dialed in—
feels like a factory ride.
I thought so too.
You looked totally in the zone.
Just watch—in tomorrow’s finals, I’m blasting off the line like a rocket.
A rocket, huh? I like the sound of that.
Ever since entering the Junior class,
Jeff Anemos has been on a winning streak.
In this Japanese Grand Prix,
if Jeff Anemos wins,
he’ll be crowned the season champion of the Junior 250cc Plus class.
Three seconds?
Yeah—he’s three seconds faster per lap
than your average time.
But listen—your best lap time
is exactly the same as Jeff’s best.
A-Are you serious?
Would I lie about something like that?
You’re not slower than Jeff,
not by a long shot.
I’m thinking of tweaking the setup one more time.
If we do that, you should be able
to run even faster.
OK—I’m counting on you, Jun.
Cut one second off that three-second gap
with your tuning.
I’ll make up the other two on the track.
No—I’ll shave off two seconds. That way, you’ll be a full second faster than Jeff.
What's wrong, kid?
What are you doing here?
Are you finished?
Just about.
Everything's perfect.
You did a great job today.
Bob, I'm sleeping here tonight.
Why? You're a rich kid.
You can stay at a hotel—like you usually do,
instead of staying at a place like this.
I want to compete with him
under the same conditions,
and beat him fair and square.
Kei,
I'll now assure you for better.
This is GP-level for sure.
What a show.
And now, it’s finally time for the
All-Japan Championship—
the Junior 250cc Class Final of the Japanese Grand Prix is about to begin!
The yellow plates with black numbers mark the bikes in the Junior Class.
Thirty riders who qualified yesterday are lined up on the grid for a 15-minute plus 2-lap showdown.
Most of them are between 15 and 18 years old—
a sign that Japan’s motocross scene is getting younger and younger.
In fact, yesterday’s qualifiers saw several riders post lap times
on par with the International A-Class.
First up, #17 on the RM—Ryuichi Shimazaki.
And #3 on the YZ—Jeff Anemos.
And here’s another rider who, like Jeff, moved up mid-season—
#55 on the CR, Ichimonji Kei.
He earned his Junior promotion after an incredible streak in the Kanto Novice Class,
where he pulled off 12 straight overall wins across two categories.
Now, we’re just two minutes from the start.
Engines are being fired up, and warmups are underway.
With the Junior 250cc Champion title on the line, we’re expecting a spectacular showdown.
And Ichimonji Kei—based on his qualifying time yesterday—
is shaping up to be the dark horse of this race.
The race is scheduled to begin at 12:15,
and it’ll be a 15-minute battle plus two extra laps.
Kei, this is a great starting spot.
You might just grab
the holeshot from here.
What about Jeff?
Yeah, he’s well-positioned too—
right next to you.
What?
Ow! What the hell was that for?!
Listen. Calm down and hear me out.
Look—Jeff’s fastest qualifying lap
was exactly the same as yours!
So just stop overthinking
and go full throttle out there.
He stopped trembling.
Jun!
All right, we’re now
10 seconds from the start!
Damn, can’t see a thing through this dust!
Screw it—full throttle!
No good—I can’t avoid it!
Whoa, a crash!
Nearly ten riders were taken out in a chain crash
just past the starting straight!
Damn it… My very first GP, and I’m caught in this mess…
And right behind him in second place—
it's Shimazaki Ryuichi, rider No.17.
And now, coming into view
at the final corner...
It’s #3, Jeff Anemos!
An absolutely dominant performance by rider #3, Jeff Anemos!
What the hell’s taking him so long?
Okay…
Kei!
All right, she’s sounding good!
He botched the start, but with this pace,
he can still catch up!
Yeah, I’ll catch 'em for sure!
He’s slicing through the pack—two riders!
Three!
Four, five!
Yes! Keep charging, Kei!
We’ve now passed
the 13-minute mark in the race.
Still in the lead is No.3, Jeff Anemos, followed by Shimazaki,
Kousaka, and Kato.
And now a stunning charge from Ichimonji!
He’s climbed all the way to 6th place!
A powerful performance proving
just why he was promoted mid-season.
Damn, how far is that kid gonna go?
Whoa! At Turn 7—he pulls off a brilliant double pass! Now he’s up into 4th!
OK! He's doing great!
Lady Luck must be winking at Jeff!
Too bad…
The gap between Kei
and the leader is 22 seconds.
Only 3 laps left.
Even at this pace, catching the top spot
might be out of reach.
That start really cost him...
Still, it'd be a shame
if it ended like this.
No.
Kei’s not the kind of guy
to give up that easily.
Yeah—he’s still got plenty left in the tank.
As long as Jeff’s up front,
he’s gonna push all the way to the top.
Whoa—Ichimonji overtakes Kousaka,
who was running third!
With just a minute left on the clock,
he moves up into 3rd place!
What an aggressive charge from Ichimonji—
he’s now closing in fast on Shimazaki in 2nd!
What? Ichimonji?!
He’s caught up to Shimazaki!
Ichimonji has caught up!
They’re side by side!
It’s neck and neck—
he's pulled even with Shimazaki!
Not bad. Try to pass me if you think you can!
Being fast alone isn’t enough to beat me!
How'd you like that?
What?!
Shimazaki, move it!
Huh? That guy's tougher than I thought!
Now’s the time!
Damn it!
The two riders collide violently!
Whoa! Shimazaki goes down!
Previously running in second place—
Shimazaki crashes out!
That means Ichimonji moves into 2nd!
Jeez, had us all sweating!
It’s weird... Even after all this riding,
I don’t feel tired—I actually feel lighter.
Jeff, I’m coming for you today!
In the Junior 250cc Final,
15 minutes have passed since the start.
Only 2 laps remain!
And just now, No.3—Jeff Anemos—
crosses the line.
He’s looking to lock in his solo lead.
Kei, the real race only starts now.
Jeff isn’t just fast—he’s sharp, too.
His sense of racecraft is impeccable.
Don't let your guard down till the very end.
No matter what, I’ve got to hang on!
Kei?
Shit!
Jeff’s right in front of me...
All right, I’ve caught up!
Move it!
Backmarkers must make way!
No, stop, Jeff!
You're being too risky!
Jeff!
This is his chance!
I did it! I’ve caught up to Jeff!
Now they're neck and neck! Ichimonji has finally pulled even with Jeff Anemos!
There he is! Go for it, Kei!
Uh-oh, this is bad. I know it's the final lap,
but they’re going way too fast.
I’m getting in front—
I’m done staring at his back.
The six-pack jump’s up ahead.
If I’m going to pass Jeff, it’s gotta be here.
A huge leap from Ichimonji Ken!
An incredible triple jump!
He’s overtaken Jeff Anemos and taken the lead!
That was a flawless triple from Ichimonji Ken,
while Jeff Anemos stuck to a double.
That's it! I've passed Jeff!
Both Jeff Anemos and Ichimonji Ken scored victories in their debut races.
For Ichimonji, who received a special promotion,
it's a fateful showdown!
Like hell I’m letting you pass!
Kei!
Oh—he’s down!
Ichimonji, who had taken the lead, crashes out!
He’s down just before Turn 5!
Top-runner Ichimonji has gone down!
It seems someone was on the track.
J-Jeff... why is Jeff...
The race isn’t over yet.
But what’s this?
Jeff Anemos has come to a stop up ahead.
Shimazaki is closing in from behind.
No! Why are you stopping?
Some kind of mechanical trouble?
Hey! Move it! Fast bikes are coming!
Th-That’s Shimazaki!
Wh-What the hell? Why’d you stop?
Je-Jeff, what kind of move is that?
He threw away the lead just to race me.
Finally, huh?
Let’s settle this properly before the finish line.
Jeff Anemos and Ichimonji Ken
have both started running again.
During the race, Jeff stopped
and gave the lead to Shimazaki.
His puzzling behavior seems driven purely by his obsession with battling Ichimonji Kei.
With half a lap left,
an unexpected event unfolded.
And he crosses the finish line!
Number 17, Shimazaki Ryuichi, takes the win!
He's the junior 250cc class champion!
But the intense battle
on the track isn’t over yet.
Dammit!
Jeff, I will pass you no matter what.
That’s my return for you
winning against me in our race.
Keep it up, Kei—this feeling,
my back’s on fire,
and your fighting spirit lights it up.
It’s strange, Kei—
our rivalry always ignites something blazing inside me.
Wh-What is this?
Feels like I’ve jumped into another world.
The scenery’s melting away...
Damn!
Trying to block me?
From here on, it's a world
only chosen riders can experience.
The frame is creaking.
The engine is screaming!
Kei,
it's the finish!
Hey, Kei!
Kei!
Kei...
Y-You idiot! You did it!
Don’t move! We’ll get you
on a stretcher right away!
Jun...
Looks like I smashed
the bike again, Jun...
Jun, help me up.
Kei.
Jeff.
N-No good, looks like my right hand’s broken.
Handshake’s with the left, then.
All right, Kei.
Jeff, you saw it too, right?
The air suddenly felt like glass,
hard as stone.
Then it shattered like it got blasted to pieces.
It was like cutting through the wind—
a strange world.
Yes, same here, Kei.
I felt that too.
J-Jeff, do you think we’ll ever ride
to outrun the wind together again?
I get the feeling that even if you
were headed to heaven,
you'd ride your bike all the way there.
Nah, I’m not going to heaven just yet.
If you're going to race in America,
I’ll go to America too.
Y-Yes, and then again...
W-We'll... We'll race!
OK, I’ll be waiting, my friend.
RAW provider
Translation
Quality check
Jefferson Taylor
Perevodildo
JmePenseBon
Heat and friction: motor oil starts with knowing the limits.
Choose Castrol.
Choose from Castrol.
Discover something new.
Feel the fresh tension.
Our sports experience: MFJ promotes the proper development of motorcycle sports
based on motorcycle safety and international rules.
To participate in the sport,
first get an MFJ license.
For inquiries, please contact the MFJ sports partner shops
shown on the signboard or call the phone number provided.
Enduro & Forest Road Edition
Now on sale!
Everyone will be moved—off-road spirit captured in 60 minutes of HiFi sound. Featuring enduro winning techniques, forest trail riding skills, and a hilarious hill climb highlight reel—an essential masterpiece video for Garurumans, proudly on sale from Garuru Planning Office. VHS and Beta formats, each 4,800 yen. For orders, see the “Monthly Garuru” mail-order section. Contact Garuru Planning Office at ☎03-264-7427.
“Monthly Garuru” — the opinion leader of off-road bike magazines.
Enduro, motocross, trials, forest trail touring—Garuru is the burning soul’s vanishing point. The nationwide off-roaders' rallying cry is Garuru! The sensation of kissing the earth, Garuru is the must-read monthly magazine for off-roaders.
Monthly Garuru, released on the 6th of every month.
Published by Jitsugyo no Nihon Sha.
Price: 480 yen
For inquiries: 03-535-4441
W-Who are you guys?
Let go! Let me go! Let go!
Execute him!
Execute?
Let go, you asshole!
Hey, wait!
Listen to me!
Hey, you two!
Let go of him!
I'm ordering you!
Kahm!
That's enough.
Kahm! This isn't
what you said would happen!
How dare you lie to me!
Shit! Just once!
Let me have her once before I die!
I don't want to die a virgin!
You are the crown princess
of Saint Evascuraze.
I won't do it!
I'm not going to do
as you say forever, you know!
You're being selfish!
"They"?
The henchmen of some old
man are right on my trail!
They've come here too!
Help me! Help me! Help me!
You'll have to come out
and tell us more about it...
Otherwise, how can we help you?
I'm scared...
A fun, exciting, and delightful electric manga book for manga-loving boys and girls all over the country!
It's true!
He really has the face of an alligator!
And so...?
Ah, you don't believe...
You don't believe me...!
But it's true!
Dream Dimension Gentleman
(Mugen Shinshi: Bouken Katsugeki Hen)
Cetus Tao, huh?
Yes, that's what they called that star on Earth.
Its size and brightness are a lot like the sun.
Dad named the second planet of this star Ozma.
That's the name of the comet
that brought us here.
Darling, check the angle
on the solar panel, would you?
Somebody's fiddled with the console.
Roger.
Again, huh? Oh well...
Dreams fly into the sky, and a heart-pounding, grand drama unfolds! A long journey to the stars that sparkle in the boundless universe has begun.
Dad, can we really live on Ozma?
Of course.
The computer decides that.
It was the one who found it, and it's the one that's investigating it while we orbit it.
Yep. While that happened, you were born,
and have grown up so much.
Chris!
Space Fantasia 2001 Nights
(Space Fantasia 2001 Ya Monogatari)
After 40 years of travelling through time and space, what did the crew seek?
This corrosion is enormous!
Young boys these days are all so pitiful and weak.
And one more thing, boy. It's best that you stop relying on technique so much.
When you're young, vigor is more important than technique.
Something you lack entirely.
Lack entirely...
Confidence
Your manuscript wasn't any good, either.
What?
Not interesting in the least.
All you did was jabber
about the fun you had,
without a hint of anything truly interesting about soaplands.
Ice age
Ryohei-kun! Listen, Ryohei-kun, you mustn't let one rejected manuscript get you down.
You've no idea how many
of my manuscripts were turned down.
Okay? Will you cheer up now?
Wanna fuck...
What?
L-Look, we can't do that!
Indeed, vigor is more important than technique.
I wanna fuck her once again!
If you'll excuse me...
What the...
Wait a minute!
Currently the most popular and best-selling manga artist, Kunitomo Yasuyuki's original work.
Marian...
Shucks, I forgot.
Aki-san, wait...
Ah! Don't go!
Story of Junk Boy going wild
in the publishing world!
Aki-san!
I beg you!
I've never been so shocked in my life
as when you said you weren't satisfied!
Wait a minute! Aki-san!
Let me do you!
Currently being serialized in Futabasha's Weekly Manga Action!
Now open for business!