July 3rd, 1873
Ma, what that?
What happened?
Now I have not a single idea where the key might be.
Achoo!
Not here! It's not here!
Doesn't seem to be here. What about there, Pochi?
No...
Well, that's very bad, so search over there too!
If we don't find it, no one gets their dinner!
Oh, come on!
Rami and Pochi present to you:
Keio Flying Squadron - Action Movie Edition
Special Original Video
Half a year has passed since the ark catastrophe...
Greetings!
Kaian the Kappa here.
Nice to meet you!
Today, I've been invited here to serve
as the presenter in charge of introducing this game.
Well, let's begin at once!
This guy who already made an appearance
is the ultra-intelligent tanuki
with an IQ of 1400 points, Doctor Pon.
Dr. Pon
And here we can see, for the first time,
the fruits of Yamataikoku's labor
in the field of technology - Touma and Shima.
Touma
Shima
And with them, Yamataikoku's 19th Queen
Yamatai Himiko, on the quest to rebuild the kingdom.
Himiko
Facing them is Rami-chan,
who manages to put up a fierce fight all by herself.
Having crossed the Chichibu range, she rows down
the Sumida river, in Ryogoku today, in Kanda tomorrow!
Last time, we saw her riding Pochi's back,
now it's Rami-chan's turn to shine once more!
This time as well, she flies and she springs
and inevitably goes berserk wherever she comes! Yes, her!
In order to lay her own hands on the treasure,
Rami-chan would go through fire and water.
Indeed, who would've thought she'd make it this far?
That said, her carefree lifestyle
makes her put it off for later time after time...
But if she doesn't find the six jewels,
hidden throughout Japan
and obtains the treasures of Yamataikoku,
her carefree and easygoing luxurious life
that she dreamt of
will come to an abrupt end,
much like dreams always do.
Always following in Rami-chan's shadow,
supporting her - only Pochi!
But this time around,
they're joined by one more companion.
Eh? Who is it, you ask?
That would be me! Kaian the Kappa!
Depending on her attitude, I can send Rami-chan to various destinations that you wouldn't be able to access normally!
Indeed, I'm such a reliable and nice guy!
Doctor Pon's minions have gotten a little better
at what they're doing,
but still can't handle her with their bare hands!
But hear me. Hear me, it's fine!
Rami-chan's power during the journey
is twice or thrice the power of their weapon!
Atami, Hinugawa, and Kusatsu remain hidden!
If you succeed collecting those,
nobody would be able to get the better of you!
In the end, you'll get a massive stage
with a chase through the space with the UFO Corps.
Now, in this big three-sided struggle for Japan,
would Doctor Pon's wisdom play the decisive role?
Or would it be Yamataikoku's technology,
wielded by Himiko?
Or perhaps, Rami-chan's drive, after all?
Then, what happened one night...
Half a year has passed since the Ark Catastrophe.
The urban area of Edo gradually keeps recovering.
Of the traces left behind by that incident,
nothing remains, but the enormous crater,
surrounding the city.
In the process of restoration works,
at the site of the future Edo Castle basement,
a mysterious discovery was made.
Inside a huge right arm,
was hidden a transparent ball with a star inside.
And with it, an old scroll.
However, those suddenly disappeared
on the very next day.
Together with Doctor Pon,
who happened to be working part-time
at that construction site to fund his activities.
A bold crime!
Part-time student
charged with embezzlement
And then, several months later...
At that time at Nanahikari family...
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Sorry for interrupting your dinner!
Queen of Yamataikoku
Himiko the 13th
I'm taking this with me. Bye-bye!
Ah! A jewel our ancestors
passed to us through generations!
Why are you just staring?
Transform and chase after her at once!
Here!
Ah! Not you!
Ouch.
Hyper Cutie Rami-chan Change!
Alright.
Ah!
There it is!
And what's that?
Huh? No way! I can't believe it!
Hey, Doctor Pon!
That is mine, so give it back!
So sorry, but that's not happening.
I'll give you something even better in return, though.
Eh? What? What?
Merry Christmas!
No way!
Good, good. The angle is right. Fire!
Huh? What's going on? What's that?
Please stop, hey!
There are five other balls like that jewel,
but of other colors.
If you collect them all, you get rewarded
with a giant treasure, they say.
Rami! Go and collect all the jewels!
Fine!
For me!
Oh?
Okay, just kidding!
Fateful rival
At last, all six jewels are in my possession!
With this, I can revive the only one who can break the seal
on this stupid enchanted door, the Mythical Giant!
Now, answer my call! Mythical Giant!
Yes, that's good.
Alright, open that gate,
behind which the treasure is hidden!
It worked It worked!
So in the end, I'm the one to have the last laugh!
Too bad for you...
But that's not happening!
You guys...
The main heroine appears!
And the story comes to a shocking end...
Pochi!
The star of the newly built Edo!
Me - Rami, and my pet Pochi!
Again and again and again,
we cause a huge commotion!
Exciting incident-filled journey in the Bakumatsu era,
Keio Flying Squadron: Action Movie Edition!
Saturn exclusive software
Keio Flying Squadron - Action Movie Edition
Released on May 17, '96
Victor Entertainment Co., Ltd.
Now available on Saturn!
We've also launched a campaign!
Battles with making a killing
Includes special goods present
Campaign underway!
Final deadline: August 31, '96 (must be postmarked on that day)
For more details, please see the guidebook inside the product
Interview with creators
Director: Honda Akira
The first thing I wanted to do was...
Was this kinda peculiar character.
I mean, the industry is full with cute and strange characters.
So I wanted to imagine there's a world where they can coexist.
That kind of world, and on top of that, some kind of game.
So, we kinda wanted to create that kind of world,
with a sense of unity.
So, initially, well, that was kinda the general idea we had.
So we wanted a story that was inspired
by the Kachi-Kachi Mountain folktale.
The result is then
synthesized on top of it.
[???]
The main character is Bunny Girl, well a rabbit, in fact.
Also inspired by the Kachi-Kachi Mountain folktale.
Both the rabbit and the tanuki.
It's just another kind of rabbit.
So that's how the rabbit came to be the main heroine.
I mean, we couldn't make it an actual rabbit, right?
And well, when I think about it,
when I think of a rabbit, I think of a bunny girl.
That was the course my thoughts took.
But well, making her a usual bunny girl
would be kinda trite too.
You know, this kind of a big-breasted older sister.
Right, so, that was not the image I wanted.
It's just... [???] How do I put it?
We wanted her to look cool, a kinda gamer girl.
And well, that was a bit too...
That didn't match my vision for it.
So, we had to think of some other way...
So... She should be a bunny girl,
but well, without the usual protruding part here.
Physically, she had to lose her sexiness.
Well, without [???]
In short, it was the cutesy bunny girl image that we aimed for.
That's also why she is so young. (12)
If she was to become the protagonist.
It was just before Meiji Restoration,
so I wanted to create a worldview that is like
the eve of a festival, where people
are cheering for a great cause.
I made a lot of adjustments, such as
picking fruits and vegetables, and
I also made a lot of movements,
like in shooting games, especially today's games.
You hit so many eggs and you hardly see
the moment when the enemy character
appears, because you get hit right away.
I tried my best to draw, but I could
hardly get anyone to look at my work.
In the second one, we're going to play a
proper action game this time.
And if we do that, the characters themselves will be a
little questionable if we make it an action game,
And, as for dying soon, I would like to
see the characters move and have fun with it.
The most difficult thing was the refugee's
eastward progress, or the beginning.
Japan 3 The characters are drawn in the
same gender to about the 4th grade, right?
It's more like the image of a researcher's
book on other animated films,
only thinner and more conflicted.
They appear to almost
disappear when viewed in game.
It depends on how many places you
are painting, and that's a bad idea.
I was told to lower the investment trust,
For me, breathing and contraction
are not the same as language.
There was, but I kept it shrunk in a way
that it was just so-so, and it was on my body.
In the end, in the end, it made me feel
that the original image remained pretty
much the same that way, on the contrary.
Yes, there is.
I had memories of the city as a whole, but
this is the first time I've been
attached to the King's You for Table.
The second half came out in the shooter,
and as for that, I'm afraid you'll have
to see the extra section in the game.
Do a little bit of everything.
Is that what you mean by that kind of "ah-ha"?
There are UFOs and mysterious things, but
they are not the same
as what love follows.
You seem to be saying on a person level
that you are quite in
love with the character.
The first 1 in the second column. That's it.
If you take the 1 of 2, your head will go all the way to the end.
However, if you hang up on one,
you can't make a phone call there.
I don't know about you, but the monkey
mode seems to be very easy this time.
Just in monkey mode.
There are many enemy characters that we
cannot see, so if possible, we would like to see them in a single film.
It was amazing and balled up in a
cozy, flowery Asakusa-like setting.
We made it like such a game so that people
could play it in an amusement park.
It would be amazing if people
could enjoy it like that.
Also, the leaving mode is much gentler.
I hope everyone will get into it and
watch it through to the end if possible.
I'm told you'll get a treasure if you make it to the end.
Why does it seems as though there won't be any end, then?!
Tamaki-chan!
Keio Flying Squadron - Action Movie Edition
now on sale for Saturn!
Eh? Launched a campaign too?
Video :
Subs :
WOWmd
Perevodildo