Hey Hiromi, let's play the Cinderella Game.
Hey wait, wait up!
Ah, Kyoko, you wanna play
the Cinderella Game too?
Huh? What's that?
We compete to see which of us
is the most popular among guys.
Whoever brings back
the hottest guy by midnight wins.
Geez, Ako. You always suddenly
come up with weird stuff like this.
Cat's Eye
Milky Gals
Ako...
Hiromi...
You'll like what's coming.
No...
Don't!
Harder...
Do it harder!
Ah! Like that...
I'm feeling it!
No...
Stop!
More...
I feel it...
No...
Don't!
Hiromi...
Ako... Ako...
No, stop...
I feel it...
Do it...
harder!
No...
So nice...
This is the best...
BUSY STUDYING!
KYOKO
Ako!
Hiromi...
Ako...
Ah, what should I do...
Yes, Hiromi...
Ako...
What should I do...
NAKAMORI
AKINA
Harder...
Do it harder!
Ah! It's here...
I can feel it...
No...
Don't...
Ako...
Harder...
I'm feeling it!
No...
Hiromi...
Ako...
No... don't!
It's here...
Harder...
Do it harder!
No...
Hiromi...
Ako...
What should I do?
It's here, Hiromi...
Here we go, Ako. Do your best.
Yeah, I'll go for it.
It's all couples around here.
Only the lame guys are by themselves.
Hey, miss.
She got one!
Perfect match.
Totally Ako's type.
A model, right?
Eh?
You're in some modeling club, right?
Are you not?
N-No...
Well, maybe I am.
Knew it!
You're different from the others.
You caught on quick.
Professional photographer?
Yeah. How about it?
Wanna try working for me
in secret from your agency?
You're just the kind I've been looking for.
Ah, sorry for the late introduction. I'm Kondo.
Ah? It's Kanda-san!
Eh?
Look!
Ah, over there! Kanda-san!
Kanda-san, wait!
Kanda-san, an autograph, please!
Crap...
Sorry, are you okay?
Y-Yes...
Looks like I ruined your clothes.
Let me get you some new ones.
N-No, that's okay.
It's really fine. I'm actually playing the Cinderella Game with my friends right now.
Ah... I mean I'm supposed
to meet up with my friends.
I won't feel right if I don't.
Why don't you get in the car?
Come on, don't be shy.
Let's get in the car.
Maybe I should just go home?
This is my studio.
Go on in, make yourself at home.
Are you scared?
No, not at all.
Don't be shy now.
What's wrong?
In love with me already?
Just wait here a sec. I'll buy you new clothes and come right back.
Okay...
What should I do...
I'm in trouble now...
What should I do?
Really, this is not right.
That was fast.
Alright, let's go.
Yes.
You're really cute, you know.
Eh? No... stop!
No... don't!
Stop... don't!
Don't...
No...
Kyoko!
Takeshi-kun?
You've gotten so pretty.
Not again...
We haven't met since our elementary school graduation, right?
Why are you in a place like this?
Takeshi-kun, what about you?
Whoa, it's really been a while.
It really has.
When was the last time we saw each other?
You know, I'm on my way back
from cram school.
Kyoko...
You left your autograph
in my graduation album, remember?
You wrote that you liked me...
Do you still feel that way?
Kyoko...
Yes...
A flower field...
Kondo-san, wait...
Wait!
Kondo-san...
No...
No... No!
Oh, god...
I'm gonna...
It's here...
Wonderful!
Hey, I'm gonna cum!
Go ahead...
Kondo-san...
I feel like I'm melting...
Takeshi...
it's beautiful.
So good...
Takeshi...
Kanda-san...
It's wonderful...
It's like we're in the ocean...
Kanda-san!
No, not there!
Kondo-san!
Kanda-san...
Yes!
Amazing...
Takeshi... it's amazing!
Kanda-san... I'm at my limit!
No... don't...
Kyoko...
Takeshi...
Takeshi!
I'm cumming...
Takeshi...
Wouldn't something like that
be the best outcome?
Let's go, Kyoko.
Should we try it?
Yeah.
Milky Gals, setting out
for the Cinderella Game right now!
Hey, why don't you come
explore the town with us?
I'm sure we can be friends!
Raw provider............ProxyMan
Translation...........Perevodildo
Quality check.........Anonymous