Family Special
Twelve Sets of Eyes
Love is sparkling eyes
An innocent heart
Someday, that all-engulfing smile
Will bring happiness to you
We don't need sad songs
As long as we have the songs of truth
The waves in the cove chant their steady rhythm
Singing songs of peace
I will cross the bridge of love
Holding hands with you
Holding hands with you...
There are more than 3,000 islands in the Seto Inland Sea,
dubbed "The Sea Garden."
The shore of Shoudoshima
is roughly 400 kilometers long.
This "Olive Island" is the second largest after Awajishima.
It is known for having
its own pilgrimage route.
The sea, the sky, and the earth
were freed from occupation in the spring of the year following the end of the war.
The long and narrow cape made the whole cove look like a lake.
From Ipponmatsu village on the opposite bank of the cove, a solitary rowing boat
departed toward that cape.
April 10,
This skinny, little old lady,
who was reappointed to the Detached Classroom on the cape
after eighteen years, is Ooishi-sensei.
At the helm is her eldest son Daikichi,
now in sixth grade.
His younger brother Namiki
is in fourth grade.
Today, she and her children
have been invited to a class reunion.
That's our Detached Classroom.
It's small.
But it was full of good students.
Mom, did you come to school by boat?
No.
By bike.
April 4,
We are children of the sea, the whitecaps
In the pine grove on the rustling seashore
The smoke is rising above the rush-thatched house
That is our old home from long ago
When I was born, I bathed in the sun
I listened to the waves like a lullaby
The ocean air comes from a thousand miles away
I breathed it in and became a child
In that high and pungent smell
The scent of flowers...
Good morning!
Wh-What was that?
A lady on a bike!
Morning! Good morning!
Oh! Careful...
I'm totally gobsmacked.
Wasn't that the new teacher?
A woman teacher, huh?
On a bicycle.
Good morning!
Daddy, a bicycle!
Oh? And a lady!
Huh?
She rode toward the school.
I wonder why.
Food                                           Sundries
GENERAL STORE
Hey, can you believe that?
I don't like that "Modern Girl."
I don't like her western clothes.
Right?
Cape Detached Classroom
Elementary school students
attended the cape's Detached Classroom
through the fourth grade.
When they reached fifth grade,
they had to go to the main elementary school,
which was five kilometers away.
This is the first year classroom.
Still, seeing you on a bicycle
was quite a shock.
Eight kilometers is a long way
to walk on foot.
Regardless, this is the first time I'm working
with a teacher fresh out of the girls' college.
It took us ten years, but we were finally accredited this year.
Glad to be working with you.
I just got my certificate,
so I'm new at this.
Thanks for having me.
This is my wife.
Pleased to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
Hey!
April
Starting
today,
you are
first years
Twelve first years. This is everyone, right?
Yes, they're all here.
You're all first years now, huh?
Yeah!
Yes!
Quiet.
Meet Ooishi-sensei, the new teacher
for this Detached Classroom.
Nice to meet you.
My house is on the opposite side of the cape.
Look.
See? Over there.
There's a lone pine tree on the opposite side of the inlet, see?
My house is next to it.
My mother is alone there,
waiting for me to come home.
Now we're going to take attendance.
Okada Isokichi-kun.
Is Okada Isokichi-kun not here?
He is!
You?
No!
Okada Isokichi-kun?
Here!
Then just answer with "Yes."
Come on, Sonki! Respond!
Does everyone call you Sonki?
Well then, Isokichi Sonki-san!
Okay, quiet.
Takeshita Takeichi-kun?
Yes!
That was a good response.
Next is Tokuda Kichiji-kun.
Kichi!
Tokuda Kichiji-kun?
Yes!
Very well.
Morioka Tadashi-kun.
Tanko!
Mo-ri-oka Tadashi-kun.
Yes.
Be quicker next time.
Aizawa Nita-kun.
Yessssss!
You seem like a bit of a busybody,
Aizawa-kun.
You're a little too loud as well.
Kawamoto Matsue-san.
Yes.
What do they call you?
Macchan.
Is your father a carpenter?
Nishiguchi Misako-san.
Yes.
Should I call you Misa-chan?
Nuh-uh.
Misa-yun.
That's certainly cute.
Kara Masuno-san.
Yup!
Try saying "Yes."
Masuno-san!
It's Maa-chan.
Kinoshita Fujiko-san.
Yes!
Yamaishi Sanae-san.
Katagiri Kotoe-san!
Yes!
Kabe Kotsuru-san.
Kabekottsuru! Kabekottsuru!
Kabekottsuru! Kabekottsuru! Kabekottsuru!
Ouch...
No! No! Stop that!
No! Stop! Stop!
What's all this clamor?
Hey, you!
Can't you be quieter?!
Chiririn! Chiririn!
Here, one bottle of oil.
Thank you.
Here's the money.
Did you see the woman teacher?
No, I didn't.
What a tomboy teacher.
Goodbye!
Oh?
She even wrote down everyone's nicknames in the class notebook.
I really wish the old teacher could stay.
Yeah.
Ooishi-sensei, who didn't know anything about this,
was approaching a slope
on the outskirts of the village,
hurrying to tell her mother
about everything
that had happened that day.
She kept pedaling steadily.
Ah! I can still see her!
I can see her!
Sensei!
Koishi-sensei!
In addition to "the woman teacher,"
the nickname Koishi-sensei
was also coined that day.
Watch him closely! Start!
That's it, you're still in!
Still in! You're still in!
Let's go!
Sensei!
Look!
My, how pretty.
As he carries a broad ax
on his shoulder, Kintaro
Rides a bear to practice riding a horse
Walk, go, stop, stop, walk, stop, stop
In the depths of Ashigara Mountain
He gathered the beasts to practice sumo
Ready your spirit! You're still in!
September 1,
It had been five months
since Ooishi-sensei began commuting
to the Detached Classroom on the cape.
They'll be saying things,
but you must stay strong.
Even when I go for a home visit,
the parents distrust me.
OOISHI
Your late father was a man
of great patience.
If it's that hard for you, don't do it.
I'm going.
Everything is a matter of enduring.
Today is 210th Day, huh?
The sky's stormy too.
Keep your spirits up.
I'll find you a good husband
in the meantime.
Good morning.
You're the teacher, but you're late!
We'll dock your pay!
Ooishi-Koishi! Ooishi-Koishi!
Quit being so smug!
Your bicycle's a wreck!
Ooishi-Koishi! Ooishi-Koishi!
Um, this is far enough.
I need to take you a little further to reach good roads.
It's dangerous until we're over this hill.
I'm indebted to you, truly.
They came to a point from which the whole village could be seen.
The teacher couldn't help but stare.
It had been horribly ravaged
by the recent storm.
Sensei, Sonki's house got crushed flat.
Oh my.
Were any of your folks hurt?
Yeah.
The old man from Yorozuya
was fixing the roof and fell off.
Yeah.
Life here is tough, huh?
No, this happens every year on 210th Day.
I'd like to take the children to the village
during the lunch break.
Going to the village is good,
but so is exercising caution.
Your reputation among the villagers
is a little controversial.
Controversial?
They could send us a thousand teachers,
but none of them would be able to avert storms.
We're used to storms.
Don't you worry.
If you'd like to help, I suppose...
Why doncha gather your pupils
and start rolling the stones
from the road back to the beach?
See that you don't stain
your western clothes!
Patience. Patience.
There.
And... now.
You know, there was a loud thud back then.
When?
When the old man from Yorozuya fell off the roof.
His wife was so surprised,
she fell on her butt.
Like this!
We can't...
Woman Teacher!
What were you laughing at just now?
Is people's misery that funny to you?
Well? Well?
You're just pretending
to clear the road!
No, I didn't mean to... I never...
You've no notion of being serious!
You'd even go as far as riding Chiririn's cart!
No, Sensei fell off her bike
and twisted her ankle, so...
Why does she even ride such a dangerous bicycle? Well?
She's a lady!
Now, let's return to school, okay?
Even Koishi-sensei makes mistakes.
The following morning,
on the way to school,
Ooishi-sensei's heart felt heavy.
You're just pretending to clear the road!
Seriously? So she can't even ride
her own bicycle properly? How embarrassing!
Patience. Patience.
Look, she's so smug again!
I hear she laughs at other people's misery.
Let's do it. Ready?
It'll be fine.
Are you sure?
Let's do it!
Sensei, we were worried for you.
Why so?
The Yorozuya missus brought you to tears.
We worried you might quit the school.
Let's go to the beach.
We'll sing a song before starting the class.
Teachers don't cry.
Deeper! Deeper! Deeper!
Is this enough?
I won't cry that easily.
What are you cooking?
A pitfall?
If you tell anyone, we'll put you in it.
Spring comes early
So at the riverside, among the thick reeds
A crab opens a store, a barbershop, that is
Cut-cut-cut. He cuts everything!
Sensei!
Don't go the—
Here comes a rabbit
The crab has a customer
Sensei! Don't step there!
Sensei!
Stay back!
You'll fall into the hole...
Man Teacher!
Don't make such a fuss.
You're in school.
It's Woman Teacher!
What?!
Sensei! Sensei!
Let's cool it down with this.
It doesn't look broken.
I can't...
This looks serious.
Ooishi-sensei, come on. Stand up.
Oh! Sensei!
Sensei!
Looks like she tore a tendon.
Food                                    Sundries
GENERAL STORE
Sensei, we should get you
to the city doctor as soon as possible!
No, we should use a boat.
This cart is shaking too much.
Sensei!
Koishi-sensei!
I hear the woman teacher got hurt!
Woman Teacher!
It's your fault, Yorozuya madam!
It's you!
It's your fault! Your fault!
What did I do?
Ten days passed, and then half a month,
but the woman teacher did not come back.
Ready?
I-I-I! Fu-Fu-Fu! Mi-Mi-Mi.
Mi-Mi!
Entering Hakone
The mountains
of Hakone
Are as swords
beneath the heavens
Kankokukan
Cannot begin
to compare
No laughing. Don't laugh!
I said don't!
Don't laugh!
Man Teacher, you got it wrong!
What's wrong?
Do! Re! Mi! Fa!
Sol! La! Ti!
Do!
Okay, then let's sing it next.
You ready? Listen closely. Singing!
The mountains of Hakone are
as swords beneath the heavens
Kankokukan cannot begin to—
Hey!
Entering Hakone
The mountains
of Hakone
Are as swords
beneath the heavens
Kankokukan
Cannot begin
to compare
What's so funny?
I don't like Man Teacher's singing one bit.
"The mountains of Hakone are
as swords beneath the heavens."
I really enjoyed
Woman Teacher's singing more.
When will she come back?
I miss our Woman Teacher!
Me too! Me too!
Why don't we go and see her?
Should we?
Let's go!
Let's go without telling anyone!
They won't scold us this way.
Good.
If we're quick, nobody will notice!
Yeah!
Let's go!
What? Nita too?
Sonki's mother also came to ask earlier.
But I really don't have a clue.
There sure ain't any children here.
They all vanished into thin air.
Spring comes early
So at the riverside, among the thick reeds
A crab opens a store, a barbershop, that is
Cut-cut-cut. He cuts everything!
It will be dark by the time we head back.
What if there are monsters?
Don't talk like that.
Whatever! Go back, you cowards!
It's the fifth years!
Hide! Hide! Hurry!
Did anyone hear talking?
It's a dog.
It's a tanuki!
We're in the town,
but where's the lone pine tree?
You can see it over there.
It's still a long way.
The road to the lone pine tree was tough.
The pine tree seemed so close
when you look at it from the cape.
Today, they couldn't even see it.
For those long eight kilometers, everyone walked in silence.
My feet hurt.
Macchan.
Hurry up.
I'm hungry!
Stop it!
I want to cry too!
A bus is coming!
If only we had money,
we could ride on it.
Does anyone have any?
Oh my.
Please stop.
My, oh my.
Sensei!
What are all of you doing here?
We wanted to see you.
We missed you!
We're so glad to see you!
Is it still a long way to your house?
No, it's right there. Look.
This is good.
They cook so good in Sensei's house!
Have as many servings as you like.
I'm already stuffed!
I'm stuffed too.
Another bowl!
Sure.
Let's all take a photo together later.
Then I'll take you back by boat.
You all need to go home.
Okay!
Is everyone ready?
Okay, I'm taking it now.
You, the littlest one. Crowd in a bit.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
Okay, here I go.
Aren't they all so cute?
They really are.
I want to teach at the classroom on the cape again.
Ask the main school principal for me.
Can you be that selfish?
They've already found a new teacher.
You're right, I...
I'll visit the cape on my way back.
Excuse me!
Here, one with beans. Five with rice.
Uh... and one with dried sardines.
You've been such a good guardian
for the children.
This is a thank you from the parents.
My, you're so kind.
And this one... A request from
the Yorozuya lady, steamed buns.
She made them specially for you.
Oh my. Thank you.
When will you be coming to the classroom?
I was thinking of going later today.
Today?
She needs to go there to say good-bye.
My heart calls me to the familiar land
To say my final good-byes
Because yesterday they sent for me...
Wrong. The first-graders came to see me
without even telling their parents.
They'd probably tell them not to come.
But my sense of duty wouldn't let me go,
beckoning me to where I belong...
In the village on the cape,
where change was scarce,
any guests, coming by sea or by land,
were discovered quickly.
Oh, it's Ooishi-sensei!
Sensei!
Food                                      Sundries
It's Woman Teacher!
It's Ooishi-sensei!
She really did come back.
What?
To say good-bye?
Yes, I won't be able to ride my bicycle for a while.
And I can't take time off forever.
You can come by boat!
I'll go pick you up every day!
Me too! Ipponmatsu is a hop, skip, and a jump away!
Sensei, you can't quit.
Come on, don't quit.
Sensei.
Why would you quit?
Sensei, the children really want you to stay.
We'll pick you up and drop you off.
You can't quit.
We've never had a teacher
as good as you.
We'll find a house for you
until your leg heals.
Thank you.
But...
Another woman teacher
will be coming soon.
Will she?
The cape town will feel
lonely without you.
Aren't you glad that Sensei's leg got better?
At least see her off with a smile!
Augh! This is so troublesome!
Cry, cry!
Cry all you want if you're a sissy!
Hmph!
Yeesh.
You have third period off.
Okay, let's see Sensei off together!
Starting next spring, I'll be teaching at the main school.
I'll be waiting for you
when you're fifth years.
Wow! That's great!
I'm so glad!
We'll be waiting.
Don't break your promise!
We mean it!
Sensei, pinky promise.
Okay, okay.
If I should lie, I'll swallow 1,000 needles.
Now, let's all sing The Light of the Fireflies together.
I prefer Seven Children!
Seven Children!
Crow, why do you cry?
Because in the mountains
I have seven cute crow children
Cute, cute crow children,
they are crying there
My cute, cute children are crying
Go to our old home in the mountains
The strong sunlight,
the sea breeze caressing her face,
the receding cape village,
and the sparkles in
the children's rounded eyes,
And look at his round eyes
would be burned into
Ooishi-sensei's memory forever.
What a good boy he is
April 4,
The turquoise waters,
the mountain peaks...
Everything was the same as before.
However, in those four years,
the Mukden Incident had happened,
as well as the Shanghai Incident.
The carpenter Kawamoto had no work.
His wife, having given birth three days ago, was sleeping.
Hurry to school.
Both Macchan and Misa bought a lunch box with a lily flower.
I know.
I wish I had one too.
Fine, fine.
Really? You will buy it?
Matsue, your mother is still in pain
from giving birth prematurely.
Once I'm better, I'll buy it for you.
A lunch box with a lily?
Yeah. With a lily, a chrysanthemum, or whatever.
Your father has had no work lately.
We're in a tight spot.
Don't cry.
Starting today, you're going to
the main school, where Ooishi-sensei is.
You're right!
Mom, get better soon.
Ooishi-sensei's first years from
the cape had become fifth years.
Whoa! Takeichi shoes are downright fancy today!
Kozuru-chan's too!
They're too big for me.
I'll try them on!
Still too big.
Mom says it's so they'll last me three years.
Okay, I'll wear them!
As he carries a broad ax
on his shoulder, Kintaro
Rides a bear to practice riding a horse...
See, Kozuru-chan?
The lunch stays warm this way.
It's because of the lily flower lunchbox, right?
What is the flower on your lunchbox, Macchan?
Mine has a red chrysanthemum.
KIMURA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Oh, Sensei!
Sensei!
KIMURA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Oh my, there's so many of you!
Sensei!
I've been waiting, thinking you'd be here any moment now.
You're all so big.
KIMURA ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
Sensei, I'm right here!
My mom gave birth to a girl.
Congratulations.
What's her name?
She doesn't have one yet.
Once Mom can get up again,
she's gonna buy me
an aluminum lunchbox.
It'll have a lily on the lid.
Hey, why not name the baby Yuriko?
Or maybe Yurie would be better?
Yurie is good!
Yurie! Yurie! Yurie!
About the marriage talks from earlier...
How does next Sunday sound for a matchmaking meeting?
The cape children are in fifth grade.
You ought to settle down now.
But...
There's always a "but" with you.
Your mother wants to see
her grandchild's face soon.
When the commencement
ceremony ended,
the children from the cape had
a long trip home ahead of them,
so they had an early meal
from their lunchboxes.
Eat quietly.
Chew your food well.
Huh? Macchan's lunchbox...
I've never seen one that's not aluminum.
Hey, look, mine has a lily on the lid.
Mine has a lily and a chrysanthemum.
Mine's a chrysanthemum.
Mine's a lily!
Goodbye, Sensei!
Goodbye!
Take care! Don't dawdle along the way!
Sensei.
My Dad's going to buy me that aluminum lunchbox with the lily on it soon.
I see.
Let me see it, okay?
Take care of you mother.
Yeah.
Good-bye.
Summer is approaching
on the 88th night of the year
Young leaves are lush
in the fields and mountains
And what do you see there?
Is that not tea picking?
On a red background, there's sedge and...
A single fishing boat rowed quickly across the calm spring sea.
Is Macchan there?!
I am!
Your mother... She suddenly took a turn for the worse.
She was taken to the hospital in town!
She's on that boat, then?
Yes.
Mom!
That happened to Matsue's mother?
Yes.
The very night she was admitted to the hospital.
Then the baby too,
like she was following her.
Ooishi-sensei
took the road to the cape on her bicycle for the first time in a long time.
She had a lily flower lunchbox
hanging from the handlebars.
Matsue-san.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Matsue-san.
It's a lunchbox with a lily on the lid.
Thank you.
Through the principal's efforts, Ooishi-sensei was married by the end of that spring.
Best             Wishes
Her husband was an engineer,
operating a ship on the Seto Inland Sea.
Even a month later,
Matsue didn't come to school.
No! No! I don't want to go to Osaka!
I wish I could let you stay here too.
But with your mother gone, I can't!
We'll have to live separately for now.
Okay?
No! No! Let me stay in this house, Dad!
I want to go to school too!
Don't you understand
after everything I've said?!
Mom!
MATSUE
So Macchan went to Osaka on the boat last night.
To Osaka?
She's getting adopted by some relatives.
We all went to see her off
part of the way, but...
Macchan didn't say a word.
It must have been painful for her.
That year, the fall school trip for the 5th and 6th graders
was a pilgrimage to Kompira Shrine.
They would leave on a boat at 4:00 in the morning
DATE
School
trip for
5th and
6th graders
Itinerary
Kompira
Shrine,
Yashima,
Ritsurin Garden
and return in the evening.
But Shoudoshima families were poor,
even if they worked hard.
Of 80 people in two groups,
only 60% of the children could go.
Of the children from the cape, only Sanae didn't come.
Sensei, what ship are you looking at?
All of them.
Sensei, I think you're looking for the ship
your husband is on.
Of course not.
Aren't you sad that Sanae-san couldn't come?
Sanae-chan didn't have a new hakama to wear on the trip.
Does that even matter?
Filled with pity for Sanae,
who was left to study all by herself,
Ooishi-sensei couldn't help
but have a heavy heart.
Where the pine grove disappears into the distance
Shadows of white sails float
Dried nets hang high on the beach
Seagulls fly low among the waves
Behold the noonday sea
Everyone, we will arrive
at Tadotsu in ten minutes.
Be sure to take all of your belongings.
Excuse me...
Uh, what is it?
Are you Ooishi-sensei's husband?!
No! He's not!
You're mistaken.
My husband is resting at home today.
They took the first train from Tadotsu
to pay a morning visit to Kompira Shrine.
They left Yashima for Takamatsu and stopped for lunch for the third time at Ritsurin Garden.
While waiting for the return boat at the pier,
Special            Regional
SO                 UV                  EN                  IRS
on a side street full of souvenir shops,
Ooishi-sensei heard a familiar voice.
Come, don't be shy!
Welcome!
Matsue-san!
Matsue-san, didn't they send you to Osaka?
It's a good thing we could meet.
Who are you?!
You can't just take her out
without telling me!
It's Ooishi-sensei, missus.
I am Ooishi of Shoudoshima's Main Elementary School.
I used to be Kawamoto Matsue-san's schoolteacher.
Oh, that's a whole different matter, then!
Thank you.
She's a very good and patient child.
Please take good care of her.
Oh, Sensei, surely you don't think we're mistreating her?
No, I didn't mean that.
It's just that I've been constantly worried about her.
Stay strong, and write to me, will you?
Yeah.
You could also pass this to her father while you're at it:
"She's in good hands."
The lily flower lunchbox that you gave me...
I cherish it as if it was you!
Thank you.
Always keep it by your side, okay?
That lady, is she your relative?
No.
I see...
Matsue! A customer is waiting!
Okay.
Sensei...
No! Smile!
No need to see me off.
I'll come again.
Okay?
Matsue!
The sun was setting.
The wind was cold, and the students were sleeping, exhausted.
Not a day would pass without Ooishi-sensei
praying for the happiness of each one of them.
After the school trip, Ooishi was unwell
and took almost ten days off.
The doctor said that her likely due date
was early March of next year.
Hello!
Well now, if it isn't the cape party again!
Sensei's illness...
Is she having a baby soon?
Kozuru-chan suggested
that we ask Sensei this.
We'd never think up
something like that on our own.
If she does, I'm going
to the midwife school in Osaka
to become a professional!
And then you won't have to worry
about the delivery!
Well, come inside now.
The photos from our school trip are ready.
Yay!
Wow!
Kozuru-chan looks so good on this one!
Hey! Show me! Show it to me!
Nonsense! Masuno-san looks
way prettier in it.
Tell me, what are you all
going to do next year?
I'll go to a middle school for girls.
And after that, a music school.
I'll go to a sewing school.
No exams there!
But I thought your mother wanted to send you to a prefectural girls' school, Misako-san.
They'd probably teach arithmetic there.
And I get a headache
just from looking at numbers.
I'll be moving next year.
Sensei, Kotoe-chan won't
study past sixth grade.
You won't even go to middle school?
But don't you like the school?
Yeah.
Should I try to ask your parents to change their mind?
Besides, it's settled already.
I made a promise.
To whom?
To my mom, that I'd help
with the housework.
She let me go on the school trip
because I won't go to sixth grade.
Instead, when I turn 18,
I'll go to Osaka to work,
and buy my own kimono
with my first paycheck!
And then, you'll find a husband?
Yeah.
I hope I find myself a husband soon!
Sensei, show us your husband's picture!
Show us a picture of the two of you!
Do you have one somewhere?
I don't know...
Perhaps I snuck one in somewhere.
Come on, Sensei! Show us!
I'm home! Huh?
Hey, how's it going?
Good morning!
Right, morning.
Hey, you said Sensei's
husband had a beard.
No, he doesn't.
Wow! He's real!
How wonderful!
You don't have a beard!
Well, maybe I should grow one.
Even at this moment of happiness with her kind husband, surrounded by innocent children,
Ooishi-sense couldn't stop a dark shadow
from suddenly crossing her mind.
That's embarrassing!
Manchukuo had been created
in March of the previous year.
Sign: Manchukuo Government House
In May, commissioned officers
from the Army and Navy conspired
Manchukuo National Founding, Commemorative Special Edition
Great Unrest In Imperial Capital
Seven Assailants Attack Prime Minister Inukai
Leaving Him In Critical Condition
With Two Bullets In His Head
Prime Minister's Residence Attacked
to assassinate Prime Minister Inukai.
Which path would Japan take from then on?
Would her husband be swallowed
by the flames of war?
The dreaded shadow of war
was steadily approaching Japan.
Ooishi-sensei couldn't help but pray that it wouldn't reach her family.
What's wrong?
You seem worried.
I've read in the papers that a lot of people speaking against the war are being rounded up.
I fear that they may start
a war on the continent soon.
If that happens,
won't you be sent there too?
What in the world are you saying?
The Manchurian Incident is finally over,
and Manchukuo has been established.
We should all be grateful
that the worst has passed.
The following February,
Ooishi-sensei had a baby, a boy named Daikichi.
After taking three weeks off,
she returned to school.
Today, I want you to think
about your future.
Sunny
Japan
Essay
"My
Future"
Draw whatever comes to your mind first.
When I grow up, I'll be a soldier!
After I finish middle school,
I'll join the military academy.
After I graduate from high school,
I'll be a fisherman, until the Army drafts me.
In the Army, I'll become a non-commissioned officer, and then a sergeant major.
Sunny
Japan
Essay
"My
Future"
Why are you so determined
to become a soldier?
Sensei, you hate soldiers?
Essay
"My
Future"
Yes. I prefer fishermen and rice farmers.
Why is that?
Death is a pitiful thing.
I'm no coward!
Essay
"My
Future"
Right, not a coward.
My own father died early in the last war.
That's why I dislike seeing men die so much.
Sunny
Japan
Essay
"My
Future"
Ours is a small school,
so even the walls have ears here.
Ooishi-sensei, saying that you hate
the military at such a turbulent time...
But my father was in the Navy.
And died a warrior's death, right?
How can you, his child, say that you
oppose war and hate soldiers?
But I really do hate them.
Ooishi-sensei, it seems your postpartum is still affecting you.
Well, schoolteachers are being brought in for questioning all over the country now.
Be cautious. Cautious.
I'm quitting the school this March.
Quitting?
I'd rather quit and run a candy store than do this.
A schoolteacher isn't allowed
to say that she's against the war.
More than half of my boys
want to be soldiers.
Can't you just keep that to yourself?
The Navy took your husband away.
Do you want your grandson to die in the army too?
Nobody would want that.
I always hoped that you'd be spared my fate.
Isn't it obvious, then,
that we should both oppose this war?
You fool...
These days, you can't hope to live long if you tell everyone the truth.
You should keep the truth to yourself.
That's just how the world is.
I'll quit the school.
As you wish.
A graduation ceremony was held
at the end of March.
It was also the day Ooishi-sensei would leave school behind.
That was the last graduation certificate to be handed out today.
And now, some parting words from Ooishi-sensei.
Did you know?
I didn't.
Sensei...
Quiet!
Quiet, everyone!
Congratulations on your graduation, everyone.
Each of you is going to walk different paths from now on.
So please stay cheerful
every step of the way.
I am also leaving the school,
to walk my own path.
But I will remember all of you
fondly for the rest of my life.
Sensei, why are you quitting?!
Tell us! Why?!
Oh, my! No, stop crying! Stop crying!
Please start the graduation song now.
It was a spring morning,
but the wind was still chilly.
Ooishi-sensei bid farewell
to the five years she had spent teaching.
I give my thanks to my teacher
For his kindness
To the garden of his teachings
I will soon return
When I think about those long years
They have flown by so quickly
Now it's time for us to part
It's time to say goodbye
Sure enough, the cape children
came to see her the very next day.
I'll be here every day,
so stop by anytime.
Okay. I'll be coming to babysit Daikichi.
Better focus on becoming a fine midwife.
Will you let me look after your babies, then?
Well, by then, I may well be
a grandmother myself.
Sensei, I'm going to enroll
in a normal school
to become a fine teacher, just like you.
Thank you. Do your best.
Then, we'll go catch the next bus now.
Give my regards to everyone on the cape.
Ah, sorry, sorry.
Now, now, now, now.
There, there, there.
Sensei, Takeichi's here.
Isokichi's here!
Oh, it's such a pleasure to see you.
Come inside.
We need to catch the next bus.
Ah, I see.
Takeichi-kun, when does your middle school start?
Next week.
I see.
Do your best.
What about you?
I'm starting as an apprentice
tomorrow night.
So you changed your mind?
Yes.
Sensei, thank you for all
you've done for us.
What shop will it be?
A pawnshop.
If I work there until I join the Army,
they'll take me in as a clerk.
Stay strong.
With enough patience,
you can be a great clerk.
Okay.
I put pencils and notebooks
in here for you.
Please share it with the cape girls.
Thank you!
I will be watching over all of you,
even when you grow big.
When her teaching is done,
a teacher becomes a student herself.
Come again, okay?
We will!
Goodbye then!
And take good care, you two!
The war that began with the Manchurian Incident eventually grew into World War II.
The fates of the twelve children
also changed drastically.
Takeshita Takeichi enlisted as a military pilot
as soon as he graduated from college.
The most boisterous and unruly child,
Aizawa Nita, went into the Navy.
Morioka Tadashi joined the army
and fought in the Guadalcanal campaign.
His unit was decimated.
Okada Isokichi was the lone survivor
of his expeditionary unit.
But a bomb explosion left him forever blind.
As for Katagiri Kotoe,
who went to work in Osaka,
she contracted tuberculosis
and died soon after returning to the village.
In August of 1945, the war ended.
Ooishi's husband, who served on a transport ship in southern seas, was killed in action.
Ooishi's third child, a girl named Yatsu, was born weak
and died soon after Ooishi's mother.
Every day, they struggled to find something to eat and something to wear.
Ooishi-sensei had to learn
to work in the field,
and she worked hard until
she got blisters on her palms.
Patience. Patience.
Her only emotional support at that time was her eldest son Daikichi,
who grew up strong and lively,
and her second son Namiki.
Then, one day, her former student
Yamaishi Sanae came to see Ooishi-sensei.
Sanae had graduated from a normal school and become a teacher.
She came to Sensei
to discuss whether she would be a substitute teacher at the Detached Classroom.
Ooishi-sensei was delighted to take her up on that offer.
And now, Ooishi-sensei was going there
for a reunion with her students of long ago.
Hey, look.
See the graves over there?
Yeah. There, on the hilltop.
Ah! I see them, I see!
I'll go visit my mother's grave first.
You two wait here for a bit.
The soldiers' graves were
at the top of the hill.
First Sino-Japanese, Russo-Japanese, Second Sino-Japanese...
The old stone monuments were arranged in order.
The newer ones were made of plain wood.
What a pity.
A life is reduced to a single wooden stake.
Won't you...
yell something for me once more?
Morioka Tadashi-kun.
Takeshita-kun too...
You wanted to go to college
and devote your life to science.
What a waste!
I'm sick of wars.
Is someone here?
My, Sensei!
Welcome! Oh my!
Come in, come in!
You! Come on in! Don't be shy!
Hey!
Really, Dai-chan?
That was a little too overwhelming for him.
Isn't he lively?
Sensei, you're finally here!
Really...
Come, this way.
Thank you.
Sensei!
Kozuru-san, is that you?
Really...
Sensei!
That's my Misako-chan!
It's been so long!
Now, sit down. Here.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Right.
Sonki-san.
Sensei,
long time no see.
Right... Right, it's been seven years!
Since the day we came to see you off.
When it happened, I thought I'd rather be dead, but I've become an Anma masseur instead.
I'd love to experience that myself.
Ah, Sonki-san.
I brought this because I wanted you to use it. Here.
The cane that I used when I hurt my foot.
I used it instead of crutches when my foot got better.
How wonderful, Sensei!
I painted it ten days ago,
so it should be dry by now.
But will bamboo really suit you?
Thank you, Sensei.
I'm going to treasure it.
Try walking too.
Right.
Come on!
He'll be fine.
He can walk anywhere with it.
I will always hold it, thinking
that it's a hand you lent me, Sensei.
Sorry for making you wait!
Thank you.
Bring the sake here too!
We don't have any.
I have some, but it's barely enough for us.
With sake, any amount is enough!
Oh my! Drinking already, Mi-chan?
When I think about my husband,
I can't sleep at night.
Here.
Thank you.
The rationed sake my husband drinks is always diluted with substitutes.
Same here. This sake was rationed to my dad.
My dad stopped drinking altogether after he lost his leg.
Thank you.
Well now, should we leave
formalities aside?
Welcome!
Where's everyone?
Waiting on the second floor.
Take the slippers!
Thanks.
Macchan.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Kichiji-san!
Sensei, fisherman Kichiji here.
Kichi!
Yeah.
That's right.
My condolences.
I served in the interior during the war,
so I couldn't come to say it sooner.
Thank you very much.
But I really think people offering their condolences only makes it more painful.
The two mementos from my husband,
playing over there, are what gives me strength.
Sensei, our Kichi provided all the sashimi today.
Well, isn't that impressive?
It's nothing. I just wanted to make sure
there's enough for Sensei.
Thank you.
Well, now that everyone is here,
should we raise a toast?
Yeah.
To Ooishi-sensei!
I wish good health to Sensei and her boys!
Well, to you!
To you!
Thank you so much.
A man is a boy's best friend.
Please let me meet with your kids and teach them what little I know.
Certainly.
I have no way of repaying your kindness.
What are you saying?
I'm just happy that you returned alive.
Better get good at Anma Massage soon.
You'll use your hands to repay Sensei.
Right.
Everyone here has been through a lot, I imagine.
That's right.
My parents wanted to send me
to music school, no matter what.
But I just don't seem
to understand the notes.
Me too.
Back when everyone went on a field trip to Kompira Shrine,
as I was watching the ship go out to sea without me,
I wanted to throw myself into the sea and drown.
Enough with everyone wanting to die!
Masuno-san, won't you sing for us again?
Sure.
Let's sing together!
We are children of the sea...
Ah... Wait a minute.
First, the photo we took
under that lone pine tree.
If anyone has it,
I want you to show it to me.
Back when I was shell-shocked...
Sonki-san, you can see that photo?
I can.
I have it here.
I even brought it with me
to the bomb shelter during the war.
Sonki-san.
There she is. Sensei's in the middle.
To the right, below, it's me.
At the lower left, it's Takeichi.
Next to him, Nita.
Next to me, Macchan.
Right?
Did I guess it right, Sensei?
Exactly!
You can see it perfectly!
Right?
I'm impressed, really!
Well. Now that's sorted,
let's sing together with Sonki!
"We are children of the sea!"
Three, four...
We are children of the sea, the whitecaps
In the pine grove on the rustling seashore
The smoke is rising above the rush-thatched house
That is our old home from long ago
When I was born, I bathed in the sun
In their singing voices, Ooishi-sensei still saw her twelve students from eighteen years ago.
I listened to the waves like a lullaby
The ocean air comes from a thousand miles away
Back then, probably none of them ever thought that parting and going their separate ways
I breathed it in and became a child
would be their fate after graduation.
In that high and pungent smell...
In your eyes
The innocent picture
From when I was still a child
Remains unfaded
In your eyes
The children's song
That we lost to the sea that day
Remains unfaded
As we get born, grow up, and start walking
Everyone has to go their own way
The unstoppable flow of time
Inevitably changes us all!
But in your eyes
I can see myself as I was that day
I am still there
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raw acquisition
Raw scanning
Presented by
Iri, Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Rezo
MartyMcFlies (LonelyChaser Fansubs)
Kineko Video
Orphan Fansubs