As always, a nice hipline.
Excuse me, boss!
Why do you always go around
feeling people's behinds?
Boss, the fruits have arrived!
Oh, they're here already?
Can you just leave then there?
Why me!?
Hey, where's Yagi?
Over there, where the shy ones are.
I wonder if they're college students...
No, as grown-up as they appear,
they're definitely in high school.
Hey, those sailors are looking
over here. Try to look friendly.
Even though we're in
high-school, don't be so reserved!
There's only a year difference between us!
After one more year, you'll be in college!
What's the matter?
Uh, nothing!
You better watch out. This guy's a virgin!
No way! This guy is so cute!
Kubota's the shy type!
Poor Kubota-san...
For Kubota-san, I'll give it to him!
Ah, how unfair!
Hey, you're in luck, Kubota!
This'll be Yarahata's graduation!
Yarahata - A Girl who has not lost her virginity by the age of 20
Yarahata?
I think I'll go and use the toilet...
That's something I'd like to
get rid of as soon as possible.
But... I can't, forever.
It may not be dramatic,
but for the first time...
a beautiful person is fine.
Fujisaki...san.
Now that I remember about that sweet
Jr. High School memory...
I was hopelessly thinking about
Fujisaki Masana-san.
It's definitely Fujisaki Masana!
You know. There is confusion at the
audition because of the fatal accident.
I'll have an alembic orange.
It boggles the mind.
It happened to a girl I know.
At the police station
they showed me the video,
"This is you, isn't it?" they said.
Isn't it horrible?
How horrible!
After all, for guys,
a woman is just a sex object.
Of course!
At the end of the date, my boyfriend
always wants to go to a motel.
I don't like guys who
don't know a girl's heart.
Yeah, but it doesn't look
good if you don't have a boyfriend.
Speaking of boyfriends, I hear
you've been arguing with Kazuya-san.
So what's going on, Fujisaki?
I know we have been through a lot...
but Kawahara and I broke up recently.
Eh? Is that so?
I see...
Oh...but, it's been a long time.
Five years, isn't it?
But, Fujisaki,
I now can say this:
I don't like Kazuya-san very much.
Yeah, I think you made the right decision.
That's right! There were
times he showed some insincerity.
He only seems cool.
Right, right, right, right!
Just because he looks nice,
he's been bragging about himself.
Yeah, he's called all my
model friends out for a date!
Yes! That's unforgivable!
Exactly!
He called me once, but I didn't want
to cause trouble with my friends at work.
Well, what if he wasn't Fujisaki's man?
For Kazuya-san, if we were just walking
together, it wouldn't look bad.
Ahhh, so then for you,
Kazuya-san's just an accessory!
I didn't say that!
Fujisaki, do you know him?
Hmmm... I don't think so.
Sheesh... I wonder if that's
a new way of picking people up.
That completely failed.
But, I never forgave you.
On top of that, Fujisaki
said she didn't know me.
Where'd he go, that Kazuya?
Being so indecisive,
that's why all the girls left.
It's because you
touched the high-schooler's butt
Cheek time's started
Come dance with me...
...Kubota-kun.
Oh! Babe!
Don't just suddenly stop!
I don't believe it!
Fujisaki-san's hair
such a nice fragrance.
I wonder if the fragrance is kinmokusei?
Scented osmanthus -
a part of the olive shrub family with fragrant flowers.
Huh? Oh no!
My groin...
Okay, don't erect, don't erect!
Kubota-kun, Kubota-kun.
W-what is it?
Lend me your ear.
Thanks for defending me just then.
Kubota-kun.
Kubota-kun... are you free now?
Kubota-kun...
Here, this is my phone number.
Ahh, my head hurts... hangover?
I did it!
Ah! He's back!
Kubota! Don't you
have any sake? Sake!
How odd...
I wonder if it's just my timing...
Fujisaki-san!
Kubota-kun!
These chance encounters...
very nice, aren't they?
Kubota-kun.
I've got this photo session coming up.
but I haven't been able
to get the pose right.
So could you give me a hand?
Will I be able to help?
Of course!
Beautiful park at night...
The location's perfect!
The stance is fine...
What kind of session is it?
It's the facial
expression of you kissing.
When you kiss, you
obviously close your eyes, right?
When you practice in front of a mirror,
by yourself, you can't really see.
This... err... umm...
Ah! Uh, uh, I...
Kubota-kun, you've got a sweet tooth,
as expected of a baker.
A part time job, huh?
How nice...
I wanted to go to college too.
Being a model is tough. In order
to look good, I'm always dieting
even though I love sweets.
I haven't had a cake in a long time.
Ah! I'll make you a diet cake!
Diet cake?
Instead of sugar,
I'll use artificial sweetener.
Instead of cream,
I'll use low-cal whip cream.
You're very smart!
Can you really make one?
I'm glad.
Eh?
Uh, err. Oh, nothing.
I'm surprised you know
all the places around here.
Well, I came here often
on dates with Kazuya...
Kubota-kun, you know, I...
Ah, it's Masana-chan.
Kazuya!
Kubota-kun,
do you want to go back?
If you just do as I say...
It can't be the same
Fujisaki-san I met initially...
I'm sorry I'm late.
I got a little dizzy.
Are you okay? You look tired.
It's better if you rest a bit.
But, that wouldn't be fair! How about...
It's okay! I'm perfectly fine.
Liar.
Uh, this? Uh that's...
uh, my meaning is on the contrary.
I can say this,
that I've noticed ever since Jr. High.
Your feelings.
But then, because Kazuya was around...
I'm sorry.
Uh, uh, wait a minute, Fujisaki-san!
I've suddenly noticed!
That, uh, the truth is, uh, uh...
I'm not prepared.
Perhaps you were talking about...
This?
Ahhhh!!
Please don't think of me as an 'H' girl.
Right now, even ordinary
girls have to have them.
I-I see.
I'll put it on for you!
Wha!? It's okay! I'll put it on myself.
Quickly, okay?
Q-quickly...
It's okay, this being your first time...
There's nothing to worry about.
Ah, ah.  You're entirely too fast!
That's why you need help, being a virgin.
Wha... what should I do?
Fuji...
Eh?
Wha... no way!
Fu... Fujisaki-san?
Fujisaki-san?
She must be really tired.
And that I was worried about losing faith...
I'm really sorry, Kubota-kun.
Me, being...
No need to apologize, Fujisaki-san.
But...
It's nothing to worry about.
After that, I called room service and
ordered smoked salmon, an egg sandwich,
and a chicken basket.  Then, with
a full stomach, fell fast asleep!
It feels good being cold.
I wonder if you remember from
Jr. High, the game center near school.
It's now a pizza place, ya know?
And the mansion standing to
the left of it? Room 201 is my room.
Tomorrow I have a photo shoot,
so, how about the day after
tomorrow, can you come over?
If it's okay with you,
we can continue from last night...
I-I'm sorry, Fujisaki-san.
I have night shift
the day after tomorrow, so...
You can't!
Please, if it is not the
day after tomorrow, I can't...
Please...
Kazushi-kun, have you been
playing around, without resting?
While you're saying that,
would you quit touching me, boss?!
What's that strange cake?
"Strange" is a bit rude.
"Healthy" cake? I think I'll have some.
Kazushi.
Yes?
"Healthy" cake is just like you.
Will you be satisfied by
eating it, or will you get fat?
You are always thinking for someone else.
But there are times when you
have to decide for yourself, right?
But, if you get slapped,
I'll be here to comfort you!
Kubota-kun!
Please, come in!
Sorry to intrude.
You know,
I have something to show you.
Kubota-kun.
Here!
Hey! This is the graduation
album from Jr. High!
Nostalgic, isn't it?
After I saw you, I felt like looking at it,
and went searching all over for it.
This is Fujisaki-san.
And in the front row, the small and
cute one, is Kobota-kun.
Both of us have changed a lot.
That's true.
After I entered high school,
I grew about 20 centimeters.
That's why, after seeing you in Roppongi,
I couldn't tell whether or not it was you.
Yea, I was hurt
that you didn't say anything.
I'm sorry, okay?
Say, do you remember what I said
two days ago, that night?
That I knew
your feelings since Jr. high?
That's why, when you
defended me at the disco,
I thought you might
still have those feelings.
I...
...must be a cruel woman...
Fujisaki-san,
is it okay if I ask a question?
What is it?
Why is it that if it weren't
today, you wouldn't like it?
To me, everything seems rushed.
Faster, the quicker I can love you...
Kubota, I love you very much.
Oh! I'm sorry!
Could you wait a minute...?
Kazuya!
What's up?
What are you doing here,
at this time of night?
Oh, you're busy.  It seems
I came at a bad time...
Don't look at me with those eyes.
I just came to pick up some things I left.
Stuff you left?
Fujisaki-san...
I'm sorry, Kubota-kun.
Can you sit over there and wait?
Fujisaki-san, did you live together?
Well, now we're even.
It looks like I'm
not the only bad one.
Us living together was wrong.
I didn't know you were
such a possessive woman.
You over there, I'm gonna
give you a good piece of advice.
Masana may have a pretty face,
but she likes to do this.
If you're not careful...
Let go. You and
I have nothing to fight over.
Why you!
Kubota-kun please, stop! Stop!
Kubota-kun, I...
That was Kawahara, wasn't it?
Obviously, he's a horrible guy. All the
things those girls said at the disco are true.
No, they're not!
He's just a big showoff.
I know... I know that he really is
a pure person.
That's true.
I'm sorry. I can't be with a
person whom looks at others too.
Fujisaki-san, please say something.
Otherwise, all of this will be...
I'm sorry.
Yo!
Kazushi, don't be disappointed!
Next time, you'll find a
better girl than Fujisaki.
This cake isn't very sweet...
Kazushi, even though he seems great,
did you know he's still a virgin?
Eh?!?
Why you...!
Hey! That's dangerous!
Stop that! Watch it!
We're safe! We're...okay!