Excuse me. This is Nippon Transport.
I've brought a delivery.
Yes, thank you. We'll let you in.
Megumi, take care of it, okay?
Sure.
I wonder what it is.
I hope it's something tasty.
Thank you as always.
Here you go.
What's inside?
Oh? A tape?
Here are your orders. This investigation concerns the recent surge in kidnappings of beautiful young women.
According to intel, there are rumors that the Taikun Country Embassy is somehow involved.
Proceed with extreme caution.
Well, I doubt you girls would let yourselves get kidnapped, but still, be careful.
What's with that attitude?
What does he mean we wouldn't get kidnapped?
That's Chief Haji for you.
Alright, time to get to work.
The Taikun Embassy
is that gloomy building, right?
Yeah, it totally gives off a creepy vibe.
First, you two go scout the area.
If you find anything, contact me immediately.
I'll check elsewhere in the meantime.
Let's go, Miki.
Roger that, Megumi.
FEMALE SPY TORTURE
THE ENEMY BASE IS A WOMEN'S BODY TORTURE FACILITY
What kind of place is an embassy anyway?
Beats me, I don't really know either.
Probably where important foreign people stay.
Would people like that really kidnap girls?
But important people usually do wild stuff,
and they're fine with deceiving others.
Yeah, it's depressing.
Ah, that's probably it.
It really does look secretive.
Megumi, what's the plan?
We'll wait until it gets dark.
Then we'll sneak in.
It worked!
This place is super suspicious.
There are lookouts.
We can't go straight from here.
The straightest path
isn't always the shortest.
Keep watch around the perimeter.
Got it.
Impressive, Megumi!
The rumors were true.
So they really were the ones behind it?
This is weird.
I wonder if something happened.
Hello? Headquarters?
This is Saiko.
Put me through to the Chief.
It's me. What is it?
Megumi and Miki went to the Taikun Embassy
and we haven't heard from them since.
Understood. I'll head over right away too.
You should get to the embassy as fast as possible.
Roger.
I see.
Now I get why people say
there are alligators living in the sewers.
It should be around here.
Jackpot.
Oopsie-daisy. Alright,
now where could they be held?
Well then, shall we get started?
I wonder what kind of reactions we'll get.
Looking forward to it, ladies.
Stop!
It tickles!
Well? Tickles, doesn't it?
Stop!
It tickles so much!
See? It tickles, right?
Stop... it tickles!
Stop... Stop!
Stop...
It's gonna feel even better now.
S-Stop...
Please...
No... make it stop... please!
No... I can't...
No more...
No...
Please... mercy!
Now it's this young lady's turn.
We'll take good care of you.
I wonder how long you can endure.
Hey... what's this?
S-Stop it!
Hey, what are you doing?!
N-No...
Hey...
It tickles!
Stop it...
N-No...
Ah! No! Not there!
Hey, I can't...
How's that? Does it tickle?
P-Please, make it stop...
Hey...
No...
Make her suffer more.
If you don't like this,
then tell us why you sneaked in here.
P-Please, make it stop...
I don't know anything.
I can't say anything...
P-Please, stop...
Have mercy, please!
P-Please...
I can't... can't take it!
Please, just stop right there, okay?
No...
We're only getting started.
Make her suffer more.
No... N-No, stop already...
No...
No more... please!
Please stop this! I can't take it!
No... more...
Forgive me... please!
Ah... no! Make it stop!
No...
So, ready to confess yet?
No! Absolutely not! Never!
Ah, please, make it stop... no more!
Forgive me...
No... I can't... anymore...
It hurts...
Please have mercy...
Please... make it stop!
I beg you...
Stop...
It hurts... please!
Really... I really don't know anything!
Hey, please...
I'm gonna die! You've gotta stop...
Ready to talk a little yet?
I swear... I don't know anything!
Confess quickly.
It's for your own good.
Please, I'm really gonna die...
I'm... at my limit...
It hurts!
Please, forgive me...
C'mon, please...
Not yet. We've still got a long way to go.
Well? Does it feel good?
P-Please... I'm...
P-Please, I c-can't...
Please, no more...
Please...
Help me, somebody...
Not yet. We're still just getting started.
N-No...
I can't breathe...
No more...
No! No...
Please... no more!
Hey, missy, the sooner you confess, the better.
N-No!
No more... no...
Make it stop!
Please...
Missy, we won't stop until you confess.
It's the truth... I swear!
I beg you, make it stop!
No...
If you don't confess, we can't stop.
Please! Please, I can't...
I beg you!
I can't take it anymore!
I can't breathe!
I can't take it anymore! Please, spare me!
Please! Please...
So? Ready to confess yet?
Ah, I'm losing it...
I'm going insane! No!
Please, make it stop!
Please... please...
We can't stop unless you confess.
I'll never talk! Absolutely never!
What a stubborn young lady.
I beg you! Make it stop!
I-I can't take it anymore!
We've only just begun. It'll only get worse.
Please... no...
The next step: the vibrator is going to set
your bodies on fire from the inside out.
How's that? Feels good, doesn't it?
Look, you're getting wet.
Feels nice, doesn't it?
Make it stop...
Alright. Now it's your turn.
No...
I can't believe this... so cruel!
Megumi!
Get a hold of yourself, Megumi!
I can't take it anymore...
I've had enough... no more!
What are you saying?
You have to stay strong!
Megumi and Miki, get out of here first
and call for backup at headquarters.
You two escape quickly too.
What about you, sis?
I'll stay and investigate a little more.
Understood.
Then I'm heading out. Be careful.
Don't worry about me.
Have you come to, young lady?
We've had the pleasure
of seeing your magnificent body.
We are all truly honored
to witness such a spectacle.
From here on, we'll help you enjoy yourself thoroughly. Are you prepared?
Of course, we intend to have
plenty of fun ourselves as well.
But before the fun begins,
could you answer one question?
We already know you're a spy, but your client's identity is still unknown.
We'd like you to tell us that.
There's no way I'd tell you something like that.
Now get these chains off me.
Only after you answer my question.
So, won't you tell me who your client is?
This little game of ours would cause problems
if it became public, you see.
Kidnapping girls is just a game to you?
What did you say?
Obviously! Kidnapping plus sexual assault —
this is a textbook crime.
Say whatever you want.
We're all enjoying this with mutual consent.
And of course, we'll be having you
join in the fun too.
You idiot! Moron!
If you do this, you'll regret it like hell later.
Hm, quite a feisty young lady.
Then please enjoy yourself
to the point of death.
Let's have some fun.
Tickle torture start!
Yessir.
No! No...
No! It tickles...
How's that? Does it tickle?
No...
No! No! No! No! No!
No... stop!
No...
It tickles...
N-No...
No...
Make it stop...
No more...
No!
Please...
No more! No! No! No!
No... stop...
I'm in pain... stop!
Ah! No...
Oh, please...
I can't breathe...
Come on now, young lady.
I think it'd be better for you
to start talking soon. What do you say?
Please... Stop! I can't take it anymore...
Please, no more... No! It hurts!
Please, make it stop...
No! No...
It hurts...
No more! No! Please...
No!
I can't breathe...
It hurts...
No... No! No! Please!
No!
Stop... make it stop!
Then confess quickly.
No... no more!
No!
N-No!
Please... have mercy!
No... I can't take it!
It hurts...
No more! No! No! It hurts...
No!
No...
It tickles!
No! Make it stop...
No! No...
No!
No! Stop! Please!
I... can't breathe...
No more...
No... No!
It hurts...
Make it stop...
Next up is the vibrator attack.
How does that vibrator feel?
Well now, how about spitting it out already?
No...
Make it stop...
I can't take it...
Who's your boss?
Confess, you wicked woman!
I don't know.
That's it. Hands up!
I'm placing all three of you under arrest
for kidnapping and rape.
Big sis, are you okay? Hang in there!
Saiko, I was so worried.
I started making arrangements
right after I got your call,
but everyone was busy
so it didn't go as smoothly as I'd hoped.
Sorry about that.
Well, since everyone made it out safely,
let's just say all's well that ends well...
Ah, Chief.
This is so embarrassing.
You saw me in such a humiliating state, Chief.
But I didn't tell them a single word about you.
I held out through the tickling
and the vibrator torture.
I acknowledge that. But you got quite wet,
didn't you? That was quite the vibrator.
The more I look, the more impressive it is.
I almost want to try it myself.
Hey sis, what's wrong?
Yeah, don't get so down about it.
The Chief saw all my most private parts!
You girls got lucky.
What do you mean "we got lucky"?
We got our share of it, alright.
Well, whatever.
Raw provider
Encoding
Translation
Editing
Proxyman
Anonymous
Perevodildo
imatu