Between a man and a woman,
the curtain of the pink sways.
Between 12 o'clock and midnight,
Come on, let's open the curtain of the pink.
Come on, let's open it, take off the veil.
A woman living inside a man,
a man living inside a woman,
no matter which one falls in love,
it's the same in swaying pink.
Even if a woman falls in love with a man,
even if a man loves a woman,
the swaying pink just keeps on swaying.
Curtain of the Pink
C-Coming!
I'll get the door!
Noriko?
What have you been doing
loafing about since midday?
Ah...
Well, the store is closed today.
Oh?
I see.
It's still as quiet as I remember it.
Brother, can I...
live here again?
Huh?
S-Sure.
I don't mind.
After all, it was you
who originally rented this room.
Really? That's a relief!
That's exactly why I love you so much!
But what about your marriage plans?
Huh?
So what became of it?
Cancelled!
Cancelled?
Yep.
"I have this much in savings
and I want two kids..." What a petty guy!
Isn't he just trying to be serious?
Not adventurous at all...
I'm only twenty, you know!
I'm at the height of my youth.
You've got nothing to eat!
Yeah, I'll go buy something now.
I guess you still can't forget that Mitamura, huh?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Hey, grab some snacks along the way, won't you?
Sure.
Thanks a bunch!
Yes?
This is Mitamura.
Noriko?
I'm back.
But I couldn't bring myself...
to forget you.
I still love you.
Love?
That's not true.
Huh?
What you really love is my manhood.
No, really...
I love you.
It's a delusion.
You're only after my body.
Yes...
B-But...
You love my manhood. You just said it.
I...
I want to be with you...
I brought you snacks!
What, you're back already?
Wh-What's with those looks?
But I just took a shower.
What if someone else had come?
I knew it could only be you.
Well, even if it's me,
I am a man too, you know.
Really? You feel that way about me?
Idiot. Who'd ever fall for his sister's huge butt?
Oh, geez.
Is it really that huge?
My sister is not at all wary of me.
Is it huge?
That's why she sees no problem
getting naked with me around.
My sister is 20 years old and I am 24,
so I see a problem with that.
But to Noriko, that notion seems nonexistent.
Delicious!
What are you looking at?
N-Nothing...
"Even though she's my little sister,
she's become quite an exquisite a woman..."
Is that it?
Stop fooling around.
More importantly,
about what we discussed earlier...
Upsy-daisy...
What's it?
Noriko...
Wh-What, are you going out now?
Yes, for a bit.
I haven't eaten out in a while.
Noriko, are you really...
Ah... By the way, some person...
Sudo-kun called you earlier. A friend?
Sudo?
I think he wanted your advice on something...
Noriko!
Master, please...
Show it to me.
Okay...
Spread it with your fingers and let me see.
Please...
take my...
Noriko...
What do you want me to do?
Put it in words.
I want your...
big thing...
inside me.
Do you get it now?
Women only want me for my manhood,
nothing besides that.
Did I walk in on something? Huh?
Ah, give me... more!
Here I come, Naoko.
Sup!
Hey. I've just come.
Welcome, Okuyama-kun.
Oh? So you're living alone
with your younger sister now?
Uh? Yeah...
I was startled when she picked up the phone...
Oops, would you look at the time!
I gotta run.
Then, I'll be off too...
No, you can stay!
I'll be back soon.
You two drink together or something.
And maybe have something stronger too.
Bye!
All according to plan.
Okuyama-kun, you're a virgin, right?
Huh? Well, sort of...
I know exactly why he left now.
Huh?
He gave you the green light, didn't he?
No need to be shy, then.
It's up to you to make her forget that guy.
Wait, not there!
Brother...
Noriko...
I'll invent some pretext and go out,
so you go ahead and do it, Okuyama.
Don't kiss that person if you don't love them.
Noriko...
Noriko? So you're back?
Have you been drinking?
Did you drink yourself into a stupor?
You'll catch a cold!
You've become a fine lady indeed...
Noriko, if only you weren't my sister...
If you weren't my sister...
Noriko...
Hello? Could I talk to Master?
My hips are still trembling.
Look, you're still so hard—
why won't you come?
Autumn Wind Melody
TV Series
Yes. I almost never ejaculate
no matter who I sleep with.
Autumn Wind Melody
TV Series
That's wrong! Don't you love anyone?
Autumn Wind Melody
TV Series
How many times
did you sleep with your fiance?
Two times, but I didn't enjoy it even once.
I realized the one I truly love is you.
Say it more precisely.
Yes, I couldn't forget your thing.
Between a man and a woman,
I love your thing.
the curtain of the pink sways.
Between 12 o'clock and midnight,
Please, let me use it once more.
the curtain of the pink sways.
It's okay, I can help myself.
Come on, let's open the curtain of the pink.
Come on, let's open it, take off the veil.
A woman living inside a man,
a man living inside a woman,
no matter which one falls in love,
it's the same in swaying pink.
Even if a woman falls in love with a man,
even if a man loves a woman,
the swaying pink just keeps on swaying.
It's me.
Sudo isn't here anymore.
He left back then, the very next day.
And I work at a cabaret now.
I'm forced to have sex anyway,
but at least I'm getting paid for it.
Didn't you come here to die with me?
N-Not at all...
It's all right.
You'll owe me 20,000 yen, though.
From today on, it's for business.
We don't have to kiss.
Naoko...
Naoko!
No! No, stop it, brother! No!
N-No!
No! No!
N-No... No, no! Stop! Stop, please! No!
Shut up! I've not been with a woman
for two and a half years.
I was going crazy just dreaming about you!
No...
N-No... No!
Stop...
N-No...
Naoko... It was me who made you a woman!
And now I'm going to remind you
of that once more...
No...
So they're brother and sister?
Could it be...
What's wrong, Naoko? It's me, your big brother!
Do you remember now?
W-We can't...
Brother!
Oh, I see. You've always liked it
from behind, haven't you?
There we go.
Here I come, Naoko...
B-Brother, it hurts...
Noriko?
I'm jealous.
Are you sleeping with your brother too?
Of course not!
Doing it with Satoru...
You can't be serious!
So you're saying you don't view him as a man?
When I'm with you...
I can't think of any other man...
Ah! Ah, not there...
So this is your G-spot.
No...
Not with your hands!
Please!
You might not be able
to walk home tonight
Master...
It's Mitamura, isn't it?!
So you're still seeing him?
You enjoy it now while you're
still young, however...
it'll bring you tears one day.
I know.
That man has a wife and a child, think about that.
I do think about that...
Do you remember how sad our mother was
when she found out dad had another woman?
B-But I love him!
Master!
No!
Noriko...
My hips are trembling.
Ah... That was refreshing.
Noriko...
Is it because you adore me?
I love you, you know...
Aye-aye, I know. So tonight,
your lovely sister will rock you to sleep.
Hush-a-bye, Hush-a-bye.
My good baby, Sleep.
When I get a boner for my sister,
we're no longer siblings.
We're just a man and a woman.
So it's only natural something like this happens.
Once I finish drinking this wine,
once this waltz is over,
Video
Dong Buttle
Ah, the final scene...
Until my body cools down,
until my heart freezes,
True Noobow Gamer
[nothing]
Ah, ah, don't go.
Quality check
not Muzussawa
not Paul Geromini
I gave you my youth,
Trans
lation
Perevodildo
and you gave me my adulthood.
That said, thank you; that said, I'm a little sad.
Lyrics booklet
not Eternal_Blizzard
I'll be acting in the final scene.
Here are my final lines...
Subtitles height check
not unowen
not anonymous
Muzu's
Nudes
'2025
Perevodildo
Typesetting