Calpis Anime Theater
Andersen Stories
The ugly duckling kid,
hates the naked king!
The tin soldier,
serves the Snow Queen!
Oh my, Andersen!
Well now, Andersen!
Mister Andersen!
You never wrote a story like this one!
This tale's a little
crazy! (Heh-heh-heh)
The world's a little crazy too!
(Ha-ha-ha)
Let's rebuild the blocks of our dreams!
Everybody, everybody, gather around! (Yay!)
Good evening, everyone, this is Canty!
Hey, everyone, do you know what these cards are?
That's right, they're entry cards
for that magic academy!
Look, I've already collected this many!
At this rate, I'll be just one short
of all 101 magic cards!
Achoo!
Never mind that,
can't you do something about this cold?
So this time...
we're heading off to a nice warm southern land for a little trip!
Let's go!
To an island far away, with no name...
Hey, are we really allowed
to just play around like this?
Of course! We've got to enjoy our vacation!
To an island far away, with no...
Come one, come all,
gather 'round, gather 'round!
Hey, mister, what kind of story
will you tell us today?
Today's story is a bit sad,
can you all keep from crying?
Sure we can!
I don't even cry when Mama scolds me!
Me too!
Oh really? I see, you're all brave kids.
Now then, do you know what is that over there?
Sure, that's a statue of Psyche!
Yes, it's the statue of Psyche,
the spirit of a butterfly.
But do you know what that other statue is?
What's that one?
Looks kinda dirty.
It's always been there,
but I never looked at it closely.
Hm, I see, I see.
Well, the sad story I'm about to tell you
is about Psyche, the spirit of the butterflies,
and the sculptor Kilt, who made
that statue of the girl riding a deer.
Psyche and...
Kilt?
Episode 49
Psyche
Yes. Long, long ago,
in a far corner of this southern land, they were two lonely lovers who bloomed briefly and sadly.
Dolls for sale!
Pretty dolls for sale!
Wood-carved dolls!
Come get your dolls!
Dolls for sale!
Kilt was an orphan, all alone.
Carrying wooden dolls on his back,
he walked the streets every day selling his carvings.
When the red sun sank over the hills of Greece,
Kilt trudged alone over the darkening hilltops,
and by the time he reached the quiet forest,
the sea breeze brushed his cheeks
and stars twinkled in the sky.
At last he came home to the little house
he and his late parents had built together.
Phew…
Dad, I'm home.
Mom, I'm home.
Guess what, I sold five dolls today!
That's never happened before.
Look, this is a doll I carved!
They're nowhere near as good
as the many sculptures Dad left behind,
but I'm getting better, right?
What do you think?
Anyway, I'll keep at it.
Someday, I'll become a fine sculptor,
just like you, Dad!
Wood-carved dolls!
Who wants one?
Even more beautiful than the petals of a flower...
Kilt's singing voice would charm
the hearts of all who heard it.
The forest animals adored his song,
and it reached even the gods of Greece—
Poseidon, god of the sea,
Zephyrus, god of the wind,
Atlas, who holds up the heavens,
and Zeus, king of the gods,
who reigns on Olympus—
all bowed their heads
and closed their eyes to listen.
On such nights, the wind grew still, the sea calm,
and the land of Greece fell into a deep, peaceful night.
Wood-carved dolls for sale! Who wants one?
But on one such night, drawn by his song,
someone appeared out of nowhere.
She sat upon a rock where the voice carried best, and listened, entranced, the whole night through.
Then, when dawn came, the Sun god Apollo whipped his flying horses high across the eastern sky,
announcing to city, forest, and every living thing
in Greece that morning had come.
And so Kilt too knew it was time
to head to town and sell his dolls again.
As always, he crossed the stream,
and as always, his forest friends saw him off.
By the time he reached the edge of the woods,
the early risers were blinking sleep from their eyes,
and Kilt started down the road toward town.
Dolls for sale…
Good morning.
H-Hey.
D-Do you need something?
No, not really.
Th-Then why are you following me?
No reason.
Hey, do you want something or not?
Nope. Not really.
Who… Who are you anyway?
My name's Psyche.
Nice to meet you.
Oh?
Psyche? A-And I'm Kilt.
Nice to meetcha!
By the way, P-Psyche—
that's a really pretty name!
Oh? But Kilt's a cool name too.
Y-Yeah?
And so the two of them,
without even knowing how, became fast friends.
For Kilt, who had always been alone,
those days felt like a dream.
And sweet, lovely Psyche was loved
by all the forest creatures too.
Their happy days passed by,
and soon, in their young hearts,
a gentle spark of love began to glow.
Then one day, as the Sun set beautifully
over the shore, Kilt said...
Hey, Psyche.
What is it, Kilt?
I...
I…
I, uh…
I love Psyche!
I love her more than anyone in the world!
And that was Kilt's awkward,
but bold confession of love.
But Psyche only smiled softly
and let silent tears fall.
Kilt thought she looked more beautiful than ever,
but he didn't understand what those tears truly meant.
The reason for Psyche's tears—
he would be forced to learn it
the next night, when he came home from town.
I'm back, Psyche.
Hey, what's this?
You're sitting in the dark again?
Huh?
Hey, Psyche? Where are you hiding?
Psyche?
Psyche!
Psyche? Psyche's gone.
She's gone!
Psyche!
Where are you?!
Hey! Psyche!
Psyche!
Psyche! Why did you leave?
Where did you go?
If you got lost in the woods,
don't be shy, just call out for help!
No matter how far or how dangerous it is,
I'll come save you, I promise.
Or… if you've stopped liking me...
No, that can't be, never!
Maybe I did something wrong
and made you upset without knowing it?
Yes, that must be it—
you just stormed off in a huff.
If that's true, then I'll apologize.
I'll apologize from the bottom of my heart.
So please, Psyche…
Psyche…
Ever since Psyche vanished from Kilt's life,
the rain never once showed signs of stopping.
A week, two weeks, then three weeks went by.
When the rain finally quieted down,
Kilt was too worn out to even
keep grieving Psyche's disappearance.
And so, for Kilt, the happy days with Psyche
became but a beautiful memory.
Run! Run!
Before long, Kilt was cheerful again,
laughing and playing with his forest friends as before.
But still…
whenever he was alone,
he often sat blankly,
like his soul had slipped away.
Wooden dolls for sale! Dolls for sale!
It must have been the blood
of his sculptor father
that made Kilt decide to carve Psyche's image from memory.
It was the first truly joyful work of his life.
A plain block of marble slowly took shape
under his hands into something beautiful.
He worked until exhaustion overtook him
and fell into a deep sleep,
his face peaceful, as if reliving
the happy days with Psyche.
He lifted his hammer again,
weary but driven, day and night.
And as the statue of Psyche
neared completion...
a strange feeling grew in Kilt's heart.
It felt as though those joyful days
had returned before his eyes.
He began to love the statue
of Psyche on the deer's back,
believing more and more
that it was Psyche herself.
O Zeus, king of the gods, I have returned.
You've done well through these long years.
You've grown into a fine being.
Thank you, my lord.
Go now, return to him at once.
Yes. I must hurry, I want to apologize
for leaving Kilt without a word.
Yes. He'll be overjoyed
to see you in such beauty. Go forth.
Yes.
Kilt!
Kilt...
I missed you, Kilt.
It's me, Psyche.
I'm so sorry for leaving you without a word.
I never meant to hurt or sadden you.
I am the spirit of a butterfly.
And to truly become one,
I had to receive the love of a human boy—
and then endure the sorrow
of parting from the one I loved.
It is painful for us too,
but such is our law.
When I left you, it broke my heart,
but deep in the forest of a hidden swamp,
I wrapped myself in white silk
and became a cocoon.
As I waited, I thought, "If I endure this darkness,
I'll become more beautiful and see Kilt again."
It was a long, dark time, but I endured it,
and today I was reborn as a full butterfly spirit.
And now…
I, Psyche, have come back to your side.
What are you talking about?
I don't know who you are,
but my Psyche came back to me long ago.
Right, Psyche?
Wh-What are you saying, Kilt?
That's only…
Psyche, isn't it strange?
Look, that woman actually thinks she's Psyche!
And she's a grown-up,
nothing like you.
Kilt! But isn't that merely a sculpture?
Don't you see? I've come back,
more beautiful than ever!
It's me...
I'm Psyche!
Please, Kilt…
Come on, Psyche,
let's ride through the night sky again!
Let's go! Run! Run!
Run!
Kilt!
It's this sculpture...
If this sculpture is gone,
Kilt...
Kilt will…
come back to me!
Ah! What are you doing!
I won't let you harm Psyche!
Psyche...
Kilt was dead.
Because he couldn't recognize Psyche,
the grown, reborn Psyche.
Holding his lifeless body close,
Psyche walked on and on along the shore.
And as the Sun sank into the sea,
she still held him tight,
then disappeared beneath the waves
to follow after him.
Though moved by her sorrow,
the gods only watched in silence.
And so ends my tale.
Poor Psyche…
Hey, old man, I'll clean the bird droppings
off the statue every morning!
Me too!
And me!
Thank you, children.
On behalf of Kilt and Psyche, I thank you.
Hey, old man, who are you, exactly?
I'm just a wandering poet.
I only wish that happy stories and sad ones alike
find a quiet place in your kind hearts.
I only wish they find a quiet place
in your kind hearts.
Come on, everyone, let's go home.
Goodbye!
Bye!
Well, Zukko, we should be heading back too.
Ugh, next week it's back to the cold again.
That's our job, remember?
See ya!
Gerda and Kai are two children
who live together in the northern lands.
One snowy day, Kai refuses to believe the old tale
about a demon told by Gerda's grandmother.
For that, the demon's icy mirror shatters,
and a shard pierces Kai's heart.
Kai becomes cold and cruel, and one day, in a blizzard, the Snow Queen takes him away to her icy realm.
She plans to make Kai her successor,
the next king of the Land of Ice.
Next week on Andersen Stories:
The Snow Queen, Part 1—
The Demon's Mirror.
Don't miss it, everyone.
See ya!
Ah, Zukko, Zukko, Zukko, Zukko, Zukko, Z!
Ah, Zukko's got his Z! (What's with that?)
The Z in Zukko means skip school (Zuruyasumi)!
The Z for sly (Zurugashikoi)!
The Z for slovenly (Zunberabou)!
The Z for silly face (Zuibun Mazui Kao))!
So what?
I'm still a boy!
(Ha! He slipped! Ha! Zuu-zuu, he slipped!)
The Z in Zukko means shameless (Zuuzuushii)!
The Z means lazy brains!
The Z for slacker (Zubari namakemono)!
The Z for clumsy fool (Zubora)!
So what? I'm still a boy!
(Ha! He slipped! Ha! Zuu-zuu, he slipped!)
Ah, Zukko's got his Z!
Ah, Zukko's Z!
Encoding & QC
Translation & TS
Quality check
wowmd
Perevodildo
Muzussawa