December 31, 2009. It's snowing.
I'm Okamoto Kentaro, and I was out hunting deep in the mountains of Okayama Prefecture.
About forty meters, I'd say.
I'd really like it to turn this way a bit more...
The rabbit I shot kicked up its hind legs once,
then stopped moving.
I, Okamoto Kentaro, was born in a seriously rural village in Okayama Prefecture.
It was seven kilometers one way
just to get to a friend's house.
The one who spent the most time playing with me
was an old fisherman who lived nearby.
He taught me about plants and animals,
how to make straw rope, how to catch fish—
all kinds of things.
Growing up watching him, I just assumed that becoming an adult naturally meant becoming a fisherman.
But the old man died soon after I entered junior high.
As a keepsake, I was given the skull
of a boar he had taken down.
Time passed, and in January 2009, I was in Tokyo.
January 1, 2009
Despite being a country bumpkin,
I was on a date at a bar in Ikebukuro.
So yeah, someday I wanna live back home
and do hunting and stuff.
What? That's awful!
You kill animals?
A-Awful?
Look, you eat meat all the time though.
Cows and pigs are different.
You're quibbling over nothing again.
I didn't think you were this barbaric.
Wh-What was that?
Fine then. I'll live my life as a country hunter.
Hmph. Goodbye, Mr. Mountain Bandit.
Bandit's Diary
Time moves forward a bit, to November 18, 2009.
Today I'm out with two other guys
from my hunting club.
Masamune
Like always, we won't catch anything today.
Aki-kun, what's up with Masamune?
Aki
Ah, Masamune came up empty again yesterday.
Hey, quiet.
Over at the eastern inlet, three mallards.
They're way too far.
Shh.
One, two, three...
From the opposite bank,
that's over eighty meters, right?
And so, since they were out of range from here,
we decided to come up with a plan.
The three mallards were more than eighty meters away.
So it was decided that I'd move while hiding on the slope side,
cut through the woods, and flush the ducks out.
Then the two guys with shotguns
would ambush them from the field below.
Ducks have a habit
of fleeing in a wide
range of directions.
All right, I'm counting on you guys.
I split off from them and headed through the woods alone.
So I don't get spotted by the ducks,
I switched to crawling partway through.
There they are.
About forty or fifty meters ahead,
they were hiding among the reeds.
If Masamune were here, I might've let him take the shot and finally score some ducks, but this is a rare chance.
Now then, about this gun of mine,
let me tell you how I got it.
Since it's a real firearm, requiring a license,
you can't just buy one easily.
May 21, 2009
Prefectural Driver's Licensing Center
Morning safety lecture, written exam in the afternoon, and same-day results.
This is where I met Aki and Masamune.
The only one who flunked
Yes!
May 22, 2009
So where do you even buy a gun?
Next step was finding a shop.
Gun and Ammunition Store
Welcome.
Turns out there was one surprisingly close.
A shotgun?
Or an air rifle?
Air rifle? You can go hunting with an air rifle, right?
Yeah, of course. Though it could easily
blow off a finger, so be careful.
Hit someone in the head and they'd probably die.
I'll take this one!
There were cheaper guns, but the name sounded cool, so I chose the Ace Hunter.
At the gun shop, I filled out the paperwork
saying I intended to buy it.
Then took a family registry copy, residence certificate,
and doctor's note to the police.
May 25, 2009
These clothes probably wouldn't make
a great impression on the police!
Life Safety Division
So I greeted them with the biggest smile I could manage.
Hello! I'm here to apply for a firearm permit!
Life Safety Division
We'll issue the permit after the review.
They handled it all pretty matter-of-factly.
July 3, 2009
Huh? The police?
Just when I'd almost forgotten I was being reviewed,
I got a call saying my gun permit was approved.
July 6, 2009
And back at the police station...
I was issued my permit, free of charge!
Then, with permit in hand,
I went to pick up the gun.
Gun and Ammunition Store
Welcome!
The case is second-hand,
so I'll throw it in as a service.
Thank you very much.
And just like that, finally,
an air rifle came to my house!
I did it, Gramps!
My own gun!
Sharp made in Chiba, Ace Hunter.
Multi-pump, single-shot air rifle.
Overall length: 98.2 centimeters.
Weight with scope: 3.4 kilograms.
50,000 yen (used)
Caliber 5 millimeters—
what you'd call a standard air rifle.
Let me also introduce our hunting club here.
Good morning.
Morning.
Natsume
This is Natsume-san, the group leader.
Before the hunt, we chat
and exchange info over canned coffee.
Apparently wild boar have been showing up
in my wife's parents' fields.
Sasaki
That area's kind of inconvenient for setting traps.
Maehara
In our group, only Sasaki has a trap license.
Oh, I have a trap license.
Type 1 Gun Hunting License
Type 2 Gun Hunting License
Trapping License
Net Hunting License
Right, I'd gotten one along with my hunting license.
In this manner, the hunting club brings together different generations, where younger members learn from veterans
*Hunting without a hunting license is a violation of the Wildlife Protection Act
as well as the Swords and Firearms Control Law!
and take on hunting requests—it's a valuable place to connect.
The rookie young hunters' strategy
Now, back to duck hunting with rookie young hunters.
Ducks on the water are moving targets,
which air rifles aren't great for.
At this distance, the pellet should hit in about 0.1 to 0.2 seconds.
Plus the pellet drops a bit, so...
Basically, you push the bullet with air.
I missed?
Whoa...
Here they come!
Huh? It's still in the same spot.
It's trying to dive, but it can't.
I must've hit its wing.
I fired a finishing shot.
It feels like a total fluke, but I got my first duck.
Yes!
But now the question was—
how do I retrieve it?
By the way, Masamune had dropped
a huge male mallard that day.
I got one!
Me too!
Guess there's no other choice.
I've gotta go in the water.
Huh?
Seriously?
In this cold, that's basically suicide by drowning.
If you kill an animal,
I believe you have a responsibility to retrieve it.
The air temperature is three degrees Celsius.
My legs feel like they're being stabbed with needles.
I lose all feeling in my feet almost instantly,
but I absolutely want that duck, so I push through it.
It's dead.
I eat meat all the time,
with the animals dying somewhere out of sight,
but doing it with your own hands really is complicated.
Man… I finally got one!
Good for you, Masamune.
More importantly, let's hurry up and go.
At the same time, the joy is also huge.
It felt the same as the first time I caught a fish as a kid.
All right. It's freezing,
but let's head home and start plucking.
To keep the feathers from flying everywhere,
I plucked it inside a plastic bag.
It probably came out to about one pillow's worth.
Some of the feathers had blue sections
and were really pretty.
I might be able to use them to make fishing flies or something.
Today's dinner table
I burned the hair off, cut off the neck and legs,
and removed the guts.
The duck's gizzard is about the size of a plum.
The pellet had wrecked both wings.
Guess the Ace Hunter packs more punch than I thought.
So, how should I cook it?
Duck makes great soup stock,
so soba was an option…
Ah!
But this shape...
screams roast chicken!
I've never made it before,
but this ingredient makes me want to try.
First, salt and pepper for the base seasoning.
Don't forget the inside, through the rear opening
where the organs came out.
Then, through the same opening: rosemary, bay leaves,
chunks of white leek, and bits of ginger.
I'll also toss in the broccoli stem
I was planning to throw away.
It's all just whatever I had at home,
but will it turn out good?
Brush the outside with olive oil and bake for 90 minutes.
Done!
Photograph of a duck actually cooked by Okamoto-sensei.
It looks amazing.
I wish I had some wine,
but I'll celebrate with a beer for now.
All right, let's dig in.
Thanks for the meal.
Most of the duck meat you see at the supermarket
is actually farmed duck.
It's tougher than chicken.
Wild duck doesn't have nearly as much fat,
and it's not very tender either.
You can't really eat this in a refined way.
This is good.
Unlike farmed chicken, the skin and fat aren't heavy,
and you really get to enjoy the bold flavor of the red meat.
For New Year's soba this year,
I'm going with duck nanban.
DUCK NANBAN!
Bandit's Diary
A hunter even more skilled than in the films.
In November 2014, I accompanied an actual hunt
for the sake of this anime production.
Perfect bore sighting, flawless scope.
For months, he waited in silence.
Okamoto-sensei using his new air rifle
My partner, let's shake up the forests of the archipelago now!
This was the first pond we visited that day,
but there were no ducks to be seen.
The reaper sniper of the one-shot kill,
This pond is about a 15-minute drive from the first pond.
As expected, there are no ducks. I wonder where they went...
lock the prey in the center of your reticle.
The free-floated barrel, aimed straight ahead.
I pulled myself together and headed to the third pond of the day,
but still couldn't catch any ducks. There are days like that...
Bullet, now break through the sound barrier.
But if you miss like that,
We visited the store where Okamoto-san bought his Ace Hunter.
the prey takes flight without mercy.
This is the Ace Hunter that Okamoto actually used.
The hollow gunshot
passes straight through my body and heart.
Old man in heaven, today, for the first time,
I hunted and ate a duck.
Translation, typesetting by Perevodildo
Encoded by Leftover Thai Red Curry
Quality checked by Paul Geromini