Original work by Daisaku Ikeda
Rainbow Across the Pacific Ocean
It's beautiful this morning too!
The sea breeze is so pleasant.
Do this while taking a deep breath
and you'll feel the most refreshed!
You can really feel that
there's more land beyond the horizon.
You seem to like the sea a great deal.
Yes. I love it.
A rainbow bridge, huh?
Eh? What's that?
My dad used to say,
"To let people from various countries
travel freely across the Pacific Ocean,
it'd be nice if we could throw
a couple of light and rainbow bridges over it."
You know the name of the Pacific Ocean
means "an ocean of peace," right?
Good morning!
Morning!
Shuu Gyokuren.
Shuu Gyokuren
Though her mother is Japanese,
she was born in China.
Recently, her whole family
has come to Japan for the first time.
Therefore, her birthplace is China.
Which is our closest neighbor just across the sea,
and a fellow Asian country, equal to ours.
Her mother has been teaching her Japanese
for all her life, so don't worry about that.
She'll become talkative in no time,
once you make friends with her.
Doesn't it sound good? Let's all get along
and help Gyokuren feel at home.
Okay!
Shut up!
You need to be brave too, Gyokuren.
Now, cheer up and greet everyone.
My name is... S-Shuu Gyokuren.
Pleased to meet you.
My name
is K-Kenta!
Pfeashed to meeth you!
Oh? A girl from China?
I know! China is where the pandas come from.
Everybody knows that!
In that case, Gyokuren
must be having a hard time here.
If Mitsuko shows Gyokuren her affection,
I'm sure Gyokuren will also like Mitsuko.
Two hearts will always find a way
to relate to each other.
The Chinese are our closest neighbors,
so it'll be fine.
They way you put it is as though
China is literally a family next door.
That's right.
Our families, countries,
and everything else is the same.
And there's nothing more important
than for two neighbors to get along.
Either way, you should be kind to her.
Okay.
Good morning!
Ah!
Chinese!
Dirty hands Gyokuren
"I c-come from Ch-China..."
G-Gyokuren!
H-How could you!
Got a problem with it?
Huh! Mitsuko can't mind her own business!
Away, you cocky broad!
Hah! Becoming friends with me? In your dreams!
But I...
What's your problem?!
Ah! The teacher is here.
My dear Hoshun,
I came to Japan, my mom's birthplace.
I started going to a Japanese school.
Still, for some reason,
I just can't get along with others.
Hoshun, I can't find another friend like you.
The Japanese teachers are all very good people.
They say, if I have enough courage,
I can make lots of friends in Japan.
Still...
Still, what can I do to have more courage?
Hoshun, I don't know!
Gyokuren.
Gyokuren!
E-Excuse me!
"My Treasure"
Then, that's it for today.
By the way, the weather will be
really nice and warm for our next class meeting.
So let's meet on the green hill
under the lighthouse in the afternoon.
The theme would be "My Treasure."
Pick the one thing you value the most
and bring it along, so as to introduce it to everyone.
I'm looking forward to it.
Mitsuko's toys
What could it be?
W-Well...
Ah! Cute.
You opened your eyes!
Blonde hair and blue eyes.
Maybe you're an American doll?
Have you been here for long?
I bet you felt lonely!
But you'll be fine now.
Because I'll be your friend.
Let's get along well, shall we?
Ah! Oh no!
A beautiful doll with blue eyes
A celluloid born in America
When we arrived to the Japanese port,
I shed a plenty of bitter tears
I can't understand the words they're saying
What would I do if I get lost?
A kind Japanese girl saw me
We got along and went to play
We got along and went to play.
What a mysterious music box.
Nice to meet you, Mitsuko.
Oh!
I am a Doll Fairy, the guardian of dolls.
Doll Fairy?
Yes. Although I'm usually invisible to a human eye,
I let you see me for how kind you've been to Emily.
So this doll's name is Emily?
Yes. Your kind feelings
can be conveyed to Emily as well.
There, why won't Emily say something too?
Eh?
If you listen really carefully,
you could hear it too.
Becoming friends with someone always begins
with listening to them quietly and intently.
Thank you, Mitsuko.
Ah! This doll Emily just spoke to me!
I've been here all alone for a long, long time.
So I was unbelievably happy when you showed up.
A long time?
"Right. She's been here since before the time
your mom and dad were born.
Eh? Since that long ago?
When I came to Japan from America,
it was 1927. Second year of Showa.
That was over 60 years ago from now.
We fostered a hope that the children of America
and Japan would live in an eternal harmony,
bound together by the feeling of warm friendship.
Over 12,000 dolls were donated by Americans.
They sent them across the Pacific,
the ocean of peace.
We welcomed the blue-eyed dolls with open arms,
as the envoys of peace and friendship.
Distributed to elementary schools
and kindergartens all over Japan,
the dolls were highly treasured by the children.
I was one of those 12,000 dolls.
I see. So you were a doll of friendship?
Still, how did you end up in a place like this?
Sadly, Japan started a war
with my homeland of America.
War?
1941. 16th year of Showa, December.
The Pacific War began.
By then, Japan was already
waging a prolonged war against China.
From that day on, our fates took a drastic turn.
A thing more tragic is hardly imaginable.
The blue-eyed dolls were made
into scapegoats for all Americans.
They were torn apart, they were burned.
All the people I met in Japan
were kind and well-meaning.
And yet,
why would they go to war to take each other's lives?
That's... That's terrible!
And the dolls didn't do anything to deserve this.
Why didn't anyone stop them?
But Emily...
How come you were saved?
What is this place?
This is what the world looked like during the war.
Oh?
Emily.
Everyone, according to the principal's advice,
we're chastising Emily today.
Chastising Emily?
Why are you staring to the sides?
You're doing it too. Go now!
I'll have a go first!
Yes.
Emily!
I was truly happy when you found me.
Stop! Please stop!
Stop!
Traitor! Coward!
Please! Not Emily.
Don't hurt Emily, the doll!
Emily isn't guilty of anything!
I also had a bad feeling about doing this.
But thanks to you, I regained my courage.
Let's make sure to protect Emily until a day comes
when we get to live in peace again, okay?
This doll of friendship
between Japan and America.
Yes, teacher.
Aren't you glad, Emily?
Huh?
That music box again...
I wonder what happened to me.
You did well, Mitsuko.
Doll Fairy?
Yes, that moment, your courage chose
to live in a bright and wonderful future.
Eh?
People encounter all sorts of challenges daily,
sometimes getting lost as to how to handle them.
Just like there are two paths to choose from
when standing on a split.
You can only decide for yourself,
which one to follow.
Two paths?
One is the path of cowardice.
Path of cowardice?
And the other is the path of courage.
Path of courage?
The path of cowardice and the path of courage -
depending on which of these two paths you choose,
your future will also change accordingly.
Just now, you chose the path of courage.
That's why Emily is currently happy,
resting in your embrace.
But just now, the kid that looked like Kenta
yelled "coward" at me.
Then, do you suppose the path of courage
is to stab the doll with a bamboo spear?
No. Not at all.
But Kenta is pretty strong,
good with the horizontal bar and is always lively.
I don't think I've ever seen him sulking.
Do you really think so?
Then, how about this?
When his mother died and Kenta was left all alone with his father, he's been feeling very lonely.
Yet, because he didn't want anyone to find out,
he started putting on intimidating airs
and bullying others all the time.
But if you do that,
you can hardly ever make any friends.
Such is the future of those who choose
the path of cowardice.
It's a road that only leads up to a dead end.
So giving in to your own weak spirit is a no-go?
Precisely!
On the contrary, the path of courage
may be painful at first,
but the further you advance on it,
the wider and clearer the road becomes.
I should tell Kenta...
Right! I should tell Gyokuren too, that in order to make some true friends,
they'll have to take the path of courage.
Tell me, grandma.
War is truly scary thing, isn't it?
That's right, Mitsuko.
I wish everyone in the world would learn to be as honest as Emily's clear blue eyes,
to carry on through their lives
with the unfaltering spirit of being kind and appreciative towards your friends, like they did as children.
If everyone did that, we'd never have
to live through that senseless war, I believe.
Yes.
A spirit of being appreciative towards your friends.
Next time, I'll be sure to become
true friends with Gyokuren.
This concludes the story
of the blue-eyed doll Emily and the Doll Fairy.
Ha! A guardian of dolls, seriously?
Isn't it just some dream you had?
Then, next is Gyokuren.
Right, it's Gyokuren's turn.
What do you have in that bag?
Come on, show it to us now.
What's wrong, Gyokuren?
Cheer up, Gyokuren.
Ah, it's so irritating!
Mitsuko, let others have their turn now.
Leave that wimp alone!
Wimp?
That there, ain't she a wimp?
What now?
You got a problem with that?
Hey, please. Let us see your treasure, Gyokuren.
We would all like to become true friends with you.
True friends?
That's why we want to hear your story,
from start to end.
We're all excited to hear
some wonderful stories about China.
Emily, what should I do?
What could I do to get Gyokuren to open up?
It's something for Emily.
Okay.
Here.
What's there?
Cute!
A beautiful Chinese doll!
I wish I had a doll like that too!
So we got a Chinese and an American doll here?
That's getting pretty global!
Emily, nice to meet you.
This is Hoshun.
My Chinese fri... Fr...
Friend.
Right! My Chinese friend has the same name as her.
Also, Hoshun is very good at dancing!
Hoshun
Hoshun and I have always been friends
ever since we were little.
She's a bright and cheerful girl.
When it was time for me to leave for Japan,
she gave me this doll.
Hoshun said she didn't want me to forget her,
that's why the doll's name is also Hoshun.
That was a wonderful story, Gyokuren.
Let's get along, shall we, Hoshun?
Oh my!
I'm so glad for you, Hoshun.
Hoshun!
Watch out, Gyokuren!
It's dangerous over there.
Hoshun! Hoshun, wait!
Gyokuren!
It got stuck so high up...
Can we really get it back?
No chance. That was awfully unlucky.
Give up on it.
I can fix you up with an even better ribbon.
Mizue!
That ribbon is a proof of my friendship with Hoshun.
If I don't have that ribbon,
I don't have Hoshun!
It's a token of warm friendship
between Gyokuren and Hoshun.
That's quite a pickle...
Kenta.
Huh?
Go get the ribbon.
M-Me?
It's a ribbon of Gyokuren's precious friendship.
Please. I know you're the only one who can get it, Kenta.
O-Okay... H-Huh?
Fine, let's do it!
No way we're losing that ribbon!
We can't afford losing it!
Ouch!
Once more!
Damn you!
Tsk! I can't reach that branch!
Kenta, use my back to jump to it!
You there, don't just stand idly!
Help me push Kenta up from the sides!
Right... Okay.
Alright!
Jump in two steps, using both me and Yuzuru!
A-Are you sure?
Don't worry! Hurry up now!
Fine, let's do it!
There!
He did it!
Don't give up, Kenta!
Boss!
Please keep going!
That's it, that's it!
Now comes the most difficult part.
We believe in you, Boss!
Keep going!
You can do it!
Kenta! Thank you for trying, but please stop now!
This is enough!
Please get down, it's getting dangerous.
Geez, you're noisy!
I'm doing this for myself!
You got a problem with that?
Keep that to yourself!
Yes. That's right!
Currently, Kenta is not struggling
for the twig of camellia, nor for the ribbon.
Instead, Kenta is fighting
to take his own path of courage!
It's raining!
Everyone, I need your handkerchiefs!
Handkerchiefs?
Tie together all the handkerchiefs you have. Quick!
What would you do with our handkerchiefs?
No questions, just do it!
I get it!
Everyone, give me your handkerchiefs!
Faster! Next strong gust will totally blow it away!
Quick, quick!
Tie them good!
Yeah.
Faster! You can do it faster!
Could you please use this too?
Thank you, Mizue.
Almost there, Kenta!
Okay...
It's finished, Kenta!
Here, don't drop it!
There, let's do it!
Wow! So pretty.
Okay, I got it.
Here, Boss!
Looks like a line of flags!
When you look at this line of handkerchiefs flags,
it feels like the whole world is holding hands!
If I don't make it with the first try,
the ribbon will be blown away!
Now!
You did it, Kenta!
Well done, Boss!
Keep it up!
You can do it, Kenta!
That's the way. That's the way!
Hooray! He did it!
That's our Boss!
Easy as that!
Hoshun. My Hoshun!
Aren't you glad? All your friends in Japan
turned out to be such caring people.
I should've gotten along with them sooner.
Don't give us all that nonsense!
Better tie it good this time, you hear?
Okay, Kenta. And thank you once again!
Didn't I tell you I wasn't doing it for you?
But you brought Hoshun her ribbon back.
You're a very good person.
I'm not complaining!
What's so funny?
Then, if you don't mind, may I tell you a bit more?
Really?
I annoyed my mom by saying
I don't want to go to school this morning.
Ever since I came to Japan, I hated going to school,
because it was so painful day after day.
And today, I was scared that I'd be laughed at
for bringing along my precious Hoshun.
But then, mom reassured me.
She said I should be proud
of being born and raised in China.
And mom was right!
I'm truly happy to be here today.
After Kenta brought Hoshun's ribbon back,
with everyone in the class assisting him,
I can see that everyone here is already my friend,
same as Hoshun, back in China.
When Hoshun back in China hears
about what happened today, she'll be... She'll be...
So very happy!
A rainbow!
And a big one!
So beautiful!
A rainbow bridge stretched across the Pacific Ocean!
What colors are there in the rainbow?
Red!
Orange!
Yellow!
Blue!
Green!
Yes, it's just like everyone says.
Without getting together different colors,
you can't build a bridge of light, a rainbow bridge.
Oh? I see.
This bridge wouldn't be quite as pretty
if it was all one color.
Green and purple, and all the other colors
are wonderful, aren't they?
That's right.
All the people, whoever they might be,
have in them one of the beautiful colors.
There's no ranking them.
Each and every person is equally #1.
Therefore, let us all mutually cherish people,
who shine in colors different from our own.
Then, which color would I be?
Huh?
Oh?
The dolls...
Those dolls
were the dolls that crossed the Pacific Ocean
together with Emily, right?
On the rainbow of friendship,
over the ocean of peace.
Now it's our turn to stretch this rainbow
all across the globe and cross it.
Friends of hope across the sea,
If you stay still and close your eyes, you'll feel
A vast ocean spreading though your eyelids
And a gentle sea breeze caressing your back
Walk upon the path of courage
Now, let's stretch a rainbow across the Pacific Ocean!
Raw by Anonymous
Translation by Perevodildo
Quality Checking by True Noobow Gamer
The end.