Otohime
I put up a cold facade whenever I'm meeting you
But in truth...
The warmth of your hands, your gentle smile
I always
loved them
I love you so clumsily
I can't even tell you I do
When I held you in my arms,
my heart was screaming things I couldn't say out loud
I want to stay by your side forever
I can't promise you happiness
and cloudless sky, though
Remember, I want to stay by your side forever
I don't need anything else
as long as I have you here with me
I still have the ticket from that time
we went to the movies together
Even if it faded
Hard days, before I know it, I was left behind
In the corner of the room
I heard your voice muttering "I want to see you"
on the other side of the phone
I was happy, but also frustrated
that I can't return your kindness
I want to stay by your side forever
I couldn't even bring myself to say it
I want to watch the same dream together
I want to stay by your side forever
I can't promise you happiness
and cloudless sky, though
I want to stay by your side forever
I don't need anything else
as long as I have you here with me
I want to stay by your side forever...
Kitty... Where's the kitty?
That's one hell of a cat,
giving us such a run for our money.
And anyway, how is that
a work for our detective agency?
Stop being so finicky.
Now that we finally found it,
we'll absolutely catch that runaway cat!
Sure, sure.
Sorry, need to catch my breath.
You all right, Micchan?
Micchan is older than you,
so don't push him too hard.
Don't make me look like a grandpa!
I'm only 25.
Whew! So old!
Gimme a break.
It doesn't matter, goddammit!
We've got work to do!
Sure, sure.
Ah, there!
Catch it!
Driving me so crazy...
Shoot, where did it go?
Dowt miwd me...
Hey kitty cat,
please come out!
I see myself in your face
a reflection of pain
Micchan, did you find it?
No luck.
Yuki, you go over there.
Somebody made you
cry over and over again
Let us know if you find it.
It's easier to corner it
if there's three of us.
Okay, got it.
Still you and I made it
through all of this for a reason
Nagisa, you go there.
I'll search this area.
Could it be that we created
affair for all seasons
Kitty cat! What are you?
Cause you and I
were meant to be lovers
The search is over for us,
there's no other
We're finally at the rainbow's end
Ah! There you are!
Stop! Stop, stop, you!
Baby, together, we'll mend
all the cracks in our heart
Ah? Hey, Nagisa,
Yuki and the cat are running away.
And love all the hurt away
Really? So much for
telling her to call us first!
Woman, you are the thing
that I hoped and I prayed for
You give you love and I'm
happy like never before
You be the strength
and I'll be your shoulder to lean on
We'll build a world and fill our whole
place with love songs
Because you and I were meant to be lovers
The search is over for us, there's no other
We're finally at the rainbow's end
Baby, together, we'll mend
all the cracks in our heart
And just love all the hurt away
My word! I need to catch it soon, or else...
Ah! Found you!
Love all the hurt away
Get back here!
Please! Wait just a moment!
Love all the hurt away
And just love all the hurt away
I'm sorry!
Nagisa! Micchan!
It's coming your way!
All right! Come at me, my fortune!
Nagisa, did you catch it?
Forget it, Yuki.
It's getting dark,
so we'll have to stop for today.
By the way, are you guys
enjoying lying on the road or something?
You can keep at it.
No, it's just... I got totally
caught in up chasing that cat!
No, don't mind me, you two.
Hirano, huh?
No...
Ah, Nagisa-kun, welcome.
Good evening, Master.
In the gentle moonlight
Why, Micchan is here too?
I hope you just walked Yuki home.
If you behave yourself inappropriately,
I'll make you pay for it.
the two are holding hands
I haven't done anything!
Master, gin and tonic for me.
Okay.
Nothing else in the world
And anyway, Micchan,
sure you should be drinking this early?
Hirano-san is drinking my special apple juice.
Only the moonlight embracing them
I wonder what gave you trouble this time.
Is pouring down
Your liver? Pancreas? Maybe kidneys?
They fear nothing but the moment of parting
Your intestines?
All at once.
Since the moment they've met
Master!
Y-Yes?
Top me up.
Micchan is having to hold back!
Ah, Master, is my gin and tonic coming?
In search of love,
Yes, I'm on it now.
the two
reached out for each other
Here, Nagisa-kun.
It reminds me, Hirano-san.
so much it hurt
Tomorrow will be three years
since Kinoshita-san passed away.
I realize it now—
Who's that Kinoshita-san?
Someone I owe...
I want only you
my life to.
Wow! Turns out even you can be grateful sometimes?
to kiss me again
I only want you, I always did
Look who's talking!
Sorry, sorry.
Now, continue from where you left off.
I only want to love you
So what did that Kinoshita-san do for you?
You brat...
His name was Kinoshita Yuma.
Don't push me away
He was the boss of the yakuza.
Ugh?! Yakuza boss?
Actually, wasn't Micchan
a detective back then?
Our sins that we carried over from yesterday
Do you think detectives
and yakuza bosses can't be friends?
I didn't say that...
But wasn't it also about three years ago
that you quit the detective work?
And the future that we can't see yet
Was it somehow related to that Kinoshita?
Kinoshita-san was a wonderful person.
Even if it hurts me,
Kind to everyone.
Strong.
I give myself up to love
And big.
Even if I tried,
I couldn’t repay him in a lifetime.
without regrets
I only want to stare at this moment
Only you forever
Only you I can't let go
I only want to believe in you...
See you, Master!
I drank too much...
That's because you gulped it down, you fool.
Micchan!
Who are you?!
Hirano, I'll kill you next time for sure.
Yukari
Yukari?
Micchan, are you okay?
You failed?
This time was just a greeting.
Something for him to reflect upon.
Well, don't let us down.
Right. But there's something
I want you to prepare.
Brother,
rest assured, I'll avenge you.
Moral
code
That bumbler Kazuma...
Oh, it's you two?
Did the exchange go smoothly?
Yeah. We wrapped up the deal
and went our separate ways, when...
What is it? Did something happen?
That's when a woman, one of Hirano's associates, suddenly crashed the venue.
What?!
We are deeply sorry.
This time, they’re gonna clean it up for good.
More importantly, Hirano, now you're destined to die even without my intervention.
Second Uchida Building
Micchan was attacked?!
Hey, are you really not hurt?
Blabbermouth.
Don’t act so chill! Who the hell was that?
You seriously have no clue?
I already said it yesterday:
you stay out of it.
Wh-Why, you...
Please!
I, Nagisa, Toshi-san, and Hayashi-kun—
everyone is worried about you!
Right?
Yes.
Th-That's right!
Don't get hung up on it,
it's nothing serious.
But it damn well is serious!
That motorcycle guy said he'd kill you!
Say something!
Micchan!
This place is bustling as always.
Director?
Hirano, I’ve got the gist of it.
Congrats.
Well, if it’s a personal matter,
you’ll have to deal with it yourself.
I know.
Director!
Just don't take your time—
we don't want it to interfere with your work.
Okay.
I'll need to head out now.
Fare well.
Director!
Isn't it dangerous to let Micchan
go outside alone?
We're all worried about Micchan!
As for you...
Don't get in Hirano's way.
Director?!
But of course, I'm not saying
you shouldn't help Hirano if you can.
O-Okay!
Hey, how long are you planning
to keep tailing me?
Don't you have your own work to do?
Don't jest!
Who’s actually gonna do his job
at a time like this?
If we want to get back to our own jobs,
we must solve Micchan's case
as soon as possible.
Suit yourselves.
But I've a place I need to be.
Don't let him shake us off!
Yeah.
Is that Hirano?
What are we gonna do?
The special seat opera ticket
stuck on the mirror
I wonder if we could use that woman
to our advantage.
A ticket to the live music club next to me
I shoved them both in my pocket
I'm planning an afternoon that's going to be a fraction of a second
Maybe I should stop by to buy some clothes?
I swear, what is he thinking—
coming to a place like this?
Ah! This sweater would look great on you!
Try it!
Scramble weekend weekend weekend
Excuse me, do you remember
what we're here for?
S-Sorry...
I want to drink in the summer, the hot season
But I just thought...
Doesn't this all look a bit like a date?
Huh?
Ah... Yeah.
It's cruel, but I loved you more than you loved me
See?
Micchan, where are you going?
To the fitting room.
Yukari Group, then?
That's right, Kinoshita's organization.
Don't forget
But I don't understand it...
So do I.
Why would Yukari Group
ever attack Hirano-san?
Besides, the Yukari Group was supposed to be disbanded after that incident.
To think it's still active...
Did Hirano-san tell you anything about it?
He's not the type to let out his secrets.
And the other group
involved in that case... what was it?
You made me wait in the air-conditioned car
Dragon King's Group.
Part of Jinga Syndicate,
Kanto Dragon King's Group.
One of the major members
of the Jinga Syndicate.
I kissed your smiling face in the sweat
I see... Dragon King's Group?
Master, won't you investigate
what Dragon King's Group is up to?
Only I'm chasing you, running out of breath, I swear I love you
Very well. Please leave it to me.
In times like this, having a big name from
the underworld on your side is a lifesaver.
You're flattering me.
It's all in the past.
I could go ahead and investigate myself,
Scramble weekend weekend weekend
but it would be awfully awkward
to have to bow to my father now.
Don't hate me if we run into each other again
Hirano-san is a lucky man
to have a boss who's this caring.
Spare me your sweet-talk.
It's just my insurance—we don't want the worst to happen to him, do we?
I can't sleep with just one gentle love
That's not right!
He's taking too long!
All my days...
Nagisa, do you think
this jacket is a tad too flashy?
Hungry weekend
Hey, Nagisa! Hey, hey, look!
Ah, excuse me! Have you seen the man who went to the fitting room earlier?
What do you think? So, so? So?
Ah, that person just left
through the back door.
He fooled us!
Huh? Wait!
Shit... He'll regret this!
Micchan! So insensitive!
Okay, let's split up and look for him.
We'll call the office later
to check where each one of us is.
Got it!
Scramble weekend weekend weekend
Shit, shit, shit!
I want to drink up the summer, the hot season...
Micchan, where did you go?
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Kinoshita
Family
Tomb
Brother, I'll avenge you soon enough.
I've finally found Hirano who had left the police force and disappeared.
I'll never forgive him for killing you.
I'll send him to hell
at the same spot where he killed you.
Geez... Where are you, Micchan?
Um, excuse me?
Huh?
You mean me?
Yes.
Ah, how can I help you?
Hirano-san sent us...
What, Micchan did?
What is it? What is it?
It's this.
Huh? What's this?
Yes, this is Otohime Detective Agency.
Toshi-san? This is Nagisa.
Why, it's you, Nagisa-kun?
What happened?
Have you heard anything from Yuki?
Huh? From Yuki-chan?
I can't say we did.
Ah, Hirano-san, welcome back.
What? Micchan returned there?
I'll be back in a moment too!
That guy...
Hey, Nagisa-kun?
What's up with Nagisa?
Well, he was asking
if we heard from Yuki-chan...
Huh?
Yes, this is Otohime Detective Agency.
We've got your woman. If you want her back, tell Hirano to come alone—
tonight at nine,
to the third pier in Yokohama.
We are the Yukari Group.
Ah, wait a moment! Hello? Hello?
What is it?
"We've got your woman," they said...
Who?! Who was it?
Th-They said it was Yukari Group.
If we want her back, Hirano-san must come alone at nine tonight,
to the third pier in Yokohama.
Huh? Where am I...
Ah, right! I suddenly...
So you're awake?
Who are you guys?!
What's this place?
What did you do to me?
I'm still a high school student!
A flowering 16-year-old!
The age at which your mind
is still in the clouds!
And I already have someone I like—Nagisa!
And... And... And I...
Here's a lively young lady.
Who are you?
My name is Kinoshita Kazuma.
Nice to meet you.
Sure you should tell her
your real name, Kazuma-san?
Don't worry.
We're sorry we had to give you
such treatment.
We'll let you go home at nine,
so please stay with us until then.
At nine?
Kazuma-san, I made the call. Hirano’s agency knows what they’ve got to do now.
So you're saying
you didn’t tell Hirano directly?
Huh? Y-Yes.
Imbecile!
It wouldn't work if the agency is involved!
I'm sorry.
Doesn't matter now.
I'll call him again later.
So it was you!
The madman who attacked Micchan!
Why do you do this?
Why are you trying to kill Micchan?
What did Micchan ever to do you?
Hirano killed my brother!
That's ridiculous!
There's no way Micchan would do that!
But he did!
Three years ago today, my brother was shot
and killed by Detective Hirano Michio!
No way...
My older brother was the head of a small group called Yukari—a yakuza, if you will.
Ever since I was a child,
And more... And more... And more...
I've been singing the reindeer song I'm so good at
My big brother and I
had a pretty big age gap.
Brother had the gift
for making people fear him.
But to me, he was always
the kindest big brother.
As the train passes by the crossing again,
Done!
it raises the night wind,
so I hold down the hem of my coat
Hey, Just a Little Love, Just a Little Love,
I want to see you
I feel sadness and excitement,
and I can be gentle when I'm alone...
Everyone who liked
my big brother said the same:
he was a strong, big,
and a wonderful person.
Until my brother...
was killed by Hirano!
No way!
That has to be some kind of mistake!
Officially, my brother was killed in a gang war.
But someone in the know told me—
it was Hirano who shot him!
The police then covered the whole thing up!
And as for Hirano...
He quit the police and ran away!
It's a lie!
It just can't be true!
Shut up!
You are our hostage to lure Hirano out.
Stay here and behave until nine o'clock.
Yuki was kidnapped?!
Who did it?
Now that it’s come to this,
you owe us the whole story.
It's no longer just about you!
No, now that it's come to this,
it's about me and me alone.
I can't let anyone else get caught up in it.
Micchan! Why do you still persist?
If I go there alone,
I know for sure Yuki will be safe.
No way! I'm not letting you go alone!
Yes, this is Otohime Detective Agency.
Is it you, Hirano?
Yes.
I'm the younger brother
of Kinoshita Yuma whom  you killed.
Ring any bell?
Your agency's woman is with us.
As we said before, the time is 9 o'clock.
Come to the third pier at 9.
You probably know
where I’ll be waiting at the third pier.
The warehouse where my brother was killed.
It goes without saying,
if the police gets involved,
or if you bring anyone at all along,
I'll kill the woman.
Is that clear?
Don't worry, I'll come alone.
So don't wait to release Yuki.
Only after I’ve sent you six feet under.
I'm going too!
Absolutely not!
He said he'll kill Yuki
if I don't come alone.
I need to leave now to be there at nine.
Micchan!
Fuck!
Off I go, then.
Kazuma-san, should you really go there alone?
Yeah. I want to settle
our score on my own.
Anyway, when the clock
strikes nine, let her go.
Yes, understood.
Stop!
Stop trying to kill Micchan!
You said your brother
was a good person, didn't you?
Micchan is a very nice person too,
a wonderful one!
So him killing your brother
definitely has to be some kind of mistake!
Please! Don't kill Micchan!
Shut up! Shut up, shut up!
I was asked to give you something.
Do you like it?
If so, you can pay him back for both of us.
I didn't mean to abuse your hospitality,
but I appreciate it.
Eh, I owe your big brother
much more than that.
It's just repayment,
so be my guest.
By the way, is it true you caught
a woman who works with Hirano?
Yes. But she has nothing to do with it.
Once I've dealt with Hirano,
we'll let her go.
Well, then!
To hell with it—I'm going too!
Don't be reckless, Nagisa-san.
Nagisa-kun, it's better to let
Hirano-san deal with it.
I can't just sit still at a time like this!
You stay here!
Nagisa-san...
I'm walking in the rain without a destination
My wounded body is wet
Tangled in a frozen murmur
Killing and wandering forever
Until I can forget your love
Sleep is my drug in that it
silently melts my lost heart
Let the soaring love dance,
wrap my trembling body
in the roses of memory
I keep my love for you to myself
Endless rain,
fall on my heart,
soothing its wounds
Let me forget
all of the hate,
all of the sadness
Days of joy, days of sadness
slowly pass me by
As I try to hold you, you are vanishing before me
You're just an illusion
When I'm awaken, my tears have dried
in the sand of sleep
I'm a rose blooming in the desert
It's a dream, I'm in love with you
Still half-asleep, I embrace you
Endless rain,
fall on my heart,
soothe its wounds
Let me forget
all of the hate,
all of the sadness
I awake from my dream
I can't find my way without you
Safety
first
Hirano Michio here!
I've come as promised.
Now give Yuki back!
Seems like you've really come on your own.
Where's Yuki?
Don't worry.
She must already be home and well by now.
Hirano, I'm Kinoshita Yuma's younger brother Kazuma.
But, but, why?
Kazuma?
Lonesome angel
Right now, somewhere,
My brother was killed
in this warehouse three years ago.
The official explanation was that it was
the result of a gang war over drug trafficking.
he's a troublemaker
But in reality, it was the police...
No, Hirano Michio,
it was you who killed him!
Micchan...
Who told you that?
That's none of your business.
You probably won't tell anyone,
and will quietly without saying "goodbye"
Was it Ishikawa?
Boss of Dragon King's Group,
Ishikawa Gozo?
Come on, Kazuma,
what are you waiting for?
Because of this, I'm so down down
After all...
Just shoot him squarely!
I'm practically a junkie, without you
Ishikawa-san told me the truth
about that incident.
It's not a lie, even now, I miss you
Not only that, he said he'd assist me
in exacting my revenge!
Kazuma-kun,
Ishikawa is leading you by the nose!
Alone again tonight, can I call you?
Shut up!
You quit the police and it took me
three years to find you, but it all ends here!
Heart beat, an excited heartbeat
You'll die, Hirano,
for killing my brother!
It hurts...
Runny nose boy,
role-playing boy
He doesn't care
He said nonsense and made me feel like it
But, but, why?
Nagisa?
Lonesome Angel
Who the hell are you?
Even now, somewhere,
Someone who cares
about this guy behind me!
he's a troublemaker
You wanna die too?
Out of my way!
Fireworks to distract me from frustration
Hell no!
Nagisa?
What are you doing, Kazuma?
Just shoot them all!
Back then, a story from the night before
Nagisa, you're not helping.
Micchan?
Kazuma-kun, if you want to shoot me, shoot.
Screaming and talking like crazy
What I did to Kinoshita
might as well have killed him.
If you believe I deserve to die for that,
do what you must.
"Wait,
But it wasn't me who shot your brother.
listen to me"
Kinoshita-san took that bullet for me
while trying to protect me.
I was so excited, no lie, even now
A small incident brought us together
I miss you
as close friends—beyond just a yakuza boss and a detective.
With lots of wine and fries to keep me going, knockin'
Kinoshita-san was indeed incredible.
He was strong and big.
I loved that in Kinoshita-san
and admired him.
knocking on the door
You're not there...
I still think of him as my real brother.
That's a lie! Don't try to bullshit me!
Innocent face,
extreme jokes...
Nagisa, Micchan, help!
We're here!
You bitch!
Yuki! Are you all right?!
Ishikawa!
Hirano! Long time no see.
I was hoping to watch you die here today,
but this little lady had to go and spoil the fun.
Ishikawa-san, what's the meaning of this?!
You useless moron! You should've just shot Hirano, no questions asked!
Ishikawa, so it was you
who orchestrated this all?
Quite right, Hirano!
I'll never forget that it was you
who had me thrown in jail!
I have a very vengeful personality.
And it looks like I'll have to get
my own hands dirty, after all.
Did you... Did you just use me, Ishikawa?!
Quite right.
I also thought it would be quite satisfying for Hirano to be shot by the brother
of the person who saved his life.
Here's something more to help you rest in peace: Kazuma, I was the one who shot your brother!
I was only aiming for Hirano, of course.
Nothing personal, Kazuma
You dirty cheat, Ishikawa!
Fuck...
So long!
Kazuma-kun, watch out!
Micchan!
Stubborn motherfucker.
Micchan, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
This was a bit like
when your brother saved me.
Yes, back then, I...
I was following the trail of drug trafficking
in the Dragon King's Group.
With Kinoshita's help,
we were finally able to expose the source.
But...
What's wrong, you punk?
Getting the chills?
D-Don't move!
You've never shot a man, have you?
But I've shot many a coward like you!
So long, you punk!
Michio?
Kinoshita-san!
It's as if I'd have killed
Kinoshita-san myself.
Hirano...
You done with pleasantries?
Yuki, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
It's Micchan who you should be...
Don't worry, I'll be okay.
Kazuma-san, I'm sorry,
they took us by surprise.
No, it's not your fault.
Asshole!
I'll make you pay for this!
Then you're all getting
on the "Earth-to-Hell" express.
Do it!
Sorry I'm late.
Master?
Who the hell are you?!
You brat...
Even when the sky plays the harp sweetly,
you just sigh so meaningfully
Even if you get hit by rain,
I'm sorry I won't immediately lend you my right
Shake your fist
For your own sake
With your own hands...
Nagisa, behind you!
Director!
Wh-Who are all of you?!
The Director of Otohime Detective Agency,
name's Jinga Himeko.
You've been quite the nuisance
to our branch.
Jinga Himeko...
W-Wait, the founder's daughter?
Now, better listen carefully.
Don't try to meddle
in our branch's affairs ever again!
Of course, I don't want to ask you.
But my father wouldn't be
anywhere as lenient as I am, I imagine.
If you heard me, get out of my sight!
C-Certainly.
Hurry up, you slackers!
With this, we shouldn't hear from them ever again.
Hey, what is it, Yuki?
Look!
Cute!
Director! I found the cat
that we were hired to find!
Now with kittens!
That makes two cases closed at once.
Hirano-san,
I'm deeply sorry.
Don't mention it.
I am still guilty of your brother's death.
Back then, the police were afraid that the media would find out
I will embrace the short days
that we ran through since I met you
about our detective-gang boss cooperation,
so they were preoccupied with sweeping the incident under the rug, rather than solving it.
That's how the incident
became a mere instance of gang war.
I'll hold you in my arms and take you away
Kinoshita's death left me uneasy.
That was what made me
antagonize the police.
You smile and your crying future
make me close me eyes for a moment
Ah! The rain's let up!
Man, I'm starving!
Ah, who's in for some Chinese food tonight?
You're too young and look dangerously likely to break
Don't look into my heart like that
Don't rush, because I believe in you
One day I'll understand
Goodbye, but stay forever
That dazzling glow
like the midsummer sky,
will keep my heart burning forever
I'll leave without saying anything,
but don't be sad
I've planted a seed in my heart
If ever you
need me, that day,
you'll hear a gentle whisper inside you
The soul that has been passed down through the ages
is a promise that will be passed down
from heart to heart, even if this body dies
Goodbye, but stay forever,
that dazzling glow,
like the midsummer sky,
will keep my heart burning forever.
The soul that has been passed down through the ages
is a promise that will be passed down
from heart to heart, even if this body dies
It's a promise!
Raw provider
Translation & typesetting
Quality check
Piyo Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer
This story is fiction and has no connection
to any real people, organizations, or names.