Wake Up, Aria! A Close Call for a Virgin Witch
No....
Stop it. No...
No!
Please... Stop!
No...
Please...
Stop it...
Please!
Wh-What was that voice just now?
A crow. Just a crow, Aria.
Really? It suddenly went “kaa,”
and it startled me.
Oh, right. I was totally moved.
About what?
I mean, being welcomed personally
by the principal.
As it happens,
I'm bringing in all of this year's new students,
including you, on this ship.
After all, you are not only my students,
but also precious cocoons destined to become treasures of the 21st-century classical music world.
Until the day you grow into beautiful,
talented butterflies,
I will cherish you with the utmost care.
Is something wrong? Another crow?
No, crows don't play the guitar.
I-Isogu! Did you come all this way for me?
Aria's knight in shining armor,
her emotional support and sweetheart,
a rock 'n' roller and hip-hop star,
and also somehow, the national pole-vaulting champion, Isogu is here!
And who exactly bestowed all these titles on you? You stalker…
Is that your boyfriend?
Of course not! What are you saying?
N-Not at all!
I've never seen or heard of such a vulgar man.
In that case, good.
You'd better not doubt me!
I really don't know him!
I could blow someone like that away with a single breath. Phew!
Oh, what a cute little pout!
Are you asking me for a kiss?
Whoa!
Oh my, he really flew away.
And there wasn't even any wind.
B-Breasts!
N-No, not exactly breasts... I mean, great boobs...
As in... very impressive building!
Thank you. That's a representative
architectural style from my homeland.
Huh? So that means that building is...
Yes. That's where you'll be spending your days:
the Royal Elegance Academy.
Whoa… That sketchy building is the academy?
It totally looks like boobs.
You are all super-elite prodigies
chosen from geniuses all over the world.
After training rigorously here under me,
you will become brilliant stars shining
across the 21st-century classical music world.
Excuse me.
Shinbi?
This is my younger sister, Shinbi.
She'll be teaching you alongside me.
Pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
Izumo Binan has arrived.
B-Binan?
Yep! Binan as in “beautiful man.”
A name reflects the person.
That's me in a nutshell.
You must be Principal Karma.
Sorry I'm late.
I was competing in a guitar contest in Italy.
Strange… I've heard of you, but this is an all-girls academy, except in special cases...
Well, I am your special case.
What?
I've already received permission
from the government.
His father has made a very generous donation to our government.
I look forward to working with you.
Same to you all.
Izumo Binan, master of classical guitar
and a computer whiz.
I've heard rumors you're a hacker.
Well, that's bad for the reputation.
I'm sure we've already investigated your case
and declined your admission.
However, your government overruled it.
Oh? It happened again…
Just when I was thinking, "I wish a thunderbolt
would strike and end this already."
Honestly…
So, you girls...
I think I asked you to tell me your names.
I... I'm Aria.
I'm Yan.
Aria and Yan, nice to meet you.
And you are?
I'm Luna, and this is my little sister, Monica.
Could you be the one who won first place
at that Italian guitar competition?
Oh? You knew already?
Yes, I'm now known as the world's number-one classical guitar prince.
My name is Karen.
Your guitar playing gave me chills.
Of course it did.
My guitar always hits you hard.
Especially down there.
Refrain from vulgar behavior!
Indeed. To become a refined musician,
one must possess proper elegance.
You in particular were chosen
from billions of young people worldwide,
handpicked by our government as future shining stars of the classical music world,
and gathered here to be carefully nurtured:
the cream of the crop.
Any behavior that stains our nation's authority
or its artistic spirit will not be tolerated.
Oh? So you're a master
of Chinese martial arts, Yan?
I wouldn't call myself a master,
but when I went to Hong Kong, my grandfather...
I learned martial arts from my father too.
Is your dad a samurai?
Not a samurai. A ninja.
A ninwhat?
Oh, please... That joke was pretty hip, Yan.
More or less.
So, is your dad really a ninja?
Yeah, from the Gasshuin style,
descended from the Yellow River lineage.
And your mom's a former Russian noble?
That's what I hear.
They even say she's a witch.
A witch? No way.
That's what I thought too: no way.
Huh?
I-Isogu?!
Hi, my cutie!
Honestly, what a clingy guy. I wish someone that annoying would just fly away!
Whoa... I'm flying away!
Huh… He really did fly away.
Could it be that I'm…
S-Sorry.
What's wrong?
I get it. You were dazzled
by how beautiful I am.
Wh-What are you talking about? No way!
Seeing how flustered you are,
that must be it.
You've just decided that yourself!
First of all, you...
Our country, Orgum,
may only be a micronation in Europe,
but by building this royal academy
and gathering talented youth
from around the world to educate them,
we are undertaking a major cultural project.
Take pride in that.
If you're just here to fool around,
you may leave at once.
Principal... I apologize.
As long as you understand.
I'll be more careful too.
Understood.
Karen, you'll receive a private lesson
tonight at 8 in the principal's room.
A private lesson from the principal himself!
I'm so honored.
What are you doing?!
This guy tried to touch Aria's butt!
N-No, that's not it! There was something stuck there, so I was trying to remove it.
What?
"If you're feeling lonely, just look up"?
Isogu!
You can let him go!
Aria?
See? You can let me go, Yan.
Don't call me so casually!
That's enough already!
This must be fate, Aria!
I'm always right behind you.
If anything happens, just turn around.
Honestly, I'm starting to get a headache.
Hey, look...
H-Huh? Where did you go, Isogu?
Ta-da! Told you I'm always right behind you.
Jeez, don't scare me like that!
What is your...
Huh? Wh-Where?
Geez...
Yeah, behind me, right... huh?
Is this kid your boyfriend?
N-No! He's a stalker.
I see. Then we'll make him leave.
Yeah...
Don't worry. I won't be rough.
And I'll keep it a secret
from the principal too.
Why, that's so kind of you!
A-Aren't you supposed to be a woman?
Ow... Hey, that hurts!
That's enough.
Now then, we'll begin a special lesson.
Close your eyes.
And let this sound and these waves
into your mind, then into your body.
Into my body...
Yes, into the center of your ecstasy.
Wh-What are you...
N-No...
Wait!
I must have that girl first.
Fine, then.
Being violated by a woman—what a joke!
It's a shame you won't remember any of this.
Now then, let me enjoy that cute,
budding little mouth.
S-Sorry.
What's wrong, Karen?
Feeling unwell?
Oh? Even you can't stop thinking about me?
Enough chatter.
Take a 15-minute break.
I wonder what's going on with her.
After those private lessons,
she actually seems worse than before.
Yeah, there was only one big mistake,
but Karen was messing up
a lot of small things too.
Really! You noticed it as well?
It wasn't just me.
Luna and Monica too.
Oh?
You mean us?
Yes.
Tonight's private lesson
is for you two, Luna, Monica.
It's an honor!
We look forward to it.
So tonight it's those two?
Then, tomorrow it should be you or me.
I'd love it if they invited us both together.
Yeah.
If we keep siphoning off their youth and talent
like this, we can live here for years and years.
Earth really is such an accommodating place.
Agreed.
I wonder what happened.
Today, Luna and Monica
were making mistake after mistake.
All after those private lessons...
It does make you wonder.
Tonight's private lesson is for you two.
Is something wrong?
You look like you have some doubts
about what's going on here.
N-No, it's just...
Right.
After Karen, Luna, and Monica
had private lessons,
they started making noticeable mistakes.
You're wondering about that, aren't you?
Uh? Yes, well...
Principal, what exactly did you...
This.
What is that?
Spirit.
Spirit?
Yes. Until now, you've been playing the piano with just your fingers.
Playing it...
...with just our fingers?
Your talent is overflowing.
That much is true.
And your technique is solid.
But your playing must come from here.
Here.
This is where you play.
You understand, don't you?
With these soft breasts...
and a wet place down there.
What are you doing?!
I'm putting that spirit
of enjoyment right into you girls.
Professor Shinbi!
What on earth are you people...
We... We are the messengers of pleasure.
Come on, you!
Let us help.
We have to save the students
from those fakes now!
Still, they really do look just like you.
But there was something different about them.
When I touched fake Shinbi there...
Still, her junk was a little different from ours.
That's not the point.
Let's save the students first!
Right, right!
S-Stop it!
Put me down!
No, not there!
No!
Splendid view.
No...
No! Stop it!
S-Stop!
It... hurts!
No... Please, no more...
Stop it!
Let them go!
Damn demons! You'll pay for this!
We're not demons.
We're actually...
aliens.
Well then, since you're already here,
let's give all five of you a good pounding.
Oh my, what a wonderful idea.
I'm here to save you, Aria!
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
What's more, I've overflown!
Lend me your strength, Mom!
Our power is fading!
O-Our arms are useless.
Catch on to this!
A-Are you an alien too?
H-How rude!
There's no way a cute girl like me is an alien.
But still... I wonder what's happening to me?
Don't mess with us!
You still want to do dirty things to us?
Then I won't forgive you!
Looks like you guys hate this sound.
Damn, that hurt...
Yan, Karen, Luna, Monica,
let's fight together!
Let the winds blow!
Let the storm come!
Looks like you want it to hurt even more.
All right, let's play!
M-My neck's getting squeezed!
Aria!
You've really made me mad now!
I won't hold back this time!
You ugly monsters,
why don't you disappear?!
Huh? What just happened?
Where did this incredible power come from?
Could it be Mom's keepsake, the ring?
Guess I really am...
kind of like a witch after all!
But I'll keep it a secret.
Swept away by you
Marshmallows the color of calm
Dazzling light, dre-dre-dreaming
This swaying feeling because it feels so good
Flower-blooming flagrance
Sweet murmurs
Spilling light, groovy rolling
This swaying feeling because it feels so good
My eyes are closed
My lips are dry
My heart is pounding
My fingertips are trembling
What's wrong, Shinbi?
Nothing at all.
Still, they’re such lively,
lovely girls, aren't they?
Raw provider
Translator
QC
Proxyman
Perevodildo
Collectr