Little Stories for Sleepless Nights
Let's take a road that goes on forever, across the hills
Translation
Perevodildo
The blue of the sky, the green
of the mountains, make my heart flutter
Timing
Perevodildo
Let's be dear friends forever,
from the bottom of our hearts
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
ImAWasteOfHair
I want to tell you with honest feelings
No matter how lonely the night gets
QC
Nemesis, Uchuu
If you've got a friend always beside you
No matter how heartbreaking your love feels
As long as your friend is with you,
you'll be all right
Let's take a road that goes on forever, across the hills
Encoding
anonymous
The sound of the ever-blowing wind
is the melody of love
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Hey!
Cat feels great today.
While staring at the wide
and deep blue sea,
he can't help thinking,
"What a nice thing it is, the sea!"
Then suddenly...
What's that?
That was strange.
Suddenly, an enormous whale appeared in front of Cat.
Riding the Whale
Riding the Whale.
Having hit his head, Cat passed out.
And the next thing he knew, he was sleeping on a bed made from a big shell.
I'm underwater!
Huh? I'm not suffocating!
Whale!
Whale started swimming smoothly
through the water with Cat on his back.
Cat thought, "There's something
funny about all this."
Hey, Whale, where are you going?
I can't understand that.
Wow!
So pretty!
It's fish!
Wow!
It's a pirate ship!
Wah!
There's the treasure!
Huh?
Wow, amazing!
Wah!
Help!
Wah! Help!
A sea of ​​ice!
How pretty!
Achoo!
Arrrrchwoooo!
Whale's throat is so big!
Little by little, Cat was getting more accustomed to it.
Even though they were in the water,
he could breathe freely,
and his body was very light.
He was sure it was some magic that
Whale used to show him various seas.
To his delight,
Cat learned about all the different things hidden underwater.
He thought, "I've come to like
the sea even more now."
But what Cat enjoyed most
were the dear friends that he made under the sea.
Thank you, Whale!
I'll see you again!
Did any of that happen for real?
Or was it just a dream he saw?
Cat can't quite understand it himself.
It happened one pleasant afternoon.
Cat was strolling along his usual route,
when suddenly...
Wah!
Ouch!
Wow, that's one big egg!
"Please take care of this child"?
Please take care of this child
It turned out that the egg had
been abandoned by some bird.
Gomatan
Gomatan.
He didn't know who the egg belonged to,
or if he could really keep it, even.
But Cat was still determined to do his best, as usual.
Then, one day...
Meowhat?
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa.
Papa, Papa, Papa.
Cat found himself very attached
to the creature that had hatched, even if it was a bit weird.
Cat named this child Gomatan.
From today onward, Cat is going to be Gomatan's foster parent.
Wah!
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa.
Go-Gomatan!
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa...
Aw, jeez.
Gomatan... Huh?
Wah!
Papa, Papa, Papa...
Gomatan was a good child.
But he had this peculiar habit
of trying to cut anything he saw.
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa...
Wah!
Ouch!
Gomatan, hey!
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa.
As time went by, Gomatan was growing bigger and bigger.
He was now big enough to help Cat out.
So Cat would sometimes relax
and forget his worries.
After that, Gomatan kept growing bigger and bigger.
It seemed as though Gomatan would never stop growing.
Gomatan!
The time for parting came suddenly.
A team from Gomatan's star
had arrived to pick him up.
Be well, okay?
May your real Papa and Mama
take good care of you.
Papa.
Papa! Papa! Papa!
Gomatan!
Though it was a very sad parting,
Cat wouldn't let himself cry.
He wanted this to become his last lesson to Gomatan:
men have to endure.
Wah!
It seems that Gomatan left Cat
a wonderful commemorative tree
as a farewell gift.
So that Cat's memory of their time together would keep growing forever.
Cat looks up at the night sky and thinks,
"I wonder where Gomatan's star is.
I wonder if Gomatan is doing well."
Today, Cat feels like he's become a little more mature than before.
That's great!
Cat loves the refreshing soda.
Drinking it makes him energetic.
"I'll spend this day doing my best!"
That's the kind of effect it has on Cat.
Envelope: To Cat
Cat! Cat! Mail for you!
Got it, thanks.
RABBIT
It's from Rabbit!
Rabbit!
Ice Cream Souvenirs
Ice Cream Souvenirs.
"Forgive my frankness, Cat.
I am currently bedridden with a cold.
Would you mind coming to see me?
Yours truly, Rabbit."
Friends from the forest who received an SOS from Rabbit
all rushed to check on their sick friend.
Rabbit's condition seemed
to be quite serious,
and all the carrots they brought as gifts remained untouched.
I... I... I...
What is it, Rabbit?
I-Ice cream...
Ice cream?
Because you have a fever,
you want to eat something cold.
Well, you can't beat
ice cream. That's a fact!
I'll go to town and buy some!
No.
If you need ice cream,
you go to Mount Kurinkurin!
Mount Kurinkurin?
Exactly!
The mountaintops of Kurinkurin are made of ice cream instead of snow.
Word is that the ice cream is so delicious,
it can remedy any illness.
What's more, it's a phantom ice cream
that no one has ever tasted before.
I'm going!
I'm going to Mount Kurinkurin!
Leave it to me to cure Rabbit.
Okay.
Take care, Cat.
Sure. See you!
Cat, come back alive, you hear?!
As time passes, I run
Right through this night with you
Raindrops fly in the wind on this
Freeway
Somehow, something's different
My heart's beating out of my chest
It's too intense for a night like this
Hurricane
Love is so easy
If we make a promise to each other
Wonderful music
Melts into the sound of rain
Let me tell you now!
Crazy running tonight
With you, my heart is racing
Dreamy driving all night
Love is always like a big hurricane
There.
Now then, gotta keep moving!
No waterfall or jungle, not even a landslide, could stop Cat.
However, before setting out to deliver
Mount Kurinkurin ice cream to Rabbit,
and getting to work on it with a commendable vigor,
Cat had forgotten something important.
Cat had no idea where
Mount Kurinkurin was.
I-Ice cream.
Rabbit!
Tell me, someone!
Where is Mount Kurinkurin?!
To the east!
Oh? It's you, Mr. Moon.
Cat, it's almost dawn.
Set out at once and walk
straight toward the rose-colored sky!
Thank you, Mr. Moon!
Cat started walking.
He headed toward the rose-colored sky,
using up every bit of strength he had left.
He was determined to fill Rabbit's favorite bottle
to the brim with ice cream from Mount Kurinkurin.
And nothing would stop him.
Mount Kurinkurin was sparkling,
caressed by the morning sun.
This is how Cat became the first cat ever
to discover the phantom ice cream.
Thanks for the meal!
Wow, it's amazing!
Delicious!
True! I could eat it forever!
The phantom ice cream
was totally worth it!
Even I feel like I could
move mountains now!
Yeah!
Thank you, Cat.
No problem.
After trying the phantom ice cream, Rabbit
was thoroughly reinvigorated,
catching everyone off-guard.
Well done, Cat.
It was a beautiful night with a clear sky.
Cat was sleeping soundly
on the tree branch above the swing.
Then suddenly...
What's the matter, Mr. Moon?
I feel kind of lonely.
Why?
Until recently,
people always looked up at me
and commented on how beautiful I was.
They even devoted songs to me.
But lately, hardly anyone looks up at me.
Ugh.
"That can't be right," thought Cat.
Even now, somewhere, someone
must be looking up at the moon
and confessing their love to someone.
Cat wanted to cheer
Mr. Moon up somehow.
I know!
Singing to Mr. Moon
Singing to Mr. Moon.
After seeing how depressed Mr. Moon was,
Cat decided to present him with a song.
Huh?
Sometimes, Cat would accidentally
extend his claws and cut the strings.
But he was still doing his best.
"Please don't cry," and then...
Eventually, he learned to play guitar well enough, so now it was songwriting time.
"Because your tears make my head wet..."
Just like that, Cat finally
made it to rehearsal.
But there were still some hurdles
for him to overcome.
Ah, ah, dear Mr. Moon,
please shine for me!
Forever.
Cat was a bit tone-deaf.
You want me to sing?
Yeah. You're good at singing, Bird.
So I want you to teach me too!
All right.
Really?
But will you be able to endure
my special training?
I will!
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2.
Still not good enough!
Piano means quiet.
This is Forte.
....Music for
Beginners
Forte means loud.
....Music for
Beginners
Got it?
..Music for
Beginners
Cat!
....Music for
Beginners
...Music for
..Music for
Beginners
Do, Re, Mi, Fa, Sol, La, Ti, Do!
Do, Ti, La, Sol, Fa, Mi, Re, Do!
In this way, Cat's singing
gradually became better.
And the day has come for his forest friends to hear his performance.
Wow-wow, Mr. Moon, please shine for me
It's such a long night without you
And I'm feeling so lonely!
Wow-wow, the silvery moonlight envelops us all
I want to see you smile
Until the end of my days
Oh, Mr. Moon!
Cat, you've done a great job!
I like the lyrics!
For sure!
Right, this song...
is like Cat's soul,
put into words and music!
Good job, Cat.
You can be a professional singer now.
Thank you, Bird.
At last, he'd be able to sing for Mr. Moon.
When he returned from the forest,
Cat couldn't wait for nightfall.
The first star!
But where had it come from?
A baby brown-eared bulbul was sleeping
peacefully inside Cat's guitar.
I'm sorry, Mr. Moon.
But tomorrow, I'll do it for sure!
Cat couldn't bring himself to throw
the peacefully sleeping baby bulbul
out of his guitar.
But that made Mr. Moon like Cat even more.
When I look at the night sky
Your warmth
Flows along with the quiet breeze, it's wonderful
Wrapped in this gentle light
I can't help thinking of the people I love
We all have moments
when our hearts tremble and feel lonely
But let these tears fly away to the stars
My tiny little dream...
I won't let it grow up
I may be tired
But I won't get lost
Someone out there loves you
Production
Amuse Video Co., Ltd.
Promotion
Bandai Co., Ltd.
Media Division