Little Stories for Sleepless Nights
Let's take a road that goes on forever, across the hills
Translation
Perevodildo
The blue of the sky, the green
of the mountains, make my heart flutter
Timing
ninjacloud
Let's be dear friends forever,
from the bottoms of our hearts
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
ImAWasteOfHair
I want to tell you with honest feelings
No matter how lonely the night gets
QC
Nemesis, Uchuu
If you've got a friend always beside you
No matter how heartbreaking your love feels
As long as your friend is with you,
you'll be all right
Let's take a road that goes on forever, across the hills
Encoding
anonymous
The sound of the ever-blowing wind
is the melody of love
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Cat and Star
Cat and Star.
On starry nights, Cat liked to spend time
sitting on his favorite roof
and just mumble something silly, like "The stars are so beautiful."
The stars are so beautiful.
Oh?
Are you okay, Star?
I-I am.
But...
But?
The Star got hurt during his fall
and could no longer return to the sky.
Star, why don't you come live with me
until your injury heals?
Sounds good.
Because it is!
After all, I love the stars!
The two were always together after that.
Round petals blooming in the rain
Swaying with a premonition of love
They're dyed in rainbow colors
That day, the two of us
Couldn't express it in words
I stopped on a street corner
And listened to the rain
For some reason, I can't forget this strange melody
And the memories still come to mind even to this day!
I gradually grew to like you
And eventually I fell in love
But when I turned around,
all I could hear were footsteps
Oh, good-bye to sorrow,
and here's to being loved
There!
I'll wait for the day when I can see you again
Rain lingers
On the cracked ground
Sing your swaying thoughts as a song
I gradually grew to like you
And eventually I fell in love
So now I can no longer forget anything
Oh, leave it to the wind, lonesome
Handsome with naughty eyes
Right there, beyond time
I love you
Congratulations, Star!
Right...
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just that for some reason...
But from that day on,
Star kept losing his vigor.
That got Cat thinking too.
"What could I do to make Star cheerful again?"
Star, look at what funny things I can do!
So, whaddya think? Wasn't that funny?
Y-Yeah...
Isn't it delicious, Star?
Ah? Yeah...
Star, look at what a funny face I can make.
So? Did you like it? Wasn't it funny?
Y-Yeah.
Even so, Star still couldn't
regain his liveliness.
Then one night, Cat finally understood.
Star belonged in the sky
more than anywhere else.
Star, you should return to the sky.
If he said that, Star would return
to the sky with an easy heart.
Cat understood full well.
You should return...
After practicing countless times,
Cat finally decided to say it today.
And so he invited Star for a walk.
As they were walking past the house with a red roof,
Cat was just about to say it.
Next, it was the house with a blue roof.
And so Cat decided to say it there.
Cat couldn't help feeling completely powerless when it was time to say it.
But once they reached
the green-roofed house,
he'd say it for sure.
Star.
What is it?
Well. Well...
Don't you think that roof is more dark green than just green?
Yeah.
Cat had never been to the sky himself.
Because it was so high up,
Cat couldn't possibly reach it on foot.
If Star returned to a place so distant,
they wouldn't be able to play,
eat dinner together,
or say hello to each other ever again.
That's why Cat found himself
unable to tell Star to go home.
Forgive me, Star.
Good morning, Star.
Star!
My dear Cat, goodbye.
Thanks for everything you've done for me.
I'll be watching over you
for as long as I live.
Star...
Cat cried.
He was saddened to see
Star leave, of course.
But even more, he was mad at himself
for not finding the strength
to let Star go at such an important time.
Star was far away now.
But Cat knew that his friend Star
would always be right by his side.
After all, Star would keep sending him playful little signals.
Bandit Cat's Clumsiness
Bandit Cat's Clumsiness.
Cat sometimes goes to the town for shopping.
And he's always cheerful on his way back.
Cat's favorite route is the rooftops
of the market district.
When one day...
You could tell at a glance
that he was a bandit,
as evident by the scars
covering his face.
So how long are you gonna dawdle here?
Make way right now!
Though he looked scary,
that Bandit Cat was a little clumsy.
So Cat felt like he couldn't
just leave him there.
Are you okay?
I did it again.
Huh? Again?
To tell you the truth, I'm a big klutz.
Claus?
Not the name.
It means my reflexes are dull.
D-Dull reflexes, you say?
I've been a really ungainly cat all my life,
failing at even simple tasks
ever since I was little.
I kept falling from roofs, trees, and bridges.
Soon enough, my face was covered with scars, as you can see now.
Oh, so you're not actually a bandit?
If anyone found out that I'm such a klutz,
everyone would make fun of me.
So I assumed a bandit's reputation instead!
But that's also why I can't make any friends.
Mr. Cat, you were lucky not to be born a clumsy cat.
So please have fun in this life
on my behalf too.
See you.
"This is a very severe case of klutz," thought Cat.
"Isn't there something I could do?"
I know!
Cat's forest friends gathered
when he called them.
They began a big special training regimen
to enhance Bandit Cat's agility.
One, two, go!
You can do it!
Don't give up!
I can't swim! I'm a cat!
Oh no! Hey! Help me!
Start!
Fight! Fight!
Though he was trying his best,
Bandit Cat couldn't get any better.
Bandit Cat was once again shocked
at his own clumsiness.
Bandit Cat, your break is over.
Let's do one last round.
I quit. My clumsiness is incurable.
And I'm tired.
Don't give up just yet!
That's right! We have to finish this training.
C'mon, gimme a break!
Back when I was little, I also couldn't climb the trees for toffee.
Same here. I'm still climbing poorly.
Everyone needs to practice to get good.
But me... I just... I just...
C'mon, everyone.
Let's hop toward the settling sun.
Yeah!
What a pain...
Encouraged by Cat and his friends,
Bandit Cat also started hopping
determinedly up the hill.
Keep going, keep going,
Bandit Cat!
You can do it!
Come on!
Keep going!
You can do it, Bandit Cat!
You can do it!
Almost there!
Come on!
You can do it!
You can do it! You can do it!
Yes, you did it!
You've done it!
Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray!
Everyone...
Even though he was covered in sweat,
Bandit Cat felt that it was
really a pleasant sweat.
Before long, Bandit Cat's
clumsiness was cured.
Even Cat himself didn't notice
when it happened.
But he was happy all the same
that lonesome Bandit Cat
had finally managed to make some friends.
Night of the Full Moon
Night of the Full Moon.
Though playtime was over,
everyone wanted a little
more time together.
And so, Cat and his friends were gazing mindlessly at the sky.
Seems to me that the sky's color
changes all the time.
Yeah.
Even the Sun itself changes to let
the Moon take its place, right?
Yeah.
There's a saying among us rabbits
that we actually came from the Moon.
That would've been funny for sure, Rabbit!
That's just fairy tale stuff, you know.
I-It's a lie.
I was just kidding.
Just kidding, nothing else.
Well, goodnight.
R-Rabbit...
Really, it was just a bad joke.
Everyone felt that their reaction had hurt Rabbit in some way.
Later that evening, after eating
his dinner and taking a bath,
Cat thought about that.
There's a saying among us rabbits
that we came from the Moon.
Cat thought to himself...
"Back then, we laughed at Rabbit's story.
But really, where did I come from, then?
My body appeared from inside Mama when I was born.
But I feel like my soul came
from a whole other place.
Since I've become friends with Star,
I feel a bit relieved
whenever I see the Moon.
Maybe it's because my soul came from somewhere up in the sky?
In my dreams, I go to places
I've never seen.
There has to be some reason
for these dreams,
where I'm soaring through the sky.
I think it's because when I dream,
my soul becomes truly free
and is able to travel on its own,
wherever it wants."
Cat!
Cat! Cat!
Rabbit!
Where are we going?
A nice place.
A nice place?
Wow!
It's the Moon!
That's it.
Rabbit's soul is also free,
so he's able to travel to the Moon itself!
About that...
Rabbit!
I wanted to apologize to Rabbit
for bursting into laughter
without a second thought.
Restless, Cat soon found himself out on the road
and was already approaching
Rabbit's house.
Cat!
Bear! Squirrel!
Raccoon!
Hey, guys! Wait for me!
Rabbit!
Friends!
And now...
We're sorry!
Forgive us, okay?
I'm glad you believe me now!
Later, Rabbit told Cat plenty of stories about the Moon.
And so, Cat ended up liking
the Moon more than ever.
Oh! It's Rabbit!
The Flying Blanket
The Flying Blanket.
It happened one warm and really pleasant morning.
Cat decided to hang
his blanket out to dry.
He thought it'd be nice if his blanket smelled of sun in the evening,
Cat got to work on it.
Warmed by gentle sun,
his blanket became nice and fluffy.
What a great feeling!
Cat couldn't wait until night
and was soon napping peacefully.
Then suddenly...
Huh?
Hey, everyone!
Huh? What's that?
It's Cat!
How's it going?
Hey!
Okay, let's do it!
Take care, Crows!
Wow! Amazing!
Hop!
Sweet!
Help!
The rainbow he was cheerfully admiring
was so beautiful
it took Cat's breath away.
It was gradually getting dark,
and Cat started to feel very lonely.
Hey, let's turn back already.
Who knows how far this blanket will fly?
I'm getting hungry.
Then suddenly...
Star noticed Cat, who was in a pickle.
Cat needs my help!
There was no way Star would leave Cat, who had shared
a meal with him,
to fend for himself.
Hey!
Hang on, Cat!
Star!
By steering his blanket
with the air escaping from it,
Cat managed to return home safely.
Thank you, Star!
If you ever need anything,
I'm always here to help!
Can I come to play,
even when I don't need anything?
Sure.
Star returned to the sky once more.
But this time, neither of them shed a tear.
After all, no matter how far away your friend is,
you'll remain friends forever.
When I look at the night sky
Your warmth flows
Along with the quiet breeze, it's wonderful
Wrapped in this gentle light
I can't help thinking of the people I love
We all have moments
when our hearts tremble and feel lonely
But let those tears fly away to the stars
My tiny little dream...
I won't let it grow up
I may be tired
But I won't get lost
Someone out there loves you
Production
Amuse Video Co., Ltd.
Promotion
Bandai Co., Ltd.
Media Division