Hyakutaro
Behind
When you hear the word ghost,
do you unthinkingly assume them
to be scary, terrifying monsters?
Certainly, there are terrifying ghosts that can harm humans.
But even then, they only comprise a small portion of all spirits.
If anything, we should consider the spirits our friends,
because spirits that protect us
are much more common.
Every person in this world surely has
a spirit that protects them.
Of course, the same goes for you.
For all of you.
We call them "guardian spirits."
Astral Projection
The house where the poltergeist phenomenon
occurred is somewhere around here?
Yes. We're almost there, at the outskirts
of a Christian cemetery.
Last night, there was a sudden,
deafening thud from underground.
Outside, everyone!
I got lucky, so it only grazed my arm.
However, a moment's delay
would've cost me my life.
Clearly enough, it was
a poltergeist phenomenon.
I've heard of it,
but I've never seen it myself.
The existence of the poltergeist phenomena is beyond doubt.
A particularly famous case that everyone knows about
occurred in Hydesville, New York.
It's also known as the Hydesville Incident of 1848.
It jump-started full-scale research into spiritual science.
Is there a reason why the phenomenon
occurred here?
Yes. In homes where poltergeist phenomena occur,
we're likely to find a medium
to whom the spirit can connect easily.
It can't be!
There aren't any mediums in our family!
No, that's not what I meant.
But then, why were things moving and flying around by themselves?
The spirit used ectoplasm, I believe.
Ectoplasm has the power to conjure images
and move objects through space.
That fact was verified by the French Nobel Prize winner, Professor Richet.
Therefore, this poltergeist phenomenon
testifies to the spirit using the medium's ectoplasm
to throw things, in order
to make a statement.
If that spirit is evil, we must expect
that it will try to hurt someone.
P-Poltergeist!
Here's what we do.
Leave the house one by one, all of you.
When the one with medium powers leaves,
the phenomenon should stop!
Ann! Bill! Darling!
H-How is this even possible?
The entire family left already!
The spirit won't settle down! Run, Ichitaro!
O-Okay!
I-It won't budge!
Knives!
H-Hyakutaro! Guardian Spirit Hyakutaro! Save me!
Hyakutaro... Hyakutaro won't come out!
Why? Why won't he come out?
Hyakutaro...
Ichitaro, what happened?!
What's going on? Open up, Ichitaro!
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
Fire and Disaster Management Agency
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Fire and Disaster
Management Agency
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
He'll be fine.
Fortunately, the cut wasn't deep,
so his internal organs are intact.
After three days' rest, he'll be good to go.
Thank you so much.
We appreciate it.
Ichitaro.
Are you feeling better now?
Yes. It still hurts a little, but I'm fine.
Dad, what about the poltergeist phenomenon in that house?
It's been quiet since then.
I see. I think you two can go home now.
I'll be fine on my own here.
I'll stay here a little longer.
You go home without me.
Okay.
That's right!
It was premature to conclude that all psychics had left the house back then.
Ichitaro also possesses
some psychic powers.
So do you, to an extent.
Funakoshi-sensei!
It seems I caught your line of thought exactly.
That means the ghost
used the latent psychic powers of one of the house inhabitants
to start the poltergeist phenomenon.
And when everyone left, it tapped into Ichitaro's easily accessible psychic powers.
That means it's still in Ichitaro's body!
It’s here!
The poltergeist is here!
O spirit behind this,
what is your name?
What are you trying to achieve
or say by manifesting yourself?!
Ichitaro!
Ichitaro's face changed!
It seems he's possessed by the spirit!
I've been confined
to my tiny crypt too long.
Now I'm finally free!
Where are you going?!
Ichitaro!
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
Wait! Hey!
Ichitaro!
Who are you, inside his body?!
Hello. Good morning!
The spiritual world is full of demons.
Nothing but demons!
If we don't treat his wound quickly,
Ichitaro will bleed to death!
Experienced psychic Funakoshi-sensei began the exorcism ceremony to rid Ichitaro
of the spirit that possessed him.
O troubled spirit, please appear
before us using Ushiro Kentaro's body.
I'm suffering. I'm in pain.
Somebody, get me out of here.
My name is Graham Smith.
I come from Great Britain.
I was stabbed almost to death on a hill
in Yokohama in 1864. But I wasn't dead.
Still, they buried me in the ground.
To this day,
I remain under Thomas Hendrick's garden east of the house.
No one ever noticed.
Let me out!
I understand. We'll dig you up and hold a proper memorial service,
so please retire peacefully
to the spirit realm!
YAMASHITA HOSPITAL
After the psychic Funakoshi-sensei paid his respects to the ghost,
the poltergeist did not manifest again.
Good to know.
But why did Hyakutaro...
Why didn't my guardian spirit Hyakutaro
come to my rescue when I needed it?
Why didn't Hyakutaro protect me?
Oh, you won't know that
unless you ask Hyakutaro himself.
What I do know, though,
is that the guardian spirit does not appear simply when you want it to.
That is certain.
Zero, there's something I want to ask
my guardian spirit Hyakutaro directly.
Why didn't he come to my rescue?
Ichitaro, people say that spirits don't appear just when it's convenient for us humans.
The same goes for your psychokinesis
or my clairvoyance and supernatural hearing.
At times, I can hear Zero's voice speaking clearly,
but sometimes it just sounds like wailing to me.
Spirits may or may not be visible.
It all depends on the extent of our psychic abilities.
But I need to talk to Hyakutaro,
whatever it takes.
With enough practice, the psychic can attain a level of power
that allows him to call freely
on his own guardian spirit
and to talk to him
without leaving this realm.
That's what I need to do.
I'm going to ask Hyakutaro what happens to a person after they die.
What the realm of the dead is like.
And many more other things!
Zero, what's the matter?!
Zero seems to be trying
to tell us something.
Zero!
Takiguchi Rido
Takiguchi Rido?
By following Zero's lead, Ichitaro found himself
at the house of Takiguchi Rido,
one of Japan's leading psychic practitioners.
It seems that as a result of playing Kokkuri,
you were able to communicate with the dead.
But an amateur can easily go astray with the game of Kokkuri.
NO
Entrance
Amateurs don't know how to be sincerely grateful to their guardian spirits.
They often try to call on them for fun,
when they have nothing better to do.
Thus, instead of guardian spirits,
other harmful spirits come, assume their name, and proceed to talk rubbish.
In other words, they end up
becoming Kokkuri-san, as you saw.
Is your gratitude to your guardian spirit sincere?
Yes. It is sincere.
Good. In that case, I will teach you
a benign way to express your gratitude.
Those who are psychically strong can do it with no trouble at all.
You're familiar with what happens when you're on the verge of falling asleep, right?
Yes. Father taught me that's when you're most likely to have a revelation.
Right. When your brain enters the state of REM sleep,
it facilitates interaction
with spiritual waves.
So we take advantage of that.
A good way to prepare for calling on your guardian spirit
is to condense your soul by meditating in front of your home shrine.
But many households don't have a shrine these days.
Yes. In that case, take a bath just before bedtime and wash your body thoroughly.
Finish by cleansing your body in cold water
and then immediately go to bed.
Try to use a pillow that's a bit too tall.
Place your palms lightly on the area
around your navel.
It's a technique for focusing your mind.
You need to keep your heels together,
but not your toes,
if that's too tiring for you.
Then, concentrate on summoning
your guardian spirit to your bedside.
Clear your mind of worldly thoughts
and focus your soul on this one wish.
Those who know their guardian spirit's name can call on it.
Those who don't can appeal to it
as "my guardian spirit."
You'll only get to ask it for one thing,
so don't be greedy.
Okay.
Those who want to see it
make an appeal with, "My guardian spirit, please show yourself."
"While I sleep, please let me engage in spiritual training."
Okay.
It'd also be a good idea
to promise it something like,
"If you let me see you, I will repay your kindness one way or another."
In my case,
if there's trash on the road,
I go ahead and pick it up, making sure that the place is clean afterward.
People don't usually pay attention to unnoticed good deeds like that,
but they count toward your good karma.
The spirits pay great heed to how virtuous the person is in our world.
Having done that, make one
earnest wish and go to sleep.
With that, I can be sure
the spirit will appear, right?
If you're psychically strong,
it may well appear that very night.
But for others, it may take from three days to a week.
It depends on one's psychic abilities
and whether or not one acknowledges the need for a guardian spirit.
If you stray from the path of virtue
for more than year
or are insincere about your wish, it may never appear at all.
I understand.
I can't promise that it's going to appear after you do this.
But I can't stress enough
how important it is to be virtuous,
sincere, and earnest about your wish.
I understand.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Dad! I think I understand now.
I know why Hyakutaro didn't appear when I got injured.
Because Hyakutaro is a guardian spirit,
I always took his protection for granted.
I thought he'd protect me no matter
what I did, however selfish or reckless.
And so I stopped praying before our home shrine, casually forgetting to thank him.
I neglected virtuousness.
I only revered Hyakutaro and spoke highly of him when it was convenient for me.
That's why Hyakutaro didn't show up.
Hyakutaro also probably knew
that this incident would not prove fatal.
Yeah. In any case, I'll try to resume it, starting tonight.
Paying respects to my guardian spirit.
You're a boy of considerable psychic ability,
so you might be able to pull it off.
Yeah.
O guardian spirit,
the venerable Hyakutaro.
I would like to know more
about the spirit realm.
Please let me attain the necessary spiritual training while I sleep.
Ichitaro. Ichitaro!
Hyakutaro! You're here so soon?
You're calling on me in a very earnest manner tonight.
I'm going to take you
to the spirit realm now.
Does that mean I'm going to die?
I'd have to be dead to go
to the world of spirits, wouldn't I?
You have nothing to worry about.
You are not dead, my friend.
Just out of your own body.
There lies the empty shell
of your mortal body.
Look. Your physical body is connected to you astral body through the soul link.
Your astral projection may fly infinitely far away from your body,
but the link won't break
as long as you're alive.
So I'm a ghost now?
That's correct. Now then, shall I show you the way out of this world?
Wow, it looks gorgeous from up here.
But I'm told only the most virtuous psychics get to see
the spirit realm while they're alive.
Why are you showing it to me?
You're special. You have a lot of promise,
so I'm giving this spiritual training.
Plus you've accumulated a lot of good karma.
But I haven't done anything.
Accumulating good karma
is not just about cleaning
the toilet or picking up litter.
Grown-ups go to work.
Children go to study.
Diligence in your daily duties is also
an important form of spiritual training.
Oh!
Those are wandering ghosts and earthbound ghosts.
Unable to go to the spirit realm,
they keep wandering along the edge.
What will happen next
to those sorts of ghosts?
Nothing until they realize that their physical body is dead.
Hyakutaro, where is the spirit realm?
Patience, my friend.
The entrance to the spirit realm is
always somewhere near you people.
It's at the base of trees, in fields,
behind waterfalls, all sorts of places.
Those with enough spiritual training
and a keen sense of the supernatural
can find it by condensing their soul.
Near the entrance to the spirit realm, fairies abound.
Tree fairies, flower fairies, water fairies.
Whenever you see a fairy,
the entrance must be close by.
There are fairies in real life too?
I thought they were a children's tale.
You don't have to believe
in them to sense it.
W-Wait!
It's so dazzling... and beautiful.
It's like a dream. Maybe it is a dream.
Ah, Hyakutaro! Is this the spirit realm?
No. We call this place the dream world.
Dream world?
In simple terms, it exists between the realm of the living and the realm of the dead.
Normally, a human being cannot enter
the spirit realm unless he becomes a spirit.
But through out-of-body experiences, this dream world is accessible
even to those who still have a physical body.
That's why plenty of normal people have been to this place.
However, even after coming here,
they fail to realize it's the dream world
and dismiss this experience as just a wild dream.
The souls of the dead pass through here
on their way to the realm of the dead.
This is the realm of the dead.
It doesn't seem all that different from our usual world.
That's correct. However, the inhabitants here are all spirits.
Moreover, these towns and forests
are not three-dimensional,
as they also belong to the spirit realm.
And it's also quite spacious.
It continues forever!
The vastness of the spirit
realm is impressive.
Every day, hundreds of thousands of people from all over the world
die and become spirits,
so it's unimaginably vast.
Above the realm of the dead
is the realm of the spirits.
Think of this realm of the dead
as a middle school for spirits.
Accomplished spirits who graduate from middle school
then proceed to high school,
the realm of the spirits.
The realm of the spirits?
That's the same as heaven, right?
It is called heaven in the West.
In the East, some think of it as the place called paradise.
Some say it's a wonderful place
where those who distinguished themselves
by good deeds during their lifetime go after they die.
From ancient times, humans believed
that the spirit realm was situated above heaven.
Is that why it's called the heavenly land,
the kingdom of heaven?
You may assume that your world
and the spirit realm overlap in different dimensions.
That mountain!
Wow! So many different towns!
The spirit realm is divided into three layers:
upper, middle, and lower.
We're currently at the lower layer.
The spirit realm consists of countless smaller communities.
Kindred souls form circular towns where they live.
Those towns number
in the hundreds of billions.
Each town is formed
around its central spirit:
a spirit who lives there, responsible for uniting that community.
The spirits of higher rank live closer to the center.
Those with lower ranks
live on the outskirts.
Um, then what's a spiritual lineage?
The lineage of spirits.
Taira Clan Family Tree
In the human world,
you call it a family tree,
Taira Clan Family Tree
which descends from
a famous ancestor, right?
Taira Clan Family Tree
Well, the spirits keep track of their lineage too.
But just because two people were relatives in the human world,
they won't necessarily share that bond as spirits.
Often, a man and a woman who were complete strangers while alive
end up sharing the same spiritual lineage and become very close, or even lovers.
So the spirits have
their kind of bloodlines too?
All right. Ichitaro, follow me.
Yes. This is it. This is the place!
It suddenly makes me feel so nostalgic.
You see now. This is the spirit town
you'll come to when you die.
It feels like I know everyone here!
That's right. If you come to a town of the same spiritual lineage,
your feelings will be shared
by everyone there.
Only people who are compatible to you
at a very profound level live in this town.
They're all your friends,
and you can trust them without question.
Up there, can you see it?
No, I don't see anything.
Just the empty sky.
That's because your sense of
the supernatural is underdeveloped.
I'll visualize it for you.
There are more towns
right above this one!
And the one at the very top is shining so bright that it lights up the sky!
The upper layer of spirit realm,
the world of the high-class spirits.
Wish I could go there...
Do you think you can handle it?
Falling into the world below, into hell, is easy.
But climbing to the upper world requires great effort every step of the way.
I want to see it with my own eyes,
even if only once.
Please, take me there.
You cannot go there as you are now.
Not without a lot more spiritual training.
Well, that's all for today.
Uh, Hyakutaro!
Hyakutaro! Where are you going?
Hyakutaro!
W-Was it a dream?
No, this must be...
A revelation. It was certainly a revelation!
......Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
I want to see the upper spirit realm,
and for that, I need to train more.
You mean the upper of the three layers of the spirit realm, right?
Just like in the records
of the greatest psychic in history,
Swedenborg.
Ichitaro, you had a useful experience.
Yes. When I went to my town at the lower layer of the spirit realm, it felt very cozy.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
What was that?
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
"When I die, I'll get stuck on the lower layer and never get to climb any higher?"
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Fine. The lower layer is more than enough for me.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Ichitaro, never give up
in anything you do.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
The moment you give up,
you stop improving.
Which layer of the spirit realm you go to
depends entirely on your future efforts.
If you strive to refine your daily conduct,
not only will you avoid falling into hell,
but you will also be well qualified to go to heaven.
It's a beautiful place,
overflowing with happiness.
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Topper3000
Rezo
Encoding
anonymous
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs