Hyakutaro
Behind
When you hear the word ghost,
do you unthinkingly assume them
to be scary, terrifying monsters?
Certainly, there are terrifying ghosts that can harm humans.
But even then, they only comprise a small portion of all spirits.
If anything, we should consider the spirits our friends,
because spirits that protect us
are much more common.
Every person in this world surely has
a spirit that protects them.
Of course, the same goes for you.
For all of you.
We call them "guardian spirits."
Kokkuri
Murder Case
Episode 1
Institute for the Development of Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Fifteen hits in one round?
That's a pretty good result, though.
How's it going?
Any luck refining your clairvoyant abilities?
Yes. Little by little, my hit rate improves.
I see. The more you practice,
the stronger your sixth sense will become.
Eventually, you may even
be able to see spirits.
Yes. My ultimate goal is to meet
my own guardian spirit.
I wonder who they are
and what I should call them.
All right, I get it.
You're an exceptionally perceptive dog.
Ichitaro.
A crop circle has been discovered in Akita.
I'm going there to study it
for a week or so.
Oh, shouldn't you leave for school soon?
Crap, I'm late!
Senri Private Middle School
Class 3-B
Hey, Ushiro, how often do you have to be late to be satified?
I'm sorry.
I've heard it countless times.
You've got some sort of sloppy spiritual science research institute at home.
But that doesn't mean
you can be sloppy too!
Why do you say that researching
the supernatural is "sloppy"?
Because it's ridiculous.
Spirits and ghosts aren't real.
But Sensei, many people have said they've seen ghosts, ever since ancient times.
What they saw was
just a hallucination.
But Sensei, both the USSR and the US are spending large chunks of money
researching paranormal phenomena
such as ESP and spirits.
And your source, I imagine, is a weekly tabloid that's just as sloppy.
How can you take
such articles seriously?
I don't agree.
The information is accurate.
Even in modern times, many people acknowledge the existence of spirits.
Why don't you be quiet?!
Do you guys seriously believe in things like ghosts?
If you have free time to believe
in stuff like that, use it to study instead.
I'll never approve of that kind of rubbish!
You can certainly disapprove
of it personally,
but what makes you so sure
that those things don't exist?
How can I believe in something
I can't see?
But can you see a human soul?
You can't see radio waves,
but you watch TV, thanks to them.
This argument is pointless!
Very well, Ushiro.
If you're so confident about it,
we'll stage an experiment here
and now to see if spirits exist.
How does that sound?
If you say there are spirits,
then I say go ahead and show them to me.
Hey, Ushiro-kun,
let's play Kokkuri-san.
Everyone's familiar with that method.
All right, let's give Kokkuri-san a try.
W-Wait a minute!
All the methods we know
for communicating with Kokkuri-san
are haphazard, arbitrary, and therefore dangerous!
Dad said I mustn't use them.
You write Kokkuri-san's name
with the kanji for "fox, dog, tanuki."
Kokkuri
Originally, our ancestors used this method, among others,
to connect with the spirits through wooden sticks.
In Japan, it's supposedly effective for summoning animal spirits.
Because this ancient method was simple and allowed even amateurs to summon spirits,
it became widespread and wildly popular.
The spirits involved in this ritual belong
to many kinds of foul people and animals.
In most cases, their answers are deceptive or jests, so people are left confused.
To summon Kokkuri-san, you need to let a foul spirit possess you,
so terrible things happened to those who tried.
This is a very ancient
and dangerous ritual.
Amateurs should never use it haphazardly, just for amusement.
Believing a fox spirit can possess you these days!
It's no laughing matter.
Then let's hurry up and play Kokkuri-san.
Worst case, I incur the wrath
of a fox spirit, right?
All right. Ushiro-kun, let's do it.
I'm still against it.
It's too dangerous to try
without a psychic present!
Ushiro!
We're all ready.
Oh?
If Ushiro opposes it that much, he probably knows that a spirit won't appear.
He's afraid we'll expose his lie.
In that case, go ahead and do it, but you're fully responsible for whatever happens.
Without a doubt.
YES
NO
Kokkuri-sama, Kokkuri-sama,
YES
NO
please visit our Senri Middle School.
YES
NO
If you are here, please answer us
with this ten-yen coin.
YES
NO
Kokkuri-sama, where did you come from?
E
ST
A
Kokkuri-sama, please tell us
the weather tomorrow.
CLE
AR
That's suspicious.
Aren't you moving it, Ushiro?
I'm not.
It's true, Sensei.
I could feel my finger go numb and move on its own!
Very well. In that case, let's ask it
something none of you could know.
Ask it the age of my mother.
Kokkuri-sama, please tell us how old the teacher's mother is.
See? It's wrong.
My mother is 72 years old.
This is a blatant fraud.
It was a ridiculous idea from the outset.
Sensei, it's dangerous to make fun of Kokkuri-san.
"K, I, L, L."
"KILL?" Kokkuri-sama is angry!
Nonsense!
Ushiro is doing it!
Give that to me!
Sensei, you can't do that
in the middle of a session!
Are you okay, Sensei?
How dare you...
Sensei, that was a misunderstanding!
My arm also moved toward you, as if someone pulled on it!
Bullshit! Don't blame the supernatural
when you launched it at me deliberately!
It's clear to everyone now.
Kokkuri-san is a lie!
There's no such thing as spirits!
Look!
Th-This is too absurd to be true.
Sensei!
S-Sensei is...
Oh no.
He's eating stones!
Hey, what should we do?
But I warned him.
R-Regardless, let's take him
to the infirmary.
You there!
What's going on?
The period isn't over yet.
What happened to Kobayakawa-sensei?
Sensei...
Wh-What are you doing?!
No!
Let go of me!
K-Kobayakawa-kun, stop it!
Calm down!
K-Kobayakawa-kun?
Hey, hurry up, people!
Call an ambulance for him!
What in the world happened?
Kobayakawa-sensei was possessed by a fox spirit.
Don't give me that nonsense!
B-But...
Kobayakawa-sensei's condition
is purely medical.
The doctors can deal with it.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Mom.
Something strange happened to our teacher today.
What did he do?
Everyone was in turmoil because he was possessed by a fox spirit,
but I don't quite understand.
I still haven't seen an actual spirit.
I wonder if guardian spirits are real.
They definitely are.
Each person has a friendly spirit accompanying him.
I only met mine once.
You've gotta be making this up!
Your father taught me how to summon them a long time ago.
I tried it once in bed before going to sleep, and it really was there!
Surrounded by a clear blue light, a beautiful princess-like face appeared before me.
Hey, isn't that Kobayakawa-sensei?
You're right, it is Kobayakawa-sensei!
When was he discharged
from the hospital?
I'm sorry for worrying
everyone so much.
S-Sensei, are you free
from the fox's curse now?
Whoa there. It's rude
to tease me like that.
Actually, I don't remember anything about
the events just before I was hospitalized.
When I came to my senses the next day,
I was already there.
I was shocked by what they told me.
The doctor assured me that something
like that is unlikely to happen ever again,
so please have no fear
about attending my class.
But then, I have to wonder
who killed Yamamoto-san?
To tell you the truth,
I had a strange dream yesterday.
A strange dream?
Yeah.
In it, a fox killed both you and me.
You, me, and Yamamoto-san played Kokkuri-san, right?
That's why I'm so scared!
Kato-kun...
Say, Ushiro.
You know a lot about this kind of thing.
It wasn't a prophetic dream, was it?
Of course not!
Kato-kun!
You're the head
of the music club, aren't you?
Y-Yes.
We're holding a meeting about
an upcoming contest. I'd like you to attend.
Okay.
Institute for the Development of
Psychic Science and Psychic Abilities
Hello?
Oh, Ichitaro?
I'm almost done
investigating the crop circles.
I've made a curious discovery too.
U-Uh, Dad!
Something terrible has happened.
We played Kokkuri-san at school,
and a girl was killed!
And then...
Calm down! Don't panic, Ichitaro.
I need you to calm down.
I'll start preparing to return to Tokyo right away.
When I'm back, I'll hear you out.
He tells me to calm down,
but how am I supposed to be calm?
For some reason, I can't stop wondering about Kato-kun.
Be quiet, Zero.
What is it? Is something wrong?
Zero, you rascal.
This is bad, Ushiro-kun!
Kato-kun was seriously injured.
An ambulance took him away!
He was unconscious.
The police suspect Kobayakawa-sensei.
They took him in for questioning already.
The music contest meeting
was over at 4:30.
I assumed he just went home and forgot all about it.
It was my fault.
Because I made Kato-kun stay behind after school!
Just fifty meters away
from the school gates,
someone hit Kato on the head
with a bat or club.
They found him there, unconscious.
It must be the curse of Kokkuri-san.
Remember when it directed you to the word "kill?"
But spirits don't normally kill humans.
But among those spirits, there are also
evil demons of enormous strength, right?
Maybe even the spirits of cats and foxes.
Spirits that are hundreds or thousands of years old
and have their tails split
into three or four.
They have the power to curse you for seven generations,
my grandma said.
Come on, everyone. There's no point brooding over it forever.
Why don't you cheer up
and study harder?
Kato-kun's bad premonition came true.
If it actually is Kokkuri-san's doing,
that would mean...
It's my turn next!
What's the matter, Ichitaro?
You seem lost in thought out here.
F-Father...
I see. So that's what happened?
I-I'm scared that I might be killed at any moment!
Why don't we try a spiritual experiment to determine the culprit?
We're going to summon the spirit of
the murdered girl and ask who killed her.
You can do that too?
Yes, though I can't guarantee
we'll succeed.
I'm going to be the medium
and lend my body to the spirit.
If a spirit appears, record it all.
The video tape in there is ultra-sensitive, so you might record the spirit's image.
Yamamoto Keiko-san's spirit,
I have condensed my own soul
and vacated my body.
If you wish to tell us anything,
please enter my body
and use it as you please.
You may also use the ectoplasm
I accumulated after years of practice.
Ushiro-kun.
Th-The one who killed me,
maimed Kato-kun,
and will come to kill you next, is him:
Kobayakawa!
Wh-What?!
Kobayakawa...
He is going to come and kill you next: Kobayakawa!
What are we going
to do about this tape?
There's no way the police, who pride themselves
on their forensic science,
could use this tape as evidence.
Why not?
Kobayakawa's name is pronounced clearly on the tape, isn't it?
You claim that the spirit
of Yamamoto Keiko said it.
But the voice on this videotape clearly belongs to a man.
Of course. The spirits don't have vocal cords,
so they have to use the medium's voice.
Then it's not much proof at all.
Besides, our own investigation
found no reason to suspect Kobayakawa-sensei of anything.
Many foreign police forces already employ psychic powers
to solve hundreds upon thousands of unsolved cases.
If this continues, I'll be too scared to go to school.
So you're saying you'd like a break from school?
For now, you have no choice except
to be wary of Kobayakawa-sensei
and to ensure that you're never alone.
Okay...
Hey, won't my guardian spirit
help me out at a time like this?
It will do whatever it can
for you, of course.
Especially if you thank your guardian spirit and treasure it every day.
Senri Private Middle School
Next, read from page 45, line 3.
You can't possibly tell by looking at him, but what if Sensei is still possessed?
Ushiro, why are you idling again?
How many times do I have to tell you to read the next fragment?!
I-I'm sorry.
Look, it's a problem
if you're unable to concentrate
on studying during these three important years.
Do I have to give you personal extra lessons after school?
A-Actually, I-I don't f-feel too well.
Please let me leave early.
Then go to the infirmary first
and have the nurse check you.
Maybe Kobayakawa-sensei actually is trying to kill me.
Gotta run. I should run while I still can.
Ushiro, where are you going, really?
Your complaint about your health was just an excuse to skip class, wasn't it?
N-No, I didn't mean to skip class.
B-But...
I don't care why you did it!
It appears I will have to give you extra lessons after school.
Got it? Don't leave the school today.
He'll kill me.
He'll kill me right here, in this classroom,
just like he did Yamamoto-san and Kato-kun...
Ushiro, I commend you for staying.
S-Sensei, what are you
going to do to me?
What are you asking? Isn't it obvious
that we're going to study?
Ushiro, why do you look so scared?
Because...
Y-You killed Yamamoto-san
and injured Kato-kun!
What makes you think that?
That's what Yamamoto-san's spirit said.
S-Sensei! That face!
H-Help me!
Is something wrong?
H-Help me! I-It's Kobayakawa-sensei...
Kobayakawa-sensei?
He's here!
What happened, Kobayakawa-sensei?
Well, as Ushiro and I were about to start a supplementary lesson,
he got scared and ran away.
Huh? He's lying!
Are you sure the incident the other day
hasn't had a lasting effect on you?
Why would you detain a student now?
You're right. That was
a little careless of me.
All right, Ushiro, you can go home now.
S-Saved...
There's no doubt. Kobayakawa-sensei attacked the other two!
Senri Private Middle School
Ushiro!
Why are you in such a hurry to leave?
In any case, your hurry ends here,
because you're not going home today!
P-Please stop, Kobayakawa-sensei!
My name is not Kobayakawa!
And I'll kill everyone who summoned and made fun of me!
Die!
Zero!
Help me.
Please help me, Guardian Spirit!
Z-Zero!
Wh-What?!
Who the hell are you?!
I am the guardian spirit of Ushiro Ichitaro, Hyakutaro Behind!
It's a fox.
So Kobayakawa-sensei really
was possessed by a fox!
Animal spirit that haunts people
and indulges in evil,
prepare to meet my purifying sword!
Go to hell!
He came. He really did show up.
My guardian spirit.
I think his name was Hyakutaro Behind?
Senri Private Middle School
Hey, have you heard?
Kobayakawa-sensei killed Yamamoto-san!
I couldn't believe my ears!
It was probably only a matter of time
before he killed Ushiro-kun too.
Was the fox spirit possessing him?
Y-Yeah.
But then, just as he swung at Ushiro,
Kobayakawa-sensei suddenly fainted.
Ushiro's a lucky guy.
Kato-kun too, because he's been saved.
Thank goodness!
But why did it have to come to that?
We could ask Kokkuri-san why.
Let's do it!
Don't ever play Kokkuri-san for mere amusement!
In spite of my protests,
after school was over,
everyone stayed in the classroom to play Kokkuri-san.
When my life was in danger,
my guardian spirit suddenly appeared to save me:
Hyakutaro Behind.
I'd like to meet you once more
and have a proper conversation with you...
Hyakutaro Behind.
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Topper3000
Rezo
Encoding
anonymous
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs