Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Here, here, here
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
A long time ago, two lovers from different families, Ijuuin and Hanamura,
were forced to part ways due to their social gap.
Their bond was so strong that they decided
to make their grandsons marry fifty years later, however,
they did not anticipate everything.
Benio was devastated by the sudden betrothal,
as it would sign the end of her "high collar" lifestyle.
Ranmaru, who wouldn't withstand separation from Benio, confessed his love to her.
And now, they're halfway into their elopement.
Episode 1
A Romantic Hangover
I made her favorite grilled chicken recipe again, hopefully she'll eat it.
Going on a hunger strike is doing no favor to her health.
Young Lady, I made grilled chicken!
Where is she...
She's gone!?
What's wrong, Nanny? Did you find more cockroaches?
Lady Hanamura has r-r-run away!
To my dear Father
What!?
Elopement?
Who did she run away with?
Ranmaru?
Ranmaru, you say?
That's a nice one, hahaha.
I'm dead serious!
What do you intend to do??
If sublieutenant Ijuuin loses face because of that,
I'll commit seppuku!
My lord!
Please don't, don't!!
I think we've gone far enough.
Shinagawa ward, 1st Street
We're still in Shinagawa?
Tokyo is a surprisingly enormous city...
Also, I'm kind of hungry...
Come to think of it, me too.
I'd love me some homemade grilled chicken now...
I thought elopement would have been more of a more romantic experience...
I'd eat anything,
but at this hour of the night no store is open.
Also, it's pitch black.
I-I'm scared, Benio!
Keep calm, Ranmaru, that will be our way to live from now on.
A shadow!!
Who's a shadow?
W-We have no money
and we don't taste good!!
Please, spare us!
Whatcha talkin' 'bout?
You dumbass!
Stop being violent!
Tsk, stop acting manly!
Actually, I'm a boy...
E-Excuse me?
Ah, I see, you have a typical "high collar" lady here with you.
Instead of idling by,
you'd better watch out for bad guys,
dressed like that.
Take this!
Amazing!
Who you think you talkin' to?
Look at this tattoo, ya better not look down on me,
cuz I'm the notorious Ushigorou the Rickshaw!
I'll fix you!
Benio!!
Stop it! Please, stop the violence!
Don't hurt Benio!
Oh my, look at that,
he's the one who ended fixed.
How laughable!
With intense training, even a Kendo stick can quash a large dragon!
So cool!
Huh, do you want some more? Come on then, I'm ready any time!
I'm shocked,
I've never lost to anyone before,
and to a girl too, at that!
So, hear me out.
Boss!
What did he just say?
Boss...?
Yes, I want to be your henchman!
Henchman?
You are joking, aren't you?
I beg you!
You see, we're eloping, right now.
I won't interfere!
Boss, you're the strongest man I've ever met!
Huh, excuse me?
No, you're the strongest woman I've ever met!
So please,
I've always been a lone wolf,
but right now I found someone
I could humbly serve, I'll even provide you food, so please take me with you!
Boss! C'mon, drink more, eat more.
Don't restrain yourself!
Sounds fun!
I'm in! First of all, let's have a toast!
If any occasiin to grab a drink, one deinks to the occasion!
Well, let's take a quick break from your elopement.
Come on, let's go with the first cup!
First of all, let's officialise our oath.
B-B-Benio!
Me too!
Bottoms up, Boss, bottoms up!
Well, it's not like modern girls
can't drink Sake.
Right, I mustn't shy away for this little!
That'd the spirit, ho!
Delicious!
Benio!
Oh, looks like you can hold your liquor, Boss.
Gulp!
Oh, great, great!
You are gutsy!
You be gusty, heh.
More! More!
Here you are!
B-Benio... H-How about our elopement?
Whaya'?
I know drunken language,
so, whatever she says, I can translate fluently.
Whaya'?
"What?"
Oh no, this is bad!
'Dja say, Ranmaru?
"What did you say, Ranmaru?"
This is awful, her eyes are completely glazed...
Hammers mark the city rhythm: whack, whack, whack!
Streetcars scurrying about, packed, packed, packed!
Benio is actually a drunkard!
Once more!
Huh? Didya call me?
Hammers mark the city rhythm: whack, whack, whack
Streetcars scurrying about, packed, packed, packed!
Is theee more some sake?
More?
More.
Whack, whack, whack, again!
This was supposed to be our elopement!
Gosh, no, no, no!!
Hanamura
Young Lady!
Benio!
It's fine, that girl is as good as disowned.
So then, we must stop looking for her?!
Oh, actually...
Ah, so you plan on staying up all night long to look for her?
Let's continue for just thirty minutes.
Young Lady!
Hammefsark the ciry rhyrhn: wyack, whack, wyack!
Stfeetcars sdurrhing about; lacked, packrs, padked!
I wonder if Benio even knows what eloping is...
According to a Kabuki story, Umekawa and Chuubei
ran away, hand in hand, following their path of love
under a moonlit sky...
That's what you call a true "honey moon"...
Come on, encore!
Hammeark ciry rhyrw: ack, ack, wyack!
Stfeefcars sfurry round: acked, packrs, padked!
...How did it come to this...
Ugh...
To the next bar.
Hey, stop pushing, it's after hours already.
Oh, come on, we're soldiers, after all.
Man, you two are really hopeless.
Relax!
Oh!
B-B-B-Benio, Benio, listen!
'Dya wan', Rambaru?
What do you want, Ranmaru?
Gimme more Sake.
Look, that's not the problem right now!
That laughing guy!
That high collar hoyden!
It's so strange, though.
Why are you here, of all places?
That's my line!
Oh, you know her?
Oh, I got it, my father told you
to take me back home?
Benio, will we have to go home?
Boss, what's the matter?
What's all of this about, Benio?
Too bad, I will never go back home!
Oh, come on, calm down.
Don't touch me!
I'm halfway into eloping with Ranmaru!
R-Right!
No point in telling us to stop!
Oh, eloping?
So, do you mean
that you're in love with Ranmaru?
Uh... O-Of course!
What a liar!
He got me!
That's wrong!
It's not a lie!
I truly love Benio!
Hey, ya lovely maiden!
Girls only elopement must not be fun!
C'mere, let's knock back more sake!
Come on, girl!
I am a boy!
Ooh, I like this attitude even more!
Ah, Benio!
Leave Ranmaru alone, you tippler!
Ya damn rat!
Hey, ya bastard!
Whatcha doin' to my Boss?
What's wrong with you?
Ushigorou!
Take this! This! And this!
Darling, I was convinced I had taught our daughter
to be womanly, and yet...
Looks fun!
Let's join in!
Hey, stop that!
I beg you to stop...
Ah, Benio!!!
What are you whining for?
Since you're behind this mess, help us!
Uh, did something hit my head?
I'm not in my element...
Mr. Sublieutenant, please make this stop!
Got it, got it.
Uhm, are you actually going to make this end?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry!
Aaah!
Stop meddling once for all!
Not that I am now in!
Dammit...
For God's sake, what the hell is wrong with tonight's customers!?
It's looking bad, the cops are coming.
Hey, Ijuuin, you'd better hurry up and exit.
We'll take care of this.
Fine, thank you.
Let's go, Benio.
I-I don't care!
Stop sticking your nose in others' business!
You slapped me...
Not even my father has ever done this before...
You're right, I slapped you.
A man that hits a woman can't even call himself a man!
I did it because you just won't listen.
What do you think would happen to your father,
an army major, if his daughter was arrested?
Come on.
Boss, please, wait!
Benio!
Aaaah!
Uh, what?
Hey, we were just drinking some sake and horsing around,
am I right?
Yup!
Are you alright?
Benio...
What...
What in the world am I doing?
Holding Sublieutenant's hand like this...
I should feel nothing for this guy,
I dislike him in fact.
And yet, with his face this close to me...
It feels like my chest is about to explode!
It's just like I'm dreaming...
My feet are floating...
Is it the sake I drank before?
Or anything else?
Everything...
Everything is straight out of a dream.
Throb
My head hurts!
This strangely resembles to a hangover.
What's that, a lady
indulging in prenuptial alcohol?!
You damn idiot!!
I am feeling all dizzy...
Why did you do such disgraceful things?
Uhm, could you lower your voice a little bit?
Shut up!
You better be grateful
for what the Sublieutenant Ijuuin did!
Ijuuin?
Do you realize you were about to get arrested?
You moron!
Hey you, what are you doing to my Boss?
Who the hell is that guy?
Oh! I forgot about him.
He's my henchman.
Henchman?
Yeah, in some way or another.
Ushigorou, that's my father.
So this is your father, Master?
Allow me to do the honors,
I'm your daughter's henchman,
my name is Ushigorou the Rickshaw.
I'm pleased to meet you!
W-What...
The daughter of an army major
adopting Yakuza manners, this is so...
Shameful, right?
What will the fiancé think about this...
Too bad, it was such a great marriage deal.
Isn't it better like this?
I never wanted to get married
from the very start.
This way, he'll probably reject me now.
He said he's not going to change his mind.
W-Why's that!?
I can't explain why he has
such a strange taste at all.
But you should thank heaven for a man
who still wants to marry a hoyden like you!
Despite all of this he hasn't given up?
That sublieutenant is so strange...
Perhaps, he just doesn't think
much about marrying.
At any rate, if I don't do anything,
I'll just end up married.
With this, my "high collar" life
will be gone for good, without even falling in love.
I was told that Ranmaru
has been sick since then,
but I'm not even allowed to visit him.
I'm sorry, Ranmaru.
Yo, Boss!
Are you feeling down?
Would you let me accompany you?
It looks like bad things
are piling up one after another.
Boss Benio's car
At Boss's orders!
Towards her edification, under any rain,
be it of tears or blood, a high collar child
steers ahead at full speed.
Boss Benio's misadventures go on,
as her henchman Ushigorou
causes turmoil in her all-girls school.
On top of all of this, she'll learn
about her friend Tamaki's unrequited love,
whom sadly, sadly,
proves to be Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
Ah, love, love, the root of every pain.
Benio's trouble will burst through the ground.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar lady:
A Messy Asakusa Opera,
don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra