Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Here, here, here
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
It's the Taishou Era, knead with Romanticism.
And that quiet girl is no other than Hanamura Benio,
A High Collar lady in her
seventeenth year...
...But a single bamboo sword is all she needs to turn into a full-blown hoyden!
Inscrutable and interesting are the ways people are brought together...
...And that's not wrong,
As fate made her run upon a
princely sublieutenant.
She challenged him,
as she wanted to test his reflexes,
only to discover that she is betrothed to him by her father.
The hell are you saying?
En garde! Ten points!
Twinkle twinkle little star,
how I wonder...
what you are...
Oh, you're finally awake, Lady.
I-I'm so mad!
I wonder who said that a warrior
should always be vigilant.
Ugh, I've never lost to anyone before!
Just thinking about it makes me all riled up!
Hello, I'm Know-Not Fellow.
Don't mind me, I'm just passing by.
Wholly cooked!
Who the hell are you?
Can't you see that I feel down?
And that guy's supposed to be my fiancé?
F-F-Fiancé? My future husband?
Episode 2
Elopement
Father!
It's not funny at all when you joke about these things,
so you'd better stop fooling around with me!
No, this is definitely not a joke.
That Ijuuin Shinobu is undoubtedly your husband-to-be.
Yikes!
Wait, this is not the time to faint yet.
Father, that's so out of the blue...
Why on earth are you doing this?
You see...
For ages, the Hanamura dynasty was a vassal family at the service of the Tokugawa Shogunate,
whereas the Ijuuin dynasty has always been a noble family.
A long time ago, your grandfather and Ijuuin's grandmother, who met by chance,
had been enamored to one other.
But unfortunately,
the night before Meiji Restoration,
both were forced to break off the relationship due to the end of the Shogunate.
However, before they parted ways, they made a pledge
that someday, were the world becoming a better place
their two bloodlines would intermix.
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually turn into one again...
In spite of that, their descent was male,
so they decided to wait until
their grandchildren's birth.
So, in other words, I'm the chosen one.
At any rate, this is a promise that predates your births.
You've got to be kidding me!
I flatly refuse this!
It is a lapsed oath by now,
no matter how you put it!
On top of that, with a guy as him, of all people.
You need to accept that this is an
imperishable promise between the families.
Imperial Rules states that
breaking promises is a taboo.
Moreover, they also go by this:
"Warriors! Shall faithfulness be your credo!"
But that guy is not a warrior, he's
a coward that takes advantage of others!
The same source tells something else:
"First and foremost, etiquette shall be followed".
Doesn't it?
Benio! Don't object to your father's words!
Also, very soon we'll be holding an informal wedding
Going to Ijuuin's house will get you to learn manners.
Understood?!
F-Father!
Nanny, is the bath ready?
There's no way...
As much as I try, he won't change his mind...
Darling,
I think I've done the right thing.
I've always seen Benio as a kid...
...But if I don't do anything, she'll end up increasingly more boyish.
Anyways, her fiancé is from reputable nobility, so she'll learn a lot,
even though it might be daunting at the beginning.
"That is the question."
"To be or not to be,
that is the question,"
make sure you remember that one well.
Phew...
This is a line from a work by William Shakespeare,
a famous English man of letters...
Hanamura Benio, interpret this!
Interpret this line: "To be or not to be,
that is the question!"
Sure!
It means that the author is asking himself whether something is there or not.
What?
What the hell are you doing, Benio? Read this!
Cheatsheet - English
Is suffering in life better than dying,
that is the dilemma.
She's blatantly reading the cheatsheet!
Uhm, should I keep on reading?
What...!
Shut up and get out of this class!
...Or not.
Saved by the bell!
Thank God, Benio!
I got defeated again...
Wait, wait, wait, Benio, what happened?
Isn't English your top subject?
You've been in a daze all morning long.
- Right?
- Well, to tell the truth...
I've been betrothed to
someone I don't even know.
Betrothed?
You, Benio?
Is he handsome?
Is he tall?
Is he a real man?
A man?
To think that you, the usual dunce, would be the first to get engaged!
Benio, you animal!
People sure have strange tastes...
Gimme your man...
Enough is enough!!
I don't care if he's handsome,
I don't feel like getting married yet!
I-I have interests, hopes and dreams too, after all!
I-It's easy for you to say this...
Oh, she even started crying.
Benio is right.
She shouldn't be forced to marry a stranger.
Tamaki...
Hang in there, Benio.
You are in your good right to reject this old-fashioned marriage custom.
Tamaki, you're the only one who understands me!
Thank you, I'll do my best!
Still, Benio,
being too picky might get you to end up alone.
Yeah, even I, am in doubt.
Living a whole life alone is tough.
Well, cheer up a bit.
Ah, that's right, haven't you said that the man is a noble?
I have.
If I'm not mistaken, you're one too, aren't you?
Yes. Life in a noble family is hard, though.
Hard? In which way?
For example, "Omawari", "Akaka",
"Iriiri",
"Okabe", "Misomiso", "Tsukutsuku", "Harihari", "Surusuru".
Do you understand any of this?
To make it short,
"Omawari" stands for vegetables.
"Akaka" are red beans.
What?
"Iriiri" are soybeans.
"Okabe" means tofu.
Moreover, "Misomiso" is miso salad.
"Harihari" stands for dried melon.
"Tsukutsuku".
"Surusuru".
Got it, Benio?
All of these are words nobles use.
They don't speak Japanese?
I wouldn't go as far,
but it's a rather different world.
A world without Japanese...
No way, I'd hate a place like that!
What should I do, Tamaki?
Welcome home, Young Master.
Good morning.
I got you, I got you, Tenmaru.
Tsumaru, good dog.
Are you doing good?
Mrs. Kisaraki, is Grandmother here?
Yes, she is currently on the terrace in the garden.
Got it.
All right, Tenmaru, Tsumaru, we'll play later.
Oh, it's you, Shinobu.
Greetings, Grandmother.
Hello, thank you for your visit.
Grandmother, yesterday
I got to meet Lady Hanamura.
Oh! Then tell me, Shinobu, how did it go?
What kind of girl was she?
She seemed to be full of spirit,
I'd say I had a good impression.
Oh, then would you even be willing
to marry that girl?
I'd do anything to make you happy, Grandmother.
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually turn into one again...
Today, as my grandson, you're granting one of my lifetime wishes.
Thank you so much, Shinobu.
Sorry for bothering you, Young Master.
This is today's share of letters for you...
All of them are from women.
Oh, yeah.
Young Master, I've heard about your engagement, but there are still these many!
I got it, I got it.
How could I blame them, though.
Our Young Master is that handsome...
I might send in a love letter too!
Greetings, Shinobu!
Hey, Tamaki.
May I come inside?
Sure.
I was on my way back from piano classes, so I figured I'd drop by.
Nice, I'd love to hear you play sometimes.
Oh.
Full of love letters as always...
I bet this amount doesn't outmatch yours.
Oh, you, sweet talker!
Today a friend of mine got betrothed.
On top of it, her fiancé is a noble.
Oh, so he's like me,
I hope I'll be as lucky.
Oh, but isn't it easier to you,
given all the proposals you get every day?
It can't possibly be...
Tamaki is too different from my fiancée.
She can't be her friend.
Hey, Shinobu,
what are you thinking about?
Oh, nothing important.
Garden of Flowers
These safflowers are a rare sight...
I think they'd match her.
Uh?
Would you send the flowers to this address?
Sure thing! Oh, are these a gift for your girlfriend?
Hmph!
Ok then, thanks a lot.
Sorry for the wait.
It's not my business,
but by acting this carelessly, your reputation will drop down!
Tamaki!
He really hasn't greeted my feelings at all,
ever since the times we were kids.
It's Spring, and yet it's still so cold.
Young Lady, the dinner is ready,
Grilled chicken, your favorite!
I don't want any.
Hm?
Oh!
It's always been her favourite dish, but she isn't even opening the door.
A hunger strike,
and she seems determined about it.
That's right.
But she'll certainly feel ill,
if she keeps on going like that.
Well, maybe we shouldn't hastily judge it,
girls who are betrothed usually start to self reflect,
Regardless of the circumstances...
This book is so funny!
Here Comes the High Collar Lady
King, King, Ki-
not funny anymore.
No matter what I do, I keep feeling down,
I don't even feel like practising fencing.
Oh, the quiet spectacle of snow...
Ranmaru!?
Benio...
You fool, what are you standing there for?
You'll just catch a cold!
Hurry up, get in.
You're hopeless.
Come on, get near the fire.
How much did you stay outside like that?
Benio, it's awful!
Betrothed... Betrothed that way!
Ranmaru...
It's terrible!!
I've always,
always liked you, ever since I was a child.
W-What's that?
That's just the truth,
but my social status is lower, and I'm one year younger than you.
That's why I've never told you.
There's nothing I can do,
it's my dad's decision and I can't go against it.
Also, according to what he said,
that second lieutenant seems to be a good man.
But to make such a decision all of a sudden when there is so much I'd like to do...
I can't be happy about it.
Benio!
Let's run away together!
Ranmaru, what the Dickens?
I'd lose everything just to be with you.
even Kabuki as well!
Am I not good enough for you?
Ranmaru...
I-It's not like that, I like you,
but in a brotherly way.
So it's ok, isn't it?
Ranmaru!
Then let's meet tonight, I'll be waiting!
To tell me something like that,
he went all this way through the snow.
But...
What is this feeling?
Why is all of this happening all of a sudden?
Well, Ranmaru is cute, after all,
so I feel like I can't just ignore him,
but running away with him? That's a bit much.
It'd be ill advised to do a drastic thing like elope...
Shakespeare said:
"Is suffering in life better than dying?
That is the dilemma."
Shut the hell up!
Young Lady?
You've received flowers from Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
Oh, I see.
Huh?
These are safflowers, right?
He even attached a card.
Let's see.
"It's not a color
I'm very fond of..."
It's not a color I'm very fond of, but, for some reason,
I still picked these safflowers for you.
"It's not a color I'm very fond of,"
so, if I had to interpret it...
Even if I he doesn't have deep feelings about me,
he still decided to send these safflowers with some kind of intention, I guess...
Safflowers, typically used as a dye...
Ouch!
Flowers meant for dyeing?
So he meant to dye my nose red!?
Everything is coming together now!
That jerk!
I didn't think he could be this mean!
I have never liked him, but now I'm completely done!
Rather than marry such a guy, I may as well run away,
no matter the price!
No one can dare make fun at me!
Let's go, Ranmaru.
Benio!
Goodbye Dad,
home, friends,
and fiancé, I'll be walking on my own from now on!
And so, walking at a fast pace alongside Ranmaru,
High Collar Benio is determined to start anew.
Escaping from the forceful engagement and live the "High Collar" way. Where will they go?
High Collar Benio is running away with Ranmaru,
following the path of true love,
might lead to unexpected encounters.
As Ushigorou from the Kurumahiki clan,
willing to become a girl's escort.
But everything will turn into a cheerful bender and a drunken singalong,
only to meet her blond
sublieutenant fiancé once again.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
A romantic hangover.
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra