Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Here, here, here
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Sorrow lurks deep within a maiden's innocent heart,
when she is shocked at the man she gazes upon,
learning that he's none other than her friend's fiancé.
Overwhelmed by an internal conflict of friendship and love, she ran away.
On the other hand, we have
another story of one-sided love:
even though he had been looking for Benio,
ah,
he didn't make it in time, as our dear high collar lady
already had a hand in yet another scuffle!
Causing all the fuss and sneaking away?
Never come back!!
Boss!
Boss, are you alright?
Ranmaru, what is up?
What is up??
I was looking for you!
Oh, I see.
Ah...
Boss, where in the hell is the one who disrespected you like this?
I have more than words to tell him!
Wait, Ushigorou.
It was my fault to begin with, so it's fine.
Hey, you!
Wherever you go, something bad happens!
First the bar and now this!
Ushi!
What are you in relation to the Boss?
I beg you, no more questions.
Let's not cause any more trouble.
Benio!
Let's hurry home, shall we?
Benio, how about I buy you some coffee
or an ice cream in that milk hall?
Ice cream...
I'm truly helpless when it comes to food...
Come on, let's go.
Benio!
Episode 5:
Godspeed, bride in training!
Milk Hall
Now, what's so funny to you?
Oh, sorry,
it's just that I was thinking back
of what had happened over there...
Hey, you...
Do you even realize what was going on?
Not only I ruined the opera,
but I also embarrassed you, didn't I?
Is that something I shall be embarrassed about?
Huh...
Had I been with any other girl,
I wouldn't have had so much fun at the Opera.
I'm dead serious!
I didn't mean to make you have fun!
After all,
we're together just because your parents told you to do so...
Also, Tamaki is a dear friend of mine...
I want her feelings to be embraced.
On top of that,
I'm so mannish and careless.
Moreover, Tamaki is such a refined girl,
anyone in their right mind would pick her over me.
Whoa...
I've never met a girl who's as self-aware as you.
I was just being modest!
Wait, I didn't mean to make fun of you.
Then what would be the reason to marry me?
Your ice cream is melting.
As soon as food is involved, I am cheated out!
Hey, could we at least get in and have some coffee?
Hell no,
boss's orders are sacrosanct,
there's no way I'd ever breach them!
Anyways...
What could they be talking about?
Benio...
What are they talking about so cheerfully?
Coffee... Coffee...
Hot as the depths of hell,
black as the darkest night,
and bitter as this love of mine.
Oh, sweet coffee...
Benio, look straight at me...
I want you to take a good look at my face.
Surely, a pretty, perfectly chiseled face...
Encircled with that bright hair,
unique among Japanese people...
Those almost transparent cheeks...
Furthermore, those expressive,
yet mysterious hazel eyes...
Those mysterious hazel and vaguely bluish eyes...
You see,
I am the son of a Japanese father
and a German mother.
My mother...
She's probably somewhere in Germany.
She, too, is a daughter from a noble family.
They both passionately became fond of one another.
However, my mother's family
would've never allowed her to marry a foreigner.
And thus, she left my father with me,
a newborn baby,
to marry a man from another family.
Since I resembled my mother a lot,
it became painful for him to even look at me.
So he left me in Japan
to go to another country,
where he eventually died.
Thus, after that,
the one who had been taking care of me,
was my grandmother.
Even now, I can't forget those days.
Shinobu! Look, look, that's a steam train!
Wow!
Amazing!
That rising smoke!
Grandmother!
If I ride on that train,
will I able to meet Mother and Father?
Hey, Grandmother!
If I keep trying, I'm sure I'll meet them!
Sublieutenant...
To think that I could feel so sorry for him...
Is it my maternal instinct awakening?
Because of this,
as I grew up, over and over again,
my grandmother dwelled on her doomed romance.
So, from childhood onward,
I formed the desire to grant her wish to see her youthful love flourish.
What the hell!?
So you settle for a loveless marriage just to please your grandmother?
Of course, that's the only motive I need.
What...!
There's no way a couple
can get along so mindlessly!
I oppose such an egoistical view on marriage!
At any rate, I don't want
the engagement to be called off.
Huh!?
This has been my grandmother's
purpose in life for all these years.
Ugh...
This guy has a severe grandmother complex!
What a gerontophile!
Don't you feel anything about this?
Doubts? Worries?
Not really.
Huh!?
What!
Oh Lord,
have mercy on this young and handsome man
engrossed in gerotonphilia!
It's not normal!
Not normal at all!
Why am I involved with something like this...
Benio!
I'm off!
It's like he would be fine with marrying anyone.
Yes, if she were from the Hanamura family,
he would marry even that giddy bimbo!
Pardon?
Shut up!!
Oh,
I thought she called me...
Acting as this towards emancipated women,
it couldn't be worse than that!
Benio!
Boss!
It seems like you had a fight!
Tell me who it was!
A fight?
Are you always so lowly perceptive?
Huh?
Aren't people aware,
that girls have their worries, too?!
Bonk
Wait, Benio!
I don't understand what's happening at all!
Boss!
Ugh...
Boss, wait, please!
Why do you care,
I'm just a girl that does nothing but fight, aren't I?
It's not like this,
you got it all wrong, Boss!
Don't misunderstand!
I didn't mean it that way!
Just stop following me!
At least listen to me.
I have a message from Nanny.
Nanny?
She said that there's no homework for tomorrow,
so you needn't worry.
Huh? I see...
Hanamura!
Heh, you can't fool me,
I'm sure that there was no homework for today,
thanks to Ushi.
Hanamura, one minute.
Teacher, there shouldn't be
homework for today, right?
Homework has nothing to do
with what I want to tell you.
Huh?
I wonder what it's about, then.
Is it true that you've been
betrothed to Sublieutenant Ijuuin?
Mhm, yeah.
Wow, so that was true.
Huh?
Humph...
How could someone like you, of all people,
marry in the noblest of all noble families?
You, who failed cooking,
sewing and etiquette.
You, with all insufficient marks!
All of them!? In other words, all 1s?
No way, getting to know the truth hurts so much!
Did I do that poorly?
Poorly? You're the worst student
who has ever stepped in this school!
You're a complete failure in every single aspect,
in any shape or form!
Huh? Look what it came to - she is crying!
A complete failure!
Insufficient marks
Did she go crazy?
What should I do?
Maybe it was the shock,
of hearing this all of a sudden...
How are you feeling? I'm Benio...
I failed everything...
Yes, that's right!
Well, isn't it great?
Hahahaha!
Tamaki...
Tamaki!
Wait, Tamaki!
Benio...
Just looking at you is painful...
The fact that you're marrying Shinobu...
I have something to tell you about that.
I...
I've always loved Shinobu, and to make it worse
you're my rival, of all people...
Just wait!
I am not going to marry him!
Aren't you going to his house
to learn marriage manners, though?
That's true.
Then it's already settled, isn't it?
There is something else you need to know...
Hey, hear me out!
I will, so be straightforward.
Roger.
To make it short, you already know
that I am worthless as a lady of the house...
Yeah, so?
So,
as my training is undergoing,
what will happen once they figure it out?
As much as Shinobu's grandmother
wants him to get married,
I don't think that she'd want him
to get married to a good-for-nothing
like me, don't you think so?
Do you think it will be alright?
Wow, Benio,
you're so clever!
This is why you're my best friend!
I love you!
Benio, you're incredible.
I see...
Will it really be alright, though?
Well, just look at me.
I had the worst grades in etiquette, cooking and sewing,
everyone else
could be a better wife than me!
It's going to be fun!
When I'm done with this vase,
we'll decorate upstairs too.
Yes, ma'am.
I want this house to be overflowed with flowers.
The sky is also clear,
it's such a beautiful day.
I just have one more thing to tell you:
please be kind and patient with them.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll be going, grandmother.
Do your best.
Take care, Young Master.
Oh, beautiful flowers...
Shinobu, do you understand what they are for?
Today is the day the girl named Benio
is stepping inside this house for the first time.
After waiting for all these years,
my wish of a lifetime
is about to be granted through my grandson.
So these flowers are for Benio?
So to speak,
I wanted to make this decoration blossom!
I wonder whether that high collar girl
will be able to appreciate all those flowers...
Even her neighbour Ranmaru
is more feminine than her.
Then, I will see you later.
Benio...
To where did Ushi go,
at such a crucial time?
He doesn't understand how I feel...
I am Ushigorou the Rickshaw,
Tokyo's most... yawn!
Ah, this world is so dull lately...
Hey you, Lady! Fancy a ride?
It's cheap.
Hell--- no!
Huh!
Man, that's rude...
Well then! Let's have a toast.
Let's go.
If you drink, don't pull,
if you pull, don't drink!!
-City Police
Good morning, I am here
to greet Lady Hanamura
in anticipation of her apprenticeship.
I politely beg leave to go call my daughter.
It's all pitch-black~
All, all, pitch black!
Hey, join so we can sing this together out loud!
Yah, let's do this.
It's all pitch-black, yeah! It's pitch-black!
Across Mount Hakone
In the past, people used to travel
on backs or in a bier.
Nowadays, as in a dream,
trains take people wherever they want to go!
All the smoke makes the tunnel pitch-black!...
It's all pitch-black!
Benio...
Is Lady Benio still changing her clothes?
Can you check in on her?
Yes, I am on it right away!
Benio!
Young Lady!
Here I am!
Did you call for me?
Chin-less Nanny.
Y-Young Lady...
That's Lady Benio!?
Benio...!
What's wrong, daddy?
Daddy?
Young lady, w-what's that look...??
What is the big fuss? What's the fuss?
I dressed myself up,
in order to celebrate
an important meeting of this kind.
This is bad news...
It appears that Benio devised
an effective deterrent tactic!
What is awaiting her?
Stormy winds,
or heavy rain?
Only Fate knows what's going to happen next!
The high collar betrothal-breaking mission has begun,
and Benio is acting as most unladylike as she can,
in order not to end up married to Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
However, oh my, oh my,
something unexpected is waiting for her...
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
A Fleeting Wedding March,
don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra