Long ago, this world was a beautiful paradise.
In this world of balance, people, demons, and gods all feared and respected each other equally.
All of them lived with the hope and belief
that this way of life would last forever.
That was Neverland.
Situated in the southwestern part of the Old Continent was the mountain kingdom of Bjor.
The man who ascended as the thirteenth Generalissimo of Bjor, Fract,
turned this country
into a warmongering nation.
Who if not we, the Bjor, deserves a place
under the sun on top of the Old Continent?
He was a natural leader and politician,
so he took command of Bjor's army
and invaded Orthozes,
a neighboring country in the north.
Although soundly defeated in his first campaign,
Fract profited from the experience.
He rebuilt his army the next year and
moved into Harbus and Glok in the south.
And then on to Axes, Elflore, and Bihlimere.
Before people realized it,
Bjor had occupied half of the continent.
This was the reality. An iron fist, ruling with brutality and fear.
Under Fract's rule,
the Old Continent was soaked in blood.
Finally, to rectify his past failure, Fract prepared to invade the last country on his border,
the agricultural nation of Orthozes.
Rich in produce,
this country was never at risk of famine.
It was a rare place where all creatures
lived in harmony with nature.
However, all they could do now was wait,
constantly in fear of Bjor's massed armies.
One man's lust for power
drags the world into chaos.
History has taught us that power
sustained by fear always leads to chaos.
This story is an episode from the lives
of those who stood up against this power.
The ones we think of as beautiful
Are not a simple coincidence or turn of fate
I know where I am, what I'm doing
And what I like most, I suppose
It's not simple, though
Show me your many sides!
I'll keep looking for you too
Not needed by one, necessary for another
In a city where buildings reflect light from all around
There's a place designated just for you
May you find it
May it shine for you
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Victory in war is always about numbers.
Before the allied armies mobilize,
we must overwhelm Orthozes,
rendering any future struggle futile.
I think we have a chance to win.
Generalissimo...
Time erases everything.
Orthozes is our Achilles' heel.
Even the previous king failed to conquer it.
Did the Generalissimo come up
with a new strategy?
Damned if I know.
But if we lose...
Our commander's only instrument is force.
He's achieved his position by modernizing and bolstering the previous king's army.
But this method has its own limitations.
If I was in charge, I'd find a better way to negotiate with the enemy.
Don't you agree?
Y-Yes, sir!
Lord Descartes is second only
to Generalissimo Fract himself.
We're evacuating.
They want us back in camp for now.
The border patrol on the Orthozes side appears to be retreating!
Maybe they saw the size of our army.
They know border guards
wouldn't be able to stop us.
All right, let's advance now!
One, two...
An ambush?
Major, should we turn back?
You guys, climb up that cliff.
Everyone else, try to move these rocks!
Tok, Orthozes
Pururu, you rascal. You came outside
even after I said not to!
How many times do I have to tell you?
A lot of scary soldiers
will overrun this place soon!
I'll be fine, Dad. Mara, Aide!
Welcome back.
Good gracious, you have no right being so cute!
You're lucky you didn't inherit your dad's looks.
What about the other villages?
They went into hiding.
How was it?
Well... we've only earned two days' pay.
If we divide it between the three of us,
it'll probably only be one day's.
In either case, we can only slow the enemy down so much.
When are the coalition reinforcements going to arrive?
Three days at the earliest. The enemy's main force is 5,000. Ours is 2,000.
If the coalition forces don't come, it's over.
I see. Bjor's army is too fast!
As expected.
Fract...
So... what should we do next, Mara?
Apparently, this village is going
to be our forward defensive line.
How are we supposed to hold here?
Why don't you ask
one of local elders about that?
In the last war, this was a major base for guerrilla operations.
That was how we stopped their advance.
Withdraw!
Here's what I think. There's a better way
to proceed than trying to stopping them.
A better way?
Yeah. Let's kill their commander.
But how?
We were this close to nailing him that night.
So... I think we can sneak into his bedroom
and catch him by surprise.
What do you think?
That begs the question
of who is going to do it.
I'll do it myself.
A muscleman like you?
Forget it! It's impossible!
Is defending this place for three days
against that horde more likely, then?!
Do you even understand our current situation?!
What are you saying?
We have orders from high command!
That's not why I'm fighting.
What are you talking about?
We're mercenaries, remember?
U-Unlike you guys, I... I'm not...
This is our job, and we're getting paid for it!
Plenty of people here would gladly
take that money instead of you!
Our job is to take others' lives
and keep our own. Isn't that clear enough?
I'm not very smart, so I can't understand even something that simple!
What the hell is wrong with that idiot?!
I'm going to strangle him, I swear!
Something has changed his mood, Mara.
You called me by name.
Shouldn't I do that?
Assassinate the Generalissimo.
Even you think Dino's plan is better?
I don't want this beautiful land to be exposed to war again.
But why should you do it?
That's what I thought
when I saw Dino and Pururu.
Let me go.
Aide...
You're crazy, you know that?
Oh, Mara!
Pururu, where's your dad?
Sleeping already.
I think Dad started hating his work
after he was no longer able to grow vegetables.
I see.
The enemy is approaching.
Please take your position.
Farmers were poor enough even without a war.
Yet they attack at a time like this.
I guess farmers really mean nothing to them.
Dino...
One way or another, we need you, Dino.
Besides, Aide is going to carry out
the plan you came up with.
Aide is?
Yeah. To ensure its success,
he has to go alone.
You say my face looks like his, right?
Maybe it does, but we only
ever got a glimpse of it.
Don't tell me... you plan
to pose as Fract himself?
I know I can't fool people
that know him personally.
But I might just get an opportunity.
That's dangerous!
I want to know who I am.
Perhaps I'll be able to learn more
if I get close to Fract.
At least... I hope that when I see his face,
I'll have a revelation or something.
So what if you do learn something?
What does it matter now?
And... if there isn't any revelation?!
What if there's no meaning to it?!
Maybe...
there is no meaning to it.
But I'll still go there.
That's my resolve now.
I'm going too.
I have a good justification for it.
You don't.
Aide...
Even when I was so close to my family,
I couldn't protect them when they needed it.
Staying here is simply too painful.
Too difficult.
That's why I raised Pururu to be
an independent girl who can take care of herself.
I thought it was better for Pururu that way,
to help her survive in our world.
That's why... I'm going with you!
So? You got a problem with that?
You're the real thing.
A true warrior, who stands up to his fate.
Idiot! What are you talking about?
You only realized it just now?
Dino, I'm sorry about earlier.
I was presumptuous.
Heh. Don't worry. I kill people for money.
That's the hard truth.
Do it for my family?
People all over the world people use the same excuse for killing each other. What about that?
I don't want to think about it.
I fight to bring an end to this war.
Only those who started the war are at fault.
That... That, I will never be able to forgive.
Yes, that's why I'm going.
Good! Then I'll go too!
I'll do it too.
After all, we're brothers in arms, right?
Pururu...
Family, huh?
That will never change, no matter the era.
But... Pururu might end up all alone.
She won't be alone.
They'll always be together,
from anywhere in the world.
But I have nothing...
and no one.
Don't you die! You have me, all right?!
Dad, why won't you hold me
in your hands anymore?
My hands are too dirty for that.
I... I...
It's fine. They don't have to be clean.
I love your hands anyway.
Pururu... Make sure to hide when they come.
Can we go now?
Yeah.
Aide, let's hurry!
Pururu, you'll be safe for now.
Generalissimo Fract!
The first battalion of the Orthozes invasion
has encountered guerrilla sabotage,
at a point two kilometers from the border.
Apparently, our forces are unable to make any progress.
Orthozes was a lucky country.
The aggressive expansion of Bjor, solely through military might,
allowed the kings and people of every country
to unite in their anxiety
into an unprecedented military alliance.
Whenever a military unit from Bjor was discovered,
it was crushed without hesitation.
The country of Bjor was driven to the point
where its very survival was in doubt.
Fract was loved as long
as he continued to win.
But now, he was universally criticized by his own people
as a dictator who has turned
the world against their nation.
How should we proceed, Generalissimo?
Hurry up and break through.
I've said it time and time again.
There is no other path than victory
for our nation of Bjor!
"For our nation?"
No, I'm sure you were
just talking about yourself.
Yes, it's the twilight of your dictatorship.
What... should I do?
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
Why can't time be captured in a bottle?
I guess we all grow up before we realize it
The sunset leaves shadows on your vacant desk
The sun goes down as if giving up
A dictionary full of pencil markings
QC
Topper3000, Uchuu
Encoding
anonymous
And torn into jagged pieces
The wish that was scattered into the galaxy that day
Will surely rise again, searching for you
Following an answer that no one knows,
even if it's hazy now
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Someday, it will shine straight toward the stars
Preview
In order to assassinate Generalissimo Fract,
we three infiltrate Keal Castle.
The key to everything,
the flow of fate will now be uncovered.
What destiny awaits Fract?
Guided along this path, is Aide both
the perpetrator and the victim of his crime?
Kingdom of Chaos: Born to Kill.
Chapter 4: Fract.
Why are people born? Why do they die?