Long ago, this world was a beautiful paradise.
In this world of balance, people, demons, and gods all feared and respected each other equally.
All of them lived with the hope and belief
that this way of life would last forever.
That was Neverland.
Situated in the southwestern part of the Old Continent was the mountain kingdom of Bjor.
The man who ascended as the thirteenth Generalissimo of Bjor, Fract,
turned this country
into a warmongering nation.
Who if not we, the Bjor, deserves a place
under the sun on top of the Old Continent?
He was a natural leader and politician,
so he took command of Bjor's army
and invaded Orthozes,
a neighboring country in the north.
Although soundly defeated in his first campaign,
Fract profited from the experience.
He rebuilt his army the next year and
moved into Harbus and Glok in the south.
And then on to Axes, Elflore, and Bihlimere.
Before people realized it,
Bjor had occupied half of the continent.
This was the reality. An iron fist, ruling with brutality and fear.
Under Fract's rule,
the Old Continent was soaked in blood.
Finally, to rectify his past failure, Fract prepared to invade the last country on his border,
the agricultural nation of Orthozes.
Rich in produce,
this country was never at risk of famine.
It was a rare place where all creatures
lived in harmony with nature.
However, all they could do now was wait,
constantly in fear of Bjor's massed armies.
One man's lust for power
drags the world into chaos.
History has taught us that power
sustained by fear always leads to chaos.
This story is an episode from the lives
of those who stood up against this power.
The ones we think of as beautiful
Are not a simple coincidence or turn of fate
I know where I am, what I'm doing
And what I like most, I suppose
It's not simple, though
Show me your many sides!
I'll keep looking for you too
Not needed by one, necessary for another
In a city where buildings reflect light from all around
There's a place designated just for you
May you find it
May it shine for you
Bjor - Gulhearts Keal Castle
Generalissimo.
I apologize for arriving so early.
I saw you from outside, so...
What is it?
Our special border patrol unit
will engage the enemy at nightfall.
I'm aware.
I gave that order myself.
Yes. But your ministers want
your personal confirmation,
because they haven't seen you
in person at all lately.
I see.
I cannot afford to lose this next battle, either.
I was in the process of formulating our tactics.
I'm... worried that if you overwork yourself,
it may damage your health.
Kanon, I have long sought to own Orthozes.
Our country is an infertile,
rocky mountain range.
What did the country right next to us do
to receive such abundant natural wealth?
I was jealous of that.
You already control many countries
across this continent.
Why do you still need to go after Orthozes?
Is it because that country was the only one
that didn't bow to your father, the previous king?
Keep this conversation between us.
If I take Orthozes, I will be a king
who surpasses my father.
Orthozes - The Border
Even I get excited when I see the border!
Huh?
You don't look like you do.
Hm? Well, I suppose you become tougher
after you've been at war for as long as I have.
No, you always seem excited to me.
That's what I mean.
What was that?!
What are you implying?!
Well, this.
Where are you going?
We come from the mercenary headquarters
with orders to reinforce the border guard.
Mara, and two others.
Mara...
Y-You mean that Mara?
Pardon me. Please proceed.
Thank you.
I guess I'm a bit famous too, huh?
Aren't you just a mercenary like us?
Well, I've also been doing this
for a long time, right?
You must pay for the crimes
you have committed.
My... crimes?
It seems I fell asleep before finishing.
To preserve at least my current self,
I'm keeping a diary.
To grasp some thread linking me to my past.
That knight called Mara...
has a big heart and a strong will.
What could that leniency in her left eye mean?
Come on, move it!
This isn't war, just a slaughter of the helpless.
Are you all right?
Let's hurry up and end this.
C-Captain!
I'm not your captain anymore.
So... you weren't even going
to say goodbye to me?
N-No.
I... thought you might be busy, so...
Have you come to dislike me?
Go ahead, be honest.
Why would I...
You're the only one I could rely on.
That's why I called for you.
Since when have you had such a surprised face?
Come to my office later.
Hey, this is quite good. My usual morning
gruel is terrible, raw bugs and all.
Where's Mara?
Mara? Who knows?
It seems her previous regiment was stationed here,
so she probably knows a lot of local people.
Knows a lot of people?
You probably don't know anybody?
If you did, you could find out
about your past more easily.
Not knowing anyone at all is weird.
Starting today, the watch will be increased at all stations.
There's also a notice from headquarters.
Set a double watch on...
Set a double watch to respond
to any situation.
It's been a while.
Yeah. Well, have a seat now.
So... what do you want?
The situation on the border
is tenser than ever.
We expect the Bjor forces to begin
a full-scale invasion any time.
Their generalissimo
had long sought to occupy our country.
I've chosen a tough time...
to rejoin you.
They've organized a special elite battalion,
tasked with wiping out our outpost.
They're planning a guerrilla operation.
Is that why we're here?
Yes. If the entire Crimson Knights regiment starts moving, they'll notice it at once.
We can only foil their plans
with a tiny unit.
Mara, I'd like you to take on this assignment.
This is a dangerous mission,
so I'll have to confer with the others.
Mara, you haven't changed a bit.
I'm only asking you because of your talent.
You must understand,
you didn't grow up on your own.
Tell me, who should be thanked
for your upbringing?
You, Captain.
That's right.
So will you do this for me?
Yes.
Excuse me!
Mara, I hope this war ends soon.
Mara!
Oh, there you are!
What?
Aide was worried about you.
Really? I'm touched.
N-No. I was just wondering
what we're going to do next.
Just wait out time for a bit more here.
I've got one more minor thing to see to.
But when I'm back,
we're going to war!
All right, finally!
Time to make some good money!
Man, war changes people, doesn't it?
Well, excuse me!
I was like this before too.
That's not what I meant.
Gimme a break!
Aide, did you need something from me?
No, it's nothing.
What's his game, following Mara?
Well, Mara will be Mara,
always going alone.
What? Where'd he go?
Is this...
I might've stumbled on something incredible!
It is an honor to have you here, sir.
Generalissimo Fract came out here to commend you personally on your good work, Olb.
I-Is that true, sir?
I am most honored, Generalissimo!
Generalissimo?
Diversionary sabotage from this front-line base will play a major role in the upcoming battle.
United in their patriotism, the people of Orthozes
will become a force to be reckoned with.
But thanks to your front line sabotage work,
the enemy response will be disrupted.
In a war involving large armies,
both sides are bound to sustain heavy casualties.
Commander, I am moved by your
respect for people's lives.
You think I respect people's lives?
Y-Yes, sir... Since you were concerned with both sides' losses...
All I want is the rich land of Orthozes.
The number of civilians killed doesn't matter.
Y-Yes, sir, roger that!
Up there!
There!
Aide?!
Over there, get her!
Not so fast!
You're not getting away.
Over there!
Shit!
Where did she go?
It would appear I can see more than you.
Now, then. If you try something, you'll die here and now.
Nobody's coming to rescue you.
While I'm risking my life here,
Captain Cerona must still be
profiting from the war,
just like she did back then.
Go ahead and get this over with,
like you said you would!
What? Why are you in such a hu—
Mara, you'll be all right now.
Aide? But how?
I followed you.
I guess Dino did too.
Yeah. Pretty much. I went after you, though,
so where the hell were you?
Exactly opposite from where you were thrashing them.
I set out after Mara directly.
What happened, Mara?
Mara, you saw Generalissimo Fract up close, didn't you?
What was he like?
I see. That similar, huh?
Thank you for saving me.
I believe in you now, Aide.
The state of Bjor has conquered
most of the Old Continent.
To resist its expansion, the remaining countries formed a coalition.
Bjor now had to live with the fact that
the alliance was aiding Orthozes militarily.
A hurried meeting was called within Bjor.
The ministers had already reached a unanimous decision.
The Orthozes invasion army
would now be put on standby.
However...
We will invade Orthozes, as planned.
After coming this far,
is there anything we need to fear?
Our country chose the path of fighting.
We have always acted on the belief
that our nation can only have
a future by winning in battle.
If we choose to back off now,
our realm might crumble in an instant.
Have you ever considered that?!
Commander Fract's fiery speech
rekindled everyone's determination.
The result was a strong reminder
that a great empire
built by fighting cannot prosper
unless it continues to show off its strength.
With this, I will become a king
greater than my father.
Original Subtitles
Anime Blitz
Transcribed by
Techdamage
Translation Check & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
Why can't time be captured in a bottle?
I guess we all grow up before we realize it
The sunset leaves shadows on your vacant desk
The sun goes down as if giving up
A dictionary full of pencil markings
QC
Topper3000, Uchuu
Encoding
anonymous
And torn into jagged pieces
The wish that was scattered into the galaxy that day
Will surely rise again, searching for you
Following an answer that no one knows,
even if it's hazy now
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Someday, it will shine straight toward the stars
Preview
The Bjor armies finally cross into Orthozes.
Dino, the fighting man,
is a legendary guerrilla fighter
who has won many similar battles in the past.
But even he...
did not choose to fight willingly.
Now, memories from the time of parting
eat away at Dino's heart.
Kingdom of Chaos: Born to Kill.
Chapter 3: Dino.
Why are people born? Why do they die?