Long ago, this world was a beautiful paradise.
In this world of balance, people, demons, and gods all feared and respected each other equally.
All of them lived with the hope and belief
that this way of life would last forever.
That was Neverland.
Situated in the southwestern part of the Old Continent was the mountain kingdom of Bjor.
The man who ascended as the thirteenth Generalissimo of Bjor, Fract,
turned this country
into a warmongering nation.
Who if not we, the Bjor, deserves a place
under the sun on top of the Old Continent?
He was a natural leader and politician,
so he took command of Bjor's army
and invaded Orthozes,
a neighboring country in the north.
Although soundly defeated in his first campaign,
Fract profited from the experience.
He rebuilt his army the next year and
moved into Harbus and Glok in the south.
And then on to Axes, Elflore, and Bihlimere.
Before people realized it,
Bjor had occupied half of the continent.
This was the reality. An iron fist, ruling with brutality and fear.
Under Fract's rule,
the Old Continent was soaked in blood.
Finally, to rectify his past failure, Fract prepared to invade the last country on his border,
the agricultural nation of Orthozes.
Rich in produce,
this country was never at risk of famine.
It was a rare place where all creatures
lived in harmony with nature.
However, all they could do now was wait,
constantly in fear of Bjor's massed armies.
One man's lust for power
drags the world into chaos.
History has taught us that power
sustained by fear always leads to chaos.
This story is an episode from the lives
of those who stood up against this power.
The ones we think of as beautiful
Are not a simple coincidence or turn of fate
I know where I am, what I'm doing
And what I like most, I suppose
It's not simple, though
Show me your many sides!
I'll keep looking for you too
Not needed by one, necessary for another
In a city where buildings reflect light from all around
There's a place designated just for you
May you find it
May it shine for you
I am infinite.
I am the world.
I am chaos.
You will answer for your crimes.
Your sins in your previous life will be punished
by your deeds in your next life.
My greatness is bound...
to exceed yours by far!
No, mine is.
What?
Wh-What was that?
That's where the Generalissimo is.
Probably. Anyway, it's been going well so far.
But it's only the beginning, isn't it?
Yeah. Things are just starting.
Is everything on plan?
Yeah.
You two certainly do look alike,
don't you, Mr. Generalissimo?
We just might, Dino.
Did you...
say my name?
I shouldn't have?
No, it's not that.
I just thought it's amazing
you remembered it.
Well, we're brothers in arms,
with the same goal now.
That's what I mean.
Right, brothers and sisters in arms.
Brothers, huh...
Yeah.
Sure.
Hey, things have been weird lately.
Hey!
Tsk, guess this is as far
as our charade gets us.
What should we do? Attack?
There's just two of them.
Hey, are you listening?
Who the hell are you, anyway?
Will you let me try to handle this?
Are you sure?
We have no choice.
You lowlifes!
Who do you think you're talking to?
I-It was you, Generalissimo?
W-We apologize.
Wh-Why are you here at this time of night?
How about, "None of your business,"
huh?
P-Pardon me, sir!
Well now, it seems we were right
to put our money on him.
Attaboy!
Let's go.
Huh? Ah, right... Yes, sir!
I hope I made the right impression.
You nailed it!
Right, Mara?
Uh? Yes, that's right.
But...
Generalissimo...
What's this?
What? Am I still dreaming?
No, it's not a dream.
I am you.
You can't run away anymore.
Wh-What did you say?
You can't escape.
Listen here, you slackers.
If it's the enemy, it doesn't matter whether you kill just one person or massacre them all.
Is that clear?
I have to snap out of this.
I...
I can't be wrong!
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
It's him, after all.
Tsk. That's right.
This guy who looks just like you
is responsible for starting this war.
If we defeat him, we defeat the lot of them.
Yeah, it'll be over right away.
No doubt about it.
Yeah.
If I defeat him...
I'll go this way.
And I'll go that way.
Hey, Mara!
Dino.
Look...
Look after Mara.
Okay...
I got you covered.
Mara!
If I defeat Fract,
it'll be over.
Feels good to work in a team.
If I defeat him... If I defeat him...
Generalissimo?
Generalissimo!
What made you get up at this hour?
Don't worry. I won't hurt you.
You took out your old clothes.
I'm sorry.
Could you take me to Fract?
This man...
The Generalissimo?
Looks like these are the soldiers' barracks.
That means he's even higher up.
Actually, why are you following me?
Ah, I should've gone with Aide, after all.
Why, if you have me?!
No...
Wh-What are you talking about?
Really, you're so boorish.
You don't get it, girl. I'm demon spawn!
Come on! I know you're not!
I saw your child, so I know you ain't one!
Believe it or not, I'm demon spawn!
It's the enemy!
Ah? L-Looks dangerous.
Get them!
I suppose.
Hey, leave it to me this time.
You go find Fract and deal with him.
Don't worry.
The man you're in love with isn't Fract.
Dino? What a cool line!
Shut up! Go already.
Our Aide is different.
He's not a bad guy!
Morons!
He's not like your commander!
Aide?
So... did you find Fract?
I did.
Mara!
It's him!
Aide?
He was right here.
Fra...
Did you seriously come after me
without knowing how I look?
What a foolish endeavor.
A-Aide?
Another me again.
Is it a dream?
Probably not.
Generalissimo!
Please run!
Kanon...
Y-You...
You bastard...
I'll kill you!
What? Is it magic?
Who the hell are you?
I am you.
I am what you are.
Why have you been pestering me?
I am you!
What are you talking about?!
Think you have the guts to do it?!
Why...
Why is this happening?
I can't be defeated now!
I remember now. This is where I died.
I am infinite.
I am the world.
I am chaos.
You are Fract.
You committed a crime.
You led the world into chaos,
and that chaos turned
the continent into hell.
Yours is a massive sin.
Your sins in your previous life will be punished
by your deeds in your next life.
Forever.
No way. My punishment is to be killed
by my own reincarnated self?
What's worse...
it is eternal.
Is there really no way to avoid this fate?
Your sins in your previous life will be punished
by your deeds in your next life.
Forever.
Did you find Fract?
This too?
Mara!
Aide?
Very well. I'll kill you...
as much as I want, then.
It's him?
Forever.
So you are me?
I remember it now.
I have...
to kill my own self.
That means I just need to defeat you...
It'll be over then!
I just have...
to kill you!
You...
Why?
Why are you so strong?
You are ultimately powerless against me in this world.
A man cannot fight his fate.
No way.
There's no...
way!
Suffer in eternity!
I defeated even my own father!
I'll put an end to this...
with my own hands!
Watch out!
I win!
What?
N-No way.
Don't give up.
Lord Fract, run!
Listen. Hear me out.
I am you.
Tsk. So what of it?
Why are you telling me now?
I have to kill you.
But that's just what he wants.
I don't think people are that stupid.
Wh-What's the point of saying that?
This punishment is eternal.
Nothing will ever change.
If so...
I'll cut this fate off myself!
I'm in control of my own destiny.
Your punishment is eternal. Eternal.
This punishment is inescapable,
because of the great suffering
you inflicted in your previous life.
Inescapable?
Is it really inescapable?
If you sacrifice your ego,
your soul might be saved.
However, if you believe that you only exist
in this cycle of time,
you'll never be able to liberate your mind.
Still, you might eventually
find peace in this cycle.
I see. In that case, would you please let me try?
To save myself, to save people.
If I manage to save the world, will I...
The one who has hitherto only sought to destroy it, now wants to save it?
I never thought that would be possible.
The human world doesn't change that easily.
No...
it can change.
Then if I fail to change it,
feel free punish me again, forever.
You people really are stupid creatures.
Well, that could be interesting.
Aide!
Fract!
Sorry.
I see.
Did you get him, Aide?
He did... He really did!
Aide, this means...
No, it's only the beginning.
It's only the beginning.
Lend me a hand.
Fract sent messengers to the allied forces,
stating his intention to surrender.
No one objected
to the decision that he alone should be held responsible for the past great war.
The way people now talked about Fract...
It seems...
people can change, after all.
The fighting was over,
and people were filled with joy.
The end of the chaos was finally in sight.
The common interests of the people came out on top and stopped the dictator.
Or so people said.
As for Fract himself,
he was, without a doubt,
sentenced to capital punishment.
But that wasn't the end of it.
The jubilation was short-lived, as the continent was soon overrun by chaos once again.
Unintentionally, the allied nations
began feuding among themselves
over the territories formerly controlled by Bjor.
With or without a dictator,
people's combativeness never disappeared.
Moreover, while Fract was awaiting his sentence, he suddenly disappeared without a trace.
As if he had never been there
in the first place.
This news spread across the continent,
becoming a legend,
until... it too disappeared.
Hurry up!
Sure, sure.
No, listen to me.
I know what I'm saying!
"Why did you stand up?
Right, we stood up to protect this country."
Oh? You kneow a lot for a child.
The beauty of the simple people
is this humility.
Actually, I also went to war
to defend this land.
Good, good.
So did you understand everything, Sogo?
Right, 'course I did.
Tell me, did you really understand?
They want to become mercenaries.
Y-Yeah, sure...
Come on!
Can't you go any faster?
Aide!
So, everyone, I hope for
a productive partnership!
Sure!
Translation & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
Why can't time be captured in a bottle?
I guess we all grow up before we realize it
The sunset leaves shadows on your vacant desk
The sun goes down as if giving up
A dictionary full of pencil markings
QC
Topper3000, Uchuu
Encoding
anonymous
And torn into jagged pieces
The wish that was scattered into the galaxy that day
Will surely rise again, searching for you
Following an answer that no one knows,
even if it's hazy now
Someday, it will shine straight toward the stars
So... why are you two following me?
I'm no longer even Aide.
That's fine! We know the truth,
and that's enough.
Right. Didn't I say we're brothers?
But let me tell you. This goal of yours,
to save the world and all, is unrealistic!
Exactly! And how do you even know these guys want you saving them?
Oh? It's a tail!
I made a promise...
It's Mara.
to protect her.
What?
Tsk! Seriously, her?
What's this about? Hey!
We're just saying you're an idiot.
Why's that?
Let's go already.
Heh? So you won't even tell me?
You'll find out as we go.
Yeah, you just might.
Only "might"? Gimme a break.
Thus, this story is just one
of the many legends of this continent,
where there's always a new legend
to forge with your own hands.
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs