Long ago, this world was a beautiful paradise.
In this world of balance, people, demons, and gods all feared and respected each other equally.
All of them lived with the hope and belief
that this way of life would last forever.
That was Neverland.
Situated in the southwestern part of the Old Continent was the mountain kingdom of Bjor.
The man who ascended as the thirteenth Generalissimo of Bjor, Fract,
turned this country
into a warmongering nation.
Who if not we, the Bjor, deserves a place
under the sun on top of the Old Continent?
He was a natural leader and politician,
so he took command of Bjor's army
and invaded Orthozes,
a neighboring country in the north.
Although soundly defeated in his first campaign,
Fract profited from the experience.
He rebuilt his army the next year and
moved into Harbus and Glok in the south.
And then on to Axes, Elflore, and Bihlimere.
Before people realized it,
Bjor had occupied half of the continent.
This was the reality. An iron fist, ruling with brutality and fear.
Under Fract's rule,
the Old Continent was soaked in blood.
Finally, to rectify his past failure, Fract prepared to invade the last country on his border,
the agricultural nation of Orthozes.
Rich in produce,
this country was never at risk of famine.
It was a rare place where all creatures
lived in harmony with nature.
However, all they could do now was wait,
constantly in fear of Bjor's massed armies.
One man's lust for power
drags the world into chaos.
History has taught us that power
sustained by fear always leads to chaos.
This story is an episode from the lives
of those who stood up against this power.
The ones we think of as beautiful
Are not a simple coincidence or turn of fate
I know where I am, what I'm doing
And what I like most, I suppose
It's not simple, though
Show me your many sides!
I'll keep looking for you too
Not needed by one, necessary for another
In a city where buildings reflect light from all around
There's a place designated just for you
May you find it
May it shine for you
So it's you.
You will be punished for the crimes
of your previous life.
You will be restored by the darkness.
Orthozes
Grezea
This scenery... I...
Please stop!
Wench, don't get cocky! Demon spawn!
C'mon, out with it!
I don't know anything! Please believe me!
Well then, sh-should we kill you?
A-Anything but that...
What's the point of leaving
you guys to live here?
Kill me, but let this child live!
Sh-Shut up!
What're you doing?!
What's the meaning of this?!
Wh-Who are you?!
You don't look like you're from this country.
P-Please help us!
Don't leave us!
Why did this guy come here?
Please! Do something!
Get outta the way!
You villains. You'd even go as far as hurting women and children?
Hurry up and get him, you slackers!
You'll be all right now.
Thank you very much!
Why, you...
Ge... Generalissimo... But why?
What?
It seems...
I know it.
This country.
Cathedral
Re... Re... Re...
Let me go! Now!
Hey.
So... why were you following me?
Really, you think I'll tell you, just like that?
So?
Shut up!
I know about you!
Around here I'm-
Is that true? If so,
tell me, please!
I need to know!
Ugh! That hurts!
You're just another money-hungry outsider!
What now?
Forgive me. I misunderstood.
I thought you'd know more about me.
You sure say strange things.
It's like you don't even know who you are.
That's right. I've lost my memory.
I-I see. You don't remember anything?
Yeah.
My name is Aide. That's all I know.
Nothing else?
Well, it doesn't matter.
Here, you only have to be strong. Like when you fought in the street earlier, you know?
That was awesome!
All right, I'll show you where you can
find work. You need some, right?
You don't seem like a bad person to me.
C'mon, this way.
I see, so the men of this city are all...
Kind of. Those that were still alive ran
for the hills. Only the rabble remained.
And yet, since we don't know when they'll attack,
only outside volunteers gather here.
People prefer not to see
the problem at times like this.
They only show up
when there's money to be made.
This city is more and more depressing.
All because of that stupid war. Damn it all.
Well, I guess there's no point
telling you all that,
because the only thing
you remember is your name.
Yeah.
My name's Leo. I make my living by recruiting mercenaries for this country.
Here, try going to this place.
Show them this piece of paper.
They should find you an assignment pretty easily.
Well, it'll be a battle assignment, of course.
I see. How much do I owe you?
Don't worry about it.
You're different from the others.
I see.
Thank you.
See ya around!
Probably that?
Let's go take a look.
Still, I'm sure I've seen
his face somewhere... Ah!
I forgot to tell him about the test!
Oh well, a guy like Aide
ought to do fine with it.
I-Is there something?
S-Something you might need
at such a lowly place?
What's the deal with you?
You're not from Bjor, are you?
Come on, move.
Get out of here! Shoo!
Well, I got this.
Oh, I see. You should've said so sooner.
Come with me.
I don't know how strong
you are, but be careful.
Some get killed here before they realize it.
Quaking in your boots, huh?
What happens here?
What, no one told you?
We use this place to find strong people
and enlist them in the army.
That way, we both make some money.
You understand? All these people
are here because they want money.
They'd put their lives on the line for it.
Only those who are stupid enough gather here.
I see.
Huh? You don't sound very enthusiastic.
No, I am.
Go and take on the guy in the back.
The back?
If you beat him, I'll get you a job.
All right.
That is, if you can win.
What is this place?
There's still more?
Are you even listening?
Hey, I've proved my strength,
so you'll have to pay me double the rate.
There's no point defeating any more of them.
In a real battle, having a normal man is little better than nothing. But if you have me...
Pardon me, but I'm fine with the normal rate,
and I need to defeat you...
to get this job.
Oh? Think you're strong?
No, I think I need to fight you to find out.
You're really clueless, aren't you, pal?
This guy is Dino, a local celebrity of sorts.
The reason we can keep doing it here
is because he kills off the intruders, without breaking a sweat. Easily.
He may be big, but his punches aren't all that painful.
They start hurting more later.
Excuse me for a second.
Some idiot's challenging Dino!
No way.
There's Dino, big as ever.
But who is that know-nothing?
We don't like outsiders like you
walking around here all high and mighty.
So what's your name?
Aide.
It's Aide.
Tsk. What a stone-faced dude.
They're laughing at me,
putting me up against someone like him.
You seem to have a big attitude as well.
Anyway, you're the one
with the biggest mouth here.
That man!
Why don't you fight back?
Are you only good at talking?
Enemy patrols!
The enemy is on high alert!
Hurry up and flee!
You should go too.
What about you?
I can't protect this country
if I run away at the sight of an enemy.
I see.
Sorry about your forehead.
Blood?
What is that guy?
Dammit! Those bastards take
our fields whenever they want!
They're important fields too, you know!
I wonder why they're not pestering us today. Something stinks!
Damn right!
Hey, you think so too, right, bro?
Why won't you say anything, huh?
You're new here.
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Another outsider in for the money, huh?!
That's all you think this country is!
No, I...
This is my country, before anything else!
We'll manage even without the likes of you!
Yeah!
We'll do just fine protecting this country!
We'll do it ourselves!
You all right?
Why didn't you do anything to him?
What they say is true.
I see.
This is...
Are you really...
A Bjornian?
Found you!
Who the hell are you?!
We'll talk later. Look, we need to run!
Run? What from?
This way!
So won't you tell us who you are?
I haven't had a single drink yet!
Let's go!
So... you're Dino. You're quite famous.
Mostly for how good you are at killing people.
I don't do it because I like it.
I have my own circumstances.
And what about you?
Hey, you, a lady's talking to you!
Say something!
That guy...
What about him?
That's Fract.
Huh? Bjor's Generalissimo?
Look at his right shoulder.
Isn't that a gecko?
That's... B-But how did their Generalissimo
end up here in the middle of the night?
Are you stupid?
Yeah, he's stupid all right,
but he has his face as well.
Well, I didn't know what the Generalissimo
looked like to begin with.
Seriously, what are you?
Well, the real one obviously wouldn't be here.
So I'm thinking he's an enemy defector.
I...
don't know.
Huh?
What do you mean, "You don't know"?
Forgive me. I... don't know who I am.
Did you... lose your memory?
Yeah. Can't say he strikes me as a bad guy,
even if he is the enemy.
That'd damn better be true!
If you lie to me, I'll crush you here and now!
Yeah. Please do.
My memory fades as soon as it's recorded.
It's the truth.
It's... the truth.
All right.
I'll believe you for now.
Then why were you trying
to enlist as a soldier here?
When I first arrived in this area,
a child guided me here.
Leo, correct?
I was also a client of his.
Well, I simply needed money.
Yeah. I still remember that name.
I need money as well.
What's wrong with you two?
Talking about money at a time like this.
Do you even understand that his zeal
brought all this upon our country?
Our country...
I know it only means money to you two,
but I, and the others, won't stand for it!
I see.
What do you mean, "I see"?
By the way, what's your name?
Do you at least know your name?
My name is the only thing I know. It's Aide.
Hm... Aide, huh? I'm Mara.
Mara of the Crimson Knights.
You know them? The Crimson...
Right, how would you possibly know?
You should know them, though,
Killing Machine Dino.
I'm not a killing machine!
Does that mean you're going to forget about us by tomorrow, Aide?
I don't know. However, this country
seems familiar, for some reason.
It's as if I've been here before.
Well, maybe you were just born here?
Born here and kidnapped by them.
They tortured you and you lost your memory.
It could happen, I think.
Don't bother thinking
with your lack of intelligence.
More importantly,
have you noticed that the enemy
has been incredibly secretive today?
It's like they're preparing for something big.
So they were enemy soldiers?
What? Did you do something?
Did you attack them?
I don't remember it well.
Aide, if you're on our side,
you can't attack them. Ever.
So... is this war happening because of me?
Could be.
Stay quiet already!
It's no use trying to figure out
the reason right now.
But wouldn't you like to be the one
responsible for saving our country?
How about it, Aide?
Yeah, maybe you're right.
I could give it a try.
If so, try to do one more thing.
Don't forget about us.
Okay?
Sure.
Gulhearts Keal Castle
Isn't that enough?
Huh? Yeah, I suppose.
Hey, hurry up and spill it already.
That's right. You know, don't you?
When are they going to attack?
Come on, I really don't know.
Still saying that?
Hey, it's the Generalissimo!
A kid, huh?
Well, I'll be! Isn't it Aide?
What are you doing here?
What is this shrimp talking about?
Hey, Aide!
Be silent, kid!
It's you, isn't it, Aide?
Shut up!
Why won't you say anything?
Kill him.
Yes, sir!
Will... do.
Original Subtitles
Anime Blitz
Transcribed by
Techdamage
Translation Check & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
Why can't time be captured in a bottle?
I guess we all grow up before we realize it
The sunset leaves shadows on your vacant desk
The sun goes down as if giving up
A dictionary full of pencil markings
QC
Topper3000, Uchuu
Encoding
anonymous
And torn into jagged pieces
The wish that was scattered into the galaxy that day
Will surely rise again, searching for you
Following an answer that no one knows,
even if it's hazy now
Presented by
Orphan Fansubs
Someday, it will shine straight toward the stars
Preview
Mara's formation is the Crimson Knights.
They're the front-line border patrol unit.
The three mercenaries work for garrison unit commander Cerona.
She raised Mara and now needs them to conduct a military operation.
Kingdom of Chaos: Born to Kill.
Chapter 2: Mara.
Why are people born? Why do they die?