Hi!
I'm Kasumi. 15 years old.
I'm Miki, 17 years old. Kasumi's older sister.
This is Shoko. Miki and her
recently became good friends.
We're
Super Real Mahjong:
🖤Kasumi🖤Miki🖤Shoko
Nice to meet you!
Super Real Mahjong:
🖤Kasumi🖤Miki🖤Shoko
Nice to meet you!
Kasumi, for how long are you gonna sleep?
Get up soon!
Ah! Always interrupting it
on the most interesting spot!
You'll be late for school!
Fine!
I'm awake, you hear?
Hello! I'm in my third year of middle school. Kurizawa Kasumi.
A maiden born on September 18th.
Blood type - A.
Ah! But just because I have A type blood,
you shouldn't assume
that I'm a serious and tough type myself!
Eh? The boy I've seen in my dream?
I couldn't quite make out his face yet. Mama just keeps interrupting it at the most interesting moment!
Still, I hope it becomes true one day...
And that's it!
Good morning!
Good morning.
I prepared toasts for you.
Okay!
What's with the cheerful looks?
You dreamt about having a date again?
Yeah, that's what happened.
So, how far did you advance today? Did you kiss him?
W-What do you mean by that?!
It was a dream! A dream!
The maiden's aspirations. First fantasies - kiss!
My, my, Kasumi.
You shouldn't confuse dreams and reality.
If you spend your morning driveling,
you'll be late for school!
Sure, sure!
Ah! Hold it, you! Aren't those mine?
Please, let me borrow them!
I can't! Those are the high-tech fashion!
Why not, just this once?
It's 8 o'clock already!
Yeah!
I know!
Will you get there in time?
I'll be alright, because...
I'm off!
Ah...
Really, why does this happen every time?
You're still there?
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Okay! I'm off!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Morning!
Good morning, Yoshiko!
Hey-hey, did you do your English homework today?
Oh, you can be sure of that! In my highly admired teacher's class, I can't afford embarrassing myself!
Well, I guess I'll have to ask for a favor as usual...
Ah! You haven't done your homework again?
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Oh come on! On the way home,
I'll buy you some orange juice or something!
Just please let me peek into your notebook!
Ah... How about you try one more time?
Then, what would you say
to eating french fries together?
Alright! I'm taking it!
Thank you very much!
The school that I attend is a middle school
for girls only, attached to a university!
I have a ton of friends here,
so every single day I'm as happy as I can get!
Still, it's after school when I get even more fired up!
"Youth spent on the court..."
Is not exactly my cup of tea.
Still, it always feels great to work up a good sweat!
Zetattelia
And after tennis, I usually go with my friends
to the Zetattelia to grab a bite.
Ah! Michael J. Fox!
That's right! I'm a huge fan of his!
This photo is simply irresistible!
You should see how tough I acted the other day!
I told them "Leave this to me!"
Eh? No way!
Did he just stare right at me?
I can also play just a tiny bit of piano.
When playing it, I imagine myself
in the middle of a huge meadow.
It's such a wonderfully pacifying feeling!
I love all kinds of flowers -
like lilac or sweet pea. And soaproot too!
That's why, when the spring
is drawing near, I'm always full of beans!
Right, right.
If we're talking about things I like - animals!
Prairie dogs and sea otters are my favorite!
When I look at all these fluffy
and cute animals, the time flies by!
I really want a boyfriend who'd embrace me
kindly like this. Who'd be like a big brother to me!
And then, I won't be oversleeping in the morning ever again.
I'd be waking up like clockwork,
wanting to see him sooner!
Right?
Eh? You're kidding, right?
I forgot to introduce my sister!
As you can see, her habit of occupying the phone for hours on end is a constant source of irritation for mom.
Naturally, for me as well.
No! No...
Hello? Miki? What's going on there?
Sorry, sorry. Kasumi interrupted me.
I'll call you some other time.
Really, what's wrong with you, Kasumi?
Your long calls inconvenience everyone!
For instance, how would we know
if a boy decides to dial me?
I don't suppose you mean the guy from your dream?
You gave him your number already?
Hey, sister.
Yes?
What does it mean when a boy
stares at a girl for a long time?
Ah? Sid something happen, after all? Do tell.
It's just that I made eye contact
with some boy I didn't know at Zetattelia today...
Could it be... Oh, cut it!
Because Kasumi always gets carried away like this,
she won't get a boyfriend even in a thousand years!
Hey! Miki here.
Today, I want to tell you a couple of things about me.
Let's see... I'm a second year student
in a high school for girls.
Libra born on October 5th.
My blood type is O.
Ah?
Who's there?
You unruly thing!
What are you thinking of?
Today as well, in the refreshing sea breeze and dazzling morning sun, I'm off to enjoy myself!
Well, that's how I would've preferred it.
In the morning, same as everyone else,
I take the train to school.
But this daily jolting in an overcrowded train
is already driving me crazy!
That is not to say I dislike the school.
Ouch!
Well, that's kinda how it goes time and again.
You get it?
My preference for free time is swimming in the pool.
I really like this feeling of being completely relaxed.
Stylishness is the girl's privilege!
I can be pretty finicky about it.
After all, you never know who'll see you today.
I can't afford appearing unsightly.
I also like wandering through the town.
Being surrounded by a lot of people
is somehow reassuring for me.
I guess I really am a people person.
That's why I also want you
to look at me at all times.
Sometimes, when wandering around alone,
I wind up at all sorts of stores.
But because my pocket money is rather tight,
I don't go beyond looking at goods.
Ah... I wonder if there's ever a good person,
who'd buy me everything I want?
I'm getting carried away a bit.
Welcome.
Hey, wait!
Get this!
Hey, you!
I also watch movies pretty often.
I don't ever miss the love story flicks.
I suppose I'm quite a bit of a romantic.
This is no good! What should I do
if I end up being unable to sleep at night?
However...
If I can do this, I don't mind
watching horrors sometimes too.
It seems, I can do reasonably well in sports,
so I don't try to push myself too hard.
I don't particularly fancy being all sweaty.
If I had to choose, I'd rather be fashionable,
always on the forward edge of trends.
Wearing things that suit me.
Come to think of it, there's just this one thing I'm so passionate about right now, it's embarrassing, even.
Hey, are you alone?
Fancy drinking some tea with me?
I'm sorry...
I...
So?
Don't you feel lonely
playing this arcade all by yourself?
Nothing...
Yes! Go, go! That way! Good!
Go!
That's right. I'm head over heels
for video games these days.
Even if I know it's embarrassing,
it's just not something I could stop doing!
I completely forgot about Shoko!
She's my best friend and we're really close-knit!
She's light-hearted, but despite that,
still considerably smart and fun to hang out with.
I'm sorry! This wasn't on purpose.
Excuse me!
Right, even if her clumsiness
is embarrassing sometimes,
I super-enjoy being around her!
Well, introduction time!
My name is Shoko.
Miki and I were classmates in middle school.
We both love the sea a great deal.
But while Miki says she likes the summer sea the most,
my choice is the autumn sea.
As I walk along the ocean at dusk,
bathing in the gentle sunlight...
What's going on?
Let's go already!
My birthday is on December 10th.
If we believe what my mom says,
it was snowing heavily on the day I was born.
Perhaps that is why I'm so fair-skinned?
I'm also a member of the cheerleading club.
My school has a very active sports division,
so we're a mighty busy club.
In summer, it's hot, but we have to shout loudly.
In winter, it's cold, but we still have to bare our legs.
I can't stand it, honestly!
But in the end, the match
is what matters the most, right?
When I see someone downcast,
or a child who doesn't look cheerful,
I just can't help cheering on them more and more!
After all, nobody likes the depressed people!
See? Everyone is cheerful after all!
Being cheerful is the best!
Ah! You there, are you fretting over something?
Then I'll cheer you on!
Right, right. I go shopping in my free time.
Toy stores are my favorite!
I suppose it's childish?
Still, I'm also an avid reader.
Yes.
Be it Tanith Lee, or Ohara Mariko.
Right now, I'm going through Salinger's
the Catcher in the Rye​.
I think I'll also let you sneak a peek
at this dream of mine.
Help me! Somebody!
No! Let me go!
Wow...
Eh? What's going on? This guy is definitely weird.
Well, why not?
After all, I love strong and sturdy guys
who step in to protect me.
You, who I made fun of,
you'll protect me, won't you?
Ah, right, right! Here's my another best friend - Pal.
He's still a cute little kitten.
What is it, Pal? You want to play?
Here, try to catch this!
Hey, Pal, get back here!
What a mischievous child you are!
Fine...
Look at this!
A very bad guy looking to disrupt the peace on earth!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, you!
Ah... I guess it'll be a while
till I get a boyfriend if I keep acting like this.
Still, I hope you understand.
I want to fall in love too!
Oh, enough of that already, Shoko!
Why not?
I think Miki is the funniest when she does that!
Because now she would really start doing it!
What am I hearing from our dear Kasumi?
Still, what I want is a kind boyfriend
who'd be like big brother to me.
What about you, Miki?
I wouldn't stand for it
if he's just kind and nothing more.
I need someone who'd comply with my whims,
but would still scold me when I'm in the wrong.
I'd hate to hang out with someone so mundane.
You may think it's a bit whimsical,
but I'd like a superhero.
What does that mean?
Well, someone sturdy
and with a strong sense of justice...
Oh no, you're watching too much TV!
Did you like it?
Did that help you understand our hearts?
If you'd like to know us better...
Ah!
We'll be waiting for you in the game!
Bonus scene!
🖤Kasumi🖤Miki🖤Shoko's Super HD Mahjong: Part 1
Hey, hey, Miki!
Yes?
I'm getting pretty tired of playing strip mahjong.
Boy, do I have some news to ease your grief...
Eh?
It's finally out!
The ultimate mahjong!
Boasting endless progression,
the latest Super Real Mahjong!
Is there a hidden pitfall to this?
Just you watch.
Wow! You're so strong in this game!
But you still have some more layers to go through!
So? So? Isn't it great?
This doesn't make any sense!
Bonus scene!
🖤Kasumi🖤Miki🖤Shoko's Super HD Mahjong: Part 2
Commander! Our forces are wiped out!
A-At this rate...
I'll have to end this all with a harakiri!
It's too early for that!
Don't you have something more to do before you die?
Ah! That's right.
After I kill my sister, I can die myself!
Hold it with rash decisions!
Don't fret! We'll just use our army's ultimate weapon!
S-Surely, you can't mean that...
Ta-da!
Raws by [Orphan-raw]
Translated by Perevodildo