Hey, what about that person?
Eh, where?
Look, there.
Wow, he's cool!
Told you the boys in university are in a league of their own.
Yes, yes!
That cockscomb is the best!
Is that really what you'd call your type?
Oh?
What are you thinking of, you two?!
We're here for a meeting with friends, remember?
Let's go there quickly!
Sure, sure, very well.
Really, sis, you just don't know when to stop.
Somehow, this part of school
feels so lonely...
Really!
I wonder what is this place.
You no longer know where we are?
Yes, the pamphlet doesn't mention
anything of the kind.
Ah!
Mahjong club
It's a mahjong club!
Oh my!
Let's go ask there.
B-But it looks kinda creepy.
There's no such place
mentioned anywhere in the pamphlet.
Whatever! Let's go, let's go!
Um, excuse us?
Is anyone here?
Sorry? Hello?
Seems like nobody's there.
This room makes me uneasy...
Let's ask somewhere else!
What can I help you with?
My! Such a cute Rabbit!
It looks like we got lost in the building.
We're looking for our friends.
Ah, that's good, that's good!
Oh, by the way, young ladies.
Anyone of you plays mahjong?
Well, we do play it, but...
W-What's this about?
Young ladies, wouldn't you like
to join me for a game or two?
Huh?
Ah, come on, come on!
Go ahead and take a seat.
Don't push me!
What kind of creature are you?
Good thing you asked.
Before you - the Great Mahjong King Ravijan!
You'll get to see with your own eyes
just how far my mahjong prowess spans!
The king of mahjong, then?
Well, well.
Show us how far your prowess spans.
W-W-What's with this unconcerned attitude?
Well, it won't stay this way for long!
I'll take it easy on you at first.
Here!
Ah! That's a ron!
I got riichi on my first try and was waiting for a dora!
It's about time I got serious!
There!
Ah, so sorry.
I got this one. Pure straight dora dora.
Nonsense! Nonsense! That's a load of nonsense!
Ah, got it!
Blessing of earth with thirteen orphans!
Ah, impressive!
Have you seen it, Rabbit?
We're in luck today!
Wait! I-It's has to be a mistake!
When the three are declaring victory all at once,
obviously, someone is mistaken!
There's no way I, the mahjong king,
would lose to a bunch of little girls like this!
You better take that back about the little girls!
Who do you think we three are?
In the game of mahjong,
there are no passers-by.
W-W-What?
Kasumi!
Miki!
Shoko!
We are the Three Super Real Mahjong Maidens!
Come again after you've trained for some more!
N-N-No way...
What's going on?
Did he go cray-cray from losing?
I see! So you were those three maidens all along!
I've been looking for you!
Ah!
W-What's that?
The grudge of all men who lost to you...
Will return right back at you!
No!
Miki's,
Kasumi's,
Shoko's
Mahjong Battle Scramble
What's going on?
Where did they come from?
Such outlandish looks!
Hey, you!
Who gave you the idea to sleep in place like this?
Ouch! What are you doing?
You came to your senses?
Ouch...
W-What kind of place is this?
You are in the town of Pinfu.
Town of Pinfu?
Now, where did you guys come from?
Oh, that's right. We suddenly fell into a strange hole.
This guy named Ravijan...
Shh! Don't you let that name
fly carelessly off your lips here!
But boy, you won't get far, looking like this!
Oh my, what happened?
No way!
You girls wanna buy some clothes?
But we've no money with us.
Pretty sure you do! Over there.
Eh? T-This?
Oh, look! The real tiles!
Kasumi, where'd you get that?
It seems I unconsciously grabbed them as I fell.
It's as they say!
Hm?
A drowning man will clutch at a mahjong tile!​
I'm unimpressed.
How absurd.
Oh my!
You can eat at my place.
Eh?
With that much money, you'll get a hefty change
even after buying new clothes and a dinner.
Can we really?
Because I live with my grandpa,
the place is a little shabby, but please don't be shy.
Ah! Lucky!
Our house is right past this street.
Hey, hey!
Ravijan - what kind of thing...
Shh!
S-Sorry.
What's that?
Eh?
They're playing mahjong with paper!
Over there too! Look!
You're right. They're using paper tiles.
Precisely.
In retaliation for losing a mahjong bout,
that rabbit monster...
took away every single mahjong tile in the country!
Is that so?
That's why the real tiles are so valuable?
That miscreant rabbit Ravijan...
Cute!
W-What's wrong?
It's... It's...
A Peeping Cat!
Hide!
Shit...
What's going on?
Hide somewhere, quick!
The damnation! This is his doing as well!
He appointed the Peeping Cat to monitor the city,
occasionally summoning a tornado like this!
He does it to take the fun of playing mahjong
away from the people of this town!
What a vile guy!
All because he's such a mahjong softie!
I wanna be flying in the sky, too...
Listen, Shoko...
I see, so Ravijan did that to you?
Could you tell us what kind of thing Ravijan is?
Sure.
One day, he just suddenly came to this country.
Nobody knows what kind of thing he is.
However...
He smells like something
that belongs to another world.
So he is not from this world?
Grandpa is an old-school fortune-teller.
That guy is using the most dubious techniques.
Keeps doing away mercilessly
with those who don't comply.
With the mahjong tiles he took away from the people,
he built a fortress off the coast,
from which he rules over all of our country.
Among the people of our country,
every single one loves and enjoys mahjong.
So we worked hard to nurture and fertilize it
as something that'll give us strength tomorrow.
Such was the country we had once, rich and beautiful.
And now that country...
Tell me, Grandpa.
Hm?
Do you have any idea where is the entrance
to another world that those three came from?
Oh, you want to know that?
Ah! You'll teach us how to find our way back?
Yeah! Grandpa's divination never misses the mark!
Yu, get everything ready.
It's there!
W-What going on?
W-What is there?
Right here!
In the middle of Ravijan's fortress!
Ah! What ill fortune...
Grandpa, hang on!
Thank you.
With that knowledge, we'll return home...
In no time!
Yay!
Hold it!
It's the evil's nest ran by Ravijan, remember?
Do you even understand what that means?
Certainly!
When we get to that bunny...
We'll beat him!
And return to our own world!
Grandpa, do you suppose that those three
could defeat Ravijan?
Hm. Yu, please bring the Scoring Stick Saber.
Scoring Stick Saber?
That's right. A long time ago,
in order to defeat Ravijan,
the townspeople joined forces and manufactured this.
Ah?
What's this?
Just a scoring stick?
I-Impressive!
As expected, when wielded by someone courageous,
it lets them project a great power with it.
Right. The young men who stood up to face Ravijan a long time ago also possessed infinite courage.
Still, the power of his magic is also tremendous.
And if you lose your courage,
the Scoring Stick Saber also becomes useless.
Just thinking about all the young men
who lost their lives fighting him...
Please, go there and defeat Ravijan!
None of us here can wield those sabers!
You're the chosen ones, the heroes!
Use those sabers to defeat Ravijan!
Avenge all the fallen townspeople!
Avenge father for me, please!
Father?
Like, your dad?
That's right.
My son, the father of my granddaughter
stood up against Ravijan and lost.
Unforgivable.
We'll make sure to...
Defeat Ravijan!
And restore peace in this world!
Well, then...
We're off!
Thank you for taking care of us.
Take care and watch your step.
Ah, right, right.
Please take this as a farewell gift.
What's this?
So pretty!
What could it be?
You use it when you're in trouble.
Thank you. Well...
Good luck!
If you run into trouble, come again anytime!
Tell me, Yu.
Ah... What is it, Grandpa?
Do you think those three can actually defeat Ravijan?
I suppose.
When the three that get along so well join forces,
I'm sure...
I'm sure!
Ouch!
You're so clumsy, sis!
What now? It was Shoko who stumbled!
It was because Kasumi was appreciating the view!
No I wasn't!
Just hurry up and get off me!
Is that all? Those cats are too weak!
Alright! Off to a good start!
We can do it!
Out of the way!
Weak!
Oh? The cat turned into a mahjong tile!
Huh?
Oh, I see!
These cats are just mahjong tiles
that Ravijan cast a spell on.
Incredible!
What do you mean?
Well, that means everything here
is made of tiles, right?
I see! In that case...
Get back here!
Hit them with the Scoring Sticks!
We'll be the richest people around!
Yes, come right in!
Get in the bag! Oh! Here too! Ah! Here too!
Here too! Here too! Here too! Here too!
Wait a minute, Kasumi!
You fight them too, not just gather the tiles!
Seeing how well you manage it,
I'd rather cheer you on.
No way...
Seems like we got rid of the most of them.
I also collected so much money!
Amazing! It enough to live like queens
for the rest of our lives!
You want to live here for the rest of your life?
There's still more?
Don't let him escape!
W-What's that?
Could it be...
Curl, curl, curl...
It happened again!
I can't take it anymore! It hurts!
Huh?
Um. I'm sorry if you find my directness inappropriate, but I got bird food here.
Would you like to buy some?
Bird food. Would you like some?
W-What was that?
No clue.
Bird food! Would you like to buy some bird food?
Oh no!
Don't give us that sparkling smile!
She's catching up!
Bird food! Would you like some...
Ah!
Ah?
That's it! Now's our chance...
To run away!
But now I feel a bit sorry for her.
Eh?
Hey...
All right, I'll buy your bird food.
How much?
Hold it!
Sure! It's just 40 tiles!
Consumption tax and basket are included as service.
Right, I could also give you a loan.
Loans are available in 6 to 12 installments,
starting at 7 tiles per month.
That's way too much!
A loan for the bird food?
Nobody would pay 40 tiles for that!
That's just nonsense!
Until I... Until I sell all of it, I can't return home!
A-All right!
I'll buy it!
Thanks for your business!
Now, why'd you make a purchase like this?
I couldn't help it!
How unfriendly!
Those statues look so unfriendly!
Gosh, you're annoying!
Who made such senseless things?
Just forget it and start walking!
There! Sis, isn't it cute?
Just stay here if you want!
I'll make it into a work of art.
Let's add some lipstick next.
What's going on here?
So creepy!
Ravijan's magic again?
It's no use! They're too nimble, I can't catch any!
What about Kasumi?
No! Help me!
What are you doing? Just throw that basket away!
But it was so expensive!
Ouch!
Watch out!
Kasumi...
Sounds like she was very delicious...
Ah, it's not her!
They're eating bird food!
Alright...
Now's our chance...
To get rid of them!
Kasumi!
Here!
Need help here as well!
Sure!
Yes, coming!
That should do it!
I-It became a 1000 points stick!
It leveled up!
Great!
Fine... Let's go!
To Ravijan's Fortress!
Whoa!
A city!
I'm tired, so why don't we stay somewhere overnight?
Agreed!
Welcome.
Do we know you?
My name is Kaori.
Where are you from, Kaori-san?
From here.
"King's Palace" Inn
Right! We're going to the fortress.
Is it still a long way from here?
Please don't be talking so irresponsibly!
Better just return home sooner!
To do that, we've no choice but to go to the fortress.
What a pity, to lose more of such young lives...
Young ladies.
If you're looking for a lodging, girls...
How about you stay at my place?
A-Almost Crying Dragon!
Almost Crying Dragon?
Somebody!
What do you say, young ladies?
Yes. We take the offer.
Sister!
Miki!
Are you quite in your mind, sister?
There, can't you see the creature on his shoulder?
P-Peeping Cat!
Which means...
This is a trap!
A challenge from Ravijan.
We can't know what's awaiting us there.
Right. That man is Ravijan's minion, which means...
He sucks at mahjong!
Ah, that's right! That's right!
I'll make sure to give you a good taste of my abilities.
Almost Crying Dragon!
They're still so young!
Poor girls!
Ah, what a pity!
Isn't there a way for us to save them?
Lots of panic-mongers in this town.
Hm! How bossy.
What?
You heard me!
I'll shut that cocky mouth of yours up for good,
when I beat you in a mahjong battle.
I'll be the one who shuts you up,
so that you don't intimidate anyone ever again.
What's with Miki suddenly
getting worked up over this?
Isn't everyone hungry?
Can't you guys ever feel the suspense of the moment?!
Sorry!
This way,
Almost crying...
Dragon.
Well, let's begin, shall we?
Pon!
Chii!
Riichi!
What the...
Ron! With a riichi, that's a yakuman!
You really did it!
As expected!
I won!
Shit!
What's that?
Just don't break into tears now!
Idiot.
That's Ravijan's minion for you!
Pathetic loser!
Wanna die yet?
Y-You'll be the ones who dies today!
No need to be so upset!
Ow-ow-ouch!
What is it this time?
Ah! Sister, look!
What should we do?
Are you sure we can handle this?
We have to. It'd be a disaster
if that thing comes to town!
Let's go!
Stop, you!
You, the monster who only bullies the weak!
Despite being so weak in mahjong himself!
May the heavens forgive you,
because you'll never get that from us!
Get ready!
We'll show you the new power
of our powered-up scoring sticks!
Amazing!
We won't lose to you!
Leave this to me!
One-two...
Seems like he really felt it, as expected!
Let's finish him off together!
Yeah!
Get this!
Now!
There!
Think about your behavior!
He's heavy!
Just pin him down harder!
Ah... What was the point of that "together"?
What do you mean?
Wasn't you the one who said "leave this to me"?
Miki, remember the balls we got from Yu?
Ah, that's right!
Here.
You defeat fire with water! Get this!
Water
It's as they say, an eye for an eye.
You fight fire with fire!
Is this all we have left?
Oil
Beat fire with oil?
That sounds kinda dangerous.
No! Don't come close!
We did it!
Drug
Is that Dragon's?
It's a drug that lets you transform
into anything you like.
How convenient!
Can I carry it?
Lucky!
"King's Palace" Inn
What now? Those three again?
Alright, I heard you.
Really, what's gong on here?
The weather was so nice when we left the inn!
That probably means
the fortress island is already near.
I'm hungry!
Kasumi!
Don't worry. I brought with me
some Dandan noodles and gyoza.
That's good! I brought babaocai and rice!
What's next?
You'll also tell me you got some "Buddha Jumps Over the Wall" soup, Sugar Carp, or Peking Duck?
That'd be good too!
I can't resist a Chinese-style soup!
Hey, hey!
I-Wheels! I-Wheels! I-Wheels! I-Wheels! I-Wheels!
What could those be?
Running pancakes?
No way!
What the hell are you doing? Wait a minute!
Round Set Temple
Ouch!
Eh! My rice's smashed!
Oh... What is that?
Could that be...
R-Ravijan?
Are you a minion of Ravijan?
I am I-Wheel, the head priest.
Head priest I-Wheels?
My orders are to prevent you from leaving this place.
East,
south,
west,
north,
white,
green,
red,
riichi,
tsumo,
ron!
Out of my way!
Ron!
What do we do next?
We're supposed to figure it out now!
You've nowhere else to run.
No sir...
It worked!
Impressive!
It powered-up again!
Fine...
There!
Growing!
Kasumi!
Miki!
Miki! We'll be fine if we transform now!
Good thinking! Kasumi!
Shoko!
Stop! Please stop!
Stop! I can't swim, at all!
Oh? Well, that's convenient.
Swimming would be perfect to shape you up!
Well, it's about time!
We did it!
Only Ravijan remains now! Come now!
To the fortress island!
Ravijan, where are you?
Come out to play!
It's time to have a real duel! Come now! Come!
Um, what should I do now?
Oh, I know! I'll discard this one!
Now, tsumo, tsumo, tsumo!
Ah! It's not what I needed!
Ooh! It's here, here, here!
Oh-ho! I hope I draw riichi next!
Eh? Ain't you a quick one? You'll only need...
Ah! I'll have pon with that!
Eh? Then, I'll answer with this. Here.
Ah! I got ron, ron, ron! Just what I needed!
You're still not good enough for this, kid! I won again!
Right, I feel bad, even.
You could really use some more practice.
I'm just too strong for you, kid!
Something happened?
Your game ends here, Ravijan.
Did you actually survive, you three?
Sorry to disappoint you!
Now, will you return us to our usual world or not?!
My, isn't that one cold way to address your friend!
I really prefer ladies who are more well-behaved!
Shut up!
Blood!
How dare you scar my perfect beautiful face!
That's it! You're not getting away with it!
It was a pretty short life.
It's true what they say,
the beautiful die first...
I still wanted to try so much more delicious stuff!
Why are you saying some nonsensical rubbish now?!
If I were you, I'd be reciting the prayer now!
Pon!
The deadly Great Buddha's virtue!
Scoring stick - level 3!
There!
Kasumi!
I'll avenge my sister!
You'll pay for this!
Too weak!
Pon!
After making it this far...
Super...
Real...
Triple...
Yakuman Beam!
White suit?!
Did it!
Earthquake?
We defeated Ravijan, so the fortress island is sinking!
Grandpa, they really did it!
Yes.
What's that?
You, girls! It's getting dark already.
Don't you need to go home?
Is it morning already?
Why did we fall asleep here?
Ah! Banzai!
Ah, but let me tell you, I'm happy to be able
to play mahjong leisurely like this again!
True, true!
Even if I thought I've had enough
of mahjong after that, in the end,
maybe that's exactly what we love it for?
I suppose.
That might just be so.
Alright, let's start!
Riichi!
Ron!
Ex-
tra
gift!
Extra gift
Miki vs. Kaori
Hello, dear viewers!
Today, on the occasion of us performing together
in the part 2, I'm meeting with kaori!
Kaori, as our tonight's guest what kind of role
would you like to play next time?
Let's see. If I could become a heroine
of a love & romance movie...
Ah? Camera is this way?
I think it fits me best.
But I know it's hopeless.
After all, I know - you guys like comedies way more!
Ah? Did I just say something rude?
No-no, it's just that Kaori is so pretty, I brought along a whole cardboard box with lovely presents for her!
My, what wonderful presents I have here!
Well, well, well? Do you now understand the full dreadfulness of a bad starting hand?
Sorry, did you say something?
Kasumi vs. Mana
Say, Mana, which role would you like to play next?
Well... Whichever role I get,
I'm gonna do my very best!
More importantly, I'd be happy just to be able
to appear in a movie together with Kasumi!
Eh? Oh no! You're making me blush when you say that!
I... I don't know what to say...
What?!
Ah! Shoko did that!
What?
It was Miki this time!
I can see the hammer, by the way!
Mana, what's the meaning of this?
Well...
Kasumi looks so cute when you hit her!
Shoko vs. Yu
Hey, Yu, what kind of story
would you like to appear in next?
Well, that'd be action, hands down!
I hope to play the lead role in an action movie one day!
Spinning kick!
Cool...
I-I'm sorry, Shoko!
I-I-I'm fine.
I get it that you like action,
but would it be a movie about monsters or tokusatsu?
Tokusatsu? Monster movies?
Only kindergarteners watch that!
I hate it.
Whoa!
Why are you so mad all of a sudden?
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
Sorry!
Good
bye!
Goodbye
Raws by [Orphan-raw]
Translated by Perevodildo