The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
What are you doing here at this hour?
Haven't you gone home yourself?
I couldn't stop wondering
what kind of practice they're doing there.
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
It's Happening!
Heated Junior Championship
Episode
It's Happening!
Heated Junior Championship
Is this their "secret training?" With such an important competition ahead, they're not taking it seriously at all!
Coach Misaki, look...
I-It's Shun-kun...
Tkachev?
No way!
Did you see it just now?
So incredibly high!
Everyone is making great progress!
How could they improve that much in just a week?
What kind of secret training
did Andrianov give them?
They all look so happy!
Would you look at that!
You young people can peep so shamelessly!
G-Grandma!
Why are you here, Madam?
I'm bringing the boys their night snacks.
After all, they're practicing like crazy.
But it seems they don't even realize that themselves.
Thanks to Andrianov's magic.
Magic?
He doesn't pressure the boys
and emphasizes the key points that motivate them.
Gymnastics has to be fun.
It being fun is what lets you overcome yourself.
Orikasa.
Yes?
Do you enjoy gymnastics?
Yes!
Let's do our best too, then.
One week later...
All right, come close now!
Gentlemen, the competitions
finally start tomorrow.
I'll be honest: it's a massive tournament
filled with people who are way out of our league.
So, on this occasion, I'd like to...
Yes, yes, we know.
Huh?
Just say "Let's do our best!"
and be done with it.
He's right!
We don't need long-winded speeches now!
Huh? But...
And now, may we have
a few words from Coach Andrianov?
Hm?
Hmm...
Well, let's just have fun tomorrow.
That seems like a perfect speech for the occasion!
Have fun?
Is that all?
Well, as expected of Andrianov, really!
With pleasure, sir!
All right! Tomorrow, we'll have our chance to show the world the results of our secret training!
Our performance is going to be mind-blowing!
It'll look great on TV!
Do you guys ever think
about something but the TV?
TV...
It's our time...
to shine!
What's wrong, Ueno-kun?
Well, it's going to be
my first tournament and all...
Take it easy, Ueno!
We don't expect anything from you anyway.
Come on, don't be a buzzkill!
You gotta be fired up too!
Yes, and Captain too.
Huh? Me too?
We...
Can do it!
Will do it!
To stand out...
Be popular...
We'll get it!
Come on, say your part!
That's right, Ueno!
All-Japan Junior Individual Championships
Wow, the place is impressive.
All-Japan Junior Championship, huh?
This tournament is still relatively new...
Practice field
What are your goals for this competition?
Let's see...
Practice field
Well, just like before, all I have to do is demonstrate the new techniques
I've acquired since last time. However...
'96 All-Japan Junior Champion Kobayakawa Kenichi
This is a very special tournament because it qualifies you for the World Championships.
I'm feeling determined.
'96 All-Japan Junior Champion Kobayakawa Kenichi
'96 All-Japan Junior 2nd place Iwao Kamura
Other competitors? Let's see...
Honestly, none of them are all that impressive.
I have no interest in them.
'96 All-Japan Junior 2nd place Iwao Kamura
I will say this, though! Kobayakawa-san, I hear you also entered in all the events.
Tsk! As long as I'm here,
you won't have gold in a single event!
'96 All-Japan Junior 2nd place Iwao Kamura
You can bet on that!
I can hear you, Kamura-kun.
Oh, you were here?
It was just a joke, you see...
I liked that!
Say, Sakashita-san, those two have an amazing sense of rivalry between them, don't they?
Of course they do!
The world championship participation is at stake.
They act like friends in public, but their real motive is to probe each other's condition.
The competition is already underway.
What an unforgiving world...
Of course it is!
Oh... But it seems not all
the participants here are that tense.
What were you thinking?
Why did you do that to you hair?
Hey...
Wh-What's so funny?!
Hey, didn't you go overboard with the pomade?
You'll also be appearing on TV today!
Oh, I see. It's the Heisei guys.
Looks like they're up to something again.
I suppose.
Hey, Fujimaki -kun!
Ah!
Saito-kun!
Oh, hey! Long time no see!
So you decided to enter this tournament too?
Did you come here from Hokkaido by yourself?
Well, that's the thing. My coach who was supposed to come with me suddenly disappeared.
Disappeared?
Yeah... He just randomly leaves and returns every now and then.
I see...
Ah, speaking of coaches, we also found...
Shun!
They told me they're not selling any alcohol at the store here!
I had no choice but to buy this.
Here, meet our coach, Andrianov-san.
Coach Sergei!
Yes!
Hey, Sakai!
Huh?
Really! Where have you been all this time, Coach?
I'm sorry, Sakai.
I completely forgot about you!
Of course... Of course!
Saito-kun, do you know Coach Andrianov?
Yeah. He's the coach who's been teaching me gymnastics in Hokkaido.
That's how it was!
Saito's...
Coach?!
Yeah...
Now it makes sense...
His Kovacs.
And his triple somersault.
Hm?
Hey.
So they're here?
They're short...
Who are they?
I'm supposed to know most of the guys
in this tournament.
Who are those guys?
They're not messing around!
I-Incredible!
H-How did they manage to stay under the radar?!
Oh man...
So they came after all?
Li Dongsheng.
What a surprise, Andrianov.
Your trainees also entered this tournament?
So, do you think you can win against me?
Against my warriors?
Now, gentlemen, what is our theme again?
Fun gymnastics!
Precisely!
Oh! Those are TV cameras!
C-Cameras?
There too!
Oh! More more here!
They're filming us!
Look, guys...
Well then, let's do out best!
The boys' first event, the floor routine,
will begin shortly.
For all gymnastics fans,
the long-awaited day has come!
We are reporting on the All-Japan Junior Championships from Tokyo KK Hall.
Commentary: Fukuzawa Tomoro
Allow me to introduce the expert commentator in the broadcast booth.
Kaizuka Yoshiyuki-san, the editor-in-chief of Weekly Gymnastics News
and a gymnastics reviewer for 40 years!
Yes, hello...
Expert: Kaizuka Yoshiyuki
Well, I might be wrong, Kaizuka-san,
but when we think of gymnastics competitions,
we usually imagine a quiet venue with a tense atmosphere, don't we?
But today is different!
I guess so... Normally, in competitions,
routines for all events are performed simultaneously.
Then this event-specific tournament is unique because only one event takes place at a time.
I see. So the spectators can watch the routines more easily and cheer for the athletes, right?
Ah, that was a great Moonsault, but the landing was unsteady! He'll definitely lose points for it!
Look, you just said "lose points," but do you know exactly how many points will he lose?
Uh? Well... Um...
N-Never mind that!
Kobayakawa's performance is over now.
Let's find out now how many points he scores.
Hey, Shun!
Madam!
Coach Andrianov!
Give it your best!
I'll also be rooting for you from here.
Remember to have fun!
Okay!
I'm feeling elated already.
A total of 13 athletes entered the floor competition.
It's finally time for Ueno's debut.
S-S-Sanada-senpai...
Uh? What is it?
I-I-I'm s-s-sc-c-c...
That performance was uncharacteristic for you.
Are you unwell or something today?
Oh, they're announcing your score.
It's out! 9.4!
Kobayakawa scored 9.4.
Kaizuka-san, gymnastics routines are scored on a scale of ten.
But the first place on the floor
is currently with Kobayakawa and his 9.4.
Well, the gymnastics score is relative.
He's still the junior champion,
so a 9.4 in this tournament isn't bad—
it would've been even lower at the Olympics.
I-I see. Indeed, that's a deep observation.
Well, to put it bluntly,
Japan's gymnastics is lacking right now.
Huh? Do you think so?
Yes! The difficulty level is too low—
it would be laughable on the world stage!
And now, next up is Ueno
from Heisei Middle School.
Ueno, it's your turn.
Y-Yes...
Ueno, Ganba!
Huh?
U-Ueno-kun...
His nerves took over.
Is he a robot now?
How can you be that timid?
Come on, make a signal!
R-R-R-Ready!
Ueno!
Ready!
Yoshio, good luck!
Andrianov's trainee?
Y-Yes. Got it. And now—a commercial break!
That was disastrously bad!
What school is he from?
All right, well done.
You did great for your first performance.
Fujimaki's one scored 1.3, remember?
Y-Yes.
And now, finally some interesting entries!
Next up is Kamura
from Urayasu Gymnastics Club!
Kamura-san, good luck!
The audience immediately cheers for him,
and he has unusually many female fans!
What? So that's how it is...
What's wrong, Sanada-senpai?
I had no idea Kamura
had that many female fans...
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
Suppose Kamura scores 9.5...
Kamura
Then, if I score 9.7 or higher while also having better looks and style...
Fight, Kamura!
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
Fight, Kamura!
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Go! Go! Sanada!
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Kamura
I get
or more
Wouldn't that be nice?
I can't afford to lose this.
Kobayakawa, look closely!
They always considered me second to you,
but your reign ends today!
It's him...
Now, it's time for the final tumbling!
I'll never be number two again!
Ah! Are you seeing this?
Kamura chooses the same Moonsault as Kobayakawa as his finishing move!
What?
I got this!
That's it!
He did it! Kamura absolutely nailed the landing!
He scored 9.55!
All right!
He even overtook Kobayakawa!
Kamura-kun, great job!
I was pushed out...
Yes, that was definitely surprising, Kaizuka-san.
Kobayakawa's score was surpassed so soon!
It's only natural.
It's a competitive environment
when situation changes every second.
Right...
Is that the best analysis you've got, you grumpy old fart?
Well, in any case, it's safe to say that this level of difficulty wouldn't be acceptable on the world stage.
So far, 11 performances have been completed,
and two more remain.
Kamura is currently in the lead with 9.55 points
among the men on the floor.
Now, the next performer
is Koda of the Nishihori Club.
At last...
What?
Here we go.
That upstart laughed in my face!
Kamura-san, he'll beat you.
What?
Beat me?
Are you saying he'll score higher than me?
Well, let's just take a look.
Hm... Don't think I've ever heard
of Nishihori College Club.
They brought five other players aside from Koda.
Do you know them, Kaizuka-san?
Who are you taking me for?
Don't underestimate my magazine's ability to gather information!
I guess I might just be the only one who knows about them in this hall!
It's that much of a mystery?
Absolutely!
The Lee Corps, led by a coach brought in from China,
is Japan's only world-class worthy gymnastics team!
All right, his performance finally starts!
Here it comes.
Yeah.
He'll beat me? Don't make me laugh!
The Japanese gymnastics
is being reborn before our own eyes!
So fast!
Can you believe that?!
Double layout somersault!
Swan's Doppel?
What's Swan's Doppel?
Swan means stretched,
and Doppel means double—double somersault.
This is it!
He performed a straight-body double somersault,
Tucked up double somersault
which generates less rotational force than a tucked double somersault!
Straight-body double somersault
And performing it on the floor
is even more difficult!
Right, but his performance is not over yet!
From the handspring...
Ch-Chain of straight-body somersaults?
They even went this far...
Impossible!
And it's time for the final tumbling!
He must have already used up most of his stamina by now.
What is he going to show next?
Ah! Here comes another one!
Straight-body double somersault!
Straight-body again?!
And he nailed it!
The landing was also perfect!
That's what I'm talking about!
This is the world-class gymnastics!
Now, what score will he get?
Will he overtake the first-place holder?
It's out! 9.75!
Impossible!
Kamura was suddenly
dragged down from the top!
They really are amazing...
Yeah.
Not bad. I'd hate to perform
after someone like that.
Well, Kaizuka-san, that was downright stunning!
Gymnastics relies on precedents, and an unprecedented routine with two straight-body somersaults
should definitely score highly!
Underwhelming.
What?!
Just a Swan Doppel...
What's so good about it?
Who's that dotard?
How long is he going to sit
at the broadcasting booth unauthorized?
I don't know... But I've been ordered by my superiors to let him sit here.
How did you like my athlete, Andrianov?
Now, it's time for the final floor routine.
The only remaining boy
is Sanada-kun from Heisei.
Ugh... Poor fella. It's already obvious that Koda is going to win the floor.
I wouldn't wanna perform after that.
H-Hey, what's that?
Huh?
What is he doing?
Oh geez. What's gotten into him?
Sanada-senpai!
That's a fine spot for the warmup!
Now, then. The final performer
is the Prince of Floor.
You'd be dead wrong
if you think that it's already over!
Hey, Sanada, that was a cool line, all right,
but what's with that pose?
Perhaps ballet was
your secret training, after all?
What kind of performance will it be,
Ganbarist Toshihiko?
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
I feel unusually big...
H-Hey... What the hell are you doing?
What?
Isn't it obvious? Warming up!
Next Ganba:
Prince of Floor! A Magnificent Swan Banquet.
We're learning the vaulting
box today, the tricky one.
Jump headfirst, run up, then kick the springboard, and place your hands
and your head on the box,
then handspring and move your legs forward.
When you learn this,
you'll learn handspring alongside this.