The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
Morisue-san won the gold medal on the high bar at the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Sydney '2000
Ganba!
I beg you, don't quit the club!
I beg you, don't quit!
I want you to stay!
Captain!
Captain...
Guys...
I love gymnastics.
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Tournament!
Ultra Special Cross Handstand
That's sneaky, Mari-chan!
Aren't we members of the same gymnastics club?
Sanada-senpai...
Now I'm fired up too!
I'll definitely do it!
Same here! After seeing Mari-chan's
back hip circle, I really feel like I can't lose!
Uchida-senpai, Higashi-senpai...
All right! Let's show them the power of our determination!
We're ready!
The final men's group,
please begin your practice.
Will everyone handle it okay?
Don't worry, Mari-chan. The boys have trained sufficiently for this day.
Yeah. They'll be fine.
Right.
Do you have enough time, Mari-chan?
Yes.
I want to root for everyone for as long as I can.
Hey, isn't that Kamura?
You're right. Kamura from Urayasu is participating in the prefectural tournament!
What happened? I thought he switched completely to Junior tournaments.
I guess we're not taking the first place this time...
I'll ask for his autograph later.
It seems I won't find any real competition here...
Um... You're Kobayakawa, aren't you?
Yeah. Are you from Gym Road magazine?
Excuse me, Kobayakawa-san, will you please sign this?
Oh! It's a nice photo.
Your expression here is perfect.
Kobayakawa?
Who'd think we'll meet the All-Japan Junior Champion here!
We actually came to interview Kamura-kun.
Are you also here to check him out?
Yeah.
Although he's still in middle school, he's already as good as us high school students.
Oh?
Is your opinion of Kamura-kun really that high?
Well, Kamura-kun will probably
steal the spotlight in the individual combined section of today’s tournament.
I have no doubts about it.
At the middle school prefectural tournament level, no one can measure up to him.
Hey, look!
Eek! What's that?
Amazing! Kamura is doing Upper Planche on the floor!
That guy is something else!
Only Kamura can pull off such strength-based techniques while still in middle school!
How did you like that,
Mr. All-Japan Champion?
I bet you never even imagined that I could master a strength-based technique like that.
Don't be cocky, Kamura-kun.
Did you hope to impress me with your Upper Planche?
I’m already working toward transitioning into a handstand from that position.
As expected, Kamura-kun has been growing by leaps and bounds lately.
I suppose.
Are you stupid—
performing it during training?!
What's the harm in that, coach? This kind of tournament is just child's play anyway.
All right!
Ready!
Ganba!
Ganba...
It turned out pretty good! Good!
Senpai, I have chilled towels
and cold drinks in there.
Oh! Thank you.
Too bad you were sidelined, Ueno!
We needed a fourth member and Fujimaki came first. But it'll be your turn next time!
Oh, it is quite all right.
Huh?
I'm small and weak. No matter what I do,
I'm always the worst in class.
Since starting gymnastics, I’ve learned to do things I never thought I could.
That alone is great!
Don't make me cry, Ueno!
The final men's group,
please begin your performance.
Let's go!
All right, let's do it!
Yes!
Hey, look at the floor section!
Remember what that guy did last time?
Yeah, that ridiculous stance on the previous tournament!
Exactly! A 1.3 points heron!
They're starting, Mari-chan.
Yes.
I'm ready!
There, it begins!
Nice!
Looking good so far.
Huh? A normal routine?
Good! Good!
Fujimaki-kun...
All right, well done warming them up!
What's the score?
8.0!
Hey, that's not a bad progress from the 1.3 you received last time for the floor!
Yes, I'm happy...
Fine, I'll carry it on!
Hey...
They're actually not bad.
Nice, nice!
Don't worry, don't worry.
I slipped up.
The rest is up to you, Higashi.
Yeah!
Oh man, that's going to be
nothing special at all.
I wonder if he'll do
the same as the last time.
Hey, Kamura is about to start on the vault.
Really? Let's go see it.
Kamura-san is up on vault!
We gotta see it!
Kobayakawa-san, don't get too startled when you see my score.
Hey, Mochida, did you catch it just now?
In perfect detail, Sakashita-san.
Too bad. Double somersault was great,
but your landing leaves a lot to be desired.
Tsk. What a dick!
Wow!
Oh?
Someone's doing
an Upper Planche on the floor!
Nonsense!
It's also a lot clearer
than Kamura's Planche before!
What did you say?!
But... But that's true.
Hey, Mochida!
Take a photo of that! Quick, get it!
R-Right...
Huh?
What the...
What?!
It can't be...!
Way to go, Higashi!
Don't you let out a fart now!
Straight-arm, straight-body press handstand!
Straight-arm, straight-body press handstand...?
Difficulty class: D
N-No way!
That's it, Higashi-senpai!
He didn't fart!
To transition into that from a Planche...
To think a middle school student can perform this kind of move...
We've got a scoop!
We'll finally make it to the front page!
Wh-Who is that?
I'm the All-Japan Champion, but even I am still training to perform a press headstand!
I'm not done yet!
My ultra jaw-dropping technique only starts now!
Huh?
He's going to jump too?!
This is my ultra jaw-dropping technique!
Cross Handstand!
Cross Handstand
How come he has a technique like that?
Who is that guy?
I-I can't believe it...
Wh-What else does he have?
How come we never covered this kind of athlete in our magazine?!
That was great, Muscle Boy!
Well done, Higashi!
Hey...
Higashi?
Higashi-senpai?
Higashi-senpai is crying?
What's wrong, Higashi?
I'm not the one crying!
It's my muscles! All this painful training paid off, so now my muscles are happy!
Yeah, right...
B-But it went really well, Higashi-senpai.
You didn't even fart...
Oh! It all came out now!
Hey, they're announcing the score!
9.4?
Could it be...
The first ever...
In the history of Heisei...
9-points score!
First ever 9-points score?
For real?!
He did it!
Phew, it went well.
Yeah.
The special training paid off, didn't it?
R-Right... Have you finished performing already?
Yes. Do you mind if I sit here until the afternoon section?
Sure, Reiko-senpai.
Your men's club is amazing!
Yes. I suppose they are.
I wonder if their other boys
brought some new moves too.
It's a secret!
Keep watching to find out.
All right. Good luck, then.
Thanks.
Floor
Goal
Fujimaki got 8.0...
Fujimaki
Uchida
You got 8.5 and I—8.8.
Sanada
Higashi
Plus Higashi-senpai's 9.4.
The team score is the sum
of the top three scores.
If Fujimaki's 8.0 is cut off...
It's 26.7.
Our goal is an average of 8.8 per person.
That sets the targeted team total
at 26.4 per event...
After the first event,
we’re already ahead by 0.3 points.
We can win... probably.
Yes. We can.
We've got this!
The top six is a piece of cake!
We might actually make it
to the top three instead!
Today, we're definitely
going for it!
They're going for it...
All right, time to take it easy now!
Relax, relax!
That's meowright!
Woof-woof!
That was sly, Misaki-san.
Oh, coach Horiuchi?
You had such wonderful boys up your sleeve, yet you never warned me when I saw you the other day.
If you mean Higashi-kun,
I had nothing to do with it.
Boys are not in my sphere of competence.
Huh? But then, who trained them?
Well, who indeed?
Men's teams, please move on to the next event and start practicing.
All right!
Let's go! Now it's my turn.
Yes!
Hey, it's them!
Look at those arms!
Those muscles are something else!
With such muscles, you'd think he's an athlete from Russia.
He probably trained for a long time.
Higashi of Heisei Middle School?
We came here to interview Kamura-kun,
but perhaps he won't be the main star of this issue!
H-Hey there...
Nice to meet you.
Now, it's vault time!
I'll work hard!
L-Look they've completely ignored those two!
Did they consider them not worth their attention?
B-Bastards!
S-Such disregard for me,
the All-Japan Champion!
Hey! Higashi from Heisei
is starting to practice vaulting!
That Higashi?
Come on, let's go see it!
Yeah! Let's go!
Hey, don't hold back
just because it's a practice.
I know!
I'll make it loud and the judges will be delighted!
Good luck, Higashi-senpai!
What kind of jump do you think it'll be?
Though it's just practice,
keep taking pictures just in case.
Got it! Leave that to me.
Wh-What was that, a simply forward jump?
So unrefined, like a gorilla!
Did you see that too?
It seems, brute force is all he got.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Well, something like this.
Your favorite style—
jumping without thinking.
It leaves an impact!
Like in a circus!
In the end, they're still
the worst team in the district.
Worst in the district?
If they have an athlete who can do a straight-arm, straight-body press handstand,
I figured they’d be a formidable opponent.
From what we just saw on the vault,
he's just a gorilla.
I suppose.
Exactly!
Ah, my bad, I didn't mean to...
Let's go, Mochida.
Oh? You don't want any more photos here?
You just saw it.
We thought they were great from their floor performances, but they suck in other events.
They're not worth paying attention to.
Oh, you think so?
The atmosphere is right.
After all, you can't expect a gorilla
to handle vault well.
I'll show you what it means to be the true vault specialist.
Uchida-senpai! Do your best!
Yeah! It feels like even the vault itself is winking to me today.
Air kiss...
Well now, I have my own practice to do.
Are their other athletes
at the same level as him?
Ah, it's that guy...
Oh, yeah! He's the one who got zero points for the X-ray at the last tournament.
X-ray?
Is that true, Misaki-san?
I don't know.
Sakashita-san, what's this thing they call x-ray?
Hm? X-ray is when...
What?!
H-How come?!
It's thanks to his "to-to-ton" rhythm!
N-Nonsense! He executed double somersault, just like me?!
What's more, your messed up the landing,
but he did it perfectly.
Who's that? How come we don't know about him?! Number 55!
Who knows...
Ready!
Wh-What now?
Hey, is it really a prefectural tournament?
Yay!
Yo, 10.0!
First—double somersault,
now one-handed handspring!
What's gotten into Heisei guys
this time around?
They're amazing!
Both Shun-kun and Uchida-kun!
Yeah, amazing!
Madam, it seems everybody was impressed with Fujimaki's one-handed handspring!
Look!
The judges are having a heated discussion!
Yes, it felt pretty good.
Do you think they can make it to 6th place?
After the floor routine, they were already 0.3 points ahead of their target.
We have enough leeway to take a small risk now.
Risk?
Mari-chan, could you please go downstairs
and pass to him my request?
Huh?
The final men's group, please complete your practice and begin performance.
Huh? But I've never practiced
anything of the kind.
But Madam says it'll make your routine even more impressive and you'll get higher scores.
Even more impressive?
But...
Fujimaki! It's time.
Yes, coming!
Fujimaki-kun, if you're confident,
I'm sure you can do it!
Yeah!
You could've sent me with that instruction.
It's fine. Mari-chan will do.
How is Fujimaki's going to improve
his routine's impact?
Beats me.
Could it be...!
I can do it.
I'll jump!
I believe in it.
I'm sure Fujimaki-kun can do it!
Jump!
Fujimaki Shun suddenly takes on
a new mysterious challenge!
What's more, will his performance leave enough of an impact?
It'll decide whether or not you'll make it to the 6th place, Ganbarist Shun!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Maybe we can do it now.
Yeah! We totally can!
And now, add a twist...
Uchida-senpai! You're not turning fast enough! You can't do it!
Next Ganba: Excited! I'm in Perfect Shape!
On parallel bars that require good balance, ultra spinning techniques are difficult to pull off.
Such as this double somersault on your arms.
This technique is Morisue,
and this is Belle.
And a technique that adds twist on it is called Tanaka, it's a hot topic right now.