The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
What for?!
Looks scary!
Why did he do that?!
Too low!
Stupid Captain!
No longer safe!
It's over!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
An overhead wire accident caused delays across the line. We apologize for the inconvenience.
Next stop is Tokyo. Tokyo.
Please watch your step.
Episode
Clash!
A Fiery Battle on the High Bar
He slipped up.
Yuichi! With your chest!
What?
He swung his chest to change his trajectory!
Orikasa...
You've always rooted for me
with all your heart!
Morisue is a really difficult technique!
You must execute a double somersault between the two bars with absolute precision!
And if you can’t handle the bars' violent shaking
with both hands the moment you land...
There's only a fraction of a second
in which you can successfully catch the bars!
If I fail to grab them now,
like during practice...
You can do it!
If I fail to catch them, I'll...
You can do it, Shindo-kun!
Exactly!
This is the only way you can build up confidence on your own!
He nailed it!
Shindo of Heisei nailed
the high-difficulty Morisue technique!
I did it!
And his finishing move
is straight-legs double somersault!
He nailed it too!
No mistakes made! Shindo executed a Morisue
and concluded his performance without slipping up!
Incredible!
His performance felt sterile at first,
but that final Morisue was great!
Captain!
That was something!
Thank you, Orikasa.
Not at all. You achieved all this
with your own ability.
Orikasa...
Whoa there, hold it!
What's between those two?
What's that atmosphere?
Yeah. I'll be damned.
It can't be.
This has to be a mistake somehow.
Oh? Orikasa-senpai's eyes are tearing up!
Oh? You think this could be
because Orikasa likes Shindo?
No way!
But Shindo-senpai really was great!
Do you think those two
could be dating already?
Then surely, they've already kissed and all...
No way!
It has to be a mistake!
Andrianov, you're happy because Shindo-kun took the plunge and challenged himself, aren't you?
Well, by all means, that was
a spectacular technique, right, Onuma-san?
Yes.
The Morisue technique was pioneered by Morisue at the Los Angeles Olympics.
It involves executing a double tucked somersault
and landing on your hands, right?
Yeah.
It wasn't as flashy as Belle that has a more interesting start, but it's still an E-level skill.
Yes, and it was spectacular!
Isn't it great?
Damn it... If only Oike
didn't botch his fucking Belle,
we'd have beaten them!
Shut up!
Imbecile!
Success or failure doesn’t matter—what counts is following Coach Lee’s commands to the letter!
Captain!
With this, we can finally hope for a clean win!
Win?
The first place is held by Kobayakawa with 9.4.
With a successful Morisue,
you should be able to beat that!
Win...
For me?
And here comes Shindo's score...
9.35!
Shit! So close!
Only half a point away from actually winning...
It's fine.
I gained something better than the victory.
Captain! You're not talking
about Reiko-sama, are you?!
Captain has just grown on more levels that one.
Thus, the first place on parallel bars remains with Kobayakawa and his 9.40.
Shindo came in second!
Not bad. I wasn't expecting a Morisue there.
With this, nobody will underestimate
Heisei any longer.
Oh no, that was still nothing special.
Our high bar performer
is the real reason Heisei can't be underestimated.
I have no doubts about him.
Oh, so it's him?
I believe, he is capable of things
beyond my imagination.
The final event for women—balance beam.
Orikasa of Heisei already started
her final routine of today.
Even on this 110 cm-high,
10 cm-wide balance beam,
she delivers a stable, breathtaking performance as if she were on the floor!
Sideways layout somersault with two twists!
She nailed it!
Olympic reserve Orikasa gave it her best
and delivered yet another flawless performance!
It was dazzling.
Thanks!
There's some really nice atmosphere
between those two.
So it's not just our imagination.
H-Hey, when did they...?
It has to be a mistake!
Reiko-sama!
You still have a whole life ahead of you.
Shut up!
Orikasa scores 9.80!
It's an indisputable victory!
Congratulations.
Well done, Orikasa.
Now it's just...
Yes, Fujimaki's performance.
Please... don't be late!
It's time for the final event of Individual Junior Championships—the men's high bar!
Participating athletes,
please begin your practice.
Is that the cream of our junior ranks?
Is that gymnast’s signature skill the Tkachev?
What is that "fun gymnastics" bullshit?
Andrianov,
it's just a silly excuse you came up with
because you can't train a winning gymnast.
This guy is nothing special either.
We have the high bar in the bag as well.
Did you see?!
I guess we can't underestimate Saito.
Coach!
It was a Kovacs!
Don't be afraid!
You just need to perform exactly
as I taught you, and we'll easily win.
Right... Even in practice, every athlete is showing off impressive skills!
The performances look really promising so far!
Yes.
And the performances finally begin!
As expected, those two
immediately claimed the top two spots.
Things might become difficult now.
And the next performer
is Matsumoto of Nishihori College!
I'll show you the difference in our abilities.
He's the younger brother
of another Nishihori gymnast
Matsumoto, who previously clinched
a spectacular victory on the pommel horse.
That said, Onuma-san,
looking back at all the previous events—
floor, pommel horse, rings, and vault—
the fact that Nishihori scored a spectacular victory in those four events so far really is impressive, isn't it?
That was unexpected!
Hm...
Yes, that's right!
Well, their coach is unparalleled, after all!
Coach Lee was brought from China
for this exactly!
That's what earned the Nishihori team
the "Lee Corps" nickname!
Why do you keep blabbering
from the rear rows?
And here it comes!
It's a Jaeger.
A backward Jaeger.
Oh! Not bad!
That's right, good.
Just focus on your own performance.
There's no reason for you to worry about what others are doing.
As long as you follow my instructions,
you'll definitely win.
I'll show you a perfect performance!
And now... It's a Gaylord!
Gaylord?!
You can't be serious!
That's it. He nailed it!
I won.
Onuma-san, once again an incredible skill
was included in the performance.
For a junior level, it's too good!
As the name suggests, this technique was pioneered
by an American gymnast Gaylord.
Lee Corps for life!
From underhand swing... Here!
You perform a tucked forward somersault while flying over the bar and catch back!
Doesn't that mean you can't even see the bar while performing it?
You do it by feel alone. Such signature techniques always involve great risks.
Only a fraction of a second separates success from failure.
Don't think it's a technique
that anyone at Heisei can handle.
Yes, I see now.
Then, he landed with a double layout somersault—
and executed it flawlessly!
Matsumoto Hiroshi of Lee Corps.
He scores 9.70!
It's an incredible 9.70!
Once again, Nishihori gymnast
wins by an extraordinary margin!
The first place is with Matsumoto!
Dammit...
They outdid us again?
That was great, Hiroshi!
Nice, Hiroshi.
Don't touch me!
Matsumoto...?
You disobeyed Coach Lee and failed us.
We effortlessly trounced every other event
at these championships!
C-Come on, you guys...
You made a joke of our collective goal.
How can you...
Why are you doing this?
What was that?
Is that a way to treat your teammate?
It has nothing to do with you!
What's wrong, Fujimaki?
They're at it again, aren't they?
Tsk. What an annoying bunch.
What was that?!
When you're trained by a third-rate coach,
of course you can't tell good from bad.
He only taught you to be cocky.
Coach Andrianov...
is the best coach ever!
The scoreboard begs to differ.
You haven't been able to beat us
in a single event so far.
If not for this idiot's slip-up,
the Lee Corps would've been invincible!
You and your coach can only dream of that!
If so, I'll show you.
Who the hell are you?
I was also taught by Coach Andrianov.
Saito-kun?
I'll show you the greatness
of Andrianov's coaching.
What was that?!
That's right!
Go for it, Saito!
You can definitely do it!
Show them your signature skill.
Signature skill? Kovacs?
Fujimaki-kun, will you help me up?
S-Sure.
He is Andrianov's gymnast too?
Did he manage to master the Kovacs?
I'll have to get a higher score than them to show the world how amazing Andrianov's coaching is, won't I?
9.70, then? Are you sure, Saito-kun?
Yeah. Only one way to find out.
And the next performer is Saito Sakae, a first-year from Hokkaido's Kitahashi Middle School.
He starts with a giant swing.
During practice, we saw Saito
perform a Kovacs.
When will he jump off now?
It's a Kovacs!
He's going for it!
Amazing as always!
Once more!
A double Kovacs?!
I have to show them!
He fell! Saito, who attempted a double Kovacs, fell down!
Shit...
Sakae, don't give up!
Your performance is still on!
Saito-kun, are you okay?
Yeah. Won't you please help me up again?
Sure!
It would've been amazing if he nailed it.
What a pity!
Tsk. He almost frightened me.
And he descends with an amazing triple somersault! He nailed it!
He did it!
Triple somersault!
What a bummer! If only he didn't fall...
Saito-kun.
Well, I pulled it off at the practice once,
so I thought I'd be able to do it here too...
Tsk. What a fucking moron.
The championships
aren't your class presentation.
You don't attempt skills
that you don't know how to do!
Isn't it inappropriate to say that?
Are you saying his Kovacs
and the triple somersault weren't amazing?
Doesn't matter how amazing your techniques are.
Gymnastics is all about the result.
9.2 is just 9.2.
Right, right. And he's nothing more
than a falling loser.
Those who can't score shit
aren't entitled to talk back to us.
Hiroshi already secured this event for us.
It would've been a total victory,
if not for Oike's stupid slip-up.
How can they say that? Even though Saito and others showed such great performances!
"Fun gymnastics?"
Do you really have the right
to talk about such nonsense
when none of your gymnasts managed
to beat any of mine in today's championships?
In that case, I must win.
And so, Saito's performance was scored with 9.2.
His signature skill was great, though.
He's just another cretin,
in the same league as Heisei!
Shut up!
And it's finally time for the final performance of today's All-Japan Junior Championships.
The final performer is Fujimaki Shun,
the first-year at Heisei.
What's wrong, Fujimaki?
Are you nervous?
No.
In that case, just relax and do your usual thing.
"Usual thing" won't do!
Fujimaki?
Is he going to change his program too?
That's unusual...
I never thought he was the type to let his emotions take over.
Lee Corps...
Shun, you mustn't forget about your own feelings
when considering what others would think.
Shun!
What happened to Fujimaki?
Shun-kun...
Fujimaki, calm down.
Here I go.
Fujimaki?
As expected, you're just
a third-rate coach, Andrianov.
Your gymnast got so worked up that he's completely stiff now.
I'll definitely win this.
Fujimaki-kun!
Why are you here, Sagara-san?
Did I... Did I make it in time?
Hey, Fujimaki-kun, are you done performing?
I was about to start...
Thank god...
S-Sagara-san...
I... I wanted to root for everyone!
I wanted to surprise you,
so I came from Fukui...
But I only made it in time
for your performance...
W-Well, please don't cry, Sagara-san.
Well... I...
You'll still get to see my routine, right?
Yeah... Yeah! I wouldn't forgive myself
if I missed your high bar!
My high bar?
Yeah... Yes!
Sagara-san.
Thank you!
Huh?
My high bar...
My high bar, huh?
Sagara-san, everyone gave it their best today.
I wish you saw it too...
Fujimaki, calm down.
It'll be fine, Captain.
I'm going to make it fun gymnastics,
just the way Coach Andrianov taught us.
Good, good. Well done, Mari-chan.
It looks like his strain is gone.
Yes...
I think it'd be better for you
to watch him perform.
Ganba, Fujimaki!
What happened, Fujimaki?
When I saw Sagara-san,
all those distant memories came back to life.
Distant memories?
I can't believe that I was able
to go to such a big tournament so soon.
Fujimaki-kun, you can do it!
Enter the goddess of victory!
Forget about everything else
and just enjoy your own performance to the fullest!
Come what may, Ganbarist Shun!
All right...
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
That's right, Shun!
It's a relaxed and fun gymnastics!
From backward swing...
He pulls up and flies over the bar!
Now, will he catch?
Attaway!
Do it like I did in the last tournament!
No way... Is he...
There it is!
The wings!
Next Ganba:
Ganba! Fly High for the Gold Medal!
Today we're learning a swing on the bar.
Overhand and underhand swing.
The swing consists of three points—
a "push, relax, and swing" triangle.
Push, relax, and swing.
Push, relax, and swing!