The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Forget about them!
You wanna let them get away with it?!
I don't care.
Uchida...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Strength Technique!
Hercules on the Rings
Episode
Strength Technique!
Hercules on the Rings
"What the rings are truly all about?"
How could you know that?
Do you think anything
can trump my performance now?
Oh! He is from Heisei too!
Higashi Denji (Heisei)
No wonder I thought something was different about him.
Put on a show, big guy!
Higashi Denji (Heisei)
He's just a fool!
A pathetic showoff with no real ability.
Higashi! This is your chance to put your muscles to use!
Higashi-senpai!
Higashi!
You can do it!
I'll go help him up.
Know your place, you damn upstart!
At best, you fucking clowns belong in a comedic gardening contest!
Hey, Higashi.
You may be the only one able
to stop the hegemony of the Lee Corps.
It pains me to say that,
but that's what I feel.
You're the strength specialist, and no other event highlights that as well as the rings.
Higashi-senpai, let me help you up.
Huh?
Well, do your best and all.
Don't let us down.
Um... What did Kamura-san want?
That's strange.
Higashi looks serious, unlike ever before.
Don't tell me he's going to arbitrary change his routine too? Please, not the human bridge on rings!
He won't be able even if he wanted to.
But Higashi-senpai really doesn't look like his usual self.
Higashi, don't panic.
Higashi-senpai?
Now, the next performer
is Higashi of Heisei Club!
Indeed, this athlete has quite the impressive physique, Kaizuka-san.
He might have some incredible strength techniques up his sleeve!
The rings performance
isn't limited to strength techniques.
He really doesn't know anything...
The highest score so far is 9.85, set by Saga of the Nishihori Club.
Can Higashi score more than 9.85?
Did we put unnecessary pressure on him
just before the performance?
Higashi! Show us those amazing strength techniques you displayed at the last district tournament again!
Cross Handstand!
Mochida...
Idiots. There's no way his composition includes any meaningful amount of strength techniques.
We already know that.
Remember.
No matter how much muscle you build,
it also adds to your weight, so you end up breaking even, more or less.
Oh, I see...
Unlike the floor, the rings also require a delicate sense of balance.
Does he look delicate to you?
Well, now that you mention it...
See? How about that, you geezer?
Just try to refute it! Come on! Try it!
You can either be ripped or be a gymnast.
We, the Lee Corps, are built different.
Coach Lee developed his own gymnastics theory
and a holistic training program, grounded in precise calculations
of instantaneous force, endurance, body weight, and other key factors.
There's no way you can possibly beat us.
Good luck, Muscles!
We're counting on you, Heisei!
And now, Higashi begins his performance!
Are you nervous, Higashi-senpai?
That was refreshing!
All right! Now I'll show 'em!
Oh, so he just needed to relax?
When Higashi farts,
it means he's in perfect shape.
Even if it stinks...
Did you hear anything just now?
I-It wasn't me.
Well, since nothing happened,
the performance may begin!
Higashi-senpai, do your best!
Damn right!
He starts from upside-down position...
We already know he's going to kick his way up.
What's there to be excited about?
Being that big is your main weakness!
At that weight, there's no way you can hold a static position for two seconds.
Wh-What?!
He immediately transitions
into a cross handstand!
H-He really is changing his routine!
Higashi... What are you...
I-Incredible! Higashi swung forward and transitioned straight into a cross handstand without any prep!
Nonsense! A cross handstand
right out of the gate?
To you, I will never lose!
A-And what's next?
Two in a row!
Good! Now hold it!
1, 2, smile!
What... He's still holding it!
Awesome!
"1, 2, smile?"
Can you believe it? Higashi pulled off
two cross handstands in a row—
effortlessly, and with a relaxed smile!
He pulled off my cross handstand with that big,
heavy body of his—and then did it twice?!
Smile...
Higashi clears the second cross handstand!
And now he pulls his arms together...
It's a straight handstand!
Seriously? Is he really just a junior gymnast?
Even a single cross handstand is a huge feat, let alone two!
Amazing! Amazing, Higashi-senpai!
1, 2, smile!
It really is cool!
Did he just say "smile" after two?
Ah, that's it!
That's what their secret training was about!
Smiling helps you relax and makes
your performance even more impactful!
It's the key to the fun gymnastics!
That's what they trained for.
Idiot! Jumping straight into strength techniques
like that will only drain your energy,
leaving you hanging helplessly for the rest of the routine.
By pushing so hard to surpass my cross handstand,
you just sealed your own fate!
The main show only starts now.
Now, after that straight handstand, Higashi is probably going
to switch to some dynamic techniques
like a swing on the rings to give his arms a break...
H-How is that possible? It's an upper planche!
Another strength technique!
This is absurd... There has to be a limit
to how much of those he can do!
1, 2, smile!
Smile...
He's smiling!
He's a lot more relaxed than Saga!
N-No way...
The best part is yet to come.
I-It can't be!
1, 2...
Smile!
It's a straight -senpai this time!
H-How is that possible...
I'm still not done!
Is it...
It really is that!
Lower planche!
Can you believe that?!
He went from upper to straight to lower planche!
It's a planche parade!
It can't be...
1, 2...
Smile!
Smile...
What's going on?
What is that guy?!
One more for the boys...
There!
Wow! How does he still have
the strength for that?!
He finishes it off with an iron cross!
I-Impossible!
W-With this, he has to defeat the Lee Corps...
1, 2...
Smayle!
He cleared it!
He nailed the iron cross as well!
I can't believe it...
From multiple cross handstands,
he transitioned into a straight handstand,
followed by an upper, straight, and lower planche—
then seamlessly moved into an iron cross?!
How?! How does he have
the strength to keep doing that?!
Ah! But wait! He's rising again!
Here it is!
Straight-arm, straight-body press handstand!
1, 2...
Smile!
And what is his finishing move?
He lands with a double
tucked up somersault and nails it!
1, 2...
Smile!
Wait, he's just like...
Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
It can't be... It can't be for real!
Denji! Horosho! Wonderful!
Nice!
I feel like some hero from Greece history!
Higashi-senpai, that was amazing!
Nicely done, Higashi!
Your catchphrase
is "Hercules" starting today.
Hey, Hercules!
Yeah!
Higashi...
It looks like the judges have finished discussing.
We'll finally see his score!
We've got this!
Currently, first place
is held by Saga with his 9.85.
Are we going to see a perfect score of 10.0?
Hurry up!
And his score is...
9... 9.6?
What?
Did they mean to make it 9.90?
The score is too low!
What's going on?
We need an explanation!
You got a death wish?!
I-It's certainly a question how it came to this.
A storm of boos is sweeping through the audience all at once!
Raise the score!
What's going on?
Higashi's moves were more dynamic,
compared to the Lee Corps athlete.
If Saga got 9.85,
Higashi should have even more than that.
I won...
Did I really win?
You won.
The score proves that.
We couldn't win against the Lee Corps...
How come? After all those strength techniques he'd shown!
His performance was miles ahead
of that of the Lee Corps!
Captain...
How did it happen?
Higashi's performance blew the audience away!
Then why...?
Dear spectators,
please maintain order!
The score just awarded was based on the official scoring criteria
and provides a fair evaluation of Higashi's performance.
What is he saying?
Official scoring criteria?
Wait a minute!
Coach!
What the—someone just jumped off the high balcony, landed so lightly,
and is now heading
straight for the referees!
Who might that foreigner be?!
What do you want?
You guys don't understand a thing
about gymnastics!
What?
What do you mean
we don't understand gymnastics?
I mean exactly what I said!
Hey, did they forget
the microphone is still on?
Whatever this is about,
it looks interesting!
Power to you, weird mister!
If someone is still not convinced,
I'll do the explaining.
Head judge...
Higashi of Heisei
had a flawed routine composition.
Hm?
Its flaw is in the lack
of dynamic techniques.
The criteria state
that the rings performance must combine dynamic, static, and strength techniques.
Dynamic techniques
Static techniques
Strength techniques
However, Higashi's composition, being biased toward strength and static techniques,
was a factor in lowering his score.
Saga also performed
cross handstand and iron cross.
We can't award Higashi with more points than Saga for the same technique.
"The same technique?"
Do they look the same to you?!
Why don't you demonstrate it, then?
The best way to demonstrate the difference is by showing it.
You can do it, right?
Who are you?
That geezer!
What the hell is he doing there?!
Don't you know who that is?
What?!
He's the one who developed all the Japanese gymnasts
competing on the world stage,
including myself.
M-Morisue-san?
You say he developed you?
That geezer?
Yeah. I couldn't possibly be more indebted to Onuma-san.
Onuma?
Onuma...
Could he be the one
behind Japan's men's gymnastics team's legendary 10-game winning streak,
starting with the Rome Olympics?
The "Legendary Assistant,"
Onuma Shigeaki?
Really? So you didn't know?
Things have really escalated quickly here!
An unidentified foreigner rushed from the audience and began arguing with the judges!
And he's preparing to climb the rings right now!
Huh? I wonder if that guy is even a gymnast.
He's probably just bluffing.
Coach Andrianov...
Don't worry about anything, Denji.
I'll show them that your performance really was the Ultra G tier.
As well as what really matters in gymnastics.
And now, the mysterious foreigner starts from an upside down pose...
Oh, what a surprise!
He kicks up and into a handstand!
What's with that foreigner?
He's probably not an amateur!
Coach Misaki, nobody's got a clue.
They'd be amazed to find out who he is.
Please watch closely. He will now show us how Saga performed his cross handstand.
What?
Hm... That does look like Saga's.
And now—Higashi's cross handstand.
I see! The difference is in their grip.
Higashi fully bent his wrists outward and held the rings
Saga
Higashi
much farther from his center
of mass than Saga did.
Saga
Higashi
That makes it much more difficult.
Saga
Higashi
Moreover, Higashi also spread his arms wider.
Saga
Higashi
Furthermore, here is Higashi's iron cross.
Oh!
Here, the grip was also different!
Really?
So Saga was cutting corners?
No, both are considered a cross handstand
and an iron cross, with the same difficulty rating.
So it doesn't affect the difficulty rating?
So then, Higashi was just tiring himself out for nothing?
However,
if the performance is deemed outstanding,
bonus points may be awarded.
Add points!
Recognize it!
Hey judges! Add the points!
Recognize Higashi!
Such a reaction from the audience...
Everyone here understands—
Higashi's performance was wonderful.
Bonus points...?
This might just do the trick!
It's wonderful...
What a wonderful atmosphere!
Add points!
Hurry up!
Add points already!
Ugh! I can't believe we let that unintelligible foreigner take everyone for a ride!
Oh, everyone, I forgot to tell you
something important.
What else is there?
This man, who just gave us a stunning demonstration on the rings,
is former gymnastics world champion
and Montreal Olympic rings gold medalist,
Sergei Andrianov.
S-Sergei?
C-Can you believe it?!
The foreigner who appeared uninvited was former world gymnastics champion Sergei Andrianov!
What a treat to see the great rings gold medalist
perform once again, right here!
Bonus points! Bonus points!
Oh! The crowd is chanting, "Bonus points!"
Bonus points!
Looks like the judges are deliberating again!
You've got the whole crowd
on your side, Higashi!
But will they heed it and raise the points?
If so, you'll overtake Saga
and take the first place!
Ultra comeback, Ganbarist Denji!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Coach...
Gymnastics is all about the points.
There's no place for humanity
in our scientifically perfect gymnastics.
He nailed it! The layout Cuervo!
And the next performer is...
Uchida of Heisei Club!
I will win!
Next Ganba: It's Impossible!
The Death of Uchida Minoru's Vault?!
Today, we're doing front hip circle on a bar.
It's a technique to kick the air with your feet.
The main difficulty is kicking.
Swing hard, then pick a timing to kick...
I think it makes more sense to kick while swinging backward, rather than from the frontmost position.