The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
Morisue-san won the gold medal on the high bar at the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics.
This is the story of our young heroes
rising to become the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal!
Their goal is the last Olympics of the 20th century!
Sydney '2000
Ganba!
Don't let go now!
R-Regrouped in the air?
Shun has...
become a bird!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Transfer Student!
Doing a Back Hip Circle in a Sailor Uniform
You got that?
Top six. Or else...
The club will be disbanded!
D-Demon...!
Taking the high bar from us wasn't enough?
That old hag acts like the women's club deserves everything under the sun!
Did you say something,
three little dolts?
Three dolts?
The "Three Dolts" special program
in the stream of embarrassment—isn't it about you?
Precisely.
That hag...
She'll never stop making fun of us!
It’s all part of her scheme.
Since it was decided by the board of directors,
there won't be taking it back.
We have to do it, somehow.
Captain, how many points do we need to score to place 6th in the district?
Oh... Let me think, who made it to the top six in the last tournament...?
Gyotoku Middle School.
Gyotoku Middle School placed 6th with 79 points.
Madam, how do you know this?
Heisei
Gymnastics
Club
Data
Don't you underestimate me.
You’re full of surprises.
In team competitions, the scores of the top three members of the team are totaled for each event.
Floor
High bar
Vaulting
If you score the maximum 10 points in each event, then the total for the three events will be 90 points.
Gyotoku School at 6th place had 79 points
across three events.
Divided by 9 for 3 people,
the average is about 8.8 per person.
What did our team score last time?
55 points.
55 divided by 9... That's...
About 6.1 per person.
Really? So we're just a few points short of 8.8?
That's the most difficult part.
Huh? Wait a minute, last time I got 8.5 on the floor,
7.5 on the high bar, and 8.5 in vaulting.
Why is our average score still so low?
That's no secret.
I see, so that's what happened?
It's because of Fujidiot, Uchidiot, and Sanadiot
dragging us down?
Don't lump us together!
I was only trying to get our performance called off for lack of members!
And that's why Fujidiot had to perform too!
U-Um, but my points were cut off...
First off, it was my zero points that got cut off.
So what?
Weren't you way below the Captain in score yourself?
It wasn't even worth mentioning!
One way or another, we've got to boost our average from 6.1 to over 8.8!
Yes, that is the main problem.
You guys are so dense.
You just need to score 6th, right?
Then we can find a way to do it.
However, you'll need to break a sweat for that.
We'll do our best!
With Ultra Ganba!
That's what I wanted to hear.
Well then, shall we try it?
Operation Ultra Ganba Part 2!
Yes!
Your first priority should be mastering more difficult techniques.
Up until now, your routines have mostly consisted of basic techniques.
Even if you perfect those,
they won’t score many points.
You're asking for too much.
If it was just the bar, we could get by,
but there are two other events as well!
I know that. Therefore, each of you will master one special technique that'll amaze the judges
in an event you're good at,
aiming for a personal score of 9.2 or higher.
9.2 in each event?
Glasses, you're good at vaulting, right?
We'll have you perform
a double front somersault.
Double front somersault...?
Double front somersault
Yeah!
You, the Muscle. You prefer techniques that allow you to show off your strength, right?
You'll perform the straight-arm, straight-body handstand.
Straight-arm, straight-body handstand!
Straight-arm, straight-body handstand
Yeah...
Uh... Wait a minute,
I'm the prince of floor here!
What are you talking about?
You have a Jaeger
that's worth a 30-carat diamond.
Diamond?
Diamond, all right!
What a Flathead!
Um, what about me?
It's all at once.
All?
You already have an average
above 8 points, right?
All you need to do is polish whatever you're doing now.
Okay...
We've got two months until the tournament
Spend the first month
learning more difficult techniques.
Then spend the remaining month perfecting the execution. All right?
Okay, let's do it!
Madam, isn't there something I could do?
You just need to keep doing what you usually do,
and you'll be all set.
That's right, only up to four members can perform.
Just leave it to us and relax!
Performing as usual?
I know I'm not a full-fledged member yet,
but I feel overlooked.
Wow! Shun-kun, you can do backflips so easily?
If only a little.
Even a backflip that smooth is amazing!
Let go! I'll go first!
Out of my way!
What the... Are you stupid?
My technique needs to be polished first!
I see. Fujimaki's presence alone motivates everyone, pushing us to aim for a better team score.
Isn't that right, Madam?
Yes, of course it worked like a charm.
Oh my, Eri, who do you think I am?
We're reviewing materials and brainstorming new supreme techniques.
Look forward to seeing the results in two months!
Supreme technique...?
It could be really helpful
if I learned something new too.
Okay, take your seats, everyone.
Sagara
This is Sagara Mariko, our new transfer student.
Treat her well, will you?
Mariko
Nice to meet you all.
You can sit over there.
Okay.
Oh? Her uniform is a sailor suit.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
Yes, hello.
Who are you?
Sagara-san, did you choose a club already?
At our school, you have to enroll
in some athletic club.
Not yet...
I'm in a pickle.
How about the volleyball club?
Well, I...
You can do it when you launch off the high bar at this angle...
Eh? Ah... This book...!
Artistic Gymnastics
Is it about the bar?
I need it for a moment!
What is this book?
No... It's not here!
Are you exercising on the high bar?
Huh? High bar?
Yeah, we do.
We're in the gymnastics club.
Gymnastics club?
Um... If it's not too much of a bother,
could you teach me how to do a back hip circle?
Back hip circle?
Run up...
Run up and... Jump!
Run up!
Got you!
Whatcha so relaxed about?
What a jerk!
Come on, everyone, take a tea break!
Aye-aye!
There's no need to rush.
Pushing yourself too hard won't do you any good.
Okay!
Fujimaki, you come here too!
What's that guy doing?
Is that a back hip circle?
If it's not too much of a bother,
could you teach me how to do a back hip circle?
Sagara Mariko...
What an odd girl.
You see, back at my previous school,
they nicknamed me "Turtle."
Turtle?
It's to say that I'm sluggish.
Before that, at the elementary
school, I was "Flatfish."
Before that—Miss Slow.
There were also "Li'l Mariko, Lame Duck,
Helpless Girl," et cetera.
The worst one was probably "Potato."
I wonder what they meant by that.
Th-That's quite an impressive list.
Did you really change schools that many times?
Yeah.
I'm a wandering transfer girl.
One more thing I noticed is that those nicknames always came after gym class.
Do you understand
what this means, Fujimaki-kun?
What I'm saying is...
It seems I'm just hopeless
when it comes to sports.
Is that why I must teach you
the back hip circle?
Just think about it.
If I can't even do this,
I'll be at a loss during the class.
I'll probably feel embarrassed.
Pathetic, even.
See?
I-I mean, it's okay if you don't wanna...
N-No...
I understand!
Huh?
I know exactly how you feel!
I really do!
Huh?
I-In truth, I'm not good at sports either.
I know how it feels to be rejected by a place!
Rejected by a place?
Ah... I'm not sure you do understand.
But you mustn't run away!
Changing schools won't solve anything!
You have to face challenges head-on!
I transferred because of my dad's job, though...
You’ll be fine.
Trust me, I’ll make sure of it!
Sure!
Let's start—this is overhand grip.
And this is the underhand grip.
You can use whichever is easier for you.
Hold it at shoulder-width.
As you pull your belly up to the bar,
sharply kick your legs.
Got it? Like this...
See?
Wow! You're good!
I also couldn't do the back hip circle
until I joined the gymnastics club.
But then it came naturally to me.
Eventually, I realized the main point: whatever you do, do it with confidence.
Okay, now you give it a shot.
Huh? I'll probably try on this one first. It's lower.
Sure.
Promise not to laugh.
All right...
Yeah, I guess I'm a lost cause, after all...
Once more!
Wait, it's dangerous!
Ow...
I screwed up.
Did you see them?
W-Wear your gym clothes next time, okay?
This'll be harder than I thought.
Wow, impressive!
Are they really in middle school?
The Heisei gymnastics club is one of a kind.
Huh? No, you see...
Only the women's team of it is outstanding.
Huh?
But the men's team is going
to get really great really soon too.
Whatcha talking about?
You're hanging out with a girl?
That's new.
Oh, you see... She's a transfer student and she wanted to know what our gymnastics club is like.
My name is Sagara Mariko.
I promise not to interfere with your practice,
so can we take just a quick tour?
Eh? Ah, sure... Be our guest!
Thank you!
When you get to know her, Sagara-san is nothing like how she seems at first.
Yeah...
Sailor uniform, huh?
She's pretty.
Pft. She's but a brat,
compared to our Reiko-sama.
Start practicing!
Aye-aye...
Hold me tight, dammit!
O-Okay, sorry!
These muscles are quite something!
That's right, Higashi-senpai
is the club's muscle...
Hey! Where are you going, Sagara-san?
Hey, Fujimaki-kun, what are you doing?
Those push-ups look weird.
That's because Higashi-senpai needs strength training for the new technique
he'll use in the upcoming tournament.
Oh?
It looks difficult...
Wow, they're so hard!
Awesome!
The hell you ticking me for?!
I'm sorry!
He's overdoing it.
There are those who can't jump even in the in the gymnastics club! He's just like me!
Hey, that wasn't very nice of you.
I'm sorry!
I'll have you know, the vaulting is actually my specialty.
Why didn't you jump, then?
It was mental training.
When you become a true specialist like me,
you'll also place great emphasis on mental training.
Right...
In the upcoming tournament,
I must achieve the highest score in vaulting.
I'm working on a secret plan for that.
So what's important here
is the rhythm when you jump.
The rhythm for kicking the springboard,
launching, and landing
needs to change from the usual "ton-ton-ton" to "to-to-ton!"
Got it? In other words, I need to...
Huh? She left!
She's so... So...
So disrespectful!
Hey, Lady!
Up here!
Hi!
What are you doing up there?
I'm contemplating the future of our club.
The future of this club truly hinges on the upcoming tournament.
Everyone is working hard.
Oh... It sounds like you're having a tough time.
No, we'll manage.
After all, there's me—the Prince of Floor with a diamond Jaeger, Sanada Toshihiko.
Hey... Where are you going? Wait!
Fujimaki-kun, gymnastics club looks fun.
If I have to choose something,
I think I'll join the gymnastics club.
Huh? are you serious, Sagara-san?
Yeah!
Then, I'll introduce you to Reiko-senpai.
Uh? Wait, Fujimaki-kun!
Get back here, Fujimaki!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Reiko-senpai!
What is it, Shun-kun?
"Shun-kun?"
This girl wants to join the gymnastics club.
Reiko-senpai is an Olympic team candidate.
Oh come on, Shun-kun!
If you train with Reiko-senpai,
you'll definitely improve.
She never forgets the important points!
Thanks to that, even I got better in no time!
Shun-kun, that's enough promoting me for now.
I'm Orikasa, the third-year.
Nice to meet you.
Let me show you around.
The women's club is this way.
Why are you daydreaming here?
Who's gonna support me?
Your care is wasted on her!
She'll quit in three days!
Huh?
I don't see her putting up with the rigorous training of our women's club either.
She wouldn't last more than a day here.
No way! Reiko-senpai is a very kind mentor,
so she'll totally be fine!
Humph! Even Reiko-sama's help won't be enough.
Exactly! Come on, we gotta work!
Why did you want to join
the gymnastics club?
Oh?
Is there something you're good at?
No, it's just...
It's not the women's gymnastics club
that I want to join.
Eh?
The club I want to join
is the men's gymnastics club!
Huh?!
Sagara-san!
Wh-What are you saying, Sagara-san?
How can a girl do that?!
Sorry for wasting your time!
I'm gonna join the men's gymnastics club!
Ah... Sagara-san!
I-I’m sorry, Reiko-senpai!
So that's what Fujimaki-kun's type is like?
Maybe even "a day" was too optimistic of a prediction.
He's fawning on her so much!
Did you see them? Did you?
She's a better fit for the men's club.
Please take care of me!
I'll do my best!
What are we gonna do?
Well...
Maybe we can make it work.
Hooray!
A female member in the men's gymnastics club? Are you sure that'll work out well?
But if it lifts everyone's spirits,
well, that's not such a bad thing.
The summer tournament is fast approaching!
You all worked hard to secure 6th place!
Go strong on your path to the gold medal,
Ganbarist Shun!
I saw it again...
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
What can you do in just one month?
There's no way...
You're no longer our Captain?
When I told you about the gold medal,
you didn't laugh, but instead said that if I dream big, I must work hard for it.
Didn't you tell me to dream big?!
Captain! I beg you not to quit!
Let me alone already!
Next Ganba: No Way!
Captain Quits the Club.
Thomas flair is performed on top of a 110-cm tall pommel horse with your legs apart.
And when you do it with your feet together, it's called circle.
Speed and size are then appraised.
This is the most stressful event out of six.