Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
Fujimaki-kun, I know you can do it.
Start!
You can do it, Fujimaki!
Fujimaki-kun, stay strong!
I can't take it anymore...
I can't balance...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
This is it!
The Grand Backflip in the Sunset
How?
How can you do it for so long?
That's because what you did
was a simple headstand.
But what I did was a handstand I learned from my senpai.
We don't have any choice.
No, if anything, it's a matter of course.
The men’s gymnastics club’s lackluster performance over the past few years is no longer tolerable.
They won’t have a leg to stand on
if we disband the club now.
You’re still on the first circle of hell!
You'll like the second circle even more.
I'm Ueno Yoshio, sir.
Thanks for having me!
With a second new member this year, we’ve got to work hard for the summer tournament.
Yessir!
Gimme a break, please!
Get back here, dammit!
All right, first-years, we'll start practicing backflips today.
B-Backflips?
Backflip! It's that trick the movie heroes
always do for some reason.
That cool trick that heroes do!
I-I-I'll do it! Backflip! I'll do it!
Can I really do a backflip?
Sanada, teach the first-years
how to do a backflip.
Oh? Want me to do it?
Well, I am the only one capable enough.
All right, guess there's no choice.
Not that I'm happy with it, of course.
That means I'll have to skip my own training.
You do look mighty happy, though!
He hates training more than anyone here.
Well then, my unfortunate first-years.
As you can see, I got roped into teaching you the backflip.
Yessir!
Watch closely.
This is a backflip—
or more formally, a back handspring.
By the way, I'll have you know, I'm the club's most advanced expert in backward somersaults.
A man whose backflips are impeccable.
They call me the Prince of Floor.
The Prince of Floor
Th-The Prince of Floor?
Yep, the Prince of Floor. And you’d better believe they’ll carve that title into my monument.
Who ever called you that?
First time I hear of it!
Shut up!
Listen up, you two. Nail the backflip, and the girls will be all over you.
Huh? All over us?
Ah!
I-I'll do my best!
Good, let's start practicing then.
Yessir!
The amateurs think that a backflip
is more difficult than a frontflip.
But really, the backflip is much easier!
That’s because during a frontflip, you can see the ground when you take off, but not when you land.
And while you can't see the ground at first
in backflip, when it's time to land...
What are you two doing?
What's wrong? Come on, jump!
O-Okay!
How's that a backflip?
I-I'm too scared to do it!
Can't do it!!
Backflip is easy once you defeat the fear of jumping backwards.
Why do you look so surprised?
That was a backflip.
It's easy.
Try it with Ueno next.
Good. Once you get used to it,
you can do it quickly.
You need to raise your legs yourself, Fujimaki.
Got it!
He's right. From the moment my hands hit the mat
to when I land, I can see it clearly.
A backflip really is a lot safer.
I can see my hands
and fix them firmly on the mat.
Good! Next we'll practice jumping.
Huh?
Jumping?
C'mon, swing your arms more.
L-Like this?
Okay, now just twist your body
and kick the mat in one smooth motion.
Okay.
For now, I’ll support you
so you don’t land on your butt.
Good children would not practice backflips without assistance.
When your hands land,
push off as hard as you can.
Good luck, Fujimaki-kun.
Okay... I'm starting!
I'm ready!
Good!
That's dangerous!
Stop! Don't do it!
Are you okay?
Ouch...
What happened?
I-I don't know...
Reiko-senpai stopped us.
Well... Try jumping again, but slowly.
Okay.
I support him so he doesn't fall...
First, I swing my arms back as hard as I can,
though it's a bit scary.
Then jump with all my might!
Stop! That's it!
Huh?
All your fingertips are facing outward.
If you backflip like that, you'll dislocate them!
Dislocate?
There’s no spinning involved in a backflip, so if your fingertips are pointed outward,
your wrists and elbows
will be locked when you land.
That means they’ll stay straight and won’t be able to absorb the impact,
leaving nowhere for the inertia to go.
You're right, I can't bend them this way.
When doing a backflip, make sure your fingertips are facing inward when you land.
That way, the inertia will be able to escape.
Sanada-senpai! It turns out,
the backflips are so complex!
Y-Yeah...
How would he know if he’s always slacking off during training?
He was this close to getting this amateur badly injured!
My bad.
"My bad" won't cut it!
That'll teach you!
Thanks.
All right!
Let's resume practice now.
Now you try, Ueno.
Good children would not practice backflips without assistance.
O-Okay...
I-I-I'm starting!
Ueno-kun is practicing pile driving!
Guess you'd better
build up your arm strength first.
Okay...
Let's go!
Fujimaki-kun, you can do it!
I did it!
That's amazing, Fujimaki-kun!
You're already so good at backflip!
Oh, I'm sure you can do it too.
I'm still far from your level.
But practicing every morning already pays off.
To think I'd be able to do a backflip myself!
I'm so glad I joined the gymnastics club.
Being able to do something you never even considered is so inspiring! I mean it.
I know, right?
Hey, how did you become interested in gymnastics, Fujimaki-kun?
Uh?
I've decided that I want to win a gold medal at the Olympics
G-Gold medal!?
Are you serious? Doesn't that mean becoming the best in the world?
The best in the world, then?
Gymnastics includes individual events, all-around events, and team events.
That means a person can win up to eight medals
in a single tournament.
I'll try chaining several backflips together now.
Chaining them?
Aren't you pushing it a bit too far?
Don't worry.
I feel that I can do it.
Watch this, consecutive backflips!
One...
Two...
I did it!
You really did!
I did it! Consecutive backflips!
Now you're one step closer to the gold medal!
Yeah!
What's the ruckus?
Good morning.
You’re so eager this early in the morning!
Good morning, Reiko-senpai!
Fujimaki-kun is awesome!
He can already do backflips continuously.
Continuously?
That's impressive!
You've only been training for a few days.
So, do you think you can make it to me from there
with nothing but backflips, Fujimaki-kun?
Uh?
Go ahead, Shun-kun!
O-Okay!
Can you really make it that far?
It should be fine.
It's only about five meters.
I'm starting!
There!
You can do it, Fujimaki-kun!
2, 3...
Reiko-senpai!
How was it, Reiko-senpai?
Huh?
Whaa...?
What's wrong, Shun-kun?
I-I'll be there in a moment!
It's strange...
I'm jumping so hard...
All right...
I'll make it there,
even if it takes 10 or 20 backflips!
What do you think?
You're not really moving
towards her, Fujimaki-kun.
Huh?
Wh-Why?
What's going on?
You wanna know, don't you?
Therefore, if we make this kind of presupposition,
we can obtain the conclusion by means of logic...
Are you unwell, Fujimaki-kun?
I got it!
My jumping power is insufficient!
It’s not about just backflipping endlessly in the same spot.
I must push harder with my legs and fly higher!
Also, swing my arms more energetically!
Fujimaki, keep standing for the rest of the class.
O-Okay...
Want to train your legs?
Yes!
Then this training is what the doctor ordered!
Squat!
What about learning the backflip?
Um, actually...
Huh? So he decided to train his legs for that?
He's so short-sighted.
Hey, Fujimaki, come here.
What is it?
Start backflipping from here.
But I need to train my legs first.
Don't argue, just do it.
I-I'll do it...
Okay, try jumping like you did in the morning.
Okay, I'm starting!
Wh-What did you do that for?
If you push my knee,
of course I'll fall backwards!
Jump just before you fall.
Huh?
Okay, let's try again with my support.
Good children would not practice backflips without assistance.
Ueno, make sure to push his legs.
Okay.
Fujimaki-kun, good luck.
Now! Jump!
So low!
Now! Push away!
Wh-What!? I jumped so far!
Training your legs won't accomplish anything.
Yours is a circus backflip.
With your knees sticking out.
My knees sticking out?
When your knees are ahead of your feet, in other words, when you jump with your knees sticking out,
you jump high,
but with no horizontal force.
So, to jump far with a backflip,
you need to make sure your knees don’t stick out and that the force of the jump is directed backwards.
So that's how it works?
Now, try again without my support.
You don't know even a fraction of the backflip yet.
Okay!
Reiko-senpai!
Shun-kun?
Done!
Sh-Shun-kun...
I couldn't wait...
I couldn't wait to show it to you!
Shun-kun...
Saw that, you first-year ding-dongs?!
This is called giant!
A-Amazing...
As expected of Higashi-senpai...
Almost as amazing as these muscles!
You two will train to do giant swing too, starting today.
Huh?
Come on, get ready!
Wow! Can't wait!
It looks scary.
Can I really perform a giant swing?
Men's club, I'll bring it home to you
just how perilous your position is.
All right, that's a good swing. Keep it up and you'll master the giant in no time!
Is that true?
There we go again with Captain's flattery...
Yes, that's great! Keep it up!
He really thinks he can master giant that soon?
Swing harder!
Aim to soar right over the bar!
O-Okay!
You can do it! Almost there!
It's a waste of time.
Enough.
No more playing gymnasts for you.
Coach Misaki!
Orikasa.
Yes?
Good morning, Coach Misaki!
Set up the uneven bars for the women.
We're dismantling this high bar.
C-Coach?
Just a moment there, Coach!
Shindo-kun, sorry, but the entire gymnasium is reserved for the women's club now.
Who is that?
The coach of the women's club...
and the part-time supervisor of our men's club.
Back from the retraining already?
Isn't there already a set of uneven bars
set up right next to it?
The men's club also needs...
The women's club has over 30 members.
One set is not enough for them.
The women’s club is made up of girls who’ve been training
since they first went to school to become All-Japan champions.
The school and parents
have high hopes for them.
They stand in stark contrast to the men's club—
the worst in the prefecture.
We know that already.
When you try to rub it in...
You only irritate me more!
Go ahead, first-years.
Start dismantling the high bar.
O-Okay!
No way!
We're not going anywhere!
You are evil!
Stop messing around!
We have no business letting those who aren't aiming for results practice in vain.
But I am...
I am aiming for results!
That's what I practice for!
With all my strength!
For results? What results can a klutz, who can't even do a giant swing, show?
Come on, put away the bar.
I can... do a giant!
If I can make a giant,
promise to let us keep the high bar!
F-Fujimaki...
That's interesting.
I'll think about it if you can.
Wait, please! Fujimaki's just getting started with gymnastics...
Captain, if he's our last chance,
I'll bet on Fujimaki!
Yeah, yeah!
Better that than passively letting them
take away our high bar!
You can do it, Fujimaki!
Aim to soar over it!
F-Fujimaki...
Shun-kun...
We're not doing gymnastics just for kicks!
I'll do it!
Giant...
He managed to rise above it!
Yes, that's good!
Just start moving from there...
Start moving and you'll make a giant swing!
Shun-kun...
After making it that far...
Why...
Did he fall?
As I said, you were just playing gymnastics.
Now, step away and let us put away the high bar.
Wait... Please wait!
What else do you expect me to wait for now?
I am... I really am still a beginner.
And I can't argue with you when you say I'm just playing at gymnastics.
But...
It's not like that for the other guys!
Huh?
If you'd seen their performance, you'd never think about putting away the high bar!
Isn't that right?
Oh, really?
Did you guys manage to get so good so fast?
N-Not really...
Fine! Give us a week!
We'll show you in a week!
Th-That's right!
Our technique will blast you away!
I'm fired up!
A week! Give us a week!
H-Hey, guys...
Guys!
One week!
Just give us a week!
All right. You piqued my interest.
I'd like to see you prove that the boys' club
isn't a disgrace to Heisei School.
A disgrace...
to Heisei School?!
Now you've done it!
It's a showdown!
Newbie gymnastics club member Fujimaki Shun,
the road to the gold medal is endlessly long.
You can now do consecutive backflips now,
but as soon as you started learning giant swings,
something unthinkable has happened!
Hey, Shun, are you sure you should've said it?
After all, it's do or die now!
Go forth, Ganbarist Shun!
It's a Showdown!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
What should I do...
So many people have come to see us.
So, are you doing fine?
Y-Yes!
You seem nervous, though.
Yeah, a bit...
Good luck. Remember that if everyone works hard,
Coach Misaki will let you keep the high bar.
I hope your wonderful performance makes all these people charmed with gymnastics.
See you.
Reiko-senpai...
Next Gamba: It's a Showdown!
A Performance that we've got to Nail!
Acrobatic jumping techniques that utilize the elasticity
of the floor are becoming increasingly sophisticated.
The awesomeness of the somersault finisher is outstanding!
Among them, the backward triple tucked somersault—Ultra E.
And the variations of Ultra E
grow ever more numerous!