The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Why are you laughing?
What’s wrong with pushing yourself
to a higher level?
Fujimaki!
You brat!
Don't get cocky!
I have to try it...
I have to try!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
I'm Motivated!
Peeping, Ocean and Intense Practice
There!
Fujimaki...
I think I accidentally destroyed Morisue's signature and footprint.
Is it too bad?
What on earth?
What is this kid?
Forget touching the ceiling,
he broke right through it...
Who's that brat?
Man, he's still in middle school,
but you can't underestimate him!
That shrimp is from Heisei Middle School.
I think it's their first time in this training camp.
Fujimaki-kun, you're actually great at this!
Fujimaki!
Yes?
Well done!
Huh?
That made us look cool!
You're a capable learner!
Hey Fujimaki, are you okay?
Yes.
I just hit my knee a bit, that's all.
You’re lucky to get away
with just a hit on the knee.
Director Sotoyama?
If you hadn't have reached the ceiling,
things might've turned out a lot worse for you.
Huh?
To reach the footprints on the ceiling,
you deliberately changed the timings of your relax, and swing stages.
Yes...
If you jump with that kind of timing
but without a ceiling above you...
You wouldn't have fallen in front of the bar.
You would’ve crashed shin-first into the bar from right above.
Ugh...
Sounds painful!
Once there was a guy who fell on the bar so hard, he broke both his legs, with bones sticking out.
Hey, I don't think it's a laughing matter.
Still, being able to fly that high
is quite an achievement.
Keep it up and don’t fear failure. Keep improving your technique with confidence. Good luck!
Okay!
All right, let's take a 20 minute break, everyone.
Aye-aye!
Hey, Fujimaki-kun!
Ah, he looked this way!
Cute!
You're from the same school
as Reiko-san, right?
That was super amazing just now!
He's blushing!
Hey, could you show us that jump again?
That was the same one
I used on the last tournament.
The one that defeated Kamura-kun, right?
Do it, do it!
What's that?
Seems like Fujimaki's harem...
Sorry to interrupt your break like that...
It's okay, no problem.
That jerk is totally getting carried away!
Good luck.
Just a back hip circle?
Just a roll forward?
He got off.
Hey, what is Fujimaki doing?
What's wrong, Shun-kun?
I'm just a bit...
Is it because of the knee you hit earlier?
Oh no, you could've just told us!
You could've just told us.
Okay, break is over.
Resume the training!
Yessir!
This should cool it down.
Thank you.
See you.
Yes...
Let's begin!
Is your knee better?
Ah... Yes, it's all good now.
Just looking at it won't suffice.
That was never my intention.
I have a lot to learn here.
Even seeing those techniques for the first time, I picture this gym during the performance,
and it feels like I’m doing it myself.
Oh? You picture it
from the athlete's perspective?
For example, that technique that Kobayakawa-san has been practicing for a while now.
The Tsukahara Vault?
He runs steadily, then handsprings sharply!
Bang! Quarter twist and landing! Thud!
That's what I mean.
You do that in your imagination?
Cartwheel jumps, quarter twists, and rear tucked somersaults?
Yes!
I guess I'll give it a try too.
H-Hey...
Throb. Bang! Twist. Roll. Thud!
Throb. Bang! Twist. Roll. Thud.
Throb. Bang! Twist. Roll! Thud.
Throb. Bang. Twist. Roll. Thud!
Throb! Bang! Twist. Roll. Thud!
Throb! Bang. Twist. Roll. Thud!
Throb. Bang! Twist. Roll. Thud!
Throb! Bang! Twist! Roll! Thud!
Yeah.
Throb!
Bang!
Twist...
What?
You can already move your body based on your imagination after just seeing it?
I guess, something like that.
That height on high bar...
This vaulting prowess...
It's like he was born for gymnastics!
This kid has a bright future ahead of him!
All right, that's all for today's practice.
Man, he worked us so hard today...
My calves are also swollen tonight!
Dammit, I'm so tired...
I'm completely exhausted.
Of course junior practice
isn’t a walk in the park!
Man, the bath you have here is amazing!
The bubbles kept coming out!
Really, it was the first time
I've seen anything like that.
I especially hate losing to this village yokel!
Um... Aren't you going to the bath too, guys?
Ah!
What happened?
It's a bath, you hear?
So what?
It might still not be too late. Let's go!
Where to?
To go peeping, of course!
Peeping?
What's wrong?
You look downbeat.
No...
What's on your mind?
I keep wondering why they called us
to this training camp.
Shindo-kun...
As expected, the junior level is out of this world.
Compared to that, we're just some upstarts from a regional tournament.
That's not true.
Orikasa...
You gave a wonderful performance.
I was moved.
Right, but I couldn't even
take part in that tournament.
Hey, did you take piano lessons, Shindo-kun?
Huh?
Yeah, back when I was little...
But I quit it very soon.
Try playing from where you left off.
I also learned a bit of it when I was little.
It was your presence that brought everyone together, wasn’t it?
It's thanks to you
that everyone could do their best.
I really think you need to be more confident.
Confident?
Yeah. And do your best!
I'll do just that, then...
Main communal bath
Open time
After me!
Main communal bath
Open time
Guys, it's a bad idea, let's stop now.
Be quiet, you idiot!
It's too late to have a cold feet now!
Yes, but I don't really...
Okay...
Guys...!
Guys!
What are you doing there, guys?
You! What the hell are you doing there?!
Hey, that's unfair!
Too bad.
By the way, where are the rest of our guys?
Dunno.
Bummer...
Hey, why am I also here?
Yes, keep it up!
Only one more trip!
All right, it's your last day today.
Do your best!
So? Why don't you guys try something
out of the ordinary, as a challenge from me?
I'm still more interested in rings!
Maybe I should try parallel bars?
Vertical, see?
You balance your weight on it.
You have to practice yourself to understand.
Should you really be giving away your secrets that easily, champion? You’ll be overtaken in no time!
And down...
The finishing move is the only clean part.
They're shaking so much!
What's wrong, Fujimaki-kun?
Are you unwell?
Aren't you going to practice on the high bar today?
No. I don't feel like it.
All-Japan Junior Gymnastics Training Camp Venue
All right! That's the end of your training camp practice. Everyone did great.
The locals are hosting a summer festival
on this beach starting tonight,
All-Japan Junior Gymnastics Training Camp Venue
so you can relax and enjoy yourselves.
Yessir!
All-Japan Junior Gymnastics Training Camp Venue
Are we going on that summer festival?
I have no energy left to have fun.
Summer!
Flirting!
Festival!
Would you look at them...
I wonder how they have the energy for that...
That's simple—they just
slacked off during practice.
Come on, Fujimaki-kun, let's go.
Y-Yeah...
Ah, Shun-kun, wait!
We're going too!
Maybe I should go too.
Me too.
Ah, me too!
Hey!
Ah, Reiko-senpai, where have you been?
We should hurry up with everyone too.
Yeah... Hey, have you seen Shindo-kun?
Shindo-san said he forgot something at the gym.
Here.
Don't lose, Uchida!
The pride of second-years is at stake!
Good luck, Shun-kun!
Don’t give him any advantage out of courtesy!
Hey, Shun-kun, can you catch that big one?
Uchida! Don't you lose to a first-year brat!
Did it!
It's one-on-one!
Ready!
Start!
Go!
You can do it!
It's pretty!
So beautiful...
Here.
Oh...
So the training camp is over?
Yeah.
"Fujimaki-kun, we didn't spend long at that training camp, but it was fun.
I was glad to make some new friends on the mainland."
I'll see you at the autumn junior tournament.
I'll participate as an additional member of another team.
After all, I already promised it to you guys,
the Heisei Middle School.
So long, and see you again in the autumn.
Yeah, all things considered,
it was a pretty meaningful training camp.
Hm, I see. Isn't that great?
Next is the junior tournament, then.
Yeah, so it would seem.
It really seems to me like it was only meaningful to him, though.
It's okay now. We can take it easy from here.
Let's try out the imaginary techniques I learned at the Junior Training Camp.
Fork with a rook. Checkmate.
Look, Minoru-kun,
can't we redo that last turn?
Checkmate with a rook!
Hey, Fujimaki, you'll get dizzy if you keep swinging in the same direction.
He's right, Shun!
What's with him?
Shun-kun?
Shun, what happened to you?
You look pale!
That's weird...
I can't let go!
Even if I try to jump off
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Shun-kun!
Reiko-senpai...
I just can't...
No matter what I do!
Enough...
Enough already!
Is it hopeless for me?
Next Ganba: Despair! Shun, Tears, and the Blood-stained Bar.
Today's technique is called Roundoff.
It's a technique that adds speed to backflips.
Unlike in a cartwheel, you run up with great force, enter from the front and twist on your hands.
The trick is to push and twist with enough strength to then get up.