Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
Raise your legs higher!
Move your ass forward!
Okay, now do it there!
No way...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
With Guts!
Hellish Handstand Battle
The first, second, and third circles of hell!
Dammit, he's still unwilling to give up?
That means I will have to resort to the final,
fourth circle of the legs-raising hell.
Get up, Fujimaki!
Yessir!
Now you do it here!
"Here," as in...?
What for did he bring me up here?
You're going to hold a leg raise stance here.
Huh?!
Right here?!
Exactly!
B-B-But what if I fall?
Then practice your landing. Any gymnast worth their salt can land from this height.
If you can't,
then quit gymnastics!
Just quit right now!
There's no way he can do it.
It's high, it's scary!
Just like I once did, you're gonna end up begging for an exemption in tears!
Uchida Minoru (1 year ago)
No! Don't make me do it, please!
Senpai! I'll never be so disrespectful again!
Come on, start crying. I'll let you off the hook
if you kneel down and apologize.
Is he really going to do it?
With how clumsy he is, he's bound to fall!
I-I-I-I'm scared...
H-Hey!
Hey!
What are you two doing other there?!
Get down! It's dangerous!
Reiko-senpai!
Uchida-kun, help him down!
Okay!
Amazing, Kageyama-kun!
You're so good at it!
Yeah, she's right. That's great!
Well, I'll be damned—
it's our very own 1.0-kun.
What do you mean?
I was watching yesterday's tournament, 1.0-kun.
Hey, what does he mean by 1.0-kun?
You're talking about Fujimaki-kun, right?
Yeah. He performed at the district gymnastics competition yesterday and scored 1.0.
Our school is famous in the gymnastics world,
it even has its very own gymnasium.
But that only goes for our women's club.
Our men's club is ranked 16th in the district...
Out of 16.
If I may, it's a stain on our school's reputation.
H-How can you say that...
Watch this.
Headstand?
A gymnastics club member should have no trouble doing this.
It seems Kageyama
is good in anything he does.
Notice how I can do it even without joining our worthless gymnastics club.
What's going on?
Kageyama is doing a headstand? Why?
What's the matter?
You go to a tournament when you can't even do a headstand?
Told ya—that gymnastics club
is a bunch of losers.
Damn it...
This is a good demonstration of our men's gymnastics club's true strength.
Their participation in the tournament was just a token effort.
That's their level—putting a guy who can't even do a headstand into the tournament.
Hey, Ueno, leave that sucker alone.
What did you expect?
Our men's club is good for nothing.
No... Ugh! O-Ouch!
That's for malingering!
All right, all right!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You'll think twice next time!
That's on Sanada. We pressured him,
and he confessed to lying about that sprain.
He just didn't want to perform with us
and look like an idiot again.
I can't believe that guy.
Darn right.
The men's gymnastics club
is a disgrace to our school.
Um... Captain?
Come on, let's practice. You've got to give it your all for your big dreams.
All right! New members start with basic physical training!
30 dashes, then 30 laps around the campus! Start!
Yessir!
I'll have you do this every day
until you want to quit the club yourself.
Good! Keep it up!
I've done... 30 dashes.
Good! Now rest for 10 minutes and go for 30 laps around the campus!
Okay...
Good job, everyone!
Yes, don't forget about tomorrow!
Yeah, I remember!
Thanks, everyone!
One more lap...
I've done... 30 laps around the campus.
Too slow!
Everyone else went home already!
Sorry!
Whatever. No more training for today.
Excuse me...
What is it?
Could you please
teach me to do a headstand?
What?
A headstand?
Yes...
First off, it's not a headstand.
In gymnastics, we call it a handstand.
Then teach me...
to do that handstand.
Don't get cocky! You've got to nail the basics first—everything else comes after.
But... then, when will we do it?
Who knows...
Depends on how fast you can master the fourth circle of leg-raising hell.
Hey, stop it!
You couldn't do it even if you tried!
Hey, get down, you idiot!
I absolutely must...
Learn to do handstand...
All right!
All right, I'll teach you!
Stop it, you hear?
I'll teach you how to do a handstand!
I'll teach you, so get down now!
Thank you!
Fujimaki!
Hey, Fujimaki, are you alive?
Yes...
You're way too reckless for a rookie!
Sorry...
We'll start tomorrow.
For today, just rest.
Okay.
The men's gymnastics club
is not a stain on the school's reputation!
With enough effort,
I can do a handstand too!
Oh? Practicing from early morning again?
I'm proud of you.
Reiko-senpai!
Wh-What are you doing?
You're not standing on your shoulders.
You'll never learn to do a handstand without a wall that way.
Watch me, okay?
Not standing on my shoulders?
But your skirt...!
Hey, Fujimaki-kun,
try holding my legs.
Okay.
Now try pushing me down
like I did with you earlier.
Huh? But won't you...
Don't worry!
Okay.
Try again!
She won't collapse!
Even though I'm pushing so hard
What the hell is he doing to my Reiko-sama?!
Try standing on your shoulders now.
On my shoulders?
Oh, Uchida-kun!
You also came early today?
Y-Yes...
Oh, I see. You two were going to hold a morning practice now? That's commendable.
Hey, Uchida-kun, could you please teach him how to stand on his shoulders?
I'm sure he'll learn it in no time with your help.
Will you do it for me?
Yes!
Stay strong.
I'm leaving him to you, Uchida-kun!
Bye.
Thank you!
All right, Fujimaki! You'd damn better believe I'm gonna teach you to stand on your shoulders!
So, Ancient Greece
was made up of polis-cities.
A polis is a community of free citizens.
Basically, they're like small countries that started forming around the 8th century BC.
Fujimaki-kun, are you practicing the handstand?
No, I'm practicing to stand on my shoulders.
On your shoulders?
Um... Why do I have to practice
with my stomach to the wall?
To do a handstand,
you just need to learn to keep your body straight while balancing on your arms and shoulders.
What allows humans to stand on two legs?
It's keeping our upper body straight,
balanced on top of our two legs.
And vice-versa for the handstand.
But if your shoulders are forward,
you will end up standing with your body curved unnaturally to maintain balance.
By standing with your belly against the wall,
you'll learn to keep your body straight.
Your shoulders are still sticking out!
See? Your shoulders are all soft.
Okay, I'm going to push your shoulders now!
Was that your attempt at a headstand just now?
Don't make me laugh!
Do you really think you'll learn
to do a headstand with that exercise?
I do!
That's what my senpai taught me!
That's a nonstarter, buddy.
Your club is bunch of clowns.
They're all considerate and good people!
How does that help you with gymnastics?
The gymnastics club members who can't even do a headstand have no room to talk!
Kageyama!
Let's have a duel!
Fujimaki will duel you!
What?
Fujimaki and you will hold a duel
to see who can hold a handstand longer!
Senpai...
Hm. Let's raise the stakes, then.
If I win, Fujimaki will quit the gymnastics club.
Huh?
And if Fujimaki wins, we'll have you play our punishment game.
Senpai, please don't decide
things like that for me!
We'll settle it here, in a week.
Think a week is enough for you?
It is.
Then it's a deal.
Oh, come on...
A week later
Pass here!
Good!
Get out of my way!
Hey, Kageyama!
You're overdoing it!
I'm sorry, Teach.
Fujimaki, are you okay?
Yes.
Okay, hurry up and get the ball!
It's today, after school.
I'm looking forward to it.
I believe in Kageyama.
That guy is a jack of all trades!
Remember that hat trick he pulled off today?
Yeah, that was quite something.
Fujimaki-kun!
Hm?
Are you really going to duel him today?
Yeah.
But your hand is injured.
I'll manage.
I take it you remember
what happens if you lose.
Yeah.
And if Shun wins, what happens then is...
It’s fine, bring on any punishment you want.
Not like there’s any way I’d lose.
Do you remember the three important points of handstand?
Yes.
You can do it.
With your shoulder-stand training,
there’s no way you’ll lose.
Yes.
Okay, let's start!
What? With Fujimaki-kun?
Yeah, and Uchida said he wants you to come see it no matter what.
I’ll have to pass. I’ve got other urgent things to take care of right now.
Please turn on the music!
Okay!
Fujimaki-kun, I know you can do it.
I have no doubt in it.
Begin!
Fujimaki-kun...
What's the matter, Fujimaki?
What’s wrong?
We’ve just gotten started!
Imbecile!
Did you forget what I taught you?!
I can't do it anymore...
I can't balance...
You're not standing on your shoulders.
You'll never learn to do a handstand
without a wall that way.
Remember! The special training of the past week!
She won't collapse!
Even though I'm pushing so hard!
Senpai...
Don't forget the three key points of handstand!
Three key points...
Of the handstand!
T-The handstand...
starts with the correct hand positioning.
To stabilize your body,
you straighten all your fingers.
Next, align your weight in a straight line.
Align my weight in a straight line...
And stand on my shoulders...
Then pull my body together...
I-Is this for real?
It's perfectly straight line!
Not everyone is capable of that...
How did he...
My fingers don't hurt!
I see!
Because my weight is perpendicular to my wrist, it doesn't hurt!
Stay strong, Fujimaki!
This isn’t just gymnastics anymore.
He deserves some cheering on!
Stay strong, Fujimaki!
Fujimaki-kun, stay strong!
Stay strong, Fujimaki! Stay strong!
Stay strong!
He did it!
That's it!
How?
How can you do it for so long?
That's because...
What you did was a simple headstand.
And I did the professional gymnastic handstand
that I learned from my senpai.
Gymnastic handstand?
So, I take it there are no objections to the proposed solution for the men’s gymnastics club situation?
We have no other choice.
No, if anything,
it's the natural course of action.
The men’s gymnastics club’s lackluster performance over the past few years is no longer tolerable.
They won’t have a leg to stand on
if we disband the club now.
You’re still on the first circle of hell!
You'll like the second circle even more.
I'm Ueno Yoshio, sir.
Thanks for having me!
With a second new member this year, we’ve got to work hard for the summer tournament.
Yessir!
Gimme a break, please!
Get back here, dammit!
Gymnastics newcomer, Fujimaki Shun,
the road to your gold medal is endlessly long,
so even being able to do a perfect handstand now is a big deal!
But it’s also not the time
to relax and celebrate.
Is something bad looming over the men’s gymnastics club?
Don't give up, Ganbarist Shun!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Let's do it! Backflip! Let's do it!
What are you two doing?
What's wrong? Come on, jump!
O-Okay!
Stop! That's not how you do it!
I can't!
Next Gamba:
This is it! The Grand Backflip in the Sunset.
Here it is! A technique called Morisue! That's right, it's the technique I coined at the Olympics!
And now that Tanaka Hikaru refined this technique at the Atlanta Olympics,
will it be called Tanaka Hikaru's technique?
Good luck, Tanaka Hikaru!