The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Hey, Fujimaki! If you keep swinging in the same direction, you'll get dizzy!
He's right, Shun!
Even if I try to jump,
I can't let go!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Despair!
Shun, Tears, and the Blood-stained Bar
My hands...
My hands just won't let go!
What did you say? You can't let go?
Shun-kun...
I've tried to jump time and time again,
but my hands just won't listen, no matter what I do.
What the hell?
Your hands won't listen?
Why won't they listen? How come?
I-I don't know, but when I try to let go of the high bar,
my hands just won't listen to what I say.
Look, you didn't kill some living being
while you were a kid, did you?
Huh?
What if the spirit of a slain creature possessed you
and made you unable to control your hands?
You’re in big trouble
if it’s not exorcised, buddy!
Amen...
Hey, you! Enough with it!
Shun, what exactly happened to you
at that training camp?
You think something in him changed
at the training camp?
That's right. It seems to me, something happened there that gave him a mental shock.
Actually, on his first day...
What did you say?
He punched a hole in the ceiling?!
Yeah. That surprised everyone.
While trying to learn a triple somersault on the high bar, he jumped too high
and crashed through the ceiling.
Did he then crash into the bar?
No, he just fell into the pit as he was supposed to,
he didn't meet the bar on his way back.
That's strange.
If he didn't even hit the bar...
What do you mean?
I don't like it.
There used to be an Olympic athlete once.
During practice,
he fell right onto the high bar,
and since then, he's been unable let go of the bar,
even while performing a giant swing.
But if Shun didn't even hit the bar...
Come to think of it, Director Sotoyama
also mentioned something similar back then.
He told them about an athlete who failed to clear the bar, landed on it shin-first,
suffered an open fracture, and had bones sticking out...
Wh-What?!
Yes, it was then. That's when Fujimaki-kun started acting strange.
Then that's the reason!
Huh?
Shun convinced himself that he would suffer the same fate!
Even though his mind wants to let go,
his body rebels!
If so, we're in a bit of a pickle.
Yeah... This problem lies in a mental plane.
If we act carelessly, we'll make it worse than if he actually hit the bar. Worst case scenario...
It might affect his future
gymnastics career, correct?
Yes... We have to do something!
Fujimaki-kun, can you land with a triple somersault now?
Yeah, I can.
Ah! Show me, show me!
Sure.
And now!
Footprints...
on the ceiling?
There's no ceiling.
We're in Madam's yard!
Crap!
High bar...
Just a dream?
That was scary...
There, you're getting sleepy.
You want to sleep.
You feel more and more sleepy...
Now, what can you see?
I can't see anything,
my eyes are closed.
Can't argue with that!
Fujimaki's leading!
Shut up! You're distracting us!
Fujimaki! You need to take it seriously too!
But I'm not messing with you!
Uchida, do you really think you can fix it with hypnosis?
Please leave it to me.
All we need to do is blow his fears away with self-suggestion.
Listen, Fujimaki.
O-Okay...
You are a bird. A bird.
Since you're a bird, you can fly.
Since you're a bird, you're not afraid of flying. Not afraid.
Did you hear? "A bird!"
What are gonna do if you
turn him into a chicken?
That's it! Your fear is gone!
You're not afraid of the high bar.
Not one bit afraid!
I-Is that true?
Uchida-senpai, are you sure it worked?
You'll know when you see it.
Okay, Fujimaki!
Now that you're a bird, you can fly!
I know you can!
Good luck, Fujimaki-kun!
Okay! Let go!
Let go, you hear?!
What are you doing?
You're a bird! A bird!
Didn't I tell you you're a bird now?
Fly!
Seriously, dude!
Fujimaki-kun!
One-two... fly!
One-two...
Fujimaki! Take a break now.
What a pain...
To think a triple somersault from the training camp would backfire at us like that...
What are we gonna do now? What to do?
He was supposed to turn into a bird...
Enough about that.
The more people around you try to help you,
the deeper your trauma progresses.
I understand how everyone feels, but that's not enough.
You have to overcome it on your own...
Shun! You will practice privately with me
early in the morning starting tomorrow.
Got it?
Yes...
Madam, you want me to exercise in rain boots?
It's not for that.
I want you to help me dig potatoes.
Potatoes?
Shun, I don't understand the reason for your condition,
but forgetting about the bar for a while would do you good.
But I have to practice...
Hm...
Whatever. If you don't worry, it'll heal soon.
Just don't push yourself too hard for now.
Let Fujimaki-kun stay away from the high bar for a while?
If we let him rest for a while, his fear will subside and he'll return to the high bar in due course.
Until then, we just have to wait.
I also agree with Madam's opinion.
I feel that if we force him to practice,
it will only deepen his fear.
That's right. In contrast with our idiotic Trio of Second-years, Shun takes himself too seriously.
That's what made his condition so severe.
I wish Mari-chan was was still here,
so we could force those two on a date.
That'd make for a nice change of pace
that Shun needs so much.
So you made him plant potatoes
for a change of pace...
Oh I'm sorry, but you'll turn into an old hag yourself in no time.
What do you mean?
I'll give it a try.
Huh?
I don't want Shun-kun to lose his future
over something like this.
So I... I'll do it myself...
I suppose you're right.
A young one would work better...
What do you mean?
I've planned a trip
to the vegetables market tomorrow.
Young one would work better, Grandma.
Shun-kun!
Hey, Shun-kun...
This way, Shun-kun!
R-Reiko-senpai is calling you...
Huh?
I'm here, Shun-kun.
Wh-What's the matter, Reiko-senpai?
Shun-kun, are you free tomorrow?
Uh? Well, I have some free time...
Let's go on a date tomorrow.
Date?!
Da—
Yes, a date.
Wha...
What the...
O-Orikasa?!
I have two tickets to the amusement park.
I wanted to go there with you.
U-Um...
Please!
O-Okay...
Say what?!
R-Reiko-senpai and F-Fujimaki-kun?!
On a date?!
This is so wrong!
Reiko-sama, why...
Why does it have to be Fujimaki of all people?
She looks great in a leotard, but Reiko-senpai in a miniskirt is simply irresistible!
She makes my muscles dance!
Guys, Reiko-senpai's beautiful legs will get dirty from your lascivious looks alone!
Hey, are we really following them even inside the amusement park?
Of course!
As his mentors, we're responsible
for the actions of our disciple.
We must watch him closely to prevent any unacceptable behavior toward Reiko-senpai.
I-I also must do that, as his classmate.
Ueno, not you too...
Ah! Fujimaki-kun is here!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all. It's all fine, Shun-kun.
Well, shall we go?
Yes.
He even has the nerve
to make Reiko-senpai wait!
We must teach him a lesson!
I'm so jealous...
I wanna go on a date too!
I've never been on a date like this in my life!
O-Orikasa...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You boys are going on a date with me.
Shun desperately needs
a change of pace right now.
But there can't be a change of pace if you keep hanging around and getting in his way!
As his mentors, you need
to be more considerate than that!
B-But that doesn't explain...
Why is it that Fujimaki gets to go on a date...
And we're digging potatoes?!
Don’t you think it’s good for everyone to reconnect with nature once in a while?
Shut up!
I didn't sign up to dig up potatoes
for the sake of another's happiness.
I'm so pissed off!
Reiko-sama...!
Now! Why don't you just shut up and dig!
Hey, look! People and cars look so small!
Uh? Yeah...
Hey, let's ride that next, okay?
Y-Yeah...
What's wrong? Are you unwell?
It's not that...
But what?
Um... Why did you invite me?
Captain or Uchida-senpai would've made more sense.
Well, it's just that...
Do you dislike me?
Huh?
Wouldn’t anyone besides Mariko-chan work?
What if it was Coach Misaki?
Or her Grandma?
N-No... Of course not.
Let's enjoy ourselves today, then!
Okay? Okay?
Sure.
Wow... I haven't been
on a roller coaster since I was a kid!
I see...
Are you afraid of this kind of thing, Shun-kun?
No, not much.
I-I see... Well, actually, I really can't...
stand this kind of thing!
Listen up, whoever draws the longest one wins.
All right...
Let's do it!
This is...
My victory...
With the last one!
Which one?
It's mine! Mine is the longest!
Whatdja say?!
It's obviously mine!
Counting with the root, it's my victory!
What was that?!
Are you stupid?
It's me!
Mine's the longest!
What are you doing?
It seems they're competing
for who gets to be in a slump next.
Because then that person will get to go on a date with Reiko-senpai.
Blithering fools!
What should we ride next
after we finish this?
I like going around in circles, so maybe... Hey!
Shun-kun?
Shun-kun!
Oh no...
What's the matter, Shun-kun?
N-No, it's just...
Shun-kun...
Shun-kun, thank you for joining me today.
It was my pleasure.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Reiko-senpai.
N-No, it's nothing.
Thank you very much for today.
Shun-kun...
If only Fujimaki could let go of the bar in the first place, none of this would have happened!
So there's no moving forward until we cure him.
Maybe send him on another date?
How about we cover the bar in oil?
That means he wouldn't be able to grab it,
and we need him to let go!
Attach a rope to his hands
and yank him off it!
Then who's gonna catch him?
Um...
Couldn't we pass a current through the bar?
What? Electric current?
Time it right and turn on the current—
he’ll fly off instantly.
O-On second thought, forget it.
It's too dangerous.
What a stupid idea.
We're not in some cartoon, you know.
No, let's pass the current through.
It has to do!
Captain?
D-Don't be ridiculous.
Please think about it.
We want to heal him, not kill him!
Just a small battery would suffice.
We only need him partly paralyzed.
We can do it with electricity!
R-Right...
Let's get to designing it at once!
I name it Operation Ultra Gamba Part 3!
C-Captain?
Uchida will procure the battery, Higashi—cords. Sanada, you take care of the switches!
O-Okay, got it...
Y-Yeah...
Hello? My name is Orikasa.
Can I talk to Shun?
Huh? He hadn't come home yet?
There's no way...
Shun-kun!
R-Reiko-senpai...
I just can't do it...
No matter what I do!
Enough already...
That's enough!
You shouldn't do that...
I'll stain your shirt...
Oh my? Did we leave our gate wide open?
I'm sure I closed it.
Unless...
That was so irresponsible of you, young man!
Well, I'll walk Orikasa home, then.
Yeah. Thank you.
Good night.
Shun, you should stay the night.
Who could it be?
It's not a thief, is it?
Wh-What's this?
Why is he here?
He's not dead, is he?
Dobriy den'!
Dobriy den'...
Oh no, it's a foreigner!
Dobriy den'!
That's how you say "Hello" in Russian!
R-Russian?
Hm? What's with your hands?
Ah, I... I got in on the high bar...
Boy... Do you like the high bar?
I-I do like it... I suppose.
Why are you here in the middle of the night?
Wow! Seiji’s mom!
I’ve dreamed of meeting you for ages!
What's this sudden outburst of love?
What happened to his hand?
You see, he doesn't seem to be able
to let go of the high bar.
Can't let go?
Oh! That disease is very easy to cure!
I can do it with a single stroke!
Single stroke?
Yes!
A single stroke, sir!
D-Don't tell me you're...
The former world champion?
Yes, Sergei Andrianov here.
Th-The world champion?
There's no way it's true, right?
How could this suspicious foreigner
be the world champion, right?
But when he says he can cured you with a single stroke, what are you going to do, Ganbarist Shun?
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
I came to return this.
Japan's national team uniform?
Is this...
Seiji's uniform?
At the world championship,
when I first met Seiji-san,
he gifted me this uniform.
Seiji was a truly wonderful athlete.
So this uniform became my talisman.
Next Ganba: A Revival!
The First Step Towards New Hope.
Today it's finally the backflip.
The first point is, if someone is afraid of jumping backwards,
hold their hands firmly
throw them over yourself.
The second point is, swing your hands strongly and jump backwards.
At first, always have someone support you.