Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
As I said, you were just playing gymnastics.
Now, step away and let us put away the high bar.
Wait... Please wait!
What else do you expect me to wait for now?
Fine! Give us a week!
It's a Showdown!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
It's a Showdown!
A Performance we Have to Nail
Huh? What on earth is this?
"Men's gymnastics club special performance?"
Currently, our men's gymnastics club practice is being disrupted by the tyranny
O-Orikasa will be there too?
of Coach Misaki, the women's club coach.
To show you how unfair this treatment is,
we, the men's club, are holding a performance
in our assembly hall to demonstrate our capabilities.
Notice that Orikasa Reiko-san
will also be present at the exhibition!
How was it?
Uh? Ah... Good...
Uh? Well, it's...
The writing is too stiff.
I'd prefer something more cool.
What?!
It doesn't grab attention enough!
What?
So this is what I get
for doing everything myself?
What did you want me to write, then?!
"We'll show you our full strength!
Come see it and be amazed!"
What's that dumb slogan?!
Whatdja say?!
I'm just saying you go it yourself!
Guys!
Wh-
What is that poster?
It's a declaration of war.
Now Coach Misaki can't back down
even if she wants to.
Can't back down?
Aren't we the only ones here who can't back down anymore?
It's even better this way, Captain.
We've already taken on that challenge.
Let's show Coach Misaki
the wonders of our techniques.
Besides, if it's Coach Misaki herself and the women's club who're going to judge us...
doesn't that put us at a disadvantage?
That's why we need to do it publicly,
with plenty of impartial judges!
Isn't that a great plan?
But there's no way Coach Misaki
would allow something like this.
That's already taken care of.
I did it with the principal's permission.
Principal! How could you allow
such a ridiculous stunt?!
These kids did it without ever consulting me!
Well, there's no need to be so formal.
I think we should give the men's gymnastics club a chance.
Give them a chance?
"The dead weight of Heisei,
the appendage of the women's club."
That's the kind of reputation they have,
to the point where even board members are increasingly calling for their dissolution.
It's a good opportunity.
I'm planning to attend as well,
so I can witness their abilities firsthand.
Then, should you personally confirm whether their skill level matches the rumors...
Yes, I'm going to take
the appropriate measures.
Misaki-san, you'll have a significant voice in the matter.
Still, what do we do now?
Got a moment, Shindo-kun?
Uh... Yes!
It's not very nice to write things like that without permission.
Oh... Yeah, sorry.
It's just... That poster... It's...
Well, what's done is done.
What's next?
Actually convincing Coach Misaki?
W-Well, we've no choice now,
so we'll try to do whatever we can.
Good luck!
Huh?
I'm rooting for you!
I hope the exhibition goes okay.
See you!
Thanks!
Yes, but still...
How can we protect the bar?
Wait!
Got it!
No!
Ugh, dang it.
Excuse me!
Come on, guys!
You're supposed to head straight home after school.
We're practicing on our way home!
Uh? I see...
Here, your ball.
Thank you.
What are you guys up to?
This! Heisei Men's Gymnastics Club Special Performance!
Are you going to perform?
Yes! The fate of our men's gymnastics club hinges on this.
C'mon, give them a flyer.
Oh... Right.
We'll distribute them for you!
Good luck!
Good! That's the spirit!
Thanks!
Thank you.
Let's keep this up!
The more people unfamiliar with gymnastics show up, the better our odds will be!
What do you mean?
Just think about it.
Whether or not we're doing our best,
do you really think that grumpy coach will back off and leave our high bar alone?
Yeah...
Sorry, but this is not a fairy tale.
Realistically, we don't have any complex technique to impress Coach Misaki!
Huh?!
That's where my plan comes in—getting the public to shower us with adoration and applause.
But how are we going to do that?
Complexity isn't necessarily the key to impressing the public.
There's also the composition
and the element of surprise.
And that's exactly what you're good at, Fujimaki.
M-Me?
Remember the tournament the other day?
Huh?
But I only made everyone laugh.
Yes, you were laughed at.
However...
This time, making the audience laugh
is the whole point!
They'll like it! Like it!
We'll make them like it!
Yes, it's your natural predisposition—
to be a comedian.
C-Comedian... you say?
Making people laugh...?
Is it really that good of an idea?
Oh no...
Still a gorilla!
I got them properly excited!
I never thought I'd end up doing something like this at home!
Our preparation must be flawless
to be well-received.
Our secret weapon will leave them speechless!
Oh, they'll be stunned, all right—
when they see something that ridiculous.
I can hear you.
That's what you call the element of surprise.
We'll be at the forefront
of expanding gymnastics' horizons.
Yes...
Look, do I really have to do this?
You can't memorize your lines?
No, that's not what I mean.
Want me to write some cooler role for you, then?
No...
It's just...
Sorry.
This all is happening because I'm
an unworthy captain. Please forgive me!
Captain, where did that come from?
Until we go there and try our utmost,
you must do your best!
Higashi, what are you doing to help our cause?
Training for a new technique
that is sure to impress everyone, of course!
So far, you're only telling others what to do.
But what will you perform yourself?
I have my own secret weapon...
this!
Isn't that just a bunch of anpans?
Yes, it's the anpans.
Anpans and vaulting.
Combining these two seemingly unrelated concepts will change the world!
Heisei Men's Gymnastics Club Special Performance
Well, they sure put on a show!
It's pretty lively too.
So many people came to see us...
What should I do?
So, how is it going?
You guys look strung out.
Y-Yes, sort of...
Good luck.
If everyone gives it their best today, even Coach Misaki will be moved and let you keep the bar.
I hope you'll deliver a performance that convinces everyone here that gymnastics is wonderful.
See you!
Reiko-senpai...
With such a crowd, our victory is practically guaranteed.
Captain! Do your best till the end!
Y-Yeah... Let's make it good.
You there,
is everything ready?
Y-Yes...
We're starting, give it your best!
Okay!
Will this really work to our favor?
Good luck, men's gymnastics club!
Defend the high bar!
You can do it! You can do it!
Special guests
Oh? They enjoy quite the popularity, it seems.
I'm looking forward to it.
Who knows what techniques they'll show us.
Give it a rest, please!
D-Did I say something wrong?
Huh?
Um...
They believe these crowds of onlookers and supporters will work in their favor.
Unfortunately,
I know all too well that it's all just smoke and mirrors to obfuscate your own incompetence.
So, what are you planning to showcase this time to magically change my mind?
The lights are out!
What's going on?
Hey?
Start!
Help me, someone! Help!
Help!
Yes, ladies and gentlemen!
Our fun gymnastics show begins!
Help!
The minions of evil are after me!
Someone! Help me!
The warrior of justice Kamen Gambus is here!
Nice!
The evil-serving monsters,
the gymnastics of justice
will stop you!
Awesome!
How could they... How...
Gymnastics air attack!
Kamen Ganba!
Case closed!
That's cool!
They liked it...
Shindo-kun, what's the meaning of this?
What does it have to do with gymnastics, huh?!
Well, Coach....
Hey... C'mere...
Come on, you can do better than this, Gorilla!
It's part of my technique too!
Like this!
What is this...
What is this farce of a performance?!
Stop it right now!
Thank you for waiting, everyone!
And now,
the true specialist Uchida will show you the cutting-edge ways to use the vaulting horse!
Please notice the anpan floating in the air!
Anpan!
What do you think is the most spectacular way to eat it?
It's the "eat without hands" game!
Watch out!
Spectacular, all right...
You're next up, Captain!
Things are going well so far.
Don't let us down!
Wha... Running away?!
Whassat?
Oh! Reiko Senpai...
Is that all? Captain was too embarrassed to perform in front of Reiko-senpai?
Reiko-senpai!
Huh?
Sh-She's not happy.
Whyssat?
Captain, hurry up!
Sorry, I just can't do it...
Really? After we made it this far?
I know! I know...
Hey, what's taking you so long?
I'm bored!
We have no choice.
Fujimaki, you go first.
O-Okay...
Use your gift of clumsiness
to make them laugh hard!
I hope you'll deliver a performance that convinces everyone here that gymnastics is wonderful.
Fujimaki-kun?
Sorry, I don't need the song.
What do you mean?
You spent so long
picking the best tune.
What should I do?
What can help us now?
I still don't know any advanced techniques.
But if I don't do something,
they'll dismantle the bar.
I can't do it now,
but I want to learn it!
Why is he just doing a normal performance?
Hey, look at Reiko-senpai.
Huh?
Whassat?
She's rooting for him...
Does she hate us this much?
You can say that again.
I want to win a gold medal!
I want to learn all the different
techniques that I can't do now.
Giant Swing, Tkachev, Jaeger, Moonsault!
There's so many techniques I want to learn!
Right now, this is the best I can do.
I can only do simple stuff like this!
But it feels good to be doing it!
So good!
Doing my very best feels great!
My whole body is rejoicing.
It's fun!
Gymnastics
is so much fun!
That's right, it's the gymnastics!
A performance that convinces everyone here that gymnastics is wonderful.
It's the most wonderful!
Yahoo!
Nicely done!
Yes, I believe that kid shows a lot of promise.
Right, Coach Misaki?
I agree.
He’s got that bounce in him.
Captain also took off his suit
and performed on high bar.
Reiko-senpai helped too.
We all did our best.
But the decision was already made by then.
You worked yourself hard,
but it was all for nothing.
It's a shame.
Don't lose your spirits.
It was a great performance.
Ah... Fujimaki-kun!
Hey...
Gymnastics is fun...
But despite that...
Hey, Mister!
If it's about that high bar,
you don't need to cry.
I know of a place where there's another bar just like that.
Huh? Another high bar?
Yeah. I'll show you, come along.
Right, wait...
What?
A high bar?
Hurry up, Mister!
We might as well take this chance
Yes!
Gymnastics newbie Fujimaki Shun,
the road to the gold medal is endlessly long!
Well, you did well so far.
But you'll have to take it seriously now.
They already took away
your high bar once!
But perhaps you can find yourself another one, somehow?
Where and when, though...
You never know!
Go, Ganbarist Shun!
Hurry up!
All right!
Coming!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
When we saw it, we were completely stunned.
Too dumbfounded to speak, even.
Next Gamba:
Who is she? The Mysterious Gymnastics Grandma.
Balancing is a technique that requires you to stand still for two seconds amidst your performance.
It may look easy, but really it's quite difficult.
Whether or not you nail it
has a big impact on your finishing technique.