The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
The pommel horse performances will begin shortly.
By the way, where did Uchida and Ueno go?
Ah!
They're there!
Why...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
It's a Revolution!
The Astonishing Rebirth of Pommel Horse With Heisei
Episode
It's a Revolution!
The Astonishing Rebirth of Pommel Horse With Heisei
The performances on the pommel horse,
the second event for men, will now begin.
All-Japan Junior Individual Championships
Uchida never practiced
on the pommel horse, did he?
Even more so for Ueno-kun!
What are those two thinking?
Are they just doing it
for some extra screen time?
I can see Uchida doing something like that, but Ueno...
Wh-Wh-Why do I have to enter too?
Today, we'll rewrite
the history of the pommel horse!
Huh?
For this day, I've cooked up some new amazing moves that no one could have even imagined.
B-But that doesn't explain
why you had to get me involved too!
That's the point!
This technique is so original and revolutionary, there's a risk the judges won't be able to grasp it.
But if I, your senpai, end up with the lowest score on the table, won’t that put you to shame?
Do you want me to have the last place?
That's why I need you as insurance.
Understand?
How am I his insurance?
All Japan Junior Individual Championships,
men's 2nd event, pommel horse.
The first performer is Matsumoto
from Nishihori College Club.
Impressive!
He's really good!
Well, isn't that a wonderful performance, Kaizuka-san?
Indeed, that Thomas flare is a work of art.
This technique was introduced by an American athlete Thomas at the Montreal Olympics.
The layout spin of his legs resembles a propeller spinning on a spindle.
It’s a challenging technique that demands rotating your body in the opposite direction of your legs.
As expected of the Lee Corps.
U-Uchida-senpai, look at that amazing technique he has!
Yeah. It's a conventional and trite technique.
Sakashita-san, it always gets me thinking...
All you ever do on the pommel horse is spinning...
Isn't that kinda monotonous?
That's not true. You're required to include turning and crossing elements in your routine.
Besides, you're not allowed to stop.
Huh? You can't stop on the pommel horse?
You need to study rules more.
Look at that, for example.
His toes have to be beautifully
extended at all times.
Even when performing complicated techniques,
your nerves must be strung tight from head to toe.
An average gymnast would have
his hands full with spinning alone.
The Magyar Travel,
named after Hungarian athlete Magyar,
who introduced it and was hailed as the God of the Pommel Horse!
Wow!
He's the real deal!
This one is amazing too.
Yeah...
Just how many more moves is he going to show?
That's a rather long performance.
And now a finishing move
from an upright position!
He nailed it!
Finished with a splendid landing.
This will surely yield him a lot of points...
It's out! 9.75!
Matsumoto from the Nishihori Club
started off with a score so high it makes your eyes jump out of the sockets!
9.75?
Well now, where's the fun in that?
At this rate, all the other entries
might as well quit right now!
Yeah.
Are they for real?
U-Uchida-senpai!
Humph. It's nothing to be afraid of.
It was merely a rehash of moves invented by someone else!
What I've brought is an original new technique that will rewrite the history of pommel horse!
I can't wait to present it to the world!
All right, well done.
The junior champion Kobayakawa
begins his performance on the pommel horse!
Right... When someone opens with such a high score,
it puts pressure on the performers that follow.
He's on a whole other level compared to them.
And... The next athlete
is Uchida from Heisei.
Hm.... Heisei, then?
What does that mean?!
Huh? Uchida-kun performs on the pommel horse?
There's no way!
When he could've possibly trained for that?
Uchida-senpai...
He's determined to give
an earnest performance.
Yeah. That's the face of determination!
Really... What the hell is he thinking?
U-Uchida-senpai,
it's not too late to quit, I think.
How can you say that
when it's finally my time to perform?
Hold this for me!
O-Okay...
Oh, I think I've seen him before on the vault...
Yeah, he's the guy who beat Kamura-kun.
Now, Uchida raises his hand!
The performance begins!
The technique that will rewrite the history of pommel horse... What could it be?
So, what kind of performance will he show us?
Ah! I-Is this...
Whassat?!
H-Handstand...
S-Sakashita-san?
Didn't you say he can't stop?
Yeah... Yet he stopped completely.
Wh-What the?
What is he doing?
The main surprise is yet to come!
What's this? I've never seen anything like this!
What's that technique?
Uchida is moving along the pommel horse on his hands! It’s like he’s dancing!
What is he doing?!
Now add a twist here!
The judges need to see it too!
Nice! You're great!
You're funny!
I've never seen a performance like that!
Tsk. So embarrassing.
That's not like I wanted to stand out!
Well then, it's about time!
Wh-What is he going to do now?
The history of pommel horse will change today!
Nailed it!
Y-You imbecile!
Without turning or crossing,
i-it wasn't even a pommel horse performance!
Looking good, Horse Dancer!
That was spectacular!
You were great!
Thank you!
Sakashita-san, seems like they liked it.
He definitely caused a sensation!
Right... That's a curious gymnast
if I ever seen one.
Ah, Morisue-san?
Somersault from a pommel horse.
It has potential for further development.
Uh? Do you really think so?
Yeah. I might task some of my students
with further researching it.
So, how many points for a performance that will revolutionize pommel horse?
4... 4.0?!
I knew it... The revolutionary ideas never find support at first.
Oh well, I came prepared with insurance
for just this situation.
Huh?
H-He's really spinning!
C-Crossing too!
What does that mean?!
Spin-spin... They scored my spin-spins higher than your performance...
I even lost to Ueno!
The results of the second men's event,
pommel horse, are out!
The winner is Matsumoto from Nishihori College!
Good job, Heisei Club!
That was fun!
Heisei is the best! Keep it up!
At least the audience liked it!
What were you thinking, really?
Oh, no need to be so grumpy!
Hey!
Huh?
Ouch...
Are you okay, Fujimaki?
Are you out of your mind? Throwing stuff like that at people is dangerous! What's the meaning of this?!
What's the meaning of this?
That's just what we wanted to ask you.
What?!
What was that you did at the pommel horse?
You looked like a fucking clown.
That's right. All the while we...
No, not just us, all the athletes in this hall are taking their performances seriously!
And yet you had to hurt the image of this tournament with your useless performance!
Useless performance?!
It was appropriately scored 4.0.
Hey, don't change the subject.
What?
One's useless performance
can hurt the image of the tournament at best,
but throwing a full thermos at another's head
can hurt someone for real!
What...
Yeah, goddamn right!
What the hell do you mean by useless?!
It was the next generation technique,
exploring the new horizons...
You're just inventing excuses, aren't you?!
Bastard! I'll fuck you up anytime!
Hey!
Please stop!
I'm fine!
What's with those frail arms?
Th-This bastard is strong...
Shit... You'll regret this!
That's more like it!
You're not beating our invincible Higashi!
Eat it!
Ow...
Idiot!
Practice field
—
Sanada, Uchida! Do you have even
a shred of common sense left in you?
Practice field
—
You just keep doing whatever you want!
Yuichi, let's look at it from a brighter perspective!
Coach Andrianov?
You guys are still pretty young as gymnasts.
What matters is enjoying your own techniques
and performing more carefree without worrying about the score!
Well, if you say so...
Huh? Where's Uchida?
He wouldn't even listen to the Coach's advice! Where did he go?!
Captain, why can't he go to the bathroom alone?
It hurts, dammit...
I didn’t give Captain any reason to punch me.
It’s such a drag that nobody understands me,
even in my own camp...
Damn it...
Wh-What do you want?!
D-Don't come close!
I reflected on it, all right?
I'm sorry about earlier.
It's too late for that now!
Why not wash other parts
of your body as well, not just hands?
Here, let me help you!
You 4.0 shithead!
Special offer just for you.
Special washing service free of charge!
Scum like you shouldn’t have entered this tournament to begin with!
That's right! Do you have any idea how much hard training we had to endure for today?!
The dilettantes like you will never match us,
the junior top class gymnasts.
At best, you belong in a comedic gardening contest!
Shit! The Gorilla is coming!
What?
Pass this to your shithead Gorilla as well:
We'll make you all eat shit in the competition!
Dammit...
Are you okay, Uchida?!
They'll fucking pay for it!
Higashi!
Forget about them!
You wanna let them get away with it?
Don't worry about me.
We...
We must have fun,
that's all that matters!
If we get fixated on competing with them,
the gymnastics will be no fun.
Getting angry will only ruin your execution.
You should just focus
on your own mood and techniques.
Still...
Forget it, I said!
If we lose our cool now,
we’ll just fall right into their trap.
The other guys will also be unable
to concentrate on their performances.
Believe me.
Uchida...
Huh? Uchida-senpai, what are you doing?
Me? Just doing my laundry.
Laundry?
Can't believe I splashed juice all over you!
Sorry, Uchida.
D-Don't mention it.
It's them...
Hold it, Higashi!
Ugh...
The performances for the third men's event,
the rings, will begin shortly.
Hey, look! One of those guys is huge!
Wow... He’s got some seriously ripped body!
Glasses was dirty and stinking,
so I washed them.
Getting angry will only ruin your execution.
You should just focus
on your own mood and techniques.
Higashi-senpai, do your best!
Good luck!
Now, we've finally reached the rings, the final men's event of the first half.
Kaizuka-san, could you tell us what the key points are in the rings competition?
Very well.
I consider it a general knowledge, though.
In this event, the competitors use two rings suspended 2.55 meters above the ground
to perform a mix of dynamic, static, and strength techniques.
In a nutshell, the key point of this event is each performer's individual strength.
I see. Strength it is, then.
Meanwhile, Kobayakawa's performance has just begun.
I knew it...
Oh... What do you mean?
Being a junior athlete, his body hasn’t fully developed yet. See? His grip is not very steady.
And he lands with a double straight-body somersault. Will he nail it?
He did!
He scores the same 9.20
as Kamura who performed previously.
Those two share the first place at the moment.
Nobody here is in the same league as me!
And the guy right next to me doesn't even qualify to compete.
What?
I’ll make sure you see firsthand what makes the Nishihori College Team, the Lee Corps, so great.
Now it's finally the Nishihori Club turn.
Once again, Lee Corps athlete is rather short...
It's part of their training.
It's that bastard again.
With Koda’s help, who previously won the floor event for his team, Saga climbs the rings.
Let's give that gorilla a clear idea
why he'll be on our level.
Hm. He looks thickheaded;
I wonder if I can get through to him.
Let's go!
Saga starts from upside-down position
and uses the recoil to climb!
And now he's in an L-Sit!
Yes! That’s a beautiful L-Sit with his body perfectly extended, all the way to his tiptoes.
He transitions from the L-Sit to the Planche.
What’s next?
Oh! It's a straight-arm, straight-body press handstand!
This was so smooth!
I have nothing to add!
B-But wait, it's a cross handstand now!
H-However, static techniques like the cross handstand
have a 2-second static hold requirement!
1...
2...
And he clears it!
From the straight-body press handstand...
Into the Cross Handstand?!
It's the special technique that Higashi-senpai used on the floor at the last regional tournament!
Amazing... Performing Higashi's strength technique on the rings!
He's not bad at all!
He performed that incredible move on the rings,
and then also pulled his arms back together
to return to the handstand!
You get it now, you geezer?
Who else can do that on the rings?
Several more backward swings...
Was that a double somersault just now?
Yes! It was an elastic Yamawaki.
Double forward somersault while holding the rings.
It's a great technique developed
by the Japanese gymnast Yamawaki.
Touching the rope is a major no-no, yet Saga seems to perform without any signs of hesitation!
Now, this one is for you, Muscle Gorilla!
Ah! And now...
The Iron Cross!
1...
2...
He cleared it!
How about this, Gorilla?
Think you can do it?
Better run while you can.
Then finally, straight-body Moonsault!
He nailed it! Even the landing is perfect!
And the score is...
A whopping 9.85!
9... 9.85?
It's simply...
Unreachable!
That rascal Saga added an Iron Cross
without consulting me.
Who is he trying that hard for?
Impressive that Saga can perform all those strength moves with such a small body.
No, quite probably it's thanks to his small body.
Huh?
Didn't you make fun of my "frail arms" before,
Mr. Muscular Demon?
Rings exercises are nothing like powerlifting.
As long as you can lift and support your own weight,
that’s all you need, even if with these slim arms!
You stand no chance of ever being on par with us.
Both you and Glasses are just human trash!
Scum like you was not supposed to qualify for this kind of tournament in the first place!
Are you done blabbering yet, Crabstick Hands?
It's my turn to show you
what the rings are truly all about.
Exactly! Go for it, Higashi!
It's time to release all the frustration.
Show the Lee Corps the true strength of Heisei Gymnastics Club!
Don't hold back, Ganbarist Denji!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
I won... Did I really win?
1, 2... Smile!
I-It can't be...
Smile!
I-Impossible!
What's going on?
Is he even human?!
Next Ganba: Strength Technique!
Hercules on the Rings.
Today we're doing a back hip circle.
There may be some who can't do it properly.
So, to do a back hip circle, curl up, tuck your chin in, and pull your legs, stick close to the high bar.
If you see someone struggle with it,
please help them get a good feel for turning.