The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
You guys will make your debut at the upcoming championships.
You'll start there and eventually turn Japanese gymnastics on its head.
Is that clear?
Yes!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
I'll be brief. How are you, Sagara-san?
Have you gotten used to the new place already?
At the moment, the team is working hard for the All-Japan Event-Specific Junior Championships.
Unlike past regionals, incredible athletes from across the country will also make an appearance!
You must be worried about us entering such a big tournament.
But we'll be fine! After all,
we have such a wonderful coach now!
He won the overall gold in individual standings at the Montreal Olympics.
Coach Sergei Andrianov,
once a gold medalist from the Soviet Union.
The tournament will be televised,
so I hope you get to catch a glimpse of it!
P.S.: Ueno-kun will also
make his debut at this tournament.
A Formidable Opponent!
The Devil's Team, the Lee Corps
Episode
A Formidable Opponent!
The Devil's Team, the Lee Corps
Right, thanks for carrying it for me.
You must be sweaty—
go take a bath while I prepare dinner.
Oh, spasibo, thank you!
Prekrasno, great!
Wh-What's going on?
Grandma! I was taking a bath!
You were here too, Eri?
That's not the right question right now!
Why is Andrianov here?!
Why shouldn't he be?
Are you jealous or something...
Goodness! Who would've thought—
the foreigners are great in more ways than one.
Come check this out too, hurry!
Unless you've seen it already?
Forget about that and do something about him already!
Ta-da!
With everyone's events decided and registration finished,
I've put together this nice little poster for us! Yay!
Let's all practice to the best of our abilities
until the championships in three weeks!
Yea— Uh?
Jackass! Why did you call me a Gorilla?!
Who's the real dumbass again?
Coach Andrianov!
Dobriy den'! Hello!
We're counting on your guidance, sir!
Sir!
Da. Yes.
However, even if you want my guidance...
I have already taught you everything I know.
E-Everything?
We already know everything?
Wh-What do you mean?
Glasses, can you do a somersault on the vault?
Double somersault?
It's a walk in the park!
What?
What was that?
What did you make him do?
Some new technique?
We'll see...
S-So high!
So high! How did I manage to jump that high?
U-Uchida!
What did you just...
What was that?
Well, the coach just told me to spin using my chest, like in a somersault...
Using your chest?
I see! So that's what happened!
When you spin with your chest,
the spin is larger than with your waist!
It's a technique that applies to all events!
H-Hey! Step away for a moment, I'll try it next!
I'll go first!
Silence! I must jump one more time to test!
What was that?!
Did you make us pass the backflip test
just to help us remember this?
Kobayakawa-san?
Hm?
I-It's you!
S-Sergei Andrianov?
But why are you here?
Kobayakawa-san, what happened?
There was something
I absolutely needed to show you.
I got this tape from Sotoyama,
the All Japan Junior Coach.
What's on it?
Could it be some sort of adult material?
Wh-What? Adult material?!
Huh?
Can't wait to see!
Well, you'll know soon enough.
It's not something you see every day.
Hey, for real...?
What, just a gymnastics video?
Cretin! Of course we were joking!
Look closely!
Oh? He's good!
A chain of special techniques...
He's moving very efficiently...
Captain, what was this technique?
D-Dunno...
And a pommel horse!
They jump so high every time!
They're not making any mistakes at all!
All signs point to this team competing
in the upcoming All Japan Junior Championships.
Huh?! Th-This is a junior team?
Yeah, when I first saw it myself,
I couldn't even imagine they were in the same league as me.
Nishihori College Junior Gymnastics Club.
When I learned they have such athletes
on a team that hasn't even debuted yet...
I've lost all confidence.
I even considered quitting.
You shouldn't feel that dispirited,
Kobayakawa-san.
Uh?
I mean, if even the All-Japan Junior champion thinks it's hopeless,
what are guys like us supposed to do?
Right, right!
We, on the other hand, are totally fine with it.
That just means we gotta fight back, harder!
Yeah! Exactly!
Come on, Kobayakawa-san!
Let's fight back together, as allies!
H-Huh?
This is what we say in times like this...
Come on, Higashi!
Yeah! I'm fired up!
Hooray! Ganba!
As expected of Heisei guys.
When I beelined here, maybe it was because of the unbending spirit I felt in you?
Let's prepare an answer!
Kobayakawa-san!
Sure you want me to get in on the spirit too?
W-We'll be in trouble!
O-Oh, is that so?
Stop! Who is that?
Huh?
Oh...
It's the coach of this team.
I wonder what his name is...
I'm sure he's Chinese, Lee...?
Fujimaki-kun, good luck!
Swing with your chest!
Say, Higashi, don't you feel like we've become
higher-level athletes,
and it's not just about learning new techniques?
Yeah. That's true.
That's the world champ for you!
That said, I wonder where Andrianov went all of a sudden. Goodness...
Nishihori College Gymnastics Club
We're here.
Now, won't you finally tell me what's the deal with suddenly making me bring you here?
Hold up! Don't just ignore me, say something!
I'm not your personal driver!
So this is it. This is the devil's den.
Huh?
A demon of ice
with no human heart.
What's wrong?
Did you sprain your ankle?
N-No, sir. It's nothing.
Then try it again.
O-Okay...
What's wrong?
Do I have to repeat myself?
I-If you would please
let me rest for just a moment...
Very well.
You can rest all you want—
once you've packed up and gone home.
H-How come...
You sprained your ankle
because you're inattentive.
We have no use for those who hurt themselves!
P-Please forgive me just this once!
Really, it's nothing!
Please, Coach Lee!
Out of my sight!
You're interrupting our practice!
Get out right now!
So how many people that makes?
Andrianov?
Long time no see.
I asked, how many people that makes?
What do you mean?
I'm asking about the number of athletes you've ruined so far.
What was that?
Don't say nonsense!
Every athlete I've coached
has reached great heights.
You, on the other hand,
are just as uncouth even after 10 years.
Bastard! Don't you dare saying you forgot about Chen Qinghua!
Chen Qinghua? Who's that?
I don't know anyone with that name.
You demonic swine!
Stop!
Really... What's wrong with you?
That got me scared!
If I'd let you hit him back then,
we'd probably be in big trouble now.
So what really happened?
Who is Chen?
Chen Qinghua was
the first ever student I coached.
16 years ago.
I worked as a coach at a gymnastics club
in Beijing for two years.
Qinghua was just ten years old at the time.
She was blessed with both great flexibility
and wonderful jumping ability.
She had all the makings
of a great athlete like Comaneci
who scored several perfect 10s
at the Montreal Olympics.
Qinghua,
do you enjoy gymnastics?
Yes! I love gymnastics!
And I love coach Andrianov too!
She was an exceptional learner,
and her progress surpassed my expectations.
But above all, she had a smile that made everyone's day brighter.
Eventually, my coach's contract ended, so I handed things over
to my successor and returned to my homeland.
"Do your best, I know you'll become a legendary gymnast one day.
Please never forget your love for gymnastics."
Three years later,
I wound up in Beijing again.
She was 15, at her peak as an athlete.
Qinghua!
Don't get distracted, Chen!
I can replace you anytime!
I'm sorry, Coach Lee!
I was speechless when I saw
how much she'd changed.
My successor, Coach Lee, imposed strict dietary restrictions and excessive strength training on her.
Qinghua was prohibited from growing any taller, and her body fat was reduced to the bare minimum.
Qinghua, do you still enjoy gymnastics?
I only enjoy it when I manage
to score higher than my opponent.
No!
That was the last time I saw her.
Her health was compromised, and it seems
she could no longer do gymnastics.
In Lee's eyes, Qinghua was merely one of the losers, probably.
But it was his guidance
that destroyed Qinghua!
Someone like him will stop at nothing to win and will discard you if you're of no use to him.
I understand how you feel.
But I can't say Coach Lee
is unconditionally wrong, either.
That's what it takes to win on the world stage.
No, even going beyond that
won't guarantee victory on the world stage.
You can't have fun and be successful
at the same time.
As a world champion,
you should know that better than anyone.
You were once the best gymnast in the socialist country, the Soviet Union.
Exactly. That's what gives me such keen understanding of it.
You saw the athletes in that gym, right?
Uh? Yes.
They were compact and lean,
quite obviously dieting.
Do you think they shone?
Huh?
Shun and the others are shining!
Gymnastics has to be fun!
But with fun alone, you can't beat those athletes Coach Lee trained.
Gymnastics isn't about winning or losing against others—it's a competition with yourself!
That's why gymnastics is fun.
These are Seiji's words.
Thanks to those words, I was able to win gold.
I was able to overcome myself because I had fun.
Father's words?
Higashi-senpai, what are you trying to do?
Original technique: Human Bridge!
How do you like this?!
How high do you think it'll score?
Are you stupid?!
Get down, Muscle Gorilla!
He's right, Higashi. Get your act together!
I'm not done yet!
Do you guys enjoy gymnastics?
Well, I guess we do.
Pulling off a good jump feels great!
I feel lucky when my muscles
twitch with excitement!
It's always fun to be able to do something you couldn't do before!
Yeah! I'm having fun too!
Yes, that's right.
These boys will win this, Eri!
Fun gymnastics
Mandore Manoff
Fun gymnastics?
Mandore Manoff?
What's that?
"Fun Gymnastics"—that's the theme for our special training for the upcoming championships!
Oh? A special training
from the world champion?
S-So what's that training going to be?
That training session's gotta be great!
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it now!
My muscles are tingling
from just thinking about it!
Coach Andrianov, we'll do as you say!
We will!
Sure, leave it to me!
What's so funny?
Take it more seriously!
B-But aren't you laughing yourself
while scolding me?
Oh geez...
Really... What on earth are they doing?
Is it fun?
It's still not one bit fun...
Even my muscles are telling me
they're not having fun!
It's embarrassing more than it is fun...
Quit grumbling and take it seriously! Ready?
All right...
Un, deux, trois, smile!
Un, deux, trois, smile...
Smile!
Oh come on...
Coach Misaki...
Is something wrong?
Get you act together!
Are you trying to sabotage our practice?
Sabotage? Why?
It just feels so surreal seeing boys
do ballet in the gym...
It's so funny we can't concentrate!
For your information...
We're not doing this for your amusement.
That's right.
Ballet is just our warm-up exercise
before practice!
If you're warming up,
do it more normally!
Oh, no...
And don't "oh, no" me!
If you're going to practice, do it seriously!
I'm fine with fun gymnastics, but the clown gymnastics is distracting us, so you'll have to stop!
We never intended to be clowns, though...
If we're both getting in the way of each other's practice, I guess there's only one option...
Huh?
What option?
Eh?
What now?
Secret training!
Secret training?!
What is it this time?
All right, boys.
Let's get out of here for now.
We're bothering the ladies.
O-Okay...
They just left...
What do you think this secret training could be, Coach Misaki?
How would I know of such nonsense?
The distraction is gone, so I'm relieved.
Come on, resume the practice, girls.
Okay!
What is that secret special training?
Well then, goodbye, Coach Misaki.
Bye. Take care on your way home.
Coach Misaki...
Are you guys going to practice now?
That's right.
We always do our warm-up elsewhere,
so we can use the gym after everyone has left.
R-Really, so that's what happened?
I was actually worried
when everyone suddenly stopped coming.
That's why it's called secret training.
Yes, yes!
I get it, it's secret, but what exactly
have you been practicing?
No comment!
Wh-What does that mean?!
Why do you have to keep it secret
even from your own gymnastics club?
This area is off-limits to you from here on.
C-Coach Misaki...
Coach Misaki!
Why are you here at this hour?
Haven't you gone home yourself?
But the boys start their secret training only after we leave, don't they?
They've been hiding it from us for a week already,
even though we're in the same club.
They don't have to go that far, do they?
I've also been wondering what they're practicing.
Huh?!
Don't just make scared faces!
What on Earth did these two see there?
And what kind of secret training
is the men's club doing?
Please tell us soon, Ganbarist Shun!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Oh! Those are TV cameras!
Camera?
Over there too!
Oh! There's more here!
Well then, let's do our best!
U-Ueno-kun!
He's so nervous!
Is he a robot now?
Ready!
Next Ganba: It's Happening!
Heated Junior Championship.
Today, we're practicing the split jump on the vaulting box!
Build up speed on your run-up,
kick the springboard, and handspring forward.
If you are not good at jumping boxes and are afraid,
learn by asking for help
with jumping over the vaulting boxes.