The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
You helped me realize it clearly.
Fujimaki-kun...
For some reason, Fujimaki-kun's back appeared so large back then.
It was truly a miracle made possible
by a future gold medalist.
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
It's a Miracle!
The Ultimate Performance for the Gold Medal
The men's final event is Heisei's performance on the high bar.
Let's go see it!
The other teams' scores...
have improved.
Shun's routine composition amounts to 9.0 points.
He needs to score 9.5.
If he scores less,
they'll get disbanded.
Listen, Fujimaki.
Yes?
Do your best, go all out!
Leave behind no regrets.
Okay! I'll do my best.
It's finally starting.
Yeah.
Yes, I understand it clearly now.
Olympics, gold medal,
becoming the best in the world...
In the end, it all comes down to me just loving gymnastics!
Class 1-B, Fujimaki Shun!
I want to win an Olympic gold medal!
His moves are very clean.
That guy's quite good.
Because his movements are so clean,
his swings appear bigger.
Yeah...
He's as cool as a cucumber!
Did he get his groove back?
Looking good, Fujimaki!
Look... Everyone is enthralled by Fujimaki-kun's performance!
Yes...
I see it now!
Until recently, I couldn't even do a handstand or a backflip.
Yet here I am, performing on a high bar!
Nice!
That's a good dislocate!
It's thanks to their support...
Thanks to meeting all of them...
That I could do my best!
Right now, all I have to think about is doing my best, right, Sagara-san?
Nice to meet you!
With just one hand!
He's doing a one-handed giant swing!
One-handed swing?
Shun-kun can do one-handed swing?
Yes, it's Shun's signature move!
A middle school student was able to master such a technique, Misaki-san?
Fujimaki-kun!
Watch me, Sagara-san!
He changed his routine composition!
He's swinging too much!
Fujimaki!
Let's go!
His special technique?
No way...
Is that...
A Gienger?
How can he keep flying for so long?
It is... It truly is...
a miracle!
What just happened?!
Whatever it was, it's amazing!
Gienger
Sideways somersault with closed legs
Gienger? No way!
But it definitely was a Gienger somersault.
From one-handed swing too!
Did he say Gienger?
I think it has a C-class of difficulty.
And from a one-handed swing
it must be even higher!
From one-handed swing?
So high!
How is he that strong?!
Fujimaki-kun is smiling!
It's like the iron bar is part of his body!
Fujimaki-kun...
I can see them...
I can see your wings.
Nice!
He nailed it!
Yeah. It was a flawless stretched twist!
I did it, Sagara-san.
Thank you...
Awesome!
What a guy!
Sagara-san?
What's with ya, my guy?!
That was epic!
You totally nailed that performance!
Look at who's been hiding such a trick!
That was quite something!
Senpai, where's Sagara-san?
Look, Fujimaki!
The judges are discussing your score!
It was a one-handed Gienger, after all.
Do you think they'll score it higher than 9.5?
Goodbye, Fujimaki-kun.
Thank you for that dream-like performance.
Come on, Mariko.
Mister, we're in a hurry to get to Tokyo Station.
If Fujimaki-kun scores 9.5,
we'll tie for 6th place
with Gyotoku Middle School.
9.5! If you get 9.5 or higher,
they'll leave our club alone!
How long are they gonna be doing it?
What's your problem?
Announce the score already!
Head judge, is there an issue with our decision?
I'd like to raise it a little more.
Raise it?
Why, sir? We previously gave Kamura a 9.2.
Compared to his program,
Fujimaki's performance is less difficult.
Since the difficulty level is lower,
we cannot possibly rate it higher than Kamura's.
Difficulty, you say?
You are all forgetting something important.
Sir?
The reaction of the audience.
Everyone in the audience was blown away
and enthralled by his performance.
Did you forget their exhilarated reaction to his techniques?
Reaction? You want to add extra points for that?
That is my judgment.
If we keep focusing on small-scale gymnastics
and just chasing difficulty scores,
Japan will eventually
lag behind the global standard.
Fujimaki's performance
was original and artistic.
I believe that his efforts must be rewarded with extra points.
What do you think?
Oh! They finally finished discussing.
Here comes nothing.
Yeah.
Heh. It was nothing special.
If I get 9.5...
9.5...
9.5!
9 and...
4?
9.4?!
A-Are they for real?
Heisei got the score in the nines for the high bar again!
Is this the end of the club?
Well done, Fujimaki.
Yeah! You're the real one!
But... But I couldn't score 9.5.
Don't be stupid!
How can you say things like that?
It's us who let you down completely!
That's right! You got friggin' 9.4!
Just relax and be happy!
Exactly!
That was amazing, Fujimaki-kun!
You showed them what it means to shine!
That was stunning!
Senpai...
That one-handed swing was great!
I definitely didn't expect that Gienger.
Keep up the good work!
We'll be looking forward to it, Heisei Guys!
How come I got 9.2 and he got 9.4?!
They gave him extra points for originality.
Before long, we'll be competing with him on junior tournaments.
Don't you think so, Kamura-kun?
Tsk. What an upstart.
Let's go interview the Heisei guys!
Yessir!
Fujimaki-kun was wonderful.
Yeah.
He really was.
Oh, that's quite impressive to see everyone so engaged.
But why are they so excited about a team that's not even in top six?
Yes, as you said,
they couldn't place in the top six.
But in the end, those kids achieved great heights regardless.
Oh? Sagara-san?
Sagara-san?
Now that's strange...
Sagara-san was here just a moment ago.
Maybe she went to bathroom?
Um... Fujimaki-san?
To Fujimaki-kun
This is from Sagara-san.
She asked me to pass it to you
when you finish your routine.
Huh?
Fujimaki-kun, I never said it before...
Because if I'd told you the truth,
I definitely would've burst into tears.
It can't be...
Hey...
Hey, Fujimaki!
Where are you going?
It can't be... It can't!
I'm writing this letter to say goodbye.
Even in my new school in Fukui,
I'll never forget all of you guys.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Well, it's embarrassing to still be unable to do back hip circle.
That's a lie.
Could it be that you're changing schools again?
Jeez... I guess I can't hide anything from you.
Yes. I'm a wandering transfer girl.
My fate is to never stay in the same place for long.
When will you move?
Not just yet...
In a little while.
We've not known each other for long,
but thank you from the bottom of my heart.
And I hope...
you forgive me for leaving
without saying goodbye.
Fujimaki?
P.S.:
Fujimaki-kun, your high bar
is a truly wonderful sight.
Don't let go of your dreams.
How could this...
How could this happen?!
Really?
She left for the Tokyo Station already?
Madam, did you know?
She wanted you to concentrate on the tournament.
That's why she never said anything.
What a truly considerate young lady.
Even so...
We didn't secure that 6th place,
and the club will be disbanded now.
Just as we were getting the hang of it too...
I just wanted to say thank you to Sagara-san...
It was thanks to her that I've been able to perform till the end.
So that's where you are?
What exactly are you doing here
instead of attending the award ceremony?
Ugh!
Coach Misaki!
Maybe she's lucky she didn't have to see
all those dispirited faces of yours.
This hag again...
However, if we take off now,
we might still make it in time.
Huh? Take off?
We'll chase her right now!
So? You going or not?
A minivan?
Coach Misaki!
Now I get it!
But Eri, aren't you...
Now then, let's get going, Madam.
No, I mean...
Yeah! No way we let Mari-chan leave without seeing her off!
Hey, wait a minute...
Orikasa, take care of the rest here.
Okay!
Okay, is everyone ready?
Ow-ow... What happened?
My bad, people.
Is that what I think it is?
Beginner's sign?!
Good Lord, Good Lord, Good Lord, Good Lord...
Okay, now we take off for real!
My belt! Give it back, Higashi!
It's too short!
Sagara-san, I...
I must tell you...
Stop yelling!
I can't drive with all this racket! Quiet down!
Oh crap!
But you've gotta say your goodbyes, haven't you?!
Hurry up! You've gotta catch up whatever it takes, Ganbarist Shun!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Goodbye, guys...
Sagara-san!
Sagara-san, where are you?
Next Ganba: Floor it! Forcing our Way Through Tokyo Station.
Ganbarist Shun is getting really exciting, don't you think?
Morisue Shinji
Next time, I will also be holding a one-point race using my fun gymnastics skills.
Please watch it, everyone.
Everyone will be helping!
Ready? Please watch it!
Next time
Watch it!
Ganbarist training course starts!