The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Are you making a mark with chalk?
Fujimaki, will my high bar lose to Kamura?
I know that I really like your Jaeger!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
It's a Challenge!
The Prince's Last Resort
Let's go!
Muscle messed up the landing,
Glasses fell down from the bar.
We really can't afford any more mistakes.
Sanada-kun must be fighting a terrible pressure right now.
Jaeger is a technique
that is really easy to fail.
If you let go even a little too early,
you won't be able to reach the bar.
If you're too slow,
you'll land right on the bar.
That's why it's used so rarely in important competitions.
We just need him to get it right.
If he does that, we'll be out of dire straits.
Sanada, good luck!
I know you can do it!
You were the one who secretly worked the hardest!
Twist and reversed turn!
It's a Jaeger!
What?
Uh...
Did he say Jaeger?!
Sanada-senpai! Ganba!
Don't let us down, Sanada!
Go for it!
Sanada-senpai!
Do your best!
Sanada!
You can do it!
It's all or nothing!
Now!
Grab it!
He can't return!
I-I'm falling!
Sanada! Don't let go!
Our gymnastics club is in your hands!
He did it!
Diamond Jaeger!
That's it!
Sanada-senpai!
Well done, Sanada!
Awesome!
Yeah...
Jaeger! He pulled it off!
I-Impossible!
The same Swan Double as Kamura!
Mochida, snap a photo! Hurry up!
Already am!
I won't let you down, Sakashita-san.
Not bad, Mochida.
And now—the landing!
Don't mess up!
Please!
He did it!
Sanada-kun is amazing!
Yeah. His wonderful Jaeger makes the girls, the old ladies and even moms fall in love alike.
Wh-What's with you?
I-I can't believe it!
Sanada-senpai, that was so cool!
He's as cool as you'd expect!
Well done, Sanada!
9...
9.25!
Amazing! He's got the best score on the high bar, even better than Kamura!
That's it!
Impressive!
That's our Sanada-senpai!
Too cool to be true!
Fujimaki, Ueno. Roll my catchphrase.
Yessir! The prince...
of Floor and High Bar!
That's better!
The Prince of Floor and High Bar
He did it!
Yes. All that's left now is for Shun to score 8.95 or higher.
Fujimaki has a 9.0 routine composition, so if he doesn't make any mistakes, the 6th place is ours!
And we'll avoid disbandment!
Yeah, that Girls' Magnet did really well.
Oh! They're loving it!
They're showering him in admiration!
All right, to top it all off, let's do that.
Huh? "That?"
Yeah, might as well go for it!
Yeah, let's make it loud!
More power to Heisei!
We are...
Heisei Middle School's...
Gymnastics club!
The agents of love and hope!
When did they three rehearse for that...
I suppose it was meant to be an encouraging chant, but...
They look stupid.
Way to go, Heisei!
Why did they make a spectacle of themselves...
I kinda wish they'd put all that energy
into their performances...
We were so anxious about those three nailing their performances, only for it to end up like this...
It's just them, but...
I'm so embarrassed!
So embarrassed!
Damn right.
We are...
Heisei's...
Gymnastics club!
Gentlemen! You're interfering with performances!
Don't you hear me telling you to stop?!
W-We're sorry...
It seems Heisei has made a name for itself in this tournament as well...
Still, I can understand their happiness.
Our club is under insane pressure to finish this tournament in the top six.
When we were on the verge of despair after Uchida's and Higashi's failures,
Sanada's Jaeger turned it all around!
Somehow, we managed to regain hope.
Both them...
And me.
And you... too?
You were supposed to dance with them?
Huh? No, I mean... Of course not! As captain, I have to rise above that!
Besides, look—my foot
is in no shape for dancing!
You would've danced if it wasn't injured!
Well, regardless, I think we're starting to see a glimmer of hope.
We'll have the sixth place, same as last time.
Heisei's last guy still hadn't performed, though.
He'll need to score 9.5 to overtake us. It ain't happening.
I guess you're right.
Wh-What was that?!
Hey, let me see it for a moment!
Wh-What's with you?
Other schools improved
their results since last time...
Hey, Ueno!
Yes?
What is it, Sanada-senpai?
Uh... What is our total score, currently?
Give me a moment.
Well, if we factor in
the 9.25 you just brought home...
Let's see...
Huh?
It's 70.25.
I-It can't be...
That's ridiculous!
I just borrowed the score sheet from some suckers over there!
What is our score?
70.25.
Right, right...
We really gave it our best!
H-Hey!
Th-That means...
If Fujimaki doesn't score 9.5 or more...
The sixth place...
It's impossible! Fujimaki-kun's routine composition only amounts to 9.0.
Even if he nails every part of it,
scoring 9.5 is impossible!
But then they'll disband the club.
Damn it! If only...
If only I didn't make a mess of that landing!
No, if only I hadn't fallen from the bar...
There's no point grieving it now!
Now they'll definitely disband us.
No way! Nothing is decided yet!
What now...
What should I do?
Fujimaki...
Fujimaki-kun?
W-Wait...
Fujimaki-kun...
Please!
Wait!
Please, wait!
Wh-What is she doing?
Mari-chan...
I can see it...
I can see it.
A powerful backhand swing
transitions into a foot circle...
And then—stretched one-handed swing.
S-Sagara-san?
I can see it.
You, on the high bar...
I can see you performing at the high bar at the Olympics.
Before this huge crowd...
In complete silence.
Everyone is watching your performance with bated breath.
You can only hear the rod crackling.
You carve out a powerful yet stead rhythm in the tense air.
And then...
I'm also there.
Finally...
They give you a thunderous round of applause and cheers.
It's a perfect 10.0!
You did it!
Fujimaki, Japan—gold medal!
S-Sagara-san?
You told me once, remember?
Though a bit shy, you told me that your dream is to win an Olympic gold medal.
However, the way you looked just now
made it seem like that dream had been crushed
and abruptly ended.
The way things are going now,
the club might be done for.
But hold on to your dreams! Please...
Your dream is my dream!
And then someday, everyone else too...
I'm sure it'll become
everyone's dream someday!
That's why...
Sagara-san...
Thank you.
Who'd think they'd be able to improve their score by 0.75 since last time.
I'm not qualified to be their coach!
Madam...
That's not true!
Up until your the high bar fiasco,
we were 1.2 points in surplus.
I'm the one who must feel ashamed,
sitting out such an important competition...
At such an important time,
all I can do is watch them...
Shindo-kun...
How do you like that?
Kamura got a 9.3 on the floor.
Murayasu team finished their performance.
Western Maehara is also through with the vault.
That was spectacular, Kamura-kun.
I look forward to competing with you at the All-Japan Junior Tournament .
The feeling's mutual, Kobayakawa-san.
And now, only the Heisei routine on the high bar remains.
Fujimaki, go in with all you've got.
Sanada-senpai?
It's fine.
We're getting disbanded either way.
Even if you fail, it doesn't change anything.
Just follow your heart there
and go all out.
Follow my heart?
Yeah. Exactly.
Follow...
Follow my heart?
Go all out as my heart wishes?
Yessir! I'll go all out!
You dumbass!
You didn't have to yell it to my ear!
Go for broke, Fujimaki!
Fujimaki-kun...
Look, it's Shun-kun!
Shun!
Fujimaki!
Shun, what on earth are you going to do?
Madam,
it's something I felt
ever since I first met Shun-kun.
If he doesn't give up and continues on the path of gymnastics, he's bound to make a great athlete.
Reiko-chan...
That's right.
I won't give up either.
Even if the club is no more,
my love for gymnastics is eternal!
Yeah, so I thought.
Fujimaki-kun...
Dad...
Is it time already?
Please, Dad.
Just a little more, that's all I ask!
I want to look at Fujimaki-kun's performance...
Please let me dream... For just a little more!
Please!
Mariko...
It's hard to see from here.
Let's go over there!
Oh... Dear!
This is the final performance
of the Heisei Men's Gymnastics Club.
Make it spectacular
and shine with excellence.
Senpai...
We made it this far!
Don't slip up now!
...I'd have said if someone here
wasn't stealing my lines!
I-It hurts! It really hurts, goddammit!
Fujimaki-kun, Ganba!
Fujimaki-kun...
Well now, it looks like they're not making it to top six, doesn't it?
P-Principal?
Yes, it's a pity,
but I guess we've no choice.
Now, all of the gymnastics club's facilities,
equipment, and expenses will be redirected for the needs of the women's team.
I look forward to your work
as the women's team exclusive coach.
Not yet!
It's not decided yet...
That kid... Fujimaki-kun can still turn the tide with his performance!
Don't leave until you've watched it!
Perhaps you're right.
Let's watch it.
Sagara-san.
Huh?
I want to be the best in the world.
I want to win gold at the Olympics.
That was the simple reason that drew me to gymnastics.
But now...
I really like gymnastics.
Yes.
It was you who helped me
understand it clearly.
Fujimaki-kun...
That's why
I believe that this performance should become the first step, not the last one.
Sagara-san, please watch closely
as I take my first steps.
Sure!
At that time, Fujimaki's back appeared so large.
And the high bar performance
he showed me, his first steps...
Will stay with me forever.
I'm sure it was a miracle made possible
by a future gold medalist.
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Do your best! Go all out!
Stop at nothing.
Yes! I'll do my best!
He's as cool as a cucumber!
Did he get his groove back?
Looking good, Fujimaki!
Look at me, Sagara-san!
What great sense of space!
It's nothing short of a miracle!
Fujimaki-kun is smiling!
I can see his wings!
Next Ganba: It's a Miracle!
The Best Performance for the Gold Medal.
Ring techniques consist of vibration techniques, force techniques, and static techniques.
They requires tremendous muscle strength and sense of balance.
Above all, pulling up while keeping your body horizontal.
Then you bend and stretch before a double somersault.
All that while not letting go of the ring!
Guczoghy is ultra E!