The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Kamura-san, he'll beat you.
What?!
It's out! 9.75!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Prince of Floor!
A Magnificent Swan Feast
Episode
Prince of Floor!
A Magnificent Swan Feast
Koda of the Nishihori Club?
Amazing...
We're witnessing the birth
of a legendary athlete.
The speed and series
of acrobatic straight-body moves...
And above all, he used the same Swan Doppel as both his opening and closing move!
It takes enormous strength!
H-Hey, what are you doing?
Hm? What?
Warming up, what else could it be!
W-Warming-up?
Well then, time to go?
Hey Ueno, say my name.
Yes?
Uh... Wh-What do you mean, Sanada-senpai?
Forget it! Geez, you're such a buzzkill.
Now, it's finally time for the last men's floor performance: Sanada from the Heisei Club.
Sanada-senpai, do your best!
The current highest score on the floor is 9.75,
held by Koda from Nishihori College, the Lee Corps.
What kind of performance
will Sanada show us?
What's there to be excited about?
After Koda's performance...
No matter what he tries,
gold will obviously stay with Koda!
Good luck!
Let's see what that special training was all about.
What is it this time?
Will he be any impressive, Andrianov?
You can do it!
Ready...
Prince of Floor!
What was that?
Did they say Prince of Floor?
How lame!
Looking good, Prince of Floor!
Good luck!
Prince of Floor! Good luck!
Prince of Floor!
The atmosphere is surprisingly relaxed...
Tsk!
He'll still lose! How embarrassing!
Go for it, Prince!
Prince!
It got out of hand...
They noticed me.
They're cheering for me.
All the TV cameras are looking at me at once!
Lucky!
Let's go!
All right, Sanada raises his hand!
Did he grow taller since the last time?
Uh? No, I don't think so...
He looks bigger somehow.
Now, let the performance begin!
Keep taking photos, just in case.
Gotcha.
He sets forth with a Roundoff!
What will he jump next?
Oh, is this...
J-Just a double tucked up somersault?
T-Tucked up double somersault!
The landing was perfect and performed at ease.
Nice!
That's a basic-level move!
What's the deal with Heisei?
Did they come here with nothing but chicken feed?
That's weird.
Hm? What's wrong, Mochida?
I missed this one.
Huh?
Well, whatever.
It was just a double somersault.
That's weird...
Hey! Where are your eyes?
You didn't catch this somersault!
For how many years
have you all been doing this?!
And the performance continues!
Sanada-senpai! Go!
Way to go!
Tucked up again?
All his moves are tucked up.
All right, this time for sure! Huh?
He's gone!
He lands! He nailed another landing beautifully!
After all the consecutive tucked up moves!
Film it, goddammit!
Well done,
Prince of Floor!
Prince   of Floor
I... I missed it again.
Seriously, Mochida?
Why can't you photograph such an easy move?
It's not easy!
What?
What are you doing?!
We can't see him for the most of the somersault!
It's not even worth our time.
He's doing all the same techniques Koda of the Lee Corps had done previously, but tucked up!
It's too goddamn easy!
You think so? It looks like a decent performance to me, though...
You're an amateur!
The only amateur here is you.
What?!
Is that all you have to offer, Andrianov?
I'm disappointed.
What do you mean it's not easy?
It's extraordinary.
I've been shooting gymnastics
for Gym Road for five years already.
But I've never seen an athlete that outstanding!
I just don't understand
what you're talking about.
B-But the problem is him...
Really? When I look at it,
it looks to me like a plain Y-shaped balance pose.
It should be a run-of-the-mill performance.
Nothing to be amazed about.
What?
Is he...
Huh?! What's that balance pose?
Sakashita-san, what do you call that balance?
A-A Russian athlete used this technique at the World Championships...
Hey, how come he has a body that flexible?
Look closer!
He's on his tiptoes!
He's doing that kind of balance pose
while standing on his tiptoes?!
A-Amazing! I told you
Heisei were up to something special!
Our secret training is paying off!
To reach that balance, Sanada-senpai
did ballet stretching every morning and night!
But it looks to me like he overdid it.
Huh?
He'd inserted ballet
even where it wasn't necessary.
What do you mean,
"where it wasn't necessary?"
Look there.
Yeah...
It looks kind of feminine.
Although Heisei is only famous for Orikasa Reiko,
their men's team is also noteworthy.
Hey, isn't it pretty cool?
Yeah, handsome.
Ready, go...
Prince of Floor!
They're loving it.
I left an impression, just as planned!
Prince of Floor, keep it up!
I don't need your cheers.
Prince of Floor!
All right...
That's how it's done!
Sanada-kun looks happy...
What a bore.
Gymnastics is all about the difficulty!
Low-level gymnasts who are just flexible
aren't worth all that buzz!
Humph. He doesn't even understand the value of a flexible body,
yet he calls himself a gymnastics expert.
What was that, you old fart?
I'm tired of you grumbling bullshit to my ear!
Kaizuka-san, please calm down!
Looking good!
What a farce...
Hey, Mochida, what did you mean earlier?
About him being the most outstanding gymnast you've seen in five years.
It's the height.
Height...
Height?!
His somersault is high.
It's abnormally high!
So high it doesn't fit in the camera frame.
They're loving it!
Hold up, the audience's reaction wasn't
that great during the first double somersault.
My final tumbling is the same as the starting one,
tucked up double somersault.
Would it really impress everyone as much
if I used that move again as the finish?
No, it won't be any fun.
Sanada-san!
Not just unhappy,
they'd be offended!
So, what kind of finishing move will he show us?
All that gymnast's techniques are
tucked variations, which don't score well.
He'd have to do something like Swan's Doppel like the Lee Corps to stand any chance!
And we know that ain't happening!
He might just go for it!
Yeah, seems so.
Huh? What do you mean?
Look closely at Sanada's face.
The sly corners of his eyes
are drooping even more than usual!
Ah!
Now we know for sure he's up to no good!
Up to no good?
He's going to change his routine!
Probably!
What?!
No way!
And he prepares to start his final tumbling!
Prince! Prince! Prince! Prince!
Oh, what a surprise!
The audience chants his moniker!
Prince...
Prince! Prince! Prince!
Whoa! It went to his head!
This is bad!
Now, he begins his run-up!
If Sanada can fly higher than Koda
during a somersault...
Sanada can also perform a straight-body Doppel!
I got everyone fired up.
I can't let them down now!
So it's a straight-body somersault!
And it's high!
Swan's Doppel.
He twists!
He added a twist to Swan's Doppel!
Ridiculous! You can't have that and straight-body somersault!
It's an Olympic-tier move!
Twist!
He twists! This is a straight-body Moonsault!
I-Incredible!
This time, I'll capture it all!
Huh?
Sanada-senpai!
Watch out!
I can do it!
I did it!
Just as he thought that he nailed it all,
Sanada lands outside of the field!
What is he trying to do?
Maybe he's trying to trick the judges...
Looking great, Prince!
What's that idiot doing?
He had never attempted the straight-body Moonsault before,
so he couldn't gauge the required distance.
Sanada-senpai looks happy
even though he made a mistake.
They love it!
They'll definitely rebroadcast it
as a special issue in the evening time slot!
His score is... 9.45!
Still, you gotta admit,
it was a spectacular performance.
Humph! He botched the finishing move!
And if he'd land in the floor area,
he'd fail it even harder!
Let's look at his finishing move in slow motion.
Huh?
Really? They failed to capture it?
Those bunglers!
It was too high for them.
Sanada's somersaults are
nothing like that of other Japanese athletes.
They simply don't fit in the normal frame.
Stop talking like you know everything, you dotard! A mistake is a mistake!
R-Run the commercial!
Heisei Middle School, then?
I should keep an eye on that team.
Prince of Floor! You were great!
This concludes the first men's event, floor exercise.
In the end, Koda from Lee Corps won with 9.75.
But it was Sanada
who garnered the most acclaim.
Wouldn't he have overtaken Koda
if he didn't bungle that Straight-body Moonsault?
But he failed.
Come, let's interview Koda!
Huh?
PRACTICE FIELD
You've got some nerve
to change your routine like that!
PRACTICE FIELD
If this was a team competition,
you'd let us all down!
PRACTICE FIELD
Yeah, but still...
Crap, Coach Andrianov is here...
He must be mad because I arbitrary changed my routine... And I slipped up too!
He really is mad!
Uh?
That was a fun performance!
I applaud your courage
and your spirit of self-challenge!
Yoshio, you did well too!
Oh no, not really...
A group of monkeys is no match for us.
All right,
that was a good start.
Our goal is to win every event and completely dominate this tournament!
Yessir!
The first women's event,
the floor exercise, will begin shortly.
The first women's event
will begin shortly.
Reiko-senpai also performs on the floor, right?
Yes! Let's watch it!
H-Hey, wait a minute!
Reiko-sama!
Hurry up!
Let's find a place where we can root for her!
What's the deal with those clowns?
So carefree!
And the very first entry
is the tournament's favorite,
Orikasa Reiko from Heisei Middle School.
Good luck, Reiko-senpai!
You can do it, Orikasa.
Shindo-kun...
Reiko-sama looked at me!
It was me!
I don't think so.
Why would she be interested
in anyone but the Prince of Floor?
Oh geez...
So we all had the same idea?
So that's where I heard about Heisei before.
Who'd think that Orikasa Reiko-chan goes to the same school as them!
Now, Orikasa Reiko prepares to perform
with the honor of Heisei Women's Club at stake.
She is #7 in all of Japan,
but in this All-Japan Junior Individual Championship,
she is the absolute women's champion!
Reiko-senpai! Good luck!
Coach Misaki, um...
I know you want to ask.
It's written on your face, Orikasa.
Uh? Really?
You caught their enthusiasm too, didn't you?
Yes. I want to try it too.
Please let me change the finishing move to that.
We haven't fully trained for it yet.
With your current composition,
you'll get 9.6 which is good enough.
As long as you don't make any big mistakes,
you'll win with a comfortable margin.
If there's a possibility I can pull it off,
I'd like to give it a shot.
I want to challenge myself, like the boys!
All right. Have a go at it, Orikasa.
To the fullest!
Okay!
And she begins her performance!
I know you can do it.
Oh, what a sight!
Yeah...
I want to enjoy gymnastics
like Shun-kun and the others.
During the secret training, they were as cheerful as if it were a game,
yet they improved drastically in just a week!
They looked genuinely happy!
I envy them...
I also want to enjoy it with all my heart!
The enjoyment engulfs your body
like the magic sand,
making you fly so lightly and easily!
Wow! This is astounding!
That twist was something else!
She added a twist to the straight-body forward somersault!
It was a one-and-a-half twist!
You can do it, Orikasa!
Amazing! She's outdone herself!
Is Orikasa really going for that?
Now, what is her finishing move going to be?
Ah, is this what I think this is?
Straight-body somersault with an added twist!
Amazing! Amazing!
She nailed it. Orikasa's performance
was absolutely captivating!
You did it, Reiko-senpai!
Reiko-senpai is awesome!
Good job!
It was Chusovitina, an E-level technique!
There it is! 9.75!
Orikasa secures her victory right away!
Isn't it great?
She did well!
Coach Misaki!
Well done, Orikasa!
Thanks!
That was wonderful.
Next, it's the world championship.
Yes. Thank you!
Congratulations, Reiko-senpai!
Orikasa, you were incredible.
Thank you. You do your best too, Shindo-kun!
Sure...
Why to Captain only?
Orikasa Reiko of Heisei unquestionably dominated the women's floor competition!
The second men's event,
the pommel horse, will begin shortly.
The pommel horse performances will begin shortly.
How boring.
Nobody from Heisei
is competing on that, right?
The pommel horse is the toughest of the six events.
Even the basic moves aren't for beginners.
By the way, where did Uchida and Ueno go?
Ah!
Look!
They're over there!
Why?!
Why...
Uchida had never even seen a pommel horse in his life!
And Ueno-kun even more so!
What are those two thinking?!
Uchida-senpai, why did we enter this event?
Quit worrying about trifles!
I've been cooking up amazing new techniques for this day—techniques no one could've ever imagined!
Are you sure? When did you find the time to practice on pommel horse, Uchida?
What's more, you dragged Ueno with you,
but what exactly are those new amazing techniques?
Should we look forward to it, Ganbarist Minoru?
We're rewriting the history of the pommel horse today!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
For this day, I've prepared amazing moves that no one could have ever imagined.
What could these techniques that'll rewrite the history of pommel horse be?
Is this...
Eh?
What...
Is this?!
Huh?
What the...
The main surprise is yet to come!
Next Ganba: It's a Revolution! The Astonishing Pommel Horse Heisei Restoration.
Today we're learning forward somersault on the boxes.
While jumping headfirst, if you never land your head on the box, that's a forward somersault.
Kick the springboard, and fly over it without touching the box with your head.
Don't forget to swing your legs up high for the best result!