The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Ready...
You guys are like monkeys!
Everyone failed!
F-Failed?
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Higher!
Operation Booby Somersault
It seems to me that Japanese gymnastics is fatally flawed, including women's.
Fatally flawed? Now hold on just a minute there.
What the hell did you mean by that?
Too low!
Too low?
Shun! At the highest point of your backflip,
your head was above this line.
A Russian athlete with the same physique as you can jump this high.
That high?!
If you want me to coach you,
you must be able to at least jump this high.
Same goes for everyone.
Seriously?
Let's look!
What's the difference?
25 cm.
25 cm? There's no way!
That's all?
I can easily jump that high with a running start.
He clearly said "no running start!"
Then just add more strength to it!
Fine... Leave it to me!
Not even close, bud!
No way... It was as high as one can go!
Coach Misaki, is this the fatal flaw
of Japanese gymnastics?
There's no way to jump this high straight up!
If we can't make that jump, we can forget about being coached by the world champ.
I... I'm not ready to give up yet!
I was so inspired when he shared what it feels like to win Olympic gold!
I was hoping he'd stay around
for at least a little while to coach us!
Shun-kun...
Surely we could all improve a lot
if we were coached by an athlete of that caliber.
Are you serious?
It's going to be an event-specific tournament.
Normally, we would never have qualified for this tournament.
But they gave us a chance, and if we're going,
we'll aim for the top. To that end...
Captain...
But how can we do it if we can't jump 25 cm higher than we do now?
Then keep jumping until you can.
If anyone has a problem with my backflip,
I'm not having any of it!
With the honor of the Prince of Floor at stake,
I can make that jump 25 cm or whatever higher!
That's my guy Uchida!
Ugh! I'm also a vault specialist.
Of course I can do it!
Senpai...
Let's make that jump—25 centimeters! Yeah!
But how are you going to do it?
Don't be a buzzkill!
I'll help you too.
Coach Misaki?
I'm coaching one of the Olympic team candidates,
so I simply can't ignore a fatal flaw of our gymnastics.
Coach Misaki!
Now that's reassuring!
How about another round, then?
We've already had two each.
Oh my, Eri, you want to join us too?
It's a declaration of war, Andrianov.
Declaration?
Of war?
Exactly! You called my coaching,
and all of Japanese gymnastics, defective.
You even went as far
as calling me a monkey trainer!
Did you really call her a monkey trainer?
Yes. It's a shame, but compared to Russia's level, they're no better than monkeys.
And what do I call someone who teaches monkeys if not a monkey trainer?
You're saying it again? Fine, then!
I already know it's no use talking to you.
I'm responsible for those kids,
and I'll do my utmost to make them jump 25 centimeters higher than they do now!
Please, go ahead and do your best!
Fujimaki, here!
Do your best!
All right. There's your goal, 25 cm above.
Fujimaki, here!
Do your best!
Jump, Fujimaki!
Ready!
That wasn't one bit higher!
S-Sir...
Like that!
How was it?
Doesn't seem to me like it was any higher...
Were you watching close enough?!
Y-Yes...
How was it?
No good.
There's no improvement in height whatsoever!
Try to swing your arms more to jump higher!
Okay!
Got it? Swing your arms harder. Swing!
Reiko-senpai, do your best!
Swing your arms to fly!
Coach...
Coach Misaki.
Huh?
Coach Misaki, as you suggested, I’m focusing on swinging my arms harder during takeoff
and tucking up my knees to jump higher, but...
Yes, I know.
Keep at it for now.
Wait... No.
Everyone, let's take a little break.
O-Okay!
I'm saved...
But is it even possible to suddenly jump 25 cm
higher in a technique as basic as ABC?
Unless it's your first time doing it...
With confidence, we can do it!
Maybe, if we had any of it left.
But all we have is disappointment!
It's not about the strength of the spring,
or the swing of the arms...
There's something else to it.
There has to be something else.
Uchida-senpai, what are you going to do with this?
Knowing the target height
before doing the jump should help.
Just watch.
Ready!
See now?
I jumped 25 cm higher!
But your head stayed on the very same level.
What!?
All you did was extend your tucked legs.
I knew it—muscle strength equals jump strength!
No amount of muscle strength is enough
to suddenly jump 25 cm higher!
It's just a question of form.
A beautiful form leads to more height.
So?
Playing it cool doesn't equal jumping higher!
Awesome, Ueno-kun!
You improved your result by 5 cm!
Eh, really?
It's nothing special!
Ueno's starting point is already low.
For you, that goal would be 30 cm higher.
No way...
Hey, you guys need to get serious!
Work on the basics—swinging your arms,
taking off, and tucking up!
Okay!
Let's do it!
25 cm higher...
What are we missing?
What happened?
Shun-kun failed his landing.
I-I'm fine.
Just lost my balance a little during the landing.
Be more careful! If you hurt yourself before the competition, I’ll be the one in trouble!
O-Okay...
Let’s wrap up practice for today.
Damn right, she is a demon!
Picking on us for every little thing!
That's only because she's nervous too.
Will that kind of practice
help us jump any higher at all?
Well, maybe the reason Russians can jump higher than us is because of the muscles, after all?
If it's about muscles, I got you covered!
I'm talking about the quality of their muscles.
Maybe the Russians and Japanese
have completely different muscle quality?
So the fatal flaw of our gymnastics
is in our muscles?
No way! This is something
no amount of practice can fix!
I’m an idiot, and taking out my frustrations on kids doesn’t help.
But I don’t understand—swinging the arms,
taking off, tucking up the knees...
What other factor can affect the height of a somersault?
Event-specific championship...
As it stands, we can’t expect anyone but Orikasa to win anything.
It's all my fault.
I have to do something...
Something...
Andrianov
Oh my, Eri.
What else do you need today?
Is he still here?
Andrianov?
He's talking to Shun and the boys.
Huh?
What was that? "You can’t do higher somersaults because you’re Japanese?"
That's what it seems to boil down to.
Russians and Japanese
have different muscle quality.
We're fundamentally different!
Even the food is different.
Even Coach Misaki is troubled now,
trying to make us do the impossible.
Please tell us clearly what it is, or neither we nor Coach Misaki will be able to go on like this.
Those kids...
You guys have no idea how mistaken you are!
Mistaken?
The Japanese can jump just as high!
I've personally known one such Japanese athlete.
Huh?
He was a studious man who worked hard
to acquire that unique technique.
It let him jump wonderfully high!
Who is that athlete?
Seiji Tadokoro, Eri's very own father!
Father?
Coach Misaki's father?
In my coaching, I prioritize
the athletes' motivation and initiative.
The 25 cm height mark
is a test for those qualities.
Believe me, guys, you can jump that high too!
Um, if you at least gave us
some hints on how to jump higher...
You'll be fine. After all,
you guys have a wonderful coach!
Eri is Seiji's daughter.
If you all work together,
you'll surely find the answer!
I understand.
We’ll be giving it our all even more now!
Father...
Father, please let me use it.
The notes you made at the peak of your career.
The secret to the height of your somersaults.
Grandma, what is this?
Hm? What have you got there?
What is this balloon-like figure?
Is it saying we should jump while attached to balloons?
Y-You can't really infer anything from this drawing alone.
My father seems to have used this notebook as a memo, so it wasn't meant for anyone else to see.
But I’m determined to get
to the bottom of this diagram.
U-Um, we’ll also try to figure it out,
each in our own way. Right?
Yes! Let's all do our best!
That's right.
How hard can it be?
It falls to me, the True Specials,
to solve this riddle.
Think I'll give up?!
I get it! It depicts the training
with a road roller!
What does that have to do with the backflip?
Hm? Dunno.
Figures...
Maybe it's a balloon after all?
So jumping with balloons it is?
It looks a bit like a bench in the park.
Maybe he wants us to use a step stool?
Man, oh man, I really wonder where everyone’s attention is.
There's always only one truth.
Did you understand something, Uchida-kun?
Yes!
This diagram is representing Newton's law of universal gravitation!
Newton?
Universal gravitation?
Precisely!
So how do we jump 25 centimeters higher?
I was getting to it.
We do it by ignoring gravity.
If we do that, we'll probably be able to jump higher.
In other words, it's about having the right mindset.
Sure, sure, sure!
Stop it, you three!
Oh?
Did you understand anything?
It says "as in Fosbury flop."
I-It's this?
Yes, the high jump with a running start.
We know what Fosbury flop is.
What does high jump have to do
with that drawing of balloons?
I don't know.
You don't know?! No way...
All I know is that 28 years ago,
American athlete Fosbury was the first to perform the backward high jump.
It seems my father thoroughly researched this technique.
So maybe the key to making you jump higher lies in it.
Sounds interesting.
Well then, let the Prince of the Floor
take a shot at it for you.
Tsk. That was pathetic!
You guys can't handle that height!
Coach Kazami of the track and field club?
Want me to teach you the Fosbury flop, Eri?
Yes, please do.
Now what do you mean
we can't handle that height?!
You're too short.
Huh?
Oh, man... She said it...
So easily.
If you're short, you can't jump high?
Don't get me wrong.
It's not that you can't jump high, it's that jumping higher doesn't convert to actual height.
Jumping higher...
Doesn't convert to height?
Jump height    Center of gravity
For the Fosbury flop, you need to move the height of the jump
plus the height of the center
of gravity over the bar.
Jump height    Center of gravity
Although jumping power
can be improved through training,
Jump height    Center of gravity
the height of your waist
from the ground, that is,
your center of gravity, remains fixed
and cannot be changed.
Which means...
Sounds deeply theoretical.
I used to worry about getting taller when I was still active as an athlete.
With that height?!
Because the taller you are,
the higher your center of gravity will be.
If your center of gravity is higher,
the same jumping force will lift you higher.
If the center of gravity is high...?
I drank a lot of milk because I wanted to grow taller,
but only certain areas ended up growing.
That's true...
That's right! This is it! This!
H-Hold on a minute, Eri!
Everyone! I get it now!
I know the secret of backflip!
Is that true, Coach Misaki?
Well, everyone, get ready
for an intense week of training!
Okay!
It's all thanks to your breasts!
Listen up, you just need to focus
and jump with complete awareness.
Okay!
What do you need that for, Uchida?
I call it "the backflip training helmet."
Rather than simply concentrating,
I will train in a fully scientific way.
R-Really?
Oh, just you watch.
Uchida-senpai, are you okay?
Of course I am!
What do you think this helmet is for?!
How about this?!
H-Higashi-senpai, you've certainly jumped higher than usual just now!
That's what I'm sayin'!
Sir, please...
You've done it, Higashi!
How did you do it?
Was it the effect of concentration?
Yeah! Coach Misaki is right!
My trapezius muscles were what lifted my body higher, even though I’ve never tried it before!
Man, it was so stupid of me to use this guy as a reference.
All right, everyone. Let's all do our best
in a way that suits us!
Whassat?!
That's it! Higashi-kun was able to jump higher! You can do it too, boys!
Higher!
With full awareness!
Reiko-sama!
Lookin' cool!
What do you think? He jumped 25 cm higher than before, just as you asked.
Any more tests?
By no means!
Kak horosho!
We did it!
Did it!
Eri... How on earth did you pull that off?
Simple—we tried to do a backflip
around the chest instead of waist.
Around the chest?
I managed to decipher that diagram dad drew.
In short, until now, we've been rotating around the waist when doing a backflip.
But the actual center of rotation
is above the waist.
If you raise it to your chest,
you can jump higher with the same power.
Oh, I see...
Shifting the axis from our usual one—
around the waist—
to the chest took a lot of concentration at first.
Yes!
So that's how you did it?
What do you say, Andrianov?
Precisely! Gymnastics is something
you do with your chest.
That's what the flaw
of the Japanese gymnastics was!
But we conquered it.
Yes, you did a great job, Miss Forehead!
H-Hold it!
A sudden kiss?
For Russians, it's normal even between men.
T-Talk about cultural barrier.
Shun!
N-No, I'll pass, sir!
I’m going to coach you until the event-specific championships in three weeks, just like I promised!
Really?
Hooray!
We did it!
Yes!
All right, people!
Until the championship,
operation Ultra Ganba is in effect!
Yeah!
Good luck, boys.
This is Kobayakawa Kenichi's routine at last year's junior competition.
And here's Kamura Iwao.
They’re currently competing
for the top spot in the junior ranks.
They’re both all-around athletes
in six disciplines.
What do you think?
Just some pathetic monkeys.
So even guys like them can reach the top of the junior ranks now?
All right, then. You'll be making your debut at the upcoming championships.
You’ll start there and eventually turn Japanese gymnastics on its head.
Is that clear?
Who are these guys
who appeared out of nowhere?
It seems they'll be competing in the next championships, and they're full of confidence!
A rival appears, Ganbarist Shun!
Now, let's start practicing!
Okay!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
It's here... It's here, the devil's den!
Huh?
Is he the devil of ice?
You devil!
Fun Gymnastics
Mandole Manoff
Fun gymnastics?
Mandole Manoff?
"Fun Gymnastics"—that’s the theme for our special training for the upcoming championships!
Eh?
Special training?
Next Ganba: A Formidable Opponent!
The Devil's Team, the Lee Corps.
Once we learned how to start a backflip, it's finally time to do it.
Stand on a high platform and have someone hold you firmly.
Backflip as if you're not going to land on your hands. Go!
It would be great if you could tuck up on top.