Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
That's right, I have these two to help me. What can I ever accomplish if I don't believe in them? Let's go!
Now! Pull him!
I-It's you again!
Exactly! Operation Ultra G starts now!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Like a Bird!
Operation Ultra Gamba
Wait just a minute!
Before you tear down the bar,
please watch our performance!
First of all, who are you guys?
W-We're...
They're the members of
Heisei Middle School's gymnastics club.
But why are you here, Coach Misaki?
To think I'd find you boys practicing at my grandma's of all places...
Grandma's?
Does that mean you're Coach Misaki's...
grandmother?
Crap!
I spoke so poorly about her
in front of her grandma...
That grumpy old maid really is a demon coach!
What's wrong, Uchida?
Excuse me!
Um...
Reiko-senpai!
Orikasa? Why are you here?
I'm not entirely sure myself.
I received this invitation to a performance...
Three of them, actually.
Invitation?
Three of them?
Are you kidding?
We’re not your personal audience!
Yeah, exactly!
We’re here to make sure the high bar gets dismantled!
Chairman, what's the meaning of this?
I mean, you see...
We're begging you!
Please give us a chance!
Captain...
Shindo-kun!
Until two weeks ago, our Heisei Men's Gymnastics Club didn't have a high bar to practice on.
That’s because Coach Misaki took apart our high bar to set up the women’s uneven bars.
Of course I did!
That equipment was wasted on someone as talentless as you.
I'd much rather let gifted athletes like Orikasa let practice more.
I agree. There's no denying that our performance was very poor.
After all, we couldn't hold a candle to Kotaro-kun, the grade-schooler.
Oh, Kotaro! Are you that good with the high bar?
Dear!
Uh?
But that was when we met him.
It was thanks to Kotaro-kun bringing us here
that we were able to discover this wonderful high bar, and above all this excellent coach.
Right, Madam?
Oh, you kids...
That's why we want
to protect this high bar!
We want you to see the performance Madam Tadokoro taught us!
Why don't you give it a rest already?
You're the worst team in the prefecture! What could you possibly learn here in mere two weeks?
Unless you're gonna hold a bread-eating contest again?
Coach...
Saying harsh things like that is what earned you the title of Demon Coach.
Wh-Wh-What now?
Are you on their side too?!
Oh...
Whatever. I don't care if you hold this performance or not!
In the end, you'll only embarrass yourselves even more!
Do it, do it!
And now, allow us to begin the performance!
Please witness the results of our two-week training with Madam Tadokoro!
Let's start with the Captain,
Shindo-senpai!
My name is Shindo Yuichi.
And... I'm going to perform a technique called Tkachev.
Pft! Tkachev, you say?
There's no way you'll ever be able to perform
such a complex technique.
Is he really going for it?
Impressive, Shindo-kun!
In just two weeks...
As expected of Madam Tadokoro.
Grandma...
Second performer: Sanada Toshihiko.
Nicknamed the Prince of Floor.
To tell you frankly,
I'm popular.
He just can’t study to save his life!
Gutless too!
Surely, you don't mean to tell me
you've learned some special technique too?
Fujimaki-kun, please do me the honor...
Sanada-senpai is going to perform Jaeger.
Jae... ger?
Jaeger?
A special technique with a D-level difficulty!
Grandma! Were you teaching him that technique without a pit?
He could injure himself if he fell!
Looks like another dangerous technique.
You can do it, Sanada!
Trust me.
What's wrong?
J-Just got some dust in my eye!
Start by doing a reversed swing.
Sanada, don't panic!
Remember to speed up the relax timing.
Sanada-senpai, Ganba!
Now! Grab it!
See? Isn't that dangerous?
He was this close to injuring himself!
Yes, exactly!
But the support crew caught him just fine...
That's true. embarrassingly enough,
my Jaeger still only has a 50% success rate.
But with a trustworthy support crew by my side,
I know I won't get injured.
It’s thanks to reliable teammates like them that I can attempt these difficult techniques.
From trust...
From trust comes courage.
It’s a universal truth we came to understand
thanks to this high bar and our amazing coach.
Oh! He did it!
Wow, impressive!
Looking great, Mister!
That was great, Sanada-kun!
Enough of this farce!
You keep saying how she's a wonderful coach,
all while having a support crew to back you up!
But in reality, it's Kotaro who got injured!
Mom!
All because she keeps teaching everyone
some weird tricks on this high bar!
Not at all! It happened because Kotaro-kun has an amazing talent for this!
Talent?! Don't make me laugh!
If he really had it, how could he get hurt?!
Yes, exactly!
Our children will keep getting hurt
until we take apart this bar!
Quite the opposite!
Without this high bar,
things will become even more dangerous.
How could things become any more dangerous than this?!
Gymnastics club second-year, Higashi Denji!
You'll have to watch me perform first!
Higashi-senpai is going to perform a double back somersault in a tight tuck.
Alright, you can do it, Higashi!
Trust us to catch you if things go south!
Aight!
It's a perfect giant swing...
Senpai! Now!
One...
Two...
You did it!
Successful landing!
Looking good, Higashi.
That was a spectacular double somersault.
You did it, Higashi-kun!
But what does a technique like this have to do with the high bar?
The successful execution of this technique
relies strongly on the height and rotational force.
But what do you think
will happen if those are insufficient?
I guess you wouldn’t be able to land on your feet
and would end up slammed to the ground.
Correct.
Kotaro-kun’s Moonsault is the same technique,
but with an added twist.
No wonder he got hurt, then!
A small child like him couldn’t possibly have the strength to soar as high as you.
Yet she made him do it!
You're wrong.
Indeed, Higashi-senpai is very strong.
But strength alone is not enough to do a double somersault.
What you also need is this high bar.
It's the bend of the bar.
Bend?
When performing techniques on a bar,
you play with the timings and use the bend of the bar to gain momentum.
Thank you, Coach Misaki!
As the coach said, the key to performing techniques successfully is the bar's bend.
Tell me, Kotaro-kun, could the high bar at school, where you got injured, bend like this?
No, it was completely hard.
But doesn’t Madam always tell you not to perform techniques on any bar other than this one?
Yes. And then she only allows me to do that when she's watching.
I see. So Kotaro got hurt because he went
against Madam’s orders and tried to perform it on an unbending iron bar?
What are you talking about? Whether it bends or not, he wouldn’t have gotten hurt
if she hadn’t taught him that technique in the first place!
Well, that's also true...
Kotaro won't play
on the high bar ever again!
For that, we need to see
this high bar removed first.
Huh?
Good! Good! Good! Good!
Good, keep moving back.
...Won't play on the high bar ever again!
For that, we need to see
this high bar removed first.
No way!
Stop!
K-Kotaro!
I won't give up on the high bar!
You can try to stop me,
I'll never give up on the high bar!
Kotaro...!
Even without the high bar here, I’ll do it wherever I can—on the bar at school or at the park!
I beg you, mom!
Don't break the bar!
I love the high bar!
When I'm doing a Moonsault,
I feel like I'm a bird, it's great!
It's the truth!
It was a misunderstanding!
If you love it that much, you can do back and front hip circles on the bar at school as much as you want!
Isn't it time to stop?
Spare the rod, spoil the child—
that's what you're doing.
But...
A ship in harbor is safe,
but that is not what ships are built for!
Overprotection does not equal love!
Right?
Dad...
I'm sorry, mom!
I’ll never try it at school again,
but please let this high bar stay!
Okay? Don't demolish it, please!
Kotaro...
Still...
You don't need to worry
about Kotaro-kun, madam.
Huh?
Madam Tadokoro really is a great coach!
With just a few of her tips, even I,
who’d never touched a high bar before, was able to swing freely on it!
Please watch this!
Looking good, Ueno!
Ueno-kun, you can do more than just swings!
A tucked backward somersault?!
D-Did he just...
Whew! I really did it!
Look!
Do you have the heart
to take the high bar away from them?
Everyone! Fujimaki-kun will perform next.
Huh?
That's right, Fujimaki. It's your turn.
Fujimaki, do your best!
Okay...
Fujimaki Shun, first-year in the gymnastics club, begins!
Good luck, Fujimaki-kun!
You can do it, Shun!
All right...
Kotaro-kun, you say you feel like a bird?
I'll also keep flying ever-higher, like a bird!
Not now!
Relaxing stage is too late!
Don't do it! If you let go now,
you'll fall onto the high bar!
Don't let go now!
Did he... Regroup in the air?
This boy, who couldn’t even do a full swing until recently,
managed to change his trajectory midair…
Something that requires an incredible sense of spatial awareness!
I keep soaring higher!
It's so high!
T-That's high!
Sh-Shun just...
Shun just...
became a bird!
It's like he has wings on his back!
No shit, that's high!
Finished!
Indeed, that was quite the spectacle!
He's good!
It's like watching the Olympics...
Did you see it, mom?
Shun flew like a bird!
Yeah...
Mom!
We've learned all these techniques
in just two weeks.
It's all thanks to Madam Tadokoro.
And we'd absolutely like
Madam to continue coaching us!
We are fully committed to safeguarding Kotaro-kun and the other children
to keep them out of the harm's way.
All we ask is that you don’t take the high bar apart!
Please!
What do you think, ladies and gentlemen?
Are you still intent on dismantling the bar?
Our Kotaro
was not very strong from birth.
We often had to rush him to the hospital
in the middle of the night.
However...
recently, I noticed something.
He had actually become much livelier
since he started coming here.
Madam.
Uh?
Too worried about my child I forgot about decency and said something rude.
Kotaro is a very considerate and good boy.
Oh... Right.
With the gymnastics club boys watching over him, he should be safe.
Gymnastics tutoring can be expensive.
But here, they get it for free!
Wouldn't it also be nice
if they let him watch them study?
I'm glad to see everyone here is so farsighted!
In that case, I don't suppose anyone objects to keeping this high bar
as a playground for the children and a training ground for these gentlemen?
No objections!
We did it!
Yes, we saved it!
Mom!
I'm so glad!
Isn't that great, Madam?
Thank you, boys...
So... Why did they call us here again?
Beats me...
Now, if I may have a minute of silence
from everyone attending...
To conclude our performance,
I, Uchida Minoru,
will perform Markelov to celebrate the survival of the high bar.
Fujimaki-kun, keep this for me.
Oh... Sure!
Now!
Markelov...
The technique for the strong
that allows you to flap your wings and soar.
I did it...
What do you think, Reiko-sama?
Did you like it?
Uchida-kun, that wasn't a Markelov.
Wha...
What you just did was a basic overhead landing.
And in Markelov, you're supposed to twist back and grabs the bar.
Markelov
Marke...
Basic
landing
Madam!
That's because a Markelov is not your level yet.
You'd need at least a month of training for it.
Not my... level?
Oh no, it was quite a
spectacular overhead landing.
Ugh... So embarrassing!
This was more like "Markeloaf!"
Well, if only you knew how glad I am
that you boys managed to save the bar.
This performance was a really great idea.
Oh, no, it was all his idea.
As the part of the Operation Ultra G.
10th out of 16 schools... No,
6th!
Yes, they'll be 6th or higher.
To that end, I would like to ask for the principal's assistance.
Yes, I appreciate it.
That is all.
Eri.
You know, Grandma...
Though I don't remember father's face clearly,
there's one thing about him I do remember.
The dad's dream.
Raise a gold medalist with that high bar.
Yes. Perhaps, that dream will finally come true.
You're thinking about him?
I knew you'd notice that kid's gift too.
We're rivals, you know.
You think we two can be rivals?
Yes. Let’s make it a duel to see who can raise a gold medalist first.
Oh? That sounds exciting.
And I don't intend to lose!
Okay! That's all for today's practice.
Madam, we're going home today, but we count on you to teach us many more various techniques.
Sure!
Hm. Are you sure you can afford to be that easygoing?
At this rate, the men's gymnastics club will be disbanded.
Huh?
Disbanded?
Yes. You need to place in the top six at the next tournament to avoid disbandment.
It was decided at the recent board meeting.
Huh? Top six?
That's madness!
What were you ranked last time?
16th out of 16 schools!
Huh?! You were at the bottom?
Hey, hey, hey! Winning the gold medal
is no longer the most pressing matter for you!
If the men's gymnastics club is disbanded,
what are you going to do next?
They say you need to place in the top six,
but that sounds like a tall order for you guys!
What'll you do, Ganbarist Shun?!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Th-That's quite an impressive list. Did you really change schools that many times?
Yeah. I'm a wandering transfer girl
If I can't even do this,
I'll be at a loss during the class.
I'll probably feel embarrassed.
Pathetic, even.
No, it's completely hopeless for me, it seems...
Next Gamba: Transfer Student!
Doing a Back Hip Circle in a Sailor Uniform!
The highlight of the high bar is the special techniques.
Straight Cosmic, Ginger, Markelov, Kovacs, Gaylord, and so on!
Their value is determined by height, stability, and scale.
If you execute them in succession,
you can hope for even more points!