The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Stop!
Dammit...
You look down on others,
you berate them just 'cause...
Are you saying we can't have dreams?!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Captain!
Remember that Safety Comes First Here
Episode
Captain!
Remember that Safety Comes First Here
All right! Uchida raises his hand!
The triple somersault
is still out of your reach!
The sheer amount of rotational force required
makes it extremely dangerous!
Oh man, so I thought...
I-I'm just asking out of curiosity!
Anyone would have chills
when making the first step into the unknown.
Even though I proudly boast
about being the vault specialist,
I still feel scared and isolated
every time I start my run-up.
But I must...
Let's go!
Don't risk your whole career, Minoru!
He runs with such drive!
Stop!
That's not the gymnastics I taught you!
I can't lose!
If I lose, everything I said was a lie!
Uchida!
Minoru!
It wasn't a lie!
A triple somersault?!
Are you insane?!
Minoru!
Turn!
Coach Andrianov was right...
I don't have the ability
to do a triple somersault yet...
It's still to early for me...
If that's the best you got,
that guy Fujimaki must be nothing special either.
Damn it...
I-It was a triple somersault!
C-C-Can you believe it?!
We saw a triple somersault on the vault
at the Junior Individual Championships!
U-Uchida-senpai...
Fujimaki...
I-It was incredible.
I got my first glimpse
into the world of triple somersaults!
I really thought I would die there...
Senpai!
C-Coach Andrianov?
He looks...
Angry.
C-Coach...
Thank god you're safe...
Don't do it ever again, Minoru!
Challenging yourself and being reckless
aren’t the same thing!
There's no courage or anything to it!
I’d never want to see my own trainee use gymnastics to destroy himself!
Don't you ever forget that!
Coach...
I was so scared...
I was scared...
I was scared to death!
But I...
I've learned to love gymnastics even more!
Minoru...
Coach...
You dumbass!
What was that about loving gymnastics?!
H-Hey! Stop it! I can't breathe!
You could think about us for once!
Uchida-senpai, I also learned
to love gymnastics even more from this!
On his second run, Heisei's Uchida executed
a forward flip, and a double tucked-up somersault!
And upon landing, his teammates
showered him in cheers!
Uchida-senpai, it was amazing!
Right...
And, um... I'm sorry.
I dropped your glasses.
I-I was deeply moved, believe me!
I'm sorry, your glasses...
H-He's angry!
I-I'm sorry, I...
I...!
Forget it, Fujimaki.
I've got another pair in the locker room.
Minoru! You never hugged me back!
W-Well, I thought you were really angry
back then, so I was feeling numb.
That was scary... Seriously!
Whoa! And Uchida's score is out! It's 9.5!
Such a shame he botched the landing...
Yes. However,
He was only able to turn at the last moment because his center of rotation was in his chest.
I think this athlete will only continue to grow.
Hm...
The first vault scored 9.4, the second—9.5.
Which means Uchida's total score is 9.45!
Points don't matter!
You're amazing, Heisei boys!
It was much better
than Nishihori's performances!
Why's that?
We're the ones who won every event so far!
Pay no mind to it.
We have our own performances to tend to.
O-Okay...
I’ll dominate the parallel bars and seal their fate with it!
At the Junior Individual Championships, the event shifts to the parallel bars,
where Oike from Nishihori Club begins his routine!
That was great!
You deserved to win this!
You're the best, Heisei!
Damn it! What did Heisei do to deserve this?
What's so great about that triple somersault?!
We, the Lee Corps,
are infinitely more talented!
What the...?
No way!
Ah! Wh-What are we seeing?
An E-class technique, Belle!
Ah! H-He fell!
Nishihori gymnast Oike failed his Belle!
A costly fall! That means
a 0.5-point deduction from his score!
Oike rises to his feet and grabs the bar
once again to resume his routine...
Wh-What's going on?!
Nishihori Club's Coach Lee pulls Oike
away from the bars!
What?
What happened?
You ignored my instructions, tried a Belle without permission, and ended up falling.
I won't let you embarrass me
any further than this!
C-Coach...
Th-That's harsh...
Coach Lee...
Get out of my sight!
Let him finish it!
Just because he failed once,
doesn't mean he has to quit halfway!
Do you think he is your property?!
You got any problem with that?
Why not let him finish his routine?
Are you trying to pick on
my methods, Andrianov?
Belle is a difficult technique.
Gymnasts sometimes fail it and fall!
You must allow them to challenge themselves!
Gymnastics must be more fun that that!
If you let him finish,
he would still have a score in the 9s!
Let him do it!
If you make him quit now,
he'll lose all confidence...
Fine by me!
With that attitude,
I don't need him on the team anyway.
Coach Lee...
So that's what you do...
That's what you do to ruin good gymnasts?!
Coach...
"I ruin good gymnasts?"
What do you think you are
to say that, Andrianov?!
"Fun gymnastics?"
What a farce!
Did you have even one athlete who outperformed mine in today's tournament?
How am I wrong, then?
What is the fault with my coaching?
Point it out for me on the scoreboard.
What do you think?
Are you fine with just quitting halfway?
I beg your forgiveness, Coach Lee!
I’ll never act without permission again!
But please... Don't give up on me!
Hmm. That's your answer. The gymnast himself
knows best who among us is right.
He knows who is capable
of leading others to the world scene.
You may have been a top-class gymnast,
but you're a third-rate coach at best.
Maybe all that alcohol went to your head
and clouded your sense of balance?
Coach...
Because Oike withdrew from competition,
he was only scored 4.0.
Onuma-san, doesn't that mean the Nishihori Club,
having swept every event so far,
is giving other gymnasts a chance at gold?
This opens up a lot of possibilities
for Kamura and Kobayakawa.
And with that, Kamura
begins his performance!
Hey, Kobayakawa also reduced
his routine's difficulty and is playing it safe.
Yeah.
They no longer have to risk.
Now that it came to this,
it could only be either Kobayakawa or Kamura.
Captain!
Hm?
It fell right into your lap!
We can finally strike back at them now!
Huh?
Them, them!
We can show them their place!
You gotta win this one!
You'll have a clear shot at it
as long as you don't slip up.
Don't slip up?
Lower the difficulty and don't slip up!
No-mistake guts!
No-mistake spirit!
Make no mistakes for no-mistake!
At this rate, we'll disappoint Coach Andrianov!
You repeating that doesn't change anything.
I never intended to make any mistakes
in my performance anyway!
Attaway!
Make no mistakes...
And win!
All right! Let's cheer him on
with our No Mistakes song!
Yeah!
Ready...
You can't do that!
Why?
The principal insisted that we don't sing any silly tunes today.
Tsk. I already thought of good lyrics...
And dance.
Uh...
Captain!
Ganba!
Captain, remember the fun gymnastics!
Fun gymnastics?
Fun
Gymnastics
Yuichi!
I-I'm fine.
But I don't think I'll ever be able
to perform Morisue...
Yuichi, don't jump to conclusions like that.
Of course, Morisue may be
an E-class technique.
It requires you to execute a perfect
double somersault right between the two bars.
The slightest deviation will result in a failure.
I guess it’s not feasible at my current level yet...
As long as you keep challenging yourself,
you'll be able to do it someday.
What matters is whether or not
you want to do it yourself.
Whether or not I want to do it myself?
Gymnastics is a fight against yourself.
It's easy to give up,
but there's nothing beyond that.
Fun
Gymnastics
Fun gymnastics?
Fun
Gymnastics
Coach Andrianov...
I might not make it in time
for the upcoming tournament,
but I’ll definitely nail the Morisue someday!
Da!
Fun
Gymnastics
That's the spirit, Yuichi.
Keep challenging yourself!
Fun
Gymnastics
Fun gymnastics?!
He can't afford mistakes right now!
Make no mistakes and win!
Um... But can't you have fun
while not making any mistakes?
Ow! Please!
They wanna win by not slipping up.
They're all aiming for an easy win?
All thanks to some cretin embarrassing us
with his mess of a performance!
Winning by making no mistakes?
But my current composition
won't score more than Kobayakawa's.
No mistakes! No mistakes!
Win with no mistakes!
They're making fools of themselves again...
Still, even if I can't win...
Next up, gauging the width of the parallel bars,
is Shindo from Heisei team!
What kind of performance will he put on?
Now, he finally starts his routine!
Shindo-kun, do it with confidence!
Good!
Take a safe starting point!
Catch the bar!
Prop up with your hands!
Don't let go of the bar!
Yes, grab it!
Come to think of it, this is the first time we're seeing Captain perform!
He was training in secret.
Just like you.
Except he didn't get cold feet.
How cruel...
Captain, you can do better than that!
You gotta relax!
Now go!
Go, go!
Shindo-kun, do your best!
Orikasa...
Did you enter on the parallel bars, Shindo-kun?
There's no one else in Heisei
doing parallel bars, right?
That's why I decided to set a precedent.
Where I lead, others will follow...
I wish I could say that, but truth is,
I’m just afraid of the shame
if I perform in the same event as my underclassmen and lose.
After all, unlike me,
those guys are actually gifted.
Spectacular! He carefully picks the reliable techniques and nails them one by one!
This performance is not like Heisei...
There's no ambition.
Twist!
No mistakes!
Safety!
Shindo-kun!
I'm fine.
What you just tried to do...
Was it Morisue?
Yeah. I thought I needed to learn
at least one major technique.
But I just don't seem
to be able to catch the bar.
Even if I pull it off here,
I'll feel shy at the tournament and...
Absolutely not!
That's just you convincing yourself!
Huh?
You don't even realize it since you're so kind,
but I do understand!
Actually, you're also incredibly gifted!
That's good!
Now twist!
No mistakes!
Andrianov, what was
that about challenging yourself?
Because of his sloppy execution,
the best he can do is mediocre safe techniques.
Now!
It's time for Morisue,
my trademark, my major technique!
No mistakes! No mistakes!
All right! The next twist
will be the finishing one!
O-Orikasa!
I know you can do it, Shindo-kun! Confidence
is not something you can build up on your own!
Yes! The last twist!
And finish!
No mistakes!
M-Morisue!
Wh-What?!
What for?!
Looks scary!
Why did he have to...
No... Not enough!
You're too low!
Stupid Captain!
No longer safe!
It's over!
Captain!
Hey, so you decided
not to play safe after all, Shindo?
I understand how you feel,
but do you have the confidence
for a high-level technique like Morisue?
Ah, whatever!
Now it's sink or swim, Ganbarist Yuichi!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Lee Corps...
Fujimaki, calm down!
Here goes nothing.
I will definitely win.
Fujimaki-kun!
Why is Sagara-san here?
Next Ganba: Clash!
A Fiery Battle on the High Bar.
Today I wanted to show you
a small underhand swing.
From this underhand position
over the bar I had shown you last time...
I swing back, climb up, then fall forward again.
And then rise again.
That was underhand swing.