The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
Morisue-san won the gold medal on the high bar at the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics.
This is the story of our young heroes
rising to become the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal!
Their goal is the last Olympics of the 20th century!
Sydney '2000
Ganba!
It's Sagara Mariko-kun.
Thanks for having me!
Can you teach me how to do
the back hip circle?
What are we gonna do now?
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
No Way!
Captain Quits the Club
So cool that you can even do that!
It's called a Planche...
Higashi-senpai, you have
such outstanding muscles!
Let me show you something even more amazing, then...
If I shift my weight forward from this position...
Awesome! You're like a drinking bird toy!
When did you learn this move?
Then finally, I do this...
I move into the handstand position!
Oh, come on, Higashi-senpai!
Can't you complete this new move without farting?
Wh-Who knows!
This is hopeless...
Captain!
Don't you also have some special move
like that of Higashi-senpai?
No, I'm not really able to perform strength techniques like that.
I wish I had that kind of talent too, but alas.
Why are you lounging here?
Coach Misaki?
Looks like everyone is doing their best.
Yeah...
The other boys are trying out some new techniques.
I wonder what you'll have to show.
Oh, seems like it's a secret?
Uh? No, not really.
Well, whatever.
I'm looking forward to this tournament.
So? Are those kids training like they should be?
Yes. They said they were inspired by some mysterious, great coach.
She's on a whole other level.
Looks like I accidentally made a few enemies in the world.
Still, this data you gave me
turned out pretty useful.
You've done your research well.
You must've observed them closely.
I just believe in fair competition.
If I left it as is, I'd have won for sure.
What a truly honest child you are.
The only thing I'm concerned about...
Captain, right?
He's a serious boy with a strong sense of responsibility.
But...
He has his weak side too...
Are you worried that he might face difficulties?
Isn't there something we could do?
For now, I suppose we can only wait and see.
Fujimaki-kun! You've completely mastered the forward handspring jump already!
N-Not really!
I'm still learning.
Precisely! You don't know a thing yet.
Let the true specialist
show you what the vault
is all about.
S-So high!
And he flies for so long!
So far too!
Do you understand where that difference came from?
Let me tell you, then.
The difference in the rhythm from the moment when you kick the springboard until you land.
In other words, you do it
with a "ton-ton-ton" rhythm.
Right...
But I'm jumping with the rhythm of "to-to-ton!"
In other words, I emphasize one part of it.
That allows you to increase height and distance
without sacrificing the momentum.
I see! That's what your
mental training was all about!
Sort of.
Your new technique is double somersault, right?
Can you perform it already?
New technique is double somersault?!
Can you do it, Uchida-senpai?
S-Sort of...
Hey! Everyone!
Uchida'll do his new double somersault now!
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Huh? Double somersault?
Uchida-kun?
New technique? No way!
Uchida's new technique!
Hey, wait a minute...
I still can't do it with full confidence...
Shindo-kun.
Yes?
Please give Uchida-kun some advice,
he seems too stiff right now.
R-Right...
U-Uchida...
Yes?!
Wh-What should I say?
He's never done the double somersault before...
Uchida-kun, be confident!
Reiko-senpai?
Your entrance rhythm is already perfect,
so I'm sure you can do it.
Just give it a try and don't worry about failing.
You think so?!
All right...
Captain, please assist me!
Right...
How am I supposed to assist him
with a double somersault?
I'll do it for you.
Coach Misaki?
He's never done it before, did he?
P-Please do it.
I'm starting!
I did it!
It feels like a dream!
Great! Congratulations, Uchida-senpai!
He really pulled it...
I-It's nothing! So? Did you like it?
Yeah, it's nothing for me! Yay! I did it!
Uchida has his double somersault.
Higashi and Sanada
are also trying out new techniques.
Meanwhile, I...
Can't even give assistance when it's needed.
Can't even give advice.
What kind of captain am I
if all I do is drag them down?
Congratulations on completing your new technique, Uchida-senpai!
Thanks.
You're so clumsy.
Hey, let's put the mat back in place. Hold it there.
There's an opening now.
Someone might get hurt.
Sorry!
No can do. It's too heavy!
Everyone is learning new techniques to get higher scores. And all I can do is just stand and watch?
Dammit... At this rate...
At this rate, I'll be just a dead weight!
Ah, Captain, give us just a moment!
We'll put the mat back now.
Huh?
Damn it all!
Captain!
This is bad! He doesn't know!
Sagara-san, hurry up!
I can't!
A taxi will come soon.
Thank you. I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Don't mention it. It's my fault.
My careless remarks made you question your position as captain,
and then I also assisted Uchida-kun myself.
I-It's not that.
You're not at fault for anything.
As for my position as a captain...
Shindo-kun...
It's my own fault.
I'm the one who's useless
and can't do anything for the team.
Don't blame yourself.
It was my responsibility as a coach to...
Please stop!
I can return home on my own.
Just leave me alone, please.
Shindo-kun...
The hell you want from me?
Can't a man practice where he wants?!
Shut up! You're in my way!
Go train somewhere else!
Like hell! I can practice wherever I want!
When did I ask for your permission?
You're on a mat that's in the middle of my run-up path, so you're in my way!
You can practice this anywhere!
Why won't you get out of my way?
What was that?!
Wh-Why are you two even arguing about it?
Please stop!
Exactly! Quit arguing and let's get going
to Madam already.
You're only thinking about your own practice,
but I need to practice on the high bar too!
I don't care!
If you need it, just go there by yourself!
Damn right!
Don't be stupid!
How can I perform Jaeger without assistance?
What was that?
The hell?
What?!
Now, now, let's not get so impatient.
We can practice in turns.
We don't need you calming us down!
I'm the one who can't practice here!
Who do you think you are?!
If there's no agreement in the team,
nobody can train.
With Captain on leave,
there's no one to set things right.
Captain!
Ah, Captain!
Please tell them to see the reason!
These guys get all worked up for no reason.
Sorry, I...
Club resignation notice
I'm quitting the club from today on.
That's all.
You and your crappy jokes again!
By the way, what's the plan for the tournament?
My leg needs two months to recover.
W-Wait, Captain!
We have to finish it in the top six! Do you want us to just resign ourselves to the club's disbandment?
That's awfully selfish!
Even though I've been working so hard
to polish my new special move!
Oh, shut up!
Your move is as special as the dirt on the roadside! It's just sloppy.
What was that?!
Ugh! You're all so noisy!
First of all... What... What...
What the hell should we do now?!
S-Start by letting us go!
Man, you almost killed us!
Damn right!
Without Captain, no matter how hard we try,
we can't hope to finish in the top six!
The club is as good as disbanded already.
I'll go find myself a less tiresome one, then.
S-Sanada-senpai, please wait a moment.
Higashi-senpai, please do something!
I'll be fine in any club where they let me train my muscles.
H-How can you say that?
Fujimaki, you should also find yourself something better to do.
Uchida-senpai!
It's all my fault...
It's because I'm so clumsy...
Because I'm so clumsy,
captain was injured!
It wasn't you fault!
I know it is!
If only I didn't have to transfer schools this year...!
Because of constant transfers,
I never had a chance to make any friends.
And just as I thought that I finally met some wonderful people that I'll make memories with...!
But instead... Instead—this...
I've ended up causing discord
with my clumsiness!
No need to cry.
Even if Captain decides to quit,
that doesn't mean the club is disbanded.
I won't let everyone drift apart!
I will... I'll think of something!
Fujimaki-kun...
Fujimaki?
Captain, please don't say that you quit the club.
Please... Please teach me gymnastics!
I've already submitted my notice.
I'm no longer your captain.
I will be the captain at the upcoming tournament!
So please tell me everything
about the captain's role!
Captain...
What are you hoping to achieve in just a month?!
Now you understand, so go home.
It can't be true.
Wasn't it you...
When I said I want to win a gold medal,
you didn't laugh, but instead
told me that if my dreams are big,
I have to work hard...
Didn't you tell me to dream big?!
Captain! I'm begging you, don't quit!
Give it a rest already!
I'm not your captain anymore!
Go home!
Do you even know how I feel right now?
Go home, end of story!
Fujimaki!
Now, now, boys shouldn't be bawling their eyes out like that.
You'll end up with salty cocoa!
Don't you worry!
It'll all be back to normal soon.
Really?
Yeah. It'll either be back to normal,
or not be at all.
Huh?
I'm talking about you.
Shun, I've got something nice for you.
A protector?
My son's keepsake.
From Coach Misaki's father?
Oh? There's a pencil inside.
It's a dream protector.
Dream protector?
Yeah. At the peak of his career,
my son devised these myself.
C-Can I really have something so precious to you?
Sure.
Listen. With your hard work,
you will bring everyone back.
But you can't lose your spirits, all right?
I'll give this protector to someone
who can inherit my high bar.
That way, I'll be supporting him during his Olympic performance as well.
I'm sure you'd be happy
to let him have your protector, Seiji.
The judo club sounds good too,
but I think it's boring.
How about all three of us
join the tennis club?
I hear it's full of cute babes.
Sounds like something you'd think.
What's wrong with it?
Ah, found you!
What are you guys doing up here?
Hey, Mari-chan.
Do you need something?
I've been searching everywhere! Jeez...
Yes, it's this.
What's that?
Presents for us?
Oh! Dat does look cute!
I stayed up all night making those for you.
I'll be waiting at Madam's house. Bye!
What?
Madam's house?
Waiting?
Huh?
Ultra Ganba
Heisei Middle School
Shindo-kun!
Orikasa?
Is it true you quit the gymnastics club?
Yeah, it is.
But why? Why did you quit?
I have my reasons.
What's it to you, anyway?
That's awfully irresponsible.
What about everyone else?
Everyone worked hard for the club,
but you abandoned them and ran away.
Isn't that cowardly?
Sorry if it is!
I'm different from you.
I'm no candidate for the Olympic team.
I don't have the strength
to pull my juniors up like you.
I can't even assist them.
I'm simply not qualified to be a captain.
Of course, a star player like you could never understand how someone useless like me feels...
O-Orikasa?
Senpai!
So you came back after all!
Whoa there.
Don't get any wrong ideas.
We had some time to kill,
so we only came to poke fun at you.
Excuse me!
What's there to make fun of?!
Whatever happened
to your own special techniques?
There's no point practicing
if Captain can't perform.
Why not put out Shun instead of the captain?
Huh?!
You mean, Fujimaki?
Th-That's a good one!
Don't make me laugh!
Instead of putting Fujimaki out there and making fools of ourselves, better just sit out the tournament.
Shun, how about you put on that protector
and show them your swings?
Uh? Sure!
Everyone worked hard for the club,
but you're abandoning them?!
Fujimaki-kun, Ganba!
How do you like that protector?
Yeah, it's great!
If I do my very best,
I'm sure it'll all work out somehow!
I'm sure everyone will come back!
If I keep working hard
with this dream protector on, I'm sure...
everything will be fine!
F-Fujimaki!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
There's no way it's true!
I believe in you.
Fujimaki-kun will be okay.
Wake up, Fujimaki-kun.
Huh?
Wake up.
Next Gamba:
Special Training! Hard Work Always Pays Off!
With vault, the moment you handspring is the key.
The push and thrust for 0.0 seconds at this moment
will greatly affect your subsequent move.
Do you understand? Once you start running in this event, you cannot stop halfway.
Moreover, it will be decided in a fraction of second, so have full resolve!