The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
I'm sure we'll meet again!
I'll keep doing my best forever!
It's a promise!
Fujimaki-kun...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Training Camp!
Heisei is on a Whole Different Level
I'll be brief. Fujimaki-kun,
are you well and doing your best?
It's been a week since we moved here,
and I've finally gotten my things in order.
Now we just have to wait for the new semester to start
How is the gymnastics club doing?
I'm sure everyone is practicing enthusiastically
for the next tournament.
Please tell them I wish you all good luck.
It's summer!
It's the sea!
And the sun!
Picking up girls...
Tanning!
Running a race to the coast!
Here I go!
Hold up, you!
No, you wait!
What do you think you're doing?
Captain! Why not, it's only for a couple of hours!
We don't get to the sea all that often!
We didn't come here to swim in the sea!
What are you guys thinking?
Hey, girls!
Where did you guys come from?
Sanada!
Yeah, yeah...
I'll be brief. Sagara-san,
we are now at the seaside town of Kujukuri.
As for how that happened...
The All-Japan Junior Advanced Training Camp?
For us?
The gymnastics association extended an invitation to us.
They said they'd like you,
the men's club, to come.
Why?
Do you really think we can go?
Your performance at the recent tournament received high praise.
Oh, I see!
We won gold in each individual event.
When you put it that way, it makes perfect sense.
Yes. Getting invited to junior advanced training camp is a big honor.
Yes, exactly!
Of course, Orikasa and others from the women's club will also be there.
You must absolutely go too.
Reiko-sama too?
Um... Where is it?
Kujukuri Beach.
Kujukuri?
I like that idea!
Kujukuri...
Kujukuri!
Well then, what would your answer be?
Absolutely yes!
I see...
Man... We came here for the advanced training camp, yet you are still so carefree!
You guys... I swear!
It's just you being too tense about it.
Oh man...
We don't go the sea all that often.
It's a training camp!
Sure, sure.
Um, are you guys going to the advanced training camp too?
Uh? Yes, we are. What about you?
Oh man, that's great!
Actually, I was also invited to that training camp,
but I came here on my own and got lost.
Interesting. Which middle school are you from?
Right... My name is Saito Sakae and I am a first-year at Kitahashi Middle School in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido? Wow, that's quite a journey.
Do you mind if I follow you?
Not at all.
Thank god! Thanks for having me!
Sure!
Saito-kun, did you perhaps happen
to win some tournament in Hokkaido?
Oh, no, of course not, sir. As a matter of fact, I've never been to any competitions before.
Wha?
You've never been to a competition?
In my middle school, I was the only member of the gymnastics team.
Is that why you they invited you to the junior training camp?
Yes, that sounds about right, sir.
By the way, what is "junior?"
What they call "junior"
are students up to high school age who belong to gymnastics schools or other such organizations.
Oh...
This training camp is where the top junior elites have come together.
Top junior elites?
We belong to no such school...
Yet we were invited...
Which means...
We're the top elite!
I see...
I bet they invited you because they mistook you for someone else.
Is that so?
Absolutely!
Holy!
They even have a pool there!
Such high ceiling!
It's more of a resort hotel
than a training camp!
Hey, let's visit that pool right away!
Aye-aye! I was in my trunks all this time!
Hey! Not here!
Are you the students of Heisei Middle School?
Y-Yes...
I've heard a lot about you guys.
I'm Sotoyama, the All-Japan
Junior Team head coach.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for having us!
Practice starts in 30 minutes at the gymnasium upstairs. Don’t be late.
What's that? We've just arrived...
He could at least let us catch our breath.
Well, if you hadn’t lingered so long at the beach, we would’ve arrived sooner.
What was that?!
N-No, it's nothing.
Wow! Are we practicing here?
Yeah. The equipment they have is amazing.
Hey, there's even a pit! A pit!
It's my first time seeing one!
Same here!
Hey, here you are, guys.
I've been waiting.
Ah, it's an honor, Kobayakawa-san.
Ah! Kobayakawa-san, the All-Japan Champion!
That last tournament was great. This time, let's do our best together at the training camp.
Aye! The feeling's mutual!
Oh? Who's that over there?
Ah! Kamura-kun!
'Sup!
Let's do our best, Kamura-kun!
As fellow medalists, right?
Fools! Don’t lump me in with the likes of you!
Behold! Straight-arm, straight-body press handstand!
Looking good, Higashi!
Not bad indeed!
That's an amazing technique!
This technique won me gold!
Look!
Wow!
I have one too!
Gold for the vault!
Wow!
Well, it's nothing special really,
but I have silver on the high bar.
Wow!
I'm so jealous!
H-Higashi-senpai, look!
What is it?
What?!
I-Is that...
Press handstand on the rings
when balancing is even more difficult!
That guy's quite something, ain't he?
Wh-What are these guys?
Is this...
Is this the junior level?
Pft. Did you finally realize what level you're at?
Amazing!
In here, the young people
who will become Olympic athletes one day.
Olympic?
That's right. You guys should take a good look
at the juniors' top class techniques.
Scared shitless, as expected.
Wow!
That's awesome, sir!
Indeed...
We're probably...
On a different level from them.
Everyone here is such a strong athlete!
They're all top-class juniors
from all over the country.
It's nothing like the district tournament level!
It really is amazing.
Even Reiko-senpai is fighting fiercely to outdo her rivals.
All right...
Hey guys!
Huh?
Let's jump into action
and practice fiercely too!
Fujimaki, what's wrong with you?
If you just look around, you'll understand.
Exactly! What do you think we can do here?
Huh? But we're wasting such an opportunity!
Look—we're surrounded by wonderful athletes!
Yes! Fujimaki-kun, I think so too.
Just watching those guys practice
is getting me excited and motivated!
I know, right?
Okay, I'll get to it then. Bye.
Yeah.
Good luck, Saito-kun!
How can one feel excited from watching those guys practice? What a simpleton.
It's because he doesn't know how much his own level is different from theirs.
I bet his own level is even lower than ours!
You wanna do a back hip circle on that?
Hey, kid, maybe you should start with a playground swing?
Do you think he's ever jumped off one?
Of course he did!
But he messed up and scraped his knee.
That's what I'm saying!
Rookie mistake. Typical.
Don't you hate it when people don't understand their own position?
Well, him being here saves us, actually.
You shouldn't talk like that.
We don't even know Saito-kun's level.
Oh, he's not bad.
Who is that?
So what's so special about it?
Ganba, Saito-kun!
What?!
Awesome! What was this move he just did?
Dunno.
I've never seen it before.
C-Could it be...!
It was a Kovacs.
Kovacs?
No way!
Was it Kovacs?
It really was!
So that was Kovacs?
The Ultra E technique!
Three times!
Triple somersault!
Seriously?!
He just pulls off a high-difficulty
Kovacs out of nowhere?
And then also chose a triple somersault
as his finishing move!
That was quite something, you know.
Not at all...
Crap!
This leaves us, the new...
Lowest level here!
Oops, I got so excited
the skin peeled off my fingers.
Saito-kun! You can perform a Kovacs?
What's a Kovacs?
Huh?
Did you like that trick that much?
You did it without knowing?!
Knowing what?
I just did what my coach taught me.
What a country yokel!
I hate his guts when he talks like that!
But it felt good.
Fujimaki-kun, you should try it too.
Sure!
We don't need anyone teaching us!
We'll just do it!
Yeah!
Hey, Higashi...
Captain, I need your help! I'm also going to do a press handstand on rings!
Higashi-senpai!
They're shaking! Shaking!
Higashi...
Why?! Why the hell?!
That cretin!
No!
I hear he's also from Heisei.
They're probably all on the same level.
Shit!
Crap! Wait a minute!
Everyone is watching!
Maybe Reiko-sama too?
Well, gentlemen, that's a fine piece of equipment you've got here.
Jesus, why is everyone in my team so helpless?
If it came to this, it falls to me, the Prince of Floor to show you the true spirit of Heisei.
Yes! You can do it, Sanada-senpai!
Yeah!
So high!
Great! You nailed it!
You're up. You gonna do it or what?
Oh no, I'll pass for now.
What's wrong, Sanada-senpai?
What about the pride of the Prince of Floor?
Fujimaki!
Yes?
We'll start with a warmup. You're helping!
Huh?
What should I do, Captain?
Ah, well, we could start with a warmup too.
There, in the corner.
Out of anyone's way.
What a bummer.
We're light years behind them.
Do you think they called us here by mistake or something?
But then there's also that kid with a Kovacs.
What can I show that'd be anywhere near that advanced?
If I remember correctly,
Kovacs is an E-difficulty technique.
That's right.
It's the highest level.
There's nothing beyond that.
Ah! I'm so miserable compared to that!
Let's go home, Captain!
We’re no match for guys
so much more advanced!
How can we ever learn anything here?
Whoa there, you have no reason to be that low-spirited.
But Captain...!
Well, I guess you’re right.
We do stand out like black sheep here.
Not just like black sheep—
like miserable sheared ones!
What will I do with you?
By the way, what is Shun doing?
Oh?
What was that amazing technique just now?
Excuse me, I gotta go.
What do you do to fly so high?
It's good to be as thoughtless as him.
He's no sense of pride, that's all.
Probably no brain either!
Guys! Everyone here is even more amazinger than I thought!
"More amazinger?"
Do you have an F in Japanese too?
Why can't you understand?
Let's practice together with everyone!
Don't make me laugh, Fujimaki!
They're on a whole different level from us!
Huh? But still...
No "Buts!"
But still...
Well now, calm down, you guys.
Fine by me.
I'll practice by myself, then.
Saito-kun! Teach me to do
that triple somersault!
"Teach me!"
What a moron.
For real! Let him embarrass himself!
Hey, look at that.
Feels like they have zero motivation.
I wonder why they even came
to this training camp.
It seems they gave a "unique" performance
at a district tournament, that's all.
Kamura-kun, you're from that area too, right?
Did that district’s level
really drop so low this time?
Dammit. These pathetic fools again...
Really...
Now, Fujimaki-kun!
Tuck in to keep your body compact!
Hey, Fujimaki-kun, are you okay?
I guess the double one is still my limit.
How did you learn to turn three times?
Fujimaki, are you really practicing the triple somersault?
Yes!
Jeez. That's where your ignorance gets you.
Are you stupid?
There's no way you can do it, you dunce.
Exactly! You’ll only embarrass yourself by biting off more than you can chew!
Yeah, he's right!
Biting off more than I can chew?
But we're at the training camp!
We came here to practice!
Excuse me, are you talking back to your senpai?
Acting so high and mighty!
But I'm not really...
Hey, cut it off, guys.
Oh? I wonder what's that?
Something on the ceiling.
Footprints?
It's Morisue's footprints.
Is it... That Morisue?
He was my peer who won gold on the high bar at the Los Angeles Olympics.
Won gold?
Huh? There's a signature next to the footprints.
Well, that's just his shtick.
So he was quite a joker, huh?
When he first tried the triple somersault here
while he still was an active athlete,
the ceiling wasn't high enough,
so he touched it with his feet.
No way... That high?
Well, he was tall for a gymnast,
that's probably what allowed him to do it.
Since then, no one else has ever touched the ceiling with his legs.
That's why the gold medalists are amazing...
Their talent and ours are worlds apart.
Oh no, that's too high.
I can't quite reach it.
What now? Were you really trying to reach it?
You must be an idiot.
How could you ever hope to reach it?
Right...
Why are you laughing?
What’s wrong with pushing yourself to a higher level? Laughing at that is just wrong!
Fujimaki!
You brat!
Don't get cocky!
H-Hey, Fujimaki!
What's with that attitude?
What's with that guy?
He's been acting up since we came here.
We didn’t try enough to keep him in line!
Arrogant bastard!
We've gotta teach him a lesson once we're back!
Yeah! Damn right! When we get home, I'll take him for a ride!
Hey, guys...
I have to try it...
I have to try!
No way I give up right off the bat!
Fujimaki-kun...
Shun-kun?
Finally at the Junior Training Camp, you understand why your unmotivated seniors are unhappy with you.
You do understand it,
but what are you going to do about it?
What are you planning to do next,
Ganbarist Shun?
Reach it!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Hey, Fujimaki-kun.
Oh, he turned!
Cute...
You're at the same school as Reiko-san, right?
That was super amazing just now!
That bastard's really getting on my nerves!
S-Senpai...
Next Ganba: I'm Motivated!
Peeping, Ocean and Intense Practice!
We're continuing today with backward roll.
Don't we all bend our hands a bit when turning?
Hand strength is important in the roll.
Put your hands next to your ears
and make a quick backwards roll.
Then, while getting up,
press the floor with your hands to rise.