Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
Is that...
A simple...
360 in the air?
I finished!
Fini            shed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Oh No!
The Terrifying Vaulting Horse Experience
I can't!
Fujimaki-kun...
I-I'm gonna practice outside!
Outside?
What's with him?
All right...
I just can't...
I just can't forget what happened back then...
Really? You're going to practice vaulting out here?
Ah, you're the girl from the Olympic team...
You're a complete rookie, right?
Never seen a vaulting horse in your life?
Yes...
So that's why you decided to practice with those?
All right.
Go ahead, try to jump over me.
Huh?!
Gotta keep an eye on number 25.
With you, we've got the vaulting horse part in the bag.
Reiko-sama,
were you paying attention?
Huh? Where did Reiko-san go?
Uchida, sorry to bother you, but could you go and call Fujimaki-kun?
Why me?
His practice time's almost up. Please!
So? What's wrong?
Um...
I mean...
Once you're in the air,
just relax and think about landing.
Okay!
Now!
That was a good jump.
Huh?
You'll be fine. If you just do what you did now,
you'll be able to vault over the horse too.
Got it, thanks!
Wh-Why? Why is Reiko-sama
helping that no-hoper?
The performances start soon.
Do your best.
Y-Yes, I will!
Uchida-senpai, what's the matter?
We'd better return now!
How dare you!
Incredible...
He pushed with such strength.
Heisei, please start your performance.
Will you perform the first for us, Higashi?
Power!
Give me extra points
for these perfect muscles!
Tsk. Muscular Gorillaman.
Power is all he got... Maybe he should've joined the powerlifting club instead?
Okay, I'm going next.
That was awesome, Captain!
It's no big deal.
Humph. Hey, Rookie.
Yes?
We always save the true specialists for later.
You don't know a thing yet.
Okay...
The key points in horse vaulting are
pushing strength, timing, and body control.
Don't get ahead of yourself
just because you jumped well once!
In this tournament, I’m going to earn the highest score and dedicate my ultimate performance to her...
Reiko-sama...
Reiko-sama is looking at me!
I must do my best!
Oh, it's that number 25 again.
How many points will he get?
Watch Uchida's performance closely.
Got it.
Well, the team score is based on our top three scores,
so you can just do a simple jump
and not worry about it.
Got it. I'll do my best.
Reiko-sama...
This is for you...
She's here... She's here... She's here!
She's not watching at me!
In her line of sight...
Fujimaki?!
Why's that?!
X... X-ray.
X-ray?
That’s what this type of mistake is called because that’s how we look during X-ray scanning...
I didn't expect that from Uchida!
O-Oh no!
Hey, the guy who got X-rayed during the vaulting horse event scored a 0!
Seriously? What's gotten into him?
So everyone is hit or miss now, huh?
H-Hit or miss?!
Captain, didn't you say that 1.0 was the lowest possible score?
That's a participation point.
But if you failed to jump,
you don't even get that.
Oh?
Did you see it? He charged right into!
It's rude to laugh so much!
I'll never forgive you, Fujimaki
More importantly,
our team is in a tight spot now.
This makes Uchida's zero points
the worst result of the team.
Fujimaki-kun, this means you have to make that jump no matter what!
Huh? But didn't you say earlier
that I can just relax...
The situation has changed. Now this is important for the team score. Please!
Huh?!
Just run, push, spread your legs, and land.
Look, we had vaulting boxes in the grade school.
This is the same thing.
Vaulting boxes in grade school...
It's do or die!
So go there as a man!
No! I don't wanna die!
R-Really? You got crushed by a vaulting box in grade school?
Yeah, I’ve had a crippling fear of vaulting boxes ever since.
Tsk. That’s enough to spook you?
Just now, I felt like I could make that jump.
But after seeing Uchida-senpai slip-up like that, I'm scared again.
You bastard!
Now you put the blame on me?!
If it weren't for you,
I'd have vaulted just fine myself!
Oh really, Mr. zero points?
Don't worry, Fujimaki-kun
If anything, the vaulting box collapsing under you is proof of your talent.
You just made that up!
Listen, if you don't jump, you'll get zero points.
Zero points, you hear?
And scoring zero is downright humiliating.
You understand?
So you're that embarrassed of me?
Maybe you should've just died there...
Don't dramatize.
No humiliation is worth dying for.
Cut it out already, won't you...
Jump, Fujimaki!
For team's sake!
For team's sake?
It'll be fine.
Go for it!
I'll try!
I have to try!
You can do it!
With guts!
Another zero points for us.
It's hopeless.
Fujimaki, what I said earlier wasn't a lie.
It’s hard to believe just by looking,
but it was actually your extraordinary leg strength and the force of your push
that caused the vaulting box
to flip and crush you.
That true, Captain?
...Probably.
You can do it!
It's so high!
That's it! Push away from the horse with your both hands!
P-Push away?!
It's his shoulders!
H-He jumped...
Right above...
Finished!
H-He landed...
On his ass!
Fujimaki-kun...
Captain...
I vaulted it for the first time!
You did well, Fujimaki-kun.
Captain!
It's the birth of Vaulter Fujimaki!
Higashi-senpai, n-not the butt!
What a funny guy. Right, Reiko?
He has a gift.
Okay, they're announcing your points.
It was my first ever vault.
Of course they'll give me 1.0.
They'll give me...
3 and...
5?
3.5?
They recognized it as a proper vault.
Did it! I did it!
Look how happy he is over some 3.5 points!
Well, why shouldn't he be?
It's his first positive score.
Yahoo!
Ugh...
Um... So gymnastics is just the floor,
the vaulting horse, and the high bar?
When you reach the national junior level,
the pommel horse, rings, and parallel bars are added to it.
It’s the same six events as in the Olympics.
But that level is still light-years away for you!
Um... Is it okay for me to go home now,
without attending the award ceremony?
It seems, the other teams aren't finished yet.
At that level, no problem at all!
Well, it doesn’t take a genius to figure out that we’ll probably end up at the bottom this time.
Come on, let's go home.
Well, what matters is that I'm now on my way to winning an Olympic gold medal.
I never had a chance to thank that girl.
Whatever, we're at the same school, right?
Tsk. His nerve...
I will never forgive him for the humiliation I endured in front of Reiko-sama!
By the way, where's Sanada?
He said he needed to stop by the hospital, so he left earlier, on the bicycle.
Huh?
Bicycle?
Oh?
Sorry, guys, but being stuck with you and looking this lame just doesn’t suit me!
Well, everyone worked hard.
Let's call it enough for today.
Fujimaki-kun, you did well too.
Oh no...
So, you want the Olympic gold medal? For a big dream like that, better start working hard tomorrow.
Captain...
Take a bath and warm up your muscles.
Got it!
All right, tomorrow, I'm doing it!
I'll be at the gym at 6:30 tomorrow morning.
Uh?
For morning practice.
Don't be late.
O-Okay! I'll do my best!
Morning practice?
Thanks for taking care of me!
Celebrate while you can.
We don't have no morning practice in our club.
It’s just an excuse to let rookies like you
get a taste of the brutal reality of gymnastics.
Tomorrow morning, you’ll face hell on earth.
No more playing the "Mr. Nice Senpai" for you!
Finally here...
I had to leave 40 minutes earlier.
Every muscle in my body aches...
I can... hardly move.
I never had any idea
gymnastics was this hard...
But I won't... give up!
My gold medal... is waiting!
You're late.
Huh? But it's only 6:30.
No talking back to your senpai!
If you're told to be here at 6:30, it's common sense to arrive 15 minutes early and wait for the others!
I-I'm very sorry!
Then hurry up and get changed!
Yessir!
I'm getting the hang of it.
By the way, is that true you're planning on winning a gold medal at the Olympics?
Judging from your performance yesterday, pigs will fly before that happens! No chance!
Um... By the way, where's everyone else?
Are you even listening, you moron?!
Y-Yes!
As with anything else, the key to gymnastics is mastering the basics.
That's what I'll be drilling into you now!
Yessir!
First is front legs raise.
Get ready.
Front legs raise?
Ugh. Goddamn amateur.
This is the front legs raise!
Front legs raise
Oh! That's cool!
Is that what the front legs raise is?
Why are you still not in position?!
Yessir!
Hold it for 30 seconds.
Start!
Yessir!
What the hell is this lousy stance?!
Raise your legs higher!
Move your ass forward!
But you know,
I can't do it well on the first try...
Listen, Fujimaki...
I scored zero in yesterday's tournament.
And lemme tell ya, it hurt like hell.
As a good senpai, I’d never want to put you through the same ordeal.
Senpai! I'll do my best!
Then start right now!
You'll cry and you'll wail.
That's the hellish legs raise training for you.
Just admit defeat and surrender!
Gotta stay strong... Gotta stay strong!
I must live up to senpai's expectations!
Tsk. He's still holding out.
All right, now do it on those!
Parallel bars?
Am I supposed to do it up there?
That's high!
Senpai, maybe I should use
the vault boxes for now?
Even you look down on me
because I got zero points.
"What can a zero point loser teach me," right?
I see...
I-I'll do it!
30 more seconds! Start!
Yessir!
That's it, start crying!
Burst into tears and apologize!
You're only on your second circle of hell!
Senpai woke up early to teach me the basics!
Ugh. He just won't give in...
Circles next!
Pull your ass up!
Stretch your toes!
It's high!
And they wobble!
That's it, cry! Cry, cry!
Don't suppress your urges!
You're on the hell's summit!
I have to stay strong so I don’t disappoint my senpai who scored zero!
I have to stay strong!
How does this damn amateur
keep going so strong?!
The first, second, and third circles of hell.
Dammit, he endured it all?
Then I have no choice but to take you to the fourth circle of legs-raising hell.
Get up, Fujimaki!
Yessir!
Now you do it here.
Here...
What does he want me
to make a stand on... here?
Do the legs raise on the handrails.
Huh?! You mean, out there?!
That's right!
B-B-B-But what if I fall?
Then you'll train in landing.
A good gymnast can easily land from this height.
If you can't...
You should quit gymnastics!
Quit it this instant!
That's too much for me!
Please don't make me do that!
Don't make me do that...!
Yes, show that unsightly side of yours,
just like I did last year!
Amateur gymnast Fujimaki Shun,
long is the road to the gold medal.
Just as you finished your first tournament, the four circles of legs raising hell were waiting for you!
You could expect this guy to be a little too harsh!
But a bit of hard work won't make you give up, right, Shun?
Your goal is an Olympic gold medal!
Surely, you can blast through the leg raise!
Go for it, Ganbarist Shun!
No way!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
The men's gymnastics club is, so to speak, a disgrace to Heisei.
H-How can you say that?
As a gymnastics club member, you should at least be able to do this.
Our gymnastics club is good-for-nothing.
It's a duel! Fujimaki will duel you!
Well then, let's say if I win,
Fujimaki will quit the gymnastics club.
Fujimaki-kun, I know you can do it.
Next Ganba:
With Guts! Hellish Handstand Battle.
The high bar is the flower of men's gymnastics. Let me introduce you to some techniques.
Tkachev, Markelov and Ginger
are all techniques named after their inventors
And then there's the American Gaylord,
who did a masterful triple somersault.