Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Ganba!
Gymnastics is so much fun!
It was all for nothing.
Too bad.
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
Who is She?
The Mysterious Gymnastics Grandma
It's this way!
But that way's just residential houses.
Where's that bar you were talking about?
Huh?
What's wrong, Ueno-kun?
Th-There was a kid flying there just now.
Huh?
Over there?
What a weird thing to say.
But I'm sure I saw it!
S-Saw it again!
Hey, did you see it too?
Give it a rest!
There's nothing there!
B-B-But...
Come quickly!
This is the place!
This house?
It's where I saw the flying kid!
They do have a high bar!
Right, but why is there a high bar
in someone's garden?
And what is that kid doing?
Could he be the one who I saw flying earlier?
Ah, Ko-chan!
Took you long enough!
Say, is this your house?
No, it's not. But you can use the high bar if you want.
What's going on here?
Well, whatever it is,
I don't see why I should mind it.
It's very well taken care of.
There are no mats,
but a nice landing pit filled with sand.
Ain't it just perfect?
Powerful! Powerful!
How 'bout that?
Impressive, Higashi-senpai!
You guys are helpless...
Watch this!
Hey, it's not something a kid should try!
H-He's good!
His swinging is more sleek and effective than Higashi's!
To think a kid could do that...
Wh-What now?
He turns and twists!
It's a Moonsault!
Moonsault?
Moonsault
And finished!
Hey, Kotaro!
G-Grandma!
Didn't I tell you before not to play on the high bar when I'm not looking?
I-It's not my fault!
They showed up, so I had to do it!
Eh?!
Who do you happen to be?
E-Erm... We, uhh... You see...
Ko-chan brought them along.
So it was you, Kotaro?
I see now.
So Kotaro jumped without permission
because he wanted to show off his prowess on the high bar to you?
Yikes!
Get back here, Kotaro!
No, I'm sorry!
Speaking of which,
you guys look like gymnasts.
Y-Yeah... Sorry for showing up in your backyard uninvited.
Actually, we're...
That sounds positively tragic!
Can't believe there's a coach who's that cruel!
"Cruel" doesn't do it justice!
She's a demon, I'm telling you!
Without a bar to practice on,
I see why you guys are in a fix.
And that's what I was getting at, Madam.
Would it be quite all right for us to use your high bar every now and then?
I don't see why I should mind.
Wow!
Do you mean it?
Go ahead!
Hooray! Hip hip hooray!
But you’ll also need to keep an eye on these kids to make sure they don’t fall.
We'd be happy to!
You can leave that to us.
Yeah.
All right, Captain!
Let’s start prepping right away
to make full use of this high bar!
Prepping?
Right! Let's double back to school!
Yeah!
Wait... What are you up to?
Isn't that a bit... sneaky?
How can you say that, Captain?
We’re totally entitled to those
after they took our high bar!
Yeah!
Are we, really?
All clear!
We're done!
Good! It fits perfectly.
Aren’t those some splendid mats you’ve got!
Grandma, this mat is safer than sand.
Yay!
So soft!
All right, we should be done here for today.
Madam, we’d like to start using it next Monday.
Sure. Feel free to come anytime.
Bye, misters!
Kotaro, from now on, only use the high bar
when the misters are around.
I know!
But man, I didn't see that coming.
A high bar in someone's yard!
That's true.
I wonder why they have it.
Well, what does it matter?
That kid—Kotaro-kun—was awesome too.
Moonsault, huh?
Who do you think taught him that?
Captain can do the Moonsault too, I believe.
Hey, Captain, is something wrong?
N-No, it’s nothing.
I guess this is where we part ways for today.
Good job, everyone!
Keep trying, Fujimaki!
Yes, almost there! Keep it up.
Swing more vigorously!
Th-This is as high as I can go...
You’ve still got a lot to learn, Fujimaki.
Yeah...
Ueno-kun, it's your turn.
O-Okay!
Madam, what were you
talking about with Ueno-kun?
Oh? So you want to know?
U-Ueno can do the full circle!
He just climbed it and started swinging!
No way...
I-It worked...
Ueno, how'd you pull that one?
G-G-Granny taught me...
Granny?
Oh, it’s nothing. I just shared a few tips with him.
Tips?
Yes, that's right.
The full circle is done in a triangular shape.
Triangle?
The basic full circle forms a triangle with push, relax, and swing as its three apex points.
Push, relax, and swing?
Yes, push, relax, and swing.
"Push" is when you stand vertically on the high bar, at the highest point of the triangle.
Push
Then, you relax your body, using the momentum of your fall
to prepare for the recoil during the upcoming swing stage.
Relax
Then finally you swing.
You swing energetically now
to gain momentum.
Swing
This triangle makes you go the full circle.
You can't do that in a simple circular shape.
All right...
Relax,
swing,
push!
Relax, swing, push!
Yes, right.
I did it! It worked, madam!
Yes, I must say,
you seem awfully knowledgeable in this.
Oh, this is still nothing!
I was the one who taught Kotaro the Moonsault, after all.
By the way, would you kids like to learn Moonsault too?
Ugh?!
A-Are you serious?!
It's actually very simple!
Hooray?
What now? Are you telling me
none of you knows how to perform it?
Are you home, Madam?
Kotaro, what's with your arm?
I'm sorry, Madam!
I really am!
Kotaro broke his arm.
All because of that high bar!
Kotaro tried to do a dangerous high bar stunt at school.
On the school bar?
I'm sorry, Granny!
We’re tired of telling you over and over to stop encouraging dangerous behavior in our children!
Everyone here agrees.
This time, we'll make sure that dangerous high bar gets dismantled!
We're going home, Mayu.
Come, Shinji.
O-Okay...
We're leaving, Kotaro.
Granny!
You've gotta save it, whatever it takes!
Please, misters!
Oh...
Madam, I can't defend you any longer.
A child got injured this time.
Takashi-san...
Worst case scenario, someone might sue you—and us along with you.
We must remove the bar
before is comes to that, you see...
They're so heartless to you!
It's not your fault that Kotaro was injured.
That's right.
Kotaro-kun did it himself,
despite your express order not to.
I'm sorry, but could you go home early today?
My yard is overgrown;
I need to pull the weeds.
So you guys are from the gymnastics club
of Heisei Middle School? Interesting.
Do you really have to tear down
Madam's high bar?
Yes, it's decided.
We'll do it on Sunday in two weeks.
How can you...
I too wish there was something I could do to prevent this.
So you're still on Granny's side?
I was the one who installed
that high bar there.
On a request from my best friend.
Seiji...
Granny Tadokoro’s son, Seiji-kun, and I
were in the university gymnastics club together.
He had outstanding abilities,
and above all, he was a hard worker.
Seiji! What on earth
were you just trying to do?
A groundbreaking technique,
never seen before.
But Seiji injured himself during practice
and had to quit gymnastics.
That was when he set up that bar in his yard.
There, Eri.
Hold up, Takashi-san!
What's with that high bar?
I asked him to install it, Mom.
You’re still at it,
even after getting hurt that badly?
You don't have to worry about anything, Mom.
But a mere month later,
Seiji died in a traffic accident.
Eventually, his wife remarried and moved out.
Madam was alone ever since then.
That’s when she started studying the high bar on her own and teaching it to local kids.
Summer vacation’s finally here!
That's it, Eri! Now!
Madam Tadokoro had become an impressive trainer to everyone's amazement.
I did it!
Teaching the children about the high bar Seiji left behind is still her reason to live, even to this day.
Hm? Rain?
I have to act!
At that moment,
we were completely dumbfounded.
We couldn’t even say a word.
I'm sorry, Seiji.
We hafta do something!
Yeah, we certainly can't stand still.
Captain, let's protect
that high bar together.
And what's your plan?
I called it "Operation Ultra G."
Ultra G?
At the 1964 Tokyo Olympics, the Japanese gymnastics team aimed for a clear victory
over the Soviets by incorporating difficult level C techniques and above.
That was Operation Ultra C.
We'll acquire some great techniques too!
How do you intend to acquire them?
And what is this G about? The techniques difficulty level only goes up to E.
It's G for Gamba!
Let's do our ultra best, okay?
Swing higher, Fujimaki!
Try harder!
Huh?
It's you again!
Good morning, Madam.
We're practicing.
Madam, you promised to teach us the high bar, remember?
That's right.
We're eager to learn.
Whether I teach you or not, they’ll come to demolish the high bar next week anyway.
We'll protect the high bar!
Huh?
All right, let's keep practicing.
Ueno, you're next!
Yessir!
Okay, your swing is great. Ganba!
Make it as great as the other day! Ganba!
Ganba, Ueno!
Listen up. In gymnastics, when you root for someone, you say "Ganba!"
Ganba! Ganba!
Ganba! Ganba! Ganba!
Next is me!
Ganba!
Ganba, Senpai!
It's just like...
Just like back then, Seiji.
Madam,
have no worries!
Have no worries, Mom.
You're right, Seiji.
I should let these kids use the high bar as much as they want for the next two weeks.
You, the muscleman!
You're not doing any relax or swing at all!
Oh...
Madam!
Don't expect me to be a lenient coach!
I have a request!
Could you please teach me how do to Tkachev?
Huh?
And I'm interested in Jaeger!
Do you know what kind
of technique Markelov is?
I want a double somersault!
Ueno-kun and I
can start with a single somersault.
While we still have this high bar, please...
Please!
You want to learn such advanced techniques in just two weeks?
I guess we'll have to try.
That'll use up what little time we have.
Might as well go for it!
Hooray!
Listen up!
Before that, you'll all need to master the circle triangle.
Push, relax, and swing—try "one-two-three," or any other rhyme you prefer to time your movements.
Okay!
Fine, then! We'll spend the next week practicing nothing but giant swings!
Push, relax, and swing!
One, two, three!
I am... Popu-lar!
Rei-ko-sama!
More... Mu-scles!
Ul-tra G!
You've done well, swinging on that bar all week long, boys.
Yes! Does that mean we can finally start learning some techniques?
You've already learned them, in fact.
Excuse me?
Listen, Tkachev, Jaeger, and the like are all just special cases of putting that triangle into practice.
I believe you should be able
to execute it flawlessly by now.
Th-Then, are you saying we can try the advanced techniques already?
Seriously?
No, there's one more
important factor to account for.
It's a spiritual foundation,
built on your courage and trust.
Courage?
Trust?
Letting go of the bar in the middle
of a swing is not for the faint of heart.
Will you boys have the courage for that?
Falling from nearly three meters high with acceleration could result in a serious injury.
Can you fully trust your support crew?
Without that spiritual foundation,
I can't teach you anything more.
No way. I can't give up now.
Madam, I'll...
Madam, I'm going to try Tkachev now.
Captain?!
Such a difficult technique right off the bat?
Thank you, Fujimaki.
But I'm the Captain here.
This role is mine to play.
I-Is that our Captain?
Looks fun!
I don't believe it.
The courage to let go of the bar!
This is it!
Let go now!
Ganba, Captain!
I screwed up...
As expected.
This is our Captain, all right.
No way... Does that mean Operation Ultra G was a failure?
Of course he can't do it yet.
I just wanted to test the strength
of your commitment.
Allow this old bag
to demonstrate her prowess now.
Huh? Isn't that a judo belt?
When the captain lets go, you guys pull the belt back and help him fly over the bar.
M-Madam, is this really how it's done?
Imagine a triangle and push yourself to the limit during relax and swing.
Captain, Ganba!
All right...
Captain, you gotta trust us to pull you back!
He's right. Leave that to us.
S-Sorry!
That's right, I have these guys supporting me here.
What can I ever achieve without trusting them? Let's go!
That's it! Pull him!
Grab the bar!
Captain!
He did it!
I did it! Did it! All right...
You have a great triangle.
Madam, what kind of triangle is my Markelov?
And my Jaeger...
How do I do double somersault?!
Easy now, no need to rush things so much.
I'll teach you that in due course over the next week.
Okay!
One week later
Grandma?
Oh, it's you, Eri?
Where's uncle Yasui?
Did he call you?
Yeah.
By the way, what's with those mats?
And is that blood I'm seeing on the bar?
These past two weeks have been really fun.
Too bad it's bound to end today.
Excuse me!
Chairman, the demolition team is still not here?
Well, to tell you the truth...
Wait a moment before you tear down the bar!
I-It's you again!
Ugh!
Coach Misaki...
But why...
Everyone, I simply ask you to hear them out for just a minute before we tear down the bar.
Hey, we gonna do it in front of Coach Misaki?
I'm still not entirely confident
in my somersaults.
Too late to be getting cold feet now!
That's right!
Operation Ultra G starts now!
Gymnastics club member Fujimaki Shun,
the road to the gold medal is endlessly long.
We know you all worked hard to defend Madam's high bar, but what is this Operation Ultra G?
Hey, what are you going to do,
Ganbarist Shun?
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Gymnastics club member,
first-year Fujimaki Shun begins!
Good!
Kotaro-kun, you looked as light as a bird.
I also want to fly ever-higher, like a bird!
Oh no!
His relax time is too late!
This is bad. If he lets go now,
he'll fall right on top of the bar!
Don't you let go!
Next Ganba:
ILike a Bird! Operation Ultra Gamba.
The high bar performances at the Atlanta Olympics were amazing.
In high bar, you save your best technique to just before landing.
However, no matter what great technique you try, if you mess up the landing, it's a failure.
Please continue to land with great ultra-techniques! Good luck, Japan!