The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
Morisue-san won the gold medal on the high bar at the 1984 Los Angeles Olympics.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Sydney '2000
Ganba!
What are you hoping to achieve in just a month?!
Captain! I'm begging you, don't quit!
F-Fujimaki!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Special Training!
Hard Work Always Pays Off
Episode
Special Training!
Hard Work Always Pays Off
Fujimaki, tighten your tuck!
No way! He swings on just one hand!
Did he just...
Captain! So you're back after all?
Fujimaki... You've gotten quite good at it. That was amazing.
Right, Madam?
Yeah, that was an impressive
one-handed swing.
One-handed swing?
It was amazing, Fujimaki-kun!
Little bastard's been busy!
Right, it's impressive that you held onto it with just one hand.
Yes...
It's thanks to this little charm incorporated into the protector.
Huh! There's a pencil inside?
If Fujimaki starts training in earnest now,
he might get something ready for the tournament.
Yeah, that's right.
Captain?
Good luck, Fujimaki.
Madam...
I'm sorry for imposing.
I entrust these guys to you now!
You can't be serious. Why are you still saying that after what we've just seen?
If Captain quits, who's gonna train Fujimaki?
I’ve lost confidence in teaching others. I’ve realized I lack both the qualifications and the ability for it.
Wait a minute! How come you've given up on gymnastics already?
Have you forgotten the thrill and joy
of landing your first Tkachev?
Sanada...
I know I’m a slacker
who can't take training seriously.
I only joined the gymnastics club because I thought doing a backflip would make me popular with girls.
Still, you've always been ridiculously kind to me.
You even stayed after school to help me out.
I was planning to quit as soon as I learned how to do a backflip.
But then I felt so obliged to you I couldn't quit!
And yet...
You betray us,
quitting over such a trifle...
Please! Don't quit!
Sanada...
I was also delighted
when you praised my vaulting.
Please, don't quit!
I love the atmosphere
of your scrupulous teaching!
So I'm begging you not to quit!
Uchida... Higashi...
I also...
only made it this far thanks to your guidance!
Same for me!
I don't wanna stay in the gymnastics club without captain!
Guys...
Captain!
Captain...
You can't quit now. Just your presence was enough to bring all these scattered people together.
Guys...
Thank you.
I...
I love gymnastics.
I'm glad we got everyone back on track.
Captain is back too.
Yeah, that's right.
This means, I also...
What's wrong, Sagara-san?
You know, I...
I might just...
Huh? What?
We'll remain friends forever, right?
Seiji, you tore this protector yourself
to teach Shun to swing on one hand, didn't you?
Thanks to you, they were all
able to unite once again.
Principal's Office
I would also like to support his request.
All right, you can go to the training camp.
Thank you.
In exchange, you must rank in the top six.
Please don't forget that, okay?
Yes!
Summer Vacations
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
Yay!
It's the
summer
vacations!
There!
Successful landing! 10.0!
Come on! Out of the way!
We need to use it too!
You probably know
that good children wouldn't jump off the roof
You're not practicing here alone!
R-Right!
There!
Stay focused till the end!
Only one week until the tournament!
Keep your spirits up!
Good luck, everyone!
We'll have some chilled watermelon later.
Here I go!
Come on! Seventh lane is too slow. Row faster!
We'll focus on vault today.
Yessir!
Whassat? What's all the fuss about?
Isn't that Kamura from Urayasu Middle School?
What's that he's doing
to our Madonna Reiko-sama?
Resting his dirty hands on her perfect shoulders!
He's grinning so wickedly, too!
Oh, sorry there, gentlemen.
A lot of magazines wanted to cover it,
so they've let us use your gym.
Are you the men's gymnastics club?
Yes, we are.
Will you perform at the next tournament?
We will.
Our Kamura needs to stay in shape too,
so you’ll be able to learn a lot from him.
Kamura-kun, could you share your aspirations for the upcoming prefectural tournament?
My aspirations?
If I'm being honest,
I haven't given it much thought.
There are only three events at the prefectural tournament: floor, vault, and high bar.
My sight is set on All-Japan Junior Tournament.
And from there—
the International Junior Olympics.
Right, Reiko-chan?
The prefectural tournaments are just child's play.
That jerk...
I'm so worked up!
He's looking down on us!
In that case, won't you show us your practice?
Huh? No high bar in here.
Well, the rings would suffice.
You there, help him up.
Why us?
Oh no, it's fine.
I don't need anyone helping me up.
Besides, they probably don’t know what moves on the rings are like anyway.
What did you say?
A jaw-dropping technique?
We just need something to silence that arrogant bastard once and for all!
We can't let him get away
with mocking us like this.
Is it really a good idea to change the performance lineup so close to the tournament?
Sanada is getting increasingly
better with his Jaeger.
Uchida has the double somersault, and Higashi has the straight-arm, straight-body press handstand.
Wouldn't it be more effective to continue perfecting the execution of those?
I can only see one of you pulling something of the kind.
Huh?
Shun, I'm talking about you.
Me?
Your shoulders seem to be uncharacteristically strong.
Let's add to the one-handed swinging
a one-handed handspring on the vault.
A one-handed handspring?
Can I really do it?
Relying on Fujimaki is a nonstarter.
That's not true!
I believe in him...
Fujimaki-kun can make it happen.
Mari-chan, you like Shin, don't you?
Huh?
You're an open book to me.
Not at all!
I couldn't say so...
Besides, Fujimaki-kun himself doesn't pay any mind to me. He's always so curt.
You know, I couldn't make any friends because I kept changing schools.
What's worse, I was never all that talkative.
That's why, with this last transfer, I did my best to stay upbeat.
I don't think Shun dislikes you.
But you see, boys grow up slowly,
compared to girls.
You're a good girl, so even Shun will notice you with just a bit more effort.
Mari-chan?
Soon, I...
Soon, I'll have to...
change schools again.
Which means...
I'll have to part with everyone again!
Madam!
When is it?
On the day of the tournament...
Is that true?
I don't wanna change schools again!
I don't wanna break up with everyone!
Wake up, Fujimaki-kun.
Wake up.
Still, what's gotten into you?
Going shopping so late at night...
Are you angry?
It's not that I'm angry, per se...
Well, with so many people gathered at one place,
we'll quickly run out of tissues, right?
Still, we could do it in the morning.
Yeah, I suppose...
I'm sorry...
But it seems you've forgotten
your promise to me.
Promise?
What happened?
Have you been practicing the back hip circle on your own?!
But I still couldn't make it work.
All I got from it were these calluses.
Hey, teach me how to do the back hip circle.
Here and now.
Okay? You promised, remember?
We'll be friends forever, right?
Why are you in such a hurry?
No...
Well, I'm tired of embarrassing myself all the time.
That's a lie.
Tell me, are you changing schools again?
I guess I can't hide anything from you.
Yes, I'm a wandering transfer girl.
It's my fate to never stay in one place for long.
When are you moving?
Not right now...
Maybe a little later.
Then we gotta do our best until then!
You can't keep your arms outstretched!
You need to pull yourself up!
Got it...
Then try again!
Okay.
Yeah, that's better already.
Don't step on the lawn
You can do it, Fujimaki-kun!
Guess I did it!
That was more than just "did it!"
Awesome!
Senpai, it hurts!
Shut up, little one!
The big day is finally tomorrow.
Yeah.
Good luck.
You too.
Thanks.
Ta-dam!
A pork cutlet!
Me and Madam put our souls into it.
Come on everyone, sit down.
At last, the day of reckoning is tomorrow.
You guys gave it your all. Now all that's left is to eat well and get a good night's sleep.
We don't need any silly slip-ups tomorrow.
Yes!
Let's dig in, then!
Thanks for the meal!
What's wrong, Ueno-kun?
You don't like the cutlets?
Don't mind if I do, then!
You can't have it all to yourself!
Exactly! You can't!
What about my share?
I can't eat...
Even with the tournament tomorrow,
I can't shake this lump in my throat.
Don't tell me you're having
a nervous breakdown.
Why would you get nervous?
Exactly! It's us who's gonna perform tomorrow.
Because if someone slips up...
No need to worry.
Nobody's going to slip up now.
Yes... I suppose.
There was so much rice left...
As usual, only Shun asked for a second helping.
I guess they really are nervous after all.
Thanks to Ueno saying that nonsense,
I can't sleep a wink now.
In case, we do slip up
and don't place in the top six...
Yeah, I'm worried too.
Same here.
I'm sorry, guys.
You're awake too, Captain?
Yeah.
Damn it, that bastard Ueno
is the only one sleeping soundly.
Huh? Where's Fujimaki?
One more time. Ready?
Yeah.
There!
Start bending your arms.
Pull yourself up to the bar!
Yes, that's good!
Good. Keep it up!
Look at your belly button.
You're doing well, Sagara-san!
You can do it!
I did it...
I did it!
Fujimaki-kun, I did it!
Yeah! It's a success.
It's beautiful!
It really is.
Sagara-san, you did a great job.
Yeah.
Anything is possible if you try hard enough.
In your new school,
no one will make fun of you.
Fujimaki-kun, thank you.
Sagara-san.
It feels wonderful
to be able to do something new.
Hard work always pays off.
Yeah, it's the best.
Mari-chan, you're changing schools again?
Guys...
Why didn't you tell us?
Well, I figured you didn't need an extra worry just before the tournament.
"Extra" worry?
That's sneaky, Mari-chan!
Aren't we all part of the same gymnastics club?
Sanada-senpai...
Fujimaki, that was goddamn well said!
Anything is possible if you try hard enough!
Now I'm fired up too!
I'll definitely do it!
Same here! After seeing Mari-chan's
back hip circle, I really feel like I can't lose!
Uchida-senpai, Higashi-senpai...
"Hard work always pays off?"
You just said something very important.
Madam...
All right, everyone!
Tomorrow, we'll send Mari-chan off
with our ultimate performance!
Yeah!
This is the solemn oath of the Heisei Men's Gymnastics Club!
No matter where Mari-chan transfers, our Ultra Gamba performance tomorrow won't embarrass her!
Middle School Gymnastics Tournament Chiba Prefecture Preliminaries
Hey, look at that.
What in the world is that?
Did they get the wrong address?
It's Heisei Middle School!
Ah, the last place of the last tournament?
What's with those T-shirts?
Got it, Mariko?
You can't be late for the train.
All right, the tournament is here!
The spirits are high!
Your goal is to demonstrate the result of your training and finish in top six!
Burn, Ganbarist Shun!
We've confirmed that all the registered men's teams have shown up.
All right! Let's show them the power of our determination!
We're ready!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
And it's much cleaner than the earlier Kamura's Planche!
What was that?!
But he's right.
Hey, Mochida! Picture this! Take the shot!
Y-Yessir!
Huh?
What!?
Next Gamba: Tournament!
Ultra Special Cross Handstand!
The floor space is 12 square meters.
The point is to move freely on this floor
to compose a big and impressive performance.
Particularly impressive is the straight diagonal movement.
All the athletes come here with their difficult special moves prepared!