The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
And here is Higashi's cross handstand.
I see! The grip is different!
Bonus points! Bonus points! Bonus points!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
It's Impossible!
The Death of Uchida Minoru's Vault?!
Episode
It's Impossible!
The Death of Uchida Minoru's Vault?!
Now, the judges have finished consulting again,
and a new score is about to be posted...
Currently, the first place is held by Saga of the Lee Corps with his 9.85 points.
Meanwhile, Higashi from Heisei,
who delivered a powerhouse performance
received a baffling 9.60—
sparking outrage among the crowd!
However, the judges yielded
to Andrianov's protest.
If he's awarded bonus points
and scores above 9.85,
Higashi will have a clear path to the world championship!
And here comes the score!
Incredible! It's the same 9.6!
No bonus points were awarded!
What the hell?!
Are you kiddin' us?!
We'll never accept this!
It spiraled out of control!
The furious crowd is now
hurling objects at the judges!
You're disrupting the tournament!
Stop hurling objects into the competition area!
Stop it, people!
It was my own fault only!
Originally, my routine was supposed to include dynamic techniques as well!
However...
I just desperately wanted to show everyone
the magnificence of my muscles.
I wanted you to see it!
I wanted you to see it...
I was so caught up in it that I impulsively changed my routine, making it too strength-focused!
And then...
I completely forgot about the score!
And about the dynamic techniques.
Therefore, people...
I...
I'm overwhelmed by the most intense emotions right now!
The fact that you were all prepared
to fight for my score tooth and nail...
Is so moving!
Your cheers
are the greatest reward I could ever wish for!
We're with you!
Well said, Hercules!
What wonderful guy he is!
Hercules-kun, you're the best!
Heracles!
Dear friends, you've heard
what Higashi just said, didn't you?
The cheering of the audience
is the best prize for him!
What wonderful words,
coming from him!
Isn't this what sports are truly about?
His contagious passion
rubbed off on me too!
That was quite a flashy performance.
But did you honestly expect them
to reconsider a score they've already given?
Of course not.
I was never counting on that.
Actually, Eri...
The audience was moved
by his breathtaking performance.
I did what I did because I wanted those thickheaded judges
to understand it too.
Fun gymnastics, Mandole Manoff, right?
Right?
And with that, the first place on the rings
goes to Saga from the Nishihori gymnastics club.
His score is 9.85!
The second place is with Higashi from Heisei Middle School. His score is 9.60.
Shit...
All those ignorant oafs don't know a goddamn thing about gymnastics!
I was the one who won!
That's right, so be proud of it.
Coach...
Gymnastics is all about the points.
There's no place for humanity
in our scientific gymnastics.
What was your score?
9.85.
What was his?
9.60.
Then what are you complaining about?
Where should we take these?
Oh, you didn't have to. Just leave them there.
I'll take care of the rest.
Thanks. I'll leave it to you, then.
Sure.
I couldn't do something like that...
Like what?
A cross handstand and an iron cross,
both of which require enormous strength.
I was also a rings specialist
during my active career.
Are you saying we should've
raised his score?
It wouldn't be strange if we did.
We're done discussing that.
Oh, Head Judge?
The performance's composition, difficulty, and landing execution
should all be judged by the same standards.
That does not, in any form,
include the audience's reaction.
We have to conform to the same standard
for all the performers.
Head Judge!
Can I ask just one thing?
What would've been if this tournament's scoring rules allowed bonus points for showmanship?
If it was up to me,
Higashi would've won.
Here are the morning scoring tables.
Thanks.
Man, that Nishihori College team is hella strong.
But the guys from Heisei
have more interesting routines.
They add a lot of nice little touches.
Like that guy... Sanada?
Who had the third place on the floor.
They flopped on the pommel horse,
but then there was that guy on the rings... Higashi?
He finished second with 9.6 points.
Yeah, that was memorable.
But the Nishihori athlete won in the end thanks to a more well-rounded composition.
What now, Andrianov?
None of your athletes can defeat any of my ones on their own.
You have no choice but to admit
your inferiority as a coach.
All right! It's the noon!
Snacks!
Lunchtime!
You, the first-year ding-dongs!
Go buy us all a lunch!
Okay!
Hold it, Uchida.
You'll do it yourself.
Huh?
Ueno was forced to perform
on the pommel horse because of you.
You need to make up for that.
Captain...
All right, I got it!
Hey, Fujimaki, let's go!
Okay!
Say, Fujimaki.
Yes?
I really thought Higashi's performance
was the most amazing there.
Yeah, it gave me chills too.
Even if they didn’t give him the score he deserved,
at least the audience knew what's what.
Yes.
That was great.
I hope I can show something like that too...
What's all the bullshit you're spewing?
"The audience knew what's what?"
Don't make me laugh!
The gymnastics competitions
are all about the difficulty and the score.
What's you're putting on
is a street performance!
What was that?!
Bear with it, Fujimaki.
Let's go.
Okay.
What a pity...
I’d hate to be coached by a second-rate trainer
and come up with an idea
as absurd as a handstand
on the pommel horse.
He's a monkey trainer
and you're his monkeys!
That's enough!
Apologize to Uchida-senpai, you all!
But it's the truth. Your coach can't compete
with Coach Lee in pure ability.
So he resorts to cheap tricks,
like making his trainees embarrass themselves.
Coach Andrianov is not like that!
He showed us all
how wonderful gymnastics is!
So what? How is it wonderful
if it doesn't convert to point?
But the people cheered for Higashi-senpai
more than for anyone else!
What?!
Fujimaki!
Are you okay, Fujimaki?
Remember your place, you scum!
What's with that look?
Apologize to Uchida-senpai.
Apologize!
Stop!
I don't care what you say about me.
But don't you touch Fujimaki!
He's no ordinary gymnast.
And he'll win Olympic gold!
He's better than any of you!
At the Olympics?
How would you know anything about it?
He's an idiot!
A blithering idiot!
What's so funny?!
Damn it all...
You look down on others...
Constantly berate them...
Can't we have dreams?
Are you saying we have no right to dream about the Olympics?!
Ridiculous!
A circus act of a gymnastics club like yours will never qualify for that!
Only those who endure grueling training like us have the right to say that!
Ah, I found them!
What's taking you so long?
How long does it take you to buy us lunch?
The afternoon part is about to start!
What happened?!
He nailed it! Layout Cuervo!
Amekura from Nishihori Club
delivered a great performance!
In this tournament,
athletes will perform two separate vaults,
and their average
will determine the final score.
What score will Amekura's first vault get?
As the name suggests, the Cuervo vault was introduced by a Cuban gymnast, Cuervo, in 1973.
Yes. Front flip, then a handspring, followed immediately by a half twist, then a backflip.
Amekura executed it
as a perfect layout backflip.
9.6! Impressive first score!
9.5!
His first attempt scored 9.6, the second—9.5.
Therefore, Amekura's final score is...
9.55!
Once again, the first place
is with a Nishihori athlete!
How can we lose?
Uchida-senpai
is a vault specialist after all!
It's your turn next.
At best pretend you're trying.
And the next performer
is Uchida of Heisei Club!
I will win this!
So high!
It's out! He performed a front roll with a twist and a tucked up front somersault!
It's a double somersault with a twist!
Did you see it just now?
He was flying so high!
He's really giving it his all!
Did he flow over the four meters line?
He used his chest to spin.
Chest, sir?
Yes, it’s a technique that lets you jump higher and soar farther than any other gymnast.
Now the score is...
9.4!
What the hell! So low?!
These judges are up to some bullshit again!
Why is it only 9.4?
It wasn't just a double somersault with a twist!
He also flew higher and farther
than any other gymnast!
I didn't think there'd be an athlete
who'd cross the four meters line.
Sir?
The lines drawn in the landing area
are used for adding or subtracting points.
You get 0.1 for flying over the 3.5 meters line.
0.2 points for flying over the 4 meters one.
However, this tournament's rules
don’t award points for height and distance.
If there was such a rule,
Uchida would've been scored with 9.6.
You get it now? You can't win in gymnastics without points!
It's the difficulty.
Difficulty is everything!
Dreaming about the Olympics with that level?
Don't make me laugh!
If that's the best you can do,
that Fujimaki is nothing to be afraid of either.
Tell me, Fujimaki, do you remember
the day when you came to join the club?
Huh?
Hey, keep moving.
O-Okay.
You started it off with quite a statement.
"I want to win Olympic gold."
Class 1-B, Fujimaki Shun.
​​I want to win gold at the Olympics!
And here...
That sure took me by surprise.
However, you couldn't even do a handstand.
And you tried to repeat
a balance pose after Captain.
To put it frankly,
I really thought you were hopeless.
But seeing how much you've improved over the past six months, I can't help but be taken aback.
What I'm getting at is..
What I said earlier wasn't a lie.
You really are amazing.
And I know you'll get that Olympic gold one day.
Uchida-senpai...
I know you will.
Uchida-senpai is weird...
He said it was as though
we'll never meet again.
Now, what kind of technique will Uchida from Heisei bring to the table this time?
It wasn't a lie, Fujimaki.
I mean it when I say you're amazing.
The first place is with Amekura and his 9.55
To win, Uchida has to score 9.7 or more in the second run.
But Uchida's second jump
is a simple Tsukahara Vault.
It wouldn't yield him 9.7.
No way... Then, we'll lose
unless he pulls off a triple somersault?
Triple somersault?
Impossible!
All right, Uchida raises his hand!
You can't perform a triple somersault yet.
It requires enormous rotational strength,
that alone is too dangerous!
Oh man, just as I thought, huh?
I-I'm just asking out of curiosity.
Anyone gets chills when taking
the first step into uncharted territory.
Even though I proudly boast about being the vault specialist,
I still feel scared and isolated
every time I start my run-up.
But I...
Let's go!
Don't risk your whole career, Minoru!
He runs up with such drive!
Stop!
That's not the gymnastics I taught you!
I can't lose!
If I lose, everything I said will be a lie!
Uchida!
Minoru!
It wasn't
a lie!
Triple somersault?!
Are you insane?!
Minoru!
Turn!
Right here in the middle of my palm
I'm feeling a strong response
I'll grab your heart right at the core
And draw a gigantic arch!
It'll glow large and beautiful in the night sky!
Oh yeah!
So, with that sparkling gaze of yours
draw me into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough
So, with that dazzling smile of yours
Draw me right into a miracle
Throw me right into the storm
I know the welcome's going to be rough!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Morisue's great technique should suit me!
Hold tight!
All right, the next twist should be final!
O-Orikasa!
You can do it, Shindo-kun.
You can't build up confidence all by yourself.
Yes, the last twist!
And finish!
No mistakes!
Next Ganba: It's Captain!
Remember that Safety Comes First Here!
Today's lesson is about the high bar overhand.
The key is to turn your wrists and bring the bar to your stomach.
Swing strongly, pull your wrists,
then pull your belly to it.
And now—for underhand!
If you learn this, you might just finally be able to do a backward giant swing!