The gold medal: a glorious brilliance achieved only through a long and arduous journey.
This is the story of our young heroes rising to become
the cornerstone of Japan's gymnastics in the 21st century.
Their goal is the gold medal at Sydney Olympics!
Shun-kun!
I can't let go, no matter what I do!
Enough...
Enough already...
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
A Revival!
The First Step Towards New Hope
W-World champion!?
Is he just making stuff up
because he’s drunk?
Can you really cure him in one stroke?
Yes, it's true! The disease of not being able to let go of the high bar is easy to cure!
Leave it to me!
Shun, I don't think he's lying.
Y-Yes...
Shun!
Oh no, he passed out!
It's true, one stroke!
One really should drink that much.
My oh my.
It's completed!
Designed for Fujimaki’s
"Can’t let go of the high bar" syndrome:
the electric shock instant recovery machine! It’s perfect!
Hey, people! It's finished!
Wake up!
You bastards! You already made me do everything myself!
Wake up! Dimwits!
Loafs! Bumpkins!
These two I don't even need to help.
And now, to commemorate its completion,
"Early morning electric shock wake-up call!"
You must absolutely never try this at home!
So, gentlemen, are you finally awake?
Shun, go put on your protector
after you finish your breakfast.
Uh? Okay...
But do you really think he's going to cure it?
What do you have to lose?
Should he succeed, we'll have nothing to complain about.
I suppose...
Can he really be a former world champion?
Yes, probably. He might be drunk blind, but he wouldn't lie.
Yes, you're probably right.
But curing it in one stroke...
I'm sure it was just drunk bragging.
Man, I'm sleepy.
Let's wrap this up quickly and then I'll go to bed.
If he goes on another date with Reiko-sama today, it’ll be the death of me.
We must do whatever it takes to help him overcome his illness as soon as possible.
All right! Operation Lightning is ready to launch!
Yeah!
So, is today’s star, Fujimaki-kun, here?
Hey, this is big! Fujimaki-kun didn't come home yesterday!
D-Don't tell me...
R-Reiko-senpai...
E-Entertained him all night long?
Unforgivable!
Are you guys thinking about something weird?
Fujimaki-kun stayed at Madam's house.
You should've started with that!
What a waste of nerves!
What's so big about it, then?
So what do we do now?
Should I call Madam's house and tell Fujimaki-kun to come?
Or maybe we will all go there ourselves?
Ueno! We set up the high bar
early in the morning
and installed our device
with considerable effort.
Yes...
Are you suggesting we just leave it as is?
Um... I'm sorry, I'll call Fujimaki-kun here at once.
Wait a minute, Ueno!
Your body is great for our purpose.
It's a perfect fit!
That's it! You'll test it first in Fujimaki's place.
H-Huh?!
Good thinking! Ueno, for the sake
of your best friend, undress.
I-I-I think I'll just call Fujimaki-kun!
No can do! In five minutes, I'll be asleep.
You slept soundly all through the night.
Do you have no consideration for your sleep-deprived senpai?
N-No...
Okay, I'll do it, Uchida-senpai.
I'm off!
Try not to be such a nuisance
to Madam Tadokoro.
Okay!
Right...
All right! We'll be here to support you,
so have no worries.
Okay. I'm starting, then!
Don't let go until I turn on the current.
Okay...
Now!
Don't ever do that!
Watch out!
Oh... Sorry.
Why did you fall to a place
like this, you dunce?!
Ugh... I erred!
It's due to the delay in activation.
I need to turn it on earlier than just before the jump.
Because if I turn it on when you're supposed to let go,
by the time it reaches you, you'll already be at a point where you can only fall flat.
It's really just a matter of fractions of a second.
And because the time frame is so small,
operating the switch is difficult.
The only way to make it just right
is to use a fully automatic switch.
Like in computers, cameras,
medical monitors...
We have nowhere near enough time or money for that! Just do it manually!
Ah... Uchida! Don't sleep!
Really?
Wh-What do we do now?
Hey, you tell me!
If this keeps up,
I'll become unable
to use the high bar myself...
Library room
Ah, there he is!
Sergei Andrianov was the overall individual champion at the Montreal Olympics!
Wow! So it was true?
Sorry...
But how come
he showed up at Madam's house?
I came to return this.
Japan's national team uniform?
Is this...
Tadokoro Seiji
Seiji's?
When I first met Seiji-san
at the World Championships,
he gifted me this uniform.
Seiji was a brilliant athlete.
This uniform has become my talisman.
When I heard about Seiji-san's passing,
I set out to return this uniform to you.
I really wish I could come sooner...
I see. So you and Seiji were friends?
Thank you for going to all this trouble...
So? Are you better now, Ueno?
Y-Yes, it doesn't hurt anymore.
Ah, so that's where you were?
Re-Re-Reiko-senpai?
It's already noon, you know.
Shindo-kun, Coach Misaki tells you
to come to the principal's office immediately.
Huh? Coach Misaki?
Allow me to introduce.
This is Kenmotsu-san from the Japan Gymnastics Association.
I'm Kenmotsu Eizo.
I hope you were able to learn a lot
at the recent junior training camp.
Huh?
It was Kenmotsu-san who used his influence
to get the the men's team invited.
I've seen your results
in the regional tournament.
That's also what I wanted
to talk to you about today.
The Junior Gymnastics Event-Specific Championships are set to take place in a month.
I really want Heisei
to take part in that tournament.
Event-Specific Championships?
Doesn't that mean individual participation?
That's right. You can choose your events yourself.
The gymnastics is entering the age of specialists.
The winners of this competition will be our top priority for next year's Junior World Championships.
Huh? W-World?
World championship?
It's sponsored by TV stations,
so it'll be broadcast to the whole world!
B-Broadcast on TV?
Broadcast on TV, huh?
Rats! The means we gotta cure Fujimaki as soon as possible.
All right, let's go to Madam's.
Yeah!
Seiji built this high bar?
Yeah...
Madam! It’s true!
He's a real world champion!
Hi! Dobriy den'! Hello!
Oh, hello...
Did you bring your protector?
Yeah!
Are your hands okay?
Y-Yeah...
Then leave it to me!
This is how we cure the
"Can't let go of the bar" syndrome.
Huh? How can I perform
such a technique if I can't even let go?
No, of course you can!
There!
T-That's impossible!
If you just do what I say, you'll be fine!
Yes!
That's good!
Jump towards me when I give you a cue!
Andrianov, what's on your mind?
I know it's hopeless.
I've tried to let go
time and time again up until now...
But I'll be in trouble if I can't get over it!
It's okay! Fly!
Trust me!
Fly!
F-Fly...
You can fly.
I can fly...
Fly!
I'm flying!
No way!
I-Impossible!
Why did it work?
Madam, I let go!
Yeah...
That was a gorgeous layout somersault!
Layout somersault? I see...
For a layout somersault, you let go of the high bar when you're moving away from it.
Until now, Shun had tried releasing the bar with triple somersault timing, which he failed before.
But this is not the same as triple somersault
that you perform above the bar.
For the layout somersault, you move away from the bar.
Was that enough to erase
his fear subconsciously?
That's right.
He holds the bar the tightest
when it's time to let go.
But I gave him a cue
and that disrupted his timing.
It worked, Shun!
It really did, Madam!
That's the world champion for you.
He really cured it in one stroke!
Yeah. It was true!
But Andrianov-san, how did the layout somersault cure me?
Oh, that's very simple!
I couldn't fly long ago due to a similar fear,
but the layout somersault helped me overcome it!
Huh? You too, Andrianov-san?
Yes!
I'll try it again before I forget!
Thank you so much!
Both from Shun and from me.
Oh no, I was just returning the old favor.
With a TV appearance at stake, we absolutely have to cure him!
But if you mess up the switch timings, it might worsen his inability to let go of the high bar!
That's right. I feel like I'd never be able to fly again. Are you listening, senpai?
Jeez...
Ah!
Uh?!
Wh-What's that?
I-Is that...
Fujimaki!
Such a clean layout somersault! Cool!
You should be more surprised he can fly, you dumbass!
Then it's cured!
His high bar syndrome is gone!
Guess we came too late, huh?
Are you kidding me?
What are we gonna do with this now?
Then, that test you made me take
was for nothing?
It was!
But it still hurts!
Dammit!
Wait for me!
Fujimaki!
Ah, guys!
I'm cured! It's all fine now.
I'm sorry for worrying you!
U-Um, did something happen?
Listen, you! I stayed up all night because of you, and you just brushed it off like it’s nothing?!
Uchida-senpai, you even did that for me...
As a punishment, you can never again...
Huh? Never again...?
Never again go on a date with Reiko-sama!
Is that all? You guys sure like to joke around!
Hey!
Boys, enough of your messing around, come close.
I'll go boil the corn you helped me pluck.
Okay!
Come on, hurry. You need to meet this person who cured me.
That healer... Is him?
That's right.
Thanks for the meal!
It's amazing!
To think we'd meet a world gold medalist at your house!
I know, right? Don't you underestimate me.
You guys have also been busy.
If you win thus Junior Event-Specific Tournament, you'll get to go to the world championship!
It moves me to tears of joy!
Yes, and it's all thanks to you.
That TV broadcast is going to boost my female fanbase again. Oh man...
Humph. You’ll just overdo it and fail,
and the whole country will see your humiliation.
I hope my muscles will look beautiful on TV!
Well then, why don't we go harvesting greens beans today?
Y-You see, we have some other business.
Excuse us!
Huh?
Oh... Excuse me too!
Oh gosh, look at how much they hate working in the fields.
Hm? When I won the Olympic gold?
Yes. I was wondering what it feels like.
Do you want to go to the Olympics, Shun?
Yeah. It was always my dream.
I also made a promise to someone.
Hm?
The Olympics? Yes, the athletes there carry a big burden on their shoulders.
National prestige,
the hopes of their compatriots.
Responsibility before your team
for all the severe practices.
And of course, your own pride.
But in front of the audience and people worldwide,
they all become distant concerns.
The only thing on your mind is your performance and how to make it perfect.
And once the performance is over,
the applause is deafening!
Kak horosho!
Everyone is genuinely praising you.
I was so happy that I cried.
Um...
Are you going home soon?
Hm?
If only possible, I wanted to ask you
to coach me until the next tournament.
It's my request too!
Madam?
Of course I can't refuse when Seiji's mom asks me to do it!
Oh? Then...
But before that, you'll need to pass one test.
I will only coach you if you clear that test.
T-Test?
That's nice.
Awesome!
I envy them.
What's all this ruckus instead of practicing?
Ah, Coach Misaki!
Who are you?
Oh, E-Eri! Dobriy den'! Hello!
Prekrasna! You're beautiful!
Stop! What are you doing?
You don't belong here!
Who are you?!
Oh! I beg your pardon. I was indebted to your father. My name is Sergei Andrianov!
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
My method of testing
is a somersault while standing.
Huh?
What's special about that?
Just a backflip?
It's a piece of cake!
All right...
Good, Fujimaki!
Oh! Uchida took off his glasses!
It's gonna be something!
Like this!
How about that?
What is he thinking?
These boys won each individual event
at the district tournament
They can backflip with their eyes closed.
Awesome, Captain!
You can do it so naturally!
For the Prince of Floor,
a simple backflip is...
too boring!
Hey, adding a frontflip is cheating!
That means everyone passes!
Well then, what are the test results?
You guys are like monkeys!
Monkeys?
Wh-What do you mean?
You guys are not even worth considering for me!
I'm no monkey trainer!
You all failed!
W-We failed?
What did we do wrong?
Japanese gymnastics,
including women’s,
is fatally flawed!
Fatally...
Flawed?
Did he say fatally flawed?
Isn't that a pretty terrifying line,
coming from a gold medalist?
Will you be all right, Ganbarist Shun?!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing it,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—the love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Apparently there is a fatal flaw in Japanese gymnastics, including women's one.
Fatal flaw?
That's interesting.
Then, let the Prince of Floor try to take it on.
Tsk. Were you even trying?
You guys can't conquer that height!
Huh?
Next Ganba:
Higher! Operation Booby Somersault.
It's finally time for the backflip part 2.
Once you swing your hands and push yourself up, try doing a backflip with assistance.
Swing your hands strongly...
If one person is not enough to assist you,
ask two people to do it.