Greetings.
A lot has happened since I left Tokyo.
It took me a while to get here since I had to work part-time and whatnot along the way,
but it’s the kind of experience
I’d never have if I were still living clockwise.
But the bike and the high school student who were gathering dust in the city
finally made it to the northernmost tip of Japan.
The northernmost point of Japan
Chapter 3
Peace Commemoration
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
"No more way forward, only the sea.
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
To:
Shinozaki,
Tokyo
And beyond it, nothing but foreign lands,
so I've no choice but to head back south."
Well, that much was
obvious enough, you dimwit.
Huh? "I'm gonna drive
to the southernmost tip next?!"
Is he even serious?!
He's the real deal.
Starting from zero on his odometer,
he made a beeline straight for Cape Soya.
Who’d have thought that habitual truant would get fired up for biking!
Isn't that what you wanted?
As long as he has his goal in sight,
he won’t notice any obstacles along the way.
As long as he has a goal,
he won’t notice any obstacles, huh?
Excuse me! Could you please
take our picture?
What, me?
Yeah.
Sure, no problem.
Okay, ready?
Thank you very much.
For us too!
Okay, say cheese!
Could you please help us too?
Sure, sure.
Okay, say cheese.
Kitakyushu University Motoclub
Toyo Gakuen University
Thanks a lot!
Sure.
Seems like I'm free at last...
Summer vacation is over,
I wonder what everyone at school is doing.
They're probably busy with homework
and preparing for the new semester...
Oh man, I'm getting homesick!
U-Um, excuse me?
Could you take our picture?
And this is all I get!
Could you two get a little closer?
Don't worry, nobody's watching!
Like this?
Yes! Perfect!
Thank you very much.
I wonder how it'll come out. I'm sure you made it look like we're a couple.
Aren't you excited to see the result?
I suppose.
Bye.
They look like a happy couple.
They probably think
you’re a walking self-timer.
Yeah... So it seems.
Bud, if you keep sporting that friendly face
around here, they’ll keep coming.
By the way, I've heard plenty about this cape,
but the real thing is not all that special.
On a sunny day, you can see Sakhalin on the other side.
Who cares?! It's cloudy today
and you can't see squat!
The cape's selling point is that you can see it, but if you can't see it, you just wasted your time!
That's some nerve you've got,
bloody Hokkaido!
Better stay clear of that creep...
Oi, bud, where are you going?
Where I'm going is none of your business!
I'm gonna grab a meal!
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Northernmost cafeteria
Ramen
Local
cuisine
Oh, in that case I'm coming along.
Welcome!
Scallop ramen, crab ramen,
hodgepodge ramen...
They'd make it from just about anything in Hokkaido!
Nobody's forcing you to order it.
I'm not saying I dislike it!
Hey proprietress!
Please make one with everything at once—
what was it, hodgepodge?
You sure eat a lot
for all your complaining.
I'm full! That wasn't half-bad.
By the way, bud.
You gave me a real dandy idea.
Hm?
'Course, I'd prefer to do it meself, but it's clear to me that you're better suited for it.
It's likely that I'm gonna lose sleep
and sweat all night if I share my plan with you!
You just need to cool down
after that bowl.
Listen up. I was watching you there at the cape for a while.
While I was eating ramen, over 20 tourist couples took commemorative photos there.
You must've ate quite a lot
to see that many.
Don't interrupt!
You can earn some good cash as a
walking camera-timer at 10 yen a shot.
If you had over 20 clients in 15 minutes,
that's 800 yen an hour.
During the peak time around 2 p.m,
I think you can make 5,000 yen in 6 hours.
You in?
Hm... I don't know...
I must be feeling pretty generous if I can give away 5,000 yen in profit for two bowls of ramen.
Huh?
Well then, good luck, bud.
And take care on the road.
See ya 'round!
Uh?! H-Hey!
Two scallops and one hodgepodge.
That'll be 1,390 yen total including tax, sir.
That cocksucker...
Thank you very much!
It’s guys like him that give
touring riders a bad name!
Look, he's so cute.
Let's take him with us.
Uh? Sure...
I really like him. I want to bring him along,
even if it won't be for long.
They're lucky...
It's 'cause they’re so wrapped up in each other
that they have to use a walking camera-timer…
Now then, I wanted to get to Saroma
before the sun goes down.
I think they have a campsite there.
Ah... I-I'm sorry!
No, it's nothing.
I-If you say so...
Have a nice trip!
Why'd I buy a map this unwieldy?
Suicide note
S-Suicide note?
Why?!
Why...
They made such a happy-looking couple! What happened?
I think it was a whitish sedan...
That's it!
Definitely not!
Wrong.
Not here either!
Where did they go?
And anyway, what am I going to say to her?
You dropped something!
Here, I wanted to give it back.
Oh my! Thanks a lot.
I'd be in a pickle without it.
That's just silly.
That's right! The police!
Like a runaway
could just waltz into a police station!
That's right, just leave them be.
If they find out who you are,
they'll send you home!
No, don't listen to him!
Standing by while someone
kills themselves is as good as murder!
Just tear it and throw it out. If they're serious about it, they'll write another one.
It's not your fault.
How can you say that?!
Yu, hurry up and find someone
to help search for those two!
The "Peace Sign" has power
beyond the biker community!
That "V" belongs to everyone involved—
it's the sign of their trust, unity, and victory!
Hey, don't point that at me!
You'll go on more journeys yet.
But if you abandon them,
those two will have no future left!
People who abandon others
always end up feeling miserable themselves,
abandoned by everyone.
Please, Yu.
Uphold the good name of the bikers.
He's right. Let's go!
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Speed
control
point
Mr. Policeman!
Ah? You can go along.
Not gonna happen!
Huh?
Well, I'll be. He got caught too?
That's beside the point!
Do you have any idea how far
over the speed limit you were going?!
You can cry or you can weep,
but you get a red ticket!
Do you think of yourself
as a traffic light or what?!
But look, enforcing the speed limit
is also an important...
Take a look!
Human lives are at stake!
Do you want that couple
to commit a double suicide?!
You should help me find them ASAP!
Nishimachi Speed ​​Control Unit
to headquarters.
Headquarters copy.
What happened? Over.
Right. This is Ohno, traffic department.
We have an emergency.
A young man and woman
wrote a suicide note.
The man is Sasaki Yasuo,
the woman is Hirakawa Noriko.
A double suicide is in the cards.
Organize an immediate search operation.
Our unit is immediately relieved from speed control duty and switched to search mode.
Over!
Thank you, Chief!
But it's not going to be easy...
A whitish car alone isn't much of a clue.
I saw that car too.
Ah! The ramen sponger!
The couple who took a pic
just before we went to eat, right?
They drove slowly for about five kilometers,
so I easily overtook them,
and they never caught up until I got stopped here.
Do you know him?
Yeah... Sort of.
I know! There's a lake
about two kilometers down the road.
Maybe that’s where they went,
to drown themselves in the lake?
I haven't thought of that!
That’s a code five-one-five,
subparagraph five-two...
What are you waiting for?!
Hurry up and start up your patrol cars!
Ah... Right.
Only me and the four-eyed one know
what our poor lads look like.
You in the cars, follow us!
But be quick, I'm not gonna wait for you!
Are you stupid?
What if your siren spooks them and they rush to kill themselves when they hear it?
What's wrong with you?
I-I suppose...
S-So neat...
Our bikes are from the same 250 cc class,
but his two-stroke is way faster!
There it is!
Lake Nakajima
That's the one!
With the Shinagawa plate!
Yeah. That's gotta be it!
What's the matter?
Well, you see...
Hey pops! Which part of the lake
has the best view of the sunset?
Hey! Why not just ask where those two went?
If I had to die with my woman,
I'd choose to die while watching the sunset!
T-Touche...
A lovers' suicide?
The place to die has to be perfect!
If I was to die alone,
I'd throw myself in the nearest ditch,
but if I had to take a woman with me,
I'd feel sorry for the lass
if we didn't pick the prettiest spot for it.
Well, that smaller island's
gotta be the top pick for the evening.
Maybe that's where your lovebirds are.
How do we get there? Which way?
You could go down the forest path
and follow the shore.
But it should be faster to go downhill
and take a boat from the boathouse.
Come to think of it, there was a couple
who headed to the boathouse.
Yes, an hour or so ago...
I'll take the forest path.
I think I can get there
in ten minutes on my bike.
Good. Put that off-road power to use.
All right, and we'll take the boat!
Yeah. And don't forget
the underwater lights and flares.
Do you have any in your patrol car?
Worst case scenario, we'll need to guide the ambulance copter to the island!
Let's go now!
Yes. It's as he says.
Can I count on you?
All right.
That was one hell of a shock.
It bottomed out!
Over there. Just a bit more!
All right...
It's not even a meter wide.
But if I need to look around the island,
I can't leave my bike here!
All right... Second gear.
Shoulders relaxed.
Grip tightly with knees...
Calm down, Yu!
Start!
I wonder if someone found the note.
We'll both fall asleep
peacefully and painlessly.
Maybe that's the blue train
that takes you to heaven?
I have no regrets.
I'm not scared of anything if I'm with you.
Come on, at this rate we'll be late!
You can row instead of me if you want!
That's your job as a civil servant!
I sure hope that bud
makes it there fast enough.
Don't let us down, off-road!
Scary!
But I have to keep on pushing!
If I slip up now, two lives will be lost!
Goodbye, Little Fox.
Need to get there in time...
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't die, please.
Death is not the answer.
You found the note, didn't you?
You even crossed that flimsy
makeshift bridge to save us?
Even though it's not your concern...
It is my concern.
I took your commemorative photo.
For us bikers this sign alone is enough
to help out one another—no words needed.
Just because we didn't talk,
doesn't mean I don't care about you.
And it doesn't matter
that you're not bike riders either.
We wanted to see that photo when it's done.
Huh?
Nori-chan, why don't we try
talking to my dad again?
If he still forbids me to marry you,
I'll cut ties with my family. Okay?
Yasuo-san...
He probably thinks I won't have the nerve
since I grew up in luxury.
It'll be fine.
Together, we'll figure something out.
No, I'm sure we'll make it.
Noriko...
Yasuo-san!
V!
I can't believe it!
Why won't you row more lively?
And because you didn't adjust to me,
we ended up going in circles, you twit!
Maybe you're right, but I'm done already...
We got in touch with your father.
He made quite the fuss, begging us
not to let you two die, you know.
Isn't he a nice dad?
It even prompted him to rethink
and allow for you two to marry.
Yasuo-san...
Nicely done, off-road!
Glad to know I didn't ride
on the drums for nothing.
However, your father
put forth his conditions.
Huh?
You must not take your time and bless him with grandchildren as soon as possible.
And I'm not even going to ticket you for speeding
if you decide to follow through on that.
Um... I'm in a bit of a hurry
so I hope you don't mind me going first.
I wish you all the best
and a happy marriage...
Let's go now.
Right, we'll be going. Bye...
Don't worry about it! Hurry up!
That was close. In the general confusion,
I managed to slip away from a red ticket!
Really, so that's why
you were so worked up?
We saved two lives today.
I'm sure the traffic department chief
had forgiven you already.
Y-You think so?
Then what about you blanking
then going ballistic the next moment?
Blanking?
My bad, my bad.
I'm Ogata Goichi.
I'm Shinozaki Yu.
So, shall we go?
Yeah.
Wait you two! You forgot to give us
your names and addresses.
It's "Passerby Bikers!"
Peace!
Ah... Hey, wait!
Don't worry.
I noted down their plates.
We’ll contact them later
about their life-saving commendation.
Ah, is that so? Age and experience
really make a difference.
What?
No! It's nothing...
The night breeze of Hokkaido
sure feels good!
What are you saying?
It's almost winter in Tohoku. Hurry up!
Right...
Left O'Clock!!
Me and Goichi,
who made a U-turn from Hokkaido,
made a detour through the Sea of ​​Japan
and landed at Niigata.
In only two months
Niigata will be covered in snow.
Just like the migratory birds,
we're heading to the south.
Niigata Station
Niigata City
Chapter 4
Gamma Express
Proprietress, I'll have another bowl!
And don't spare any condiments!
Coming up!
Here, bon appetit.
Your appetite is already monstrous.
It's getting cold outside!
We gotta heat ourselves up
to counteract it.
You always have a good excuse.
You and your gamma are alike—
one eats food, the other fuel,
but both run best when they’re full.
Quit flattering me!
Shall we get going?
It really is getting cold—
the engine barely starts on the first try.
I suppose...
Ah, humans too!
Hey, any plans for this Sunday?
Wanna go somewhere?
Really, Yu? You're into schoolgirls?
That's not what I meant! I'm just saying that everyone is dressed up in winter clothes.
Well, you're not wrong there.
A uniform, huh?
Aoi-chan and the other discipliners aren't having it easy...
Hm?
Who's that lass?
Aoi-chan or whatever.
Yes, she's a discipliner at my...
Whoa there!
Let me try to guess first.
I'd say, not exactly a girlfriend, rather...
Has the flame died out between you two?
She's just my childhood friend!
Why, that just means you will keep
blowing hot and cold over and over again
The machines are more sensitive
to seasons than us.
Oi! Don't change the subject.
Have you written her a letter yet?
No...
Called her?
Not really.
You're not a good lover, you know!
She's just a childhood friend,
can't you hear?!
Well, that's not the only way
to tell when a man falls in love.
More importantly, haven’t you at least called your family once all this time?
Well I send postcards
to my sister sometimes...
But that's a one-sided connection! You gotta listen to what they have to say sometimes.
I don't have a family, so no one's gonna worry
about where I am or how I'm doing.
I don't need it.
I know they're fine.
Your big sister sounds like a kind lass.
I wonder if she was
doting on you and spoiling you.
C'mon, Yu.
What are you thinking?
You even got Papa to send me here
to give you a proper smacking.
Ugh?
I really don't wanna miss
the lecture at 9 today.
Sorry, but I need to be in my seat before the lecture hall is full.
I guess...
I bet she's also driving
a European compact car.
That's right, it must be something like Audi.
She has a long hair,
curling down from her shoulders...
Wearing traditional Japanese clothes...
No doubt about it,
she’s definitely not the type to think of straddling an off-road bike and going trekking!
So? Isn't that right, Yu?
All right, I guess I will call them.
They might get uneasy
if I disappear for too long.
Shino zaki
Yes, this is Shinozaki.
Ah, yes.
Huh?
Wh-What did you say?!
Line is busy.
I got excited for nothing.
You're weird, mate.
What's there to be scared of?
Uh, I guess you're right, I shouldn't get worked up calling my own family.
Okay, one more try.
I sure hope it's not dad who's on the phone.
Yes, this is Shinozaki.
Ah, thank god!
Hey sis, it's me, Yuu!
Yu?! Where are you now?
Niigata?
Oh come on, you're still drifting in the boondocks?!
If I was you, I'd rush here!
Something happened to Aoi-chan!
What... Aoi-chan got in a traffic accident?!
Apparently, she saw someone on the street
and mistook them for you.
So she rushed to call out to them.
So... How is she?
She's not dead, right?
She doesn’t have any external injuries,
but she hit her head hard.
She's in coma due to a brain hemorrhage.
They're gonna operate on her at 5:30, but there might not be enough blood for a transfusion.
She’s AB type, and they don’t have much of that blood type in stock.
I'm type A and her family is no good either.
They're calling her classmates for help now,
but they haven't had much luck.
I'm type AB!
But you're in Niigata!
And even if you do come,
you can't donate more than 400 cc.
Don't worry, Yu.
I’ll team up with other uni students,
and we’ll gather 10 or even 20 liters in no time.
It'll be fine.
Okay, I gotta hurry and start calling them now. I’m hanging up.
Ah... Hello?
Damn it... Damn it,
why does it have to be like that?!
I have the same blood type
but I can't help in any way!
Who cares about 400 cc?
They can take all of my blood for her!
All right... Let's go, Yu!
Huh?
If we take the Kanetsu Expressway,
from the Kurosaki Interchange to the Nerima exit,
it's 299 km.
Then it's 20 km more to Shinjuku hospital.
You can make it in 2.5 hours if you try.
That's not gonna work.
My Serow is not made for speed...
I know that already, you twit!
I never let others ride my baby,
but I'll lend it to you just this once!
You go there on my Gamma!
It's as your sister said—
you can donate 400 cc at most.
But those 400 cc could be
what ultimately saves her!
However, my Gamma is special—you're used to four-strokes, so you'll need to learn anew.
But they're both bikes, so what gi—
If you think so, you're dead wrong!
Ugh! I've no time to teach you now!
Just remember everything you’ve seen and heard from me since we left Soya,
and use it to your advantage!
C'mon, let's go!
Every minute counts!
Okay...
Niigata         toll         gate
With that Gamma, as long as you don’t let the revs drop below 8,000,
you won’t lose to anything under 750 cc.
Oi, bud! Make sure to bring her back!
Don't get killed!
The driving feeling is quite different
from my Serow.
Maybe it's the vibration?
That said, this two-stroke sure is fast...
I'll get used to this speed right away.
If I then floor it, I'll make it in time.
Ojiya?
Next is Echigo Kawaguchi.
55 km to the Shiozawa Ishiuchi Service Area.
It should take me about 30 minutes...
Once I pass Shiozawa, I won't be able to refuel
until the Akagi Kogen Service Area.
If one liter should last me 20 km,
I can just wait until Akagi to refuel.
Tokyo Medical University Hospital
Phone Corner
There's still time, will you come?
Make haste then.
I'll sign you up. Thank you.
Phone Corner
This makes 8 people.
We should have 3,200 cc total.
Yeah? Then come at once!
I'll be waiting!
5 people? That means
we'll have the 5 liters needed.
Ah, that's right.
There's also the student dormitory!
Phone Corner
I'll try to secure some surplus too.
The Gamma’s gas tank holds 17 liters.
If you drive normally,
you can squeeze out
45 km per liter without refueling.
However, if you really rev it up,
the fuel efficiency’s downright terrible.
You'll run faster than anyone in the world,
but you'll also run out of gas faster.
I could make two separate stops, but I'll probably save time if I fill it up all at once.
I'll try to make it...
Don't tell me you're out of gas!
Shiozawa Ishiuchi
Shiozawa Ishiuchi Gas Station
Welcome!
Excuse me, I'd like a full tank.
Got it!
17 liters?!
Are you kidding me?
17 liters per 126 km...
That fuel consumption is ridiculous!
You got 17.2 liters.
That'd be 2,125 yen including tax.
Excuse me?
Yeah...
We refueled before the Kurosaki gate,
so I rode for about 130 km.
That means... under 8 km per liter!
Yes, thank you!
Do you have a hole
in your gas tank or something?!
That was a close call...
This won't be easy!
One full tank amounts to less than 130 km.
This means I can't ride all the way to Takasaka
without refueling in Akagi or Kamisato.
Goichi strapped me onto a terrible bike!
That idiot and his idiotic appetite!
If I rev it up this much...
I see.
This also means more time lost refueling.
Shoot! I have to choose between time and gas!
I still have around 200 km to go.
And I haven’t even pushed it past 120 km/h yet.
All right!
The asphalt of the city shines after the rain,
the center line is dyed in the evening glow
Wow! What's this acceleration?
What's going on!
Goichi, you dumbass!
I'll never forget your gentle eyes,
your silhouette waving to me
Don't be afraid, Yu.
My Gamma will only truly start to shine now.
Past 8,000 revs, she's real rocket!
Whenever I'm swept away by the flow of time,
I come back stronger,
pushing harder the accelerator of my heart
100... 170 km/h?
I’ve maxed out the speedometer!
I'm gonna crash!
Right now Ride on Heart
to the unreachable tomorrow
Ride the wind and spread your wings
The f-front wheel...
Then you realize Ride on Heart
What if not the words
can prop up your dreams?
Huh? What's up with you?
The difference is enormous.
An explosive power kicks in past 6,000 revs.
Meanwhile, there's barely
any torque at low revs.
It really is a two-faced engine,
like Jekyll and Hyde!
I-I'm scared!
I swear I'll never
ride it again!
I have about 170 km to go.
There's no time to spare!
I'll complain about it some other time!
I need to deliver my blood to Aoi-chan by 5:30!
Once again Ride on Heart
If you just give up,
I'm coming, Aoi-chan!
Lights on in the tunnel
Nothing will come out of it
Thrilling Ride on Heart
As soon as your cross into the off-road
the smile won't leave your face
Once again Ride on Heart
If you just give up,
Nothing will come out of it
Thrilling Ride on Heart
As soon as your cross into the off-road
the smile won't leave your face
Yu must be terribly worried by now.
Maybe I shouldn't have told him?
There's nothing he can do from Niigata.
Well, just call him again once the surgery is over.
Don't worry, look how much we've gathered.
Shinozaki-san?
Ah... Yes?
You've secured enough blood already.
We're all set.
Thank god!
We are truly grateful
to everyone who came to help.
You've gathered so much
for our daughter...
Um...
Hm?
Yu!
Please take my blood too.
I have AB type.
But it was only around 2:30
when you called from Niigata!
It's 5:00 now, so he got here from Kurosaki in only 2.5 hours!
That’s Moe’s little brother for you!
He must’ve kept it floored the whole 300 km!
But you seem too fatigued
for the procedure...
Please...
You should take his blood as well.
Even if it's only 100 or even 50 cc.
He’s Yu—the boy Aoi-chan
kept calling out to in her delirium.
My brother risked his life to carry
it to her over 300 km—please, take his blood!
C'mon, be a sweetheart!
What do you have to lose?
This way, please.
Operation in progress
Aoi-chan...
It was a complete success.
She'll recover with no lasting effects.
Thank you ever so much, everyone.
Yu-kun, you have my deepest gratitude.
Ah... It's nothing...
Oh, how happy Aoi will be
when she hears about it!
N-No, I mean...
It was the power of your love for Aoi-san.
Hey, Moe!
Here, black coffee.
Oh, thank you.
Tetsuo-san had one with milk.
No, I also chose black today.
Oh? How very unusual.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I was expecting you to come.
And if I didn't come?
I’d cut ties with you.
We wouldn’t be siblings anymore.
That alone is enough of a reason
to beeline back.
That was quite the fright.
Whoever takes you in as his wife
must be tough as nails.
Ah! I hope you don't seriously mean it.
Don't mind me.
Good to know.
So this is it? The Gamma that Goichi gave you to help you make it in time?
Oh... You're lucky that you had her
to make that journey on.
This is no ordinary RG250 Gamma.
It’s an early production model,
with performance nearly as good as a racer.
In other words,
it's closer to a professional vehicle.
Moreover, the exhaust system and suspension
are apparently tuned for racing.
Just looking at her, I feel like I can understand the character of that guy Goichi who is riding her.
I bet that was scary. You’ve never ridden a four-stroke before, huh?
When I first revved mine up,
it scared me shitless.
Yeah. But it's amazing once you get used to it.
With a two-stroke, it's like the controls
are wired directly to your nerves.
The throttle response is like night and day
compared to a four-stroke.
I wonder if that's what a lighter frame does?
I can't deal with this crooked bike...
Here. Try it now.
And now you come back
on a two-stroke Gamma!
But hey, how much gas did it guzzle?
That, I can't tell you!
That much was to be expected.
Women only care for the size of your wallet...
What was that?
No, nothing...
Well, I shouldn't keep Goichi waiting.
H-Hey, hold it! You're leaving already?
That's so inconsiderate!
Sorry.
All right. But you’d better
ride carefully on your way back.
I know. The fatigue from the ride out
is catching up to me.
Besides, this return trip
isn't for some life-threatening reason.
Yes.
That's what I was saying.
Yuu, what should we tell Aoi-chan
when she wakes up?
Tell her, "Peace!"
Well then.
Give my thanks to Goichi-kun!
Do your best!
And off he went.
He's different now...
That's right.
He seems to be more resolute now.
Yes, but besides that... it's his eyes.
His eyes have life in them.
Nothing like when I was
seeing him off in the summer.
You could say he has the eyes
of someone experienced.
Why are you saying something so cheesy?
Well, even though it technically went according to my plan, I'm still a little worried.
All right, let’s work together
to get you full marks on the next test!
Whoops!
My bad, my bad.
Kanetsu Expressway
Nerima Entrance
Aoi-chan, though it's still a one-way connection, I wish you well.
In just a little while, I'll be back.
Exposed to the wind, I gaze blankly
at the familiar hustle and bustle of the town
Leaning on my shoulder,
still innocent, your tired neck
It's just the two of us
When we gaze at each other
on a casual morning,
love is always, always there
Because I believe,
and now, Good Luck & See You Again
Raw
Translation / TS
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
True Noobow Gamer