Bank of Japan Note - 10,000 Yen
With Pictures
An Introduction to Japanese Economics
While just passing by,
Suddenly we meet
Meguriai surechigau
Just like headlights of this familiar city
That come and go
kono machi o ikikau Headlight
Once you had a dream
Anata no yume
That I failed to live up to
tsumetaku kawashita
To this day, I repent of what I did
ano toki no watashi o
During the times we spent together
kuyande shimau
Ah, once upon a time,
When the fate brought us all together
Ah once upon a time hito wa dare mo min'na
That was not to make us hurt each other
kizutsuku tame ni deau wake janai no
Thank you for your love
Even if we had to part once,
We'll meet again somewhere
Dokoka de aeru to wakaretakedo
I came to realize -
Tomodachi ni mo
Until the end of times,
koibito ni mo
Friends or lovers once
Can never return to being them again
modorenai koto dake wakatte ita
Episode 1
Japan-USA Trade Frictions
Welcome, Matsumoto Sawako!
Is she really coming on that flight?
Ah... Greeting people at the airport is just not my thing.
Shouldn't have agreed to this job.
Are you the Taihei Finance representative?
Yes...
I'm Matsumoto Sawako.
I'm so glad you decided to start your career at Taihei!
Leaving behind many of our male employees,
you now qualify as a super-elite, with a huge advantage
of graduating abroad from Harvard Business School!
I've never met someone so amazing!
Not only that, you got a Master's degree
in Business Administration - MBA!
Not to mention the astounding success that the launch
of Hayate Motor Company's first factory in the U.S. had been!
I can't stress it enough how much I admire you!
I wonder what happened, it's not even the rush hour yet.
Ma'am, these days,
this part of the city is constantly like that.
I see... It'll take a little longer than expected.
Yukie, I feel like walking the rest of the way on feet.
Let's get off here.
Detroit, Michigan. October 1980.
This year, the American automobile industry output
experienced a sharp decline,
compared to last year's 11,480,000.
Thus, the "number one in the world" position
was yielded to Japan.
The U.S. had to content themselves with being number two.
We're boycotting the Japs!
That's right! We won't tolerate no dumping!
Exactly!
The government must immediately
impose import restrictions!
We'll take our jobs back by force!
It's a Japanese car!
Show 'em what we think of it!
Let's flatten the Jap car!
Right, right!
Let's get it!
Here I go!
Watch out!
Central Motor Company chairman, Hoffman
It's me. Put me through to Washington.
Hoffman's play is pretty obvious.
General Manager of the President's Office, Showa Motor Co., Ltd.
He is scheming to stir a commotion big enough
for Washington to start feeling the pressure.
CEO, Showa Motor Co., Ltd.
Consequently, this pressure is projected on our government,
who would eventually cave in to export self-restrictions.
And if it looks like we are restricting exports
of our own free will,
that would serve to deliver us
from any political or legal repercussions.
And once the restrictions are imposed, the foreign market
would distinctly feel the shortage of Japanese cars.
Without a doubt, prices will also rise.
Naturally, it's what Hoffman is aiming for.
If the prices go up, the sales of the Japanese cars go down.
In turn, Central Motor Company, currently on the skids,
would be able to catch a breath.
So it's only a stopgap measure, after all.
Those guys are too busy
playing their zaitech-like money games.
Meanwhile, their production facilities
are neglected and operate ancient tools.
If you compare the number of personnel
needed to produce a single car,
the aggressive optimization had allowed us to reduce it
to less than one-third of what they need, and it's not over yet.
Those fellows are spooked by every smallest trifle.
It's a problem.
But a self-restriction inevitably entails
a local production, right?
Correct. The workers' demand
of getting employed has to be met.
Until then, the unrest would only grow more rabid.
Sir, our rivals at Kostar Motors
are steadily ramping up their preparations.
And the Hayate, following next,
have already switched to local production this year.
For our company, too...
Still, we're facing the same old problem as before, aren't we?
What I mean is, just like we always do at times like this,
we should take a plunge for a decisive surgical action.
Business Headquarters Office
The self-restrictions are finally places.
The government couldn't hold out any longer.
They set the next year's estimate
at only 1,680,000 cars produced?
Well, that was a one-sided battle all along.
Anyway, I'll go report it to the department chief.
Ouch...
Are you blind...
Department chief! We have just received a telex...
Self-restrictions, right?
Just now, I've received a call
from the executive director of Hayate Motor Company.
Oh, I see...
Matsumoto, at Hayate, they're extremely grateful
for your mediation in arranging their local production.
Oh... But all I did was provided
some superficial assistance on the spot.
You can be infinitely humble,
but Hayate consider your early prediction
of such a turn of events,
as well as your advice
of taking a plunge with local production,
a testimony to your extremely keen foresight.
It gave them no less than 2 or 3 years of advantage
over two other major companies - Showa and Kostar.
Well, have you ever seen a woman studying abroad,
let alone in Harvard Business school?
I'd wager their appreciation lies with this fact alone.
Manager, what is that "where have you seen a woman" talk?!
Yukie...
At any rate, the said Showa Motor Co.
had also made contact with us.
Eh? Showa did?
They'd like to hear a straightforward lecture from you,
recounting all the difficulties Hayate had,
when opening a local production plant.
Which means Showa are also starting
to seriously consider the possibility of local production..?
Their intentions are unclear.
Mikawa and Matsumoto,
on the evening of Saturday, would you be able
to meet with their Manager of the President's Office?
Terribly sorry, but on Saturday, I'm tending
to some personal matters in Kyoto, therefore I can't.
Hey! Goyo Trading are effectively running a monopoly now.
This is our chance to snatch Showa
from under their noses!
In here, I have everything pertaining
Hayate's local production, documented and arranged.
Consulting this notebook,
should sate their curiosity to a sufficient extent.
Kyoto
It all turned out exactly according to my calculations.
Soichiro Funaoka, Professor at the Institute of Economic Research,
University of Kyoto. (Sawako's mentor)
If the self-restrictions are imposed,
the Japanese cars will rise in price by an average of $2,000.
Thus, even if the exports fall, that increase in price
would be enough to cover our losses.
No, we might even end up profiting from this.
And then, the American car makers
would also jump on the bandwagon, increasing prices.
In the end, it's the ordinary American customers
who would suffer the most losses?
Well, more or less so.
It'll become a textbook example
of a joint U.S.-Japan cartel.
But I shouldn't think it'll be a lasting enterprise.
What do you mean by that?
The exchange rates...
After 1970, the American foreign trade balance
turned into a deficit.
Surplus      Deficit
Japan-USA Foreign Trade Profitability Chart
Blue chart - Japan
Billions of dollars
Red chart - USA
Since then, with every year passing,
the deficit had been deepening.
Year
(Note) Vertical axis is represented by a logarithmic function
(Source) Nomura Research Institute "Business World Observation May 1984"
At the same time, the budget deficit
had also been worsening.
So to fill this void somehow,
they relied on loans from other countries.
But as you well know,
a loan is something you pay back with an interest.
Yes.
As a result, the American foreign debt
cannot be paid back now,
without printing out dollars, the world's currency
in ridiculous amounts so as to cover the interest rates.
I.e. we'll see an outflow of dollars.
As a result, the dollar would depreciate,
entailing a major shift in the exchange rates.
With yen strengthening against the dollar?
Correct. One dollar, currently traded for about 200 yen,
will then drop to under 170 yen if not less.
And the decline might not end there.
But if that turns out to be the case,
Japan would be in favor
of switching to local production in the U.S., right?
That's what I'm getting at.
And then, the main issue becomes...
The surge of domestic unemployment?
The subcontractors are probably going
to be hit the hardest by that change.
If you're doing this research for Showa,
you might be interested in records on subcontractors, right?
Are you...
Archives department chief, Yuki.
Ah, I apologize...
I never stopped by to sell hello
and just helped myself to it...
I work in Business Headquarters...
Matsumoto Sawako, isn't that right?
Yes...
You've already been introduced to me via a proxy.
Yukie...
Actually, I always come here when I need a break.
Oh!
In the late 70s, I also had the experience of dealing with
frictions, pertaining the foreign trade of color TVs.
We'll be in dire straits,
if we switch to local car production, right?
Yes...
Actually, if that helps, would you like me
to get you the records on color TVs local production?
Those would be of great service to me!
Now, where was it...
Yukie, what kind of person Yuki is, exactly?
The guy who's a thousand times as sharp as our Manager.
Although people said he had
a bright future waiting for him,
it seems, he had to take the blame
for something unfortunate
and was made into a window-starer,
removed from the line of promotion.
Two years after the self-restrictions were imposed.
Because the price of Japanese cars rose,
The American industries have also been able
to ramp up the prices.
The performance of the imperiled Central Motor Company
also began to improve.
Then, as the yen rose because of the changes
in the American monetary policies,
Central Motor Company Shareholders' Meeting
the price of Japanese cars also rose once again.
...and so, I'm proud to announce that the unjust
yen depreciation, low wages, long working hours,
government protectionism,
and other foul means the Japanese used for profiteering
were subjected to international criticism.
Japan was left no choice but to radically alter its ways.
But above all, the dollar-yen exchange rate
is approaching a reasonable level.
It is weakening the competitiveness of Japanese cars.
In time, it will create conditions,
where their manufacturers have no choice, but to step forth
and switch to local production in our country.
If the battle is in the U.S.,
the prospect of losing it is nonexistent for us.
Furthermore, I expect
that large quantities of our "Central" cars
would soon comprise a significant part
of our exports to Japan!
We're not amused!
Moving the factories to the U.S.
would only result in unemployment!
Showa Motor Co. Workers Union President
Katsutoshi Sato
For us, simple workers,
it's all harm and no gain!
Be firm in your opposition,
for the sake of our union's survival!
Don't let them steal our jobs!
Not in a thousand years,
we'll be the martyrs to the trade frictions!
Isn't that right, gentlemen?!
At the board meeting this morning,
our company had made a decision
towards switching to local production in the U.S.
Therefore, we ask you,
Goyo and Taihei representatives,
Goyo Trading Business Headquarters
General Manager Gondo                   Kunio Tsugawa
to come up with an optimal strategy
for organizing our local production.
I'd like you to consider all the possibilities.
Huh. Must be you're trying to make fun of us.
What the interest in competition,
when your opponent is a softie girl fresh out of school?
Tsugawa, please watch your language.
Okay...
Toda, we hope you don't go too hard on us this time.
No, we're the ones hoping you don't go too hard.
Do you mind if I ask just one thing?
Please do.
Labor unions problem,
what do you intend to do about them?
You can trust us to deal with that issue
and devote yourself fully to developing the strategy.
Goyo's Gondo is the one with the bitter record
of repetitively making fun of us.
This time, we must do our utmost to best those guys.
Department chief, please trust me to deal with this.
Anticipating this kind of a scenario -
Hayate consulting us about factory relocation,
I had already secretly drawn up a strategy!
Oh, that's pretty handy.
I'll present them with a revolutionary idea
of taking over local plants.
Just let me draw up a report,
you'll see everything yourself!
Sounds good. Matsumoto,
what's your plan on dealing with this assignment?
I thought I'd start with a research
on subcontractors' situation.
Subcontractors?
What use you think will come out of it
at this stage?
If you have nothing better to do with your time,
you should rather come help with my work!
With all due respect to your idea,
Goyo Division are likely to have already made
necessary arrangements regarding potential candidates.
But if we take a non-standard approach now,
Showa would be more inclined
to favor us in the future.
I believe, it's the only way to ensure that.
Indeed, we also have to deal with the pressing issue
of deciding how to dispose of parts subcontractors.
I got it. I want you to also draw up a report
in the nearest time.
Okay.
Use as much money as you need.
Don't be picky with methods.
Just see to it that our cover isn't broken.
Make every possible precaution about that.
I know that much.
Tsugawa, we two have quite the history
of doing business together.
With only union backing him, Sato already has the ambitions
to run for the upper house of the Diet.
We just need to get hold of a good scandal about him.
Or fabricate one.
Whoa, whoa, now it's really heating up, isn't it?
Yeah...
After building up our trust with Showa for all that time,
no way I give them up to the likes of Taihei.
Ever since the self-restrictions were placed,
the plant had not expanded an inch.
And our future prospects are also less than bright.
Because of the strengthening yen, right?
After everything Showa have done for us,
speaking ill of them is the last thing I'd wanna do...
But we always end up being the ones to feel the crunch.
That may very well be true.
Currently, Showa are seriously considering
switching to local production in the U.S.
Ah... What was it just now?
You can't be serious!
I'm told the Showa's labor union
is vehemently opposed to it.
And now they're readily accepting it?
Yes... It appears so, for the moment.
But then, even if they build the assembly line over there,
what would they put on it, without the Japan-made parts?
It's us, the small subcontractors,
who make the Japanese cars so great and affordable!
Do you suppose they'll make us
send the parts there all the way from Japan?
That would've been reasonable, but...
They're about to reinstate a law that says,
unless over 50% of the car,
including parts, is made locally,
it's still considered an import.
But if that happens...
What do they suppose will become
of little companies like mine?
It can't be... I'm obviously too old to immigrate now!
Matsumoto, for the subcontractors,
this is a matter of life and death!
Isn't it within Taihei's power to create some new job for us?
A new work for car parts manufacturers...
Taking over a poorly managed local company?
That's a gutsy plan, if I do say so myself.
Mikawa, if we choose your approach,
this job would call for some sharp practice.
Without going that far,
we'll never be able to win Showa over!
Especially if it results in a cheapest plan of all!
That may well be true,
but it also means
a huge initial investment would be required.
If Showa fall short of the investments required,
our company could look after them with our own funds.
And then, our company could also use it
to do business there.
Boy, are you meticulous.
Alright, fly to U.S. immediately
and secure the property for us.
Got it!
Matsumoto, you got something to offer too?
Yes. I was curious:
once Showa relocate their production to the U.S.,
how would they supply the car parts there?
In particular, my research was focused
on how would subcontractors weather that storm.
So, what were your conclusions?
A few years ago, we had similar trade frictions over color TVs.
During those, the Japanese manufacturers
were also unanimously switching to local production.
As a result, the export of color TVs to the U.S.
is now virtually nonexistent.
Electrical appliance manufacturers
moved everything abroad, including their parts divisions.
However, the subcontractors that were left behind
still made it through with little trouble.
Oh?
But that was because the lines
that were previously making TVs for the U.S.
could be effortlessly converted to VTR production lines.
In the form of VTRs,
a terrific pinch hitter had entered the field.
Are you saying that no such pinch hitter
can appear in the automobile industry?
Exactly. Cars use considerably more parts than TVs.
The numerous subcontractors also vary in size and obviously enough, cannot all follow the parent company abroad.
You were proactively urging Hayate
to commit to the local production.
Yet for Showa, you're skeptical about it...
By then, Hayate had much fewer subcontractors,
so they didn't run into a lot of trouble settling this.
I get it.
But then, have you any solution
for cutting this Gordian Knot?
Yes. Together with Yukie
and the archives department chief Yuki,
we can draw up a new business plan,
that'd facilitate a closer cooperation with the subcontractors.
I see. Please do that as soon as possible.
Okay!
A takeover of a local enterprise? I see.
Sounds very much like our Manager Mikawa.
But hey, stealthily buying out someone else's company...
Isn't it too high-handed?
Especially when you have no idea
how people working there would feel about it.
Chairman Sato!
After opposing it so vehemently,
how come you suddenly changed your stance?!
How do we explain this to the union members, who've always
been believing the management unquestionably?!
Well, I thought I explained this point to you
multiple times already.
Not even a trade union can exist in isolation
from the international economic environment.
What the... Don't tell me
you've made a shadow deal with the company!
How rude! One should know
what he can say and what he can't.
I think you'd be quite amused to see what's inside here.
What could it be?
Showa Motor Union chairman: spicy story!
This is a sham!
Too bad I couldn't care less whether or not it is.
But I bet a great many people would like
to see this jolly kind of article in the evening news.
After all, it's a scandal, concerning a big shot labor union chairman, aiming to run for the upper house of the Diet.
How is that not an attention grabber?
With all due respect to the Taihei company efforts,
it has been decided that the production lines expansion
would be conducted according to the plan
proposed by Goyo side, this time.
What did you say?!
Are you saying our plan was in some way deficient?
No, it wasn't exactly deficient. It's just...
"Just" what?
Both proposals involved a takeover of a local enterprise.
They were similar to the point where both
chose North Carolina as a destination.
Goyo chose a takeover, too?
The key difference was in the cost.
On the Goyo side, it was an agricultural equipment
manufacturer about to go bankrupt.
What...
So the Japanese company
that bought up this manufacturer's shares had been Goyo?!
Did it in the nick of time.
Well, regarding the alternative proposal...
The Subcontractors Strategy,
developed by Taihei's Matsumoto
was also deemed highly novel by our company's board.
Therefore, we hope for a productive future cooperation
with Taihei and their out-of-the-box analysis.
If you say it's so out-of-the-box,
you should start acting upon it ASAP.
Matsumoto, having helped myself to reading your report,
I'd like to subscribe to every word he said.
Showa are usually rather slow on the uptake,
so I'd rather have you working for us.
Gondo! We'd be in trouble if that happens.
Oh, it was just a "what if" soliloquy.
It was a bit hard to tell...
North Carolina, USA
I hear the company's new owners are Japanese.
They're going to turn this into an assembly plant
for Japanese cars. And they're going to keep us on.
I'd salute this new owner even if he's a monkey,
as long as I don't get laid off.
But I've heard that workers in Japan
are treated like slaves.
Aren't we all corporate slaves?
Well, if worse comes to worst,
we can appeal to the union. They'll do something about it.
Every time we rely on them,
we end up paying even more!
At any rate, we should let the Japanese know
that things won't be all that simple.
It's a shame Department Chief and Manager got overlooked,
but at least we know our efforts bore some definite fruits.
Sawako, let's have a big party tonight!
Yukie, nothing wrong with having a big party,
but really, this is a watershed moment
both for us and for the Goyo guys.
For Goyo too?
Right. Even after they get the factory going,
they'll only be able to talk about success when the cars
they make are no inferior to those assembled in Japan.
In the end, isn't it wonderful,
when people of different backgrounds,
languages, and skin colors work on them side by side?
I guess so...
However, a few years from now, when every single Japanese manufacturer switches to local production model,
there'll surely come a time when supply exceeds demand
and a surplus of cars will form.
Sawako,
I have a strong feeling
it'll be your turn to act once again.
I pray that your business style, born from considerateness,
remains forever this way!
IMF - The International Monetary Fund
evaluated the consequences of the restrictions,
placed from 1981 to 1984 on exports from Japan to the U.S.
A detailed summary of the damage incurred
by ordinary American consumers is as follows:
Over these four years, the prices of all new
American-made cars rose by an average of 50%.
Had export self-restrictions not been placed,
they place the expected increase in price to just 27%.
As a result of this, the combined amount of money
overpaid by the consumers was over $17 billion.
Converted to yen at the exchange rate of that period,
it's about 4 trillion yen.
Which makes it a trillion yen yearly.
In the next episode
The amount of money being traded on currency market
annually is $400 trillion.
With the yen rate violently fluctuating,
the eyes of the exchange dealers are glued to it.
Newly put in charge of the Exchange Consulting Subdivision,
Matsumoto Sawako
is also closely observing the corrections of the price.
Next time in the Introduction to Japanese Economics:
Exchange Game. Don't miss it.
Episode 2
Exchange Game
Driving down the midnight highway
Mayonaka no highway
Crossing through my memories
yokogitte yuku Memories
Just tonight, I ask you to be silent
Tada damatta mama ano hi~
Eye to eye, we stare at each other
Eye to eye mitsume teta
Some nostalgic love song
Natsukashī Love song
Slowly flowing out from the radio
nagareta From the radio
It's like fighting back
Tojikometa
this sadness, that's been locked away for long
kanashimi o tataku yō ni
Oh baby play for me!
Soul music
Sweet soul music
It's suffocating, let me hear it
setsunaku kika sete
Sweet soul music
I love you!
While you gently continue to sing
yasashiku utatte
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Raws by [unknown]