Bank of Japan Note - 10,000 Yen
With Pictures
An Introduction to Japanese Economics
While just passing by,
Suddenly we meet
Meguriai surechigau
Just like headlights of this familiar city
That come and go
kono machi o ikikau Headlight
Once you had a dream
Anata no yume
That I failed to live up to
tsumetaku kawashita
To this day, I repent of what I did
ano toki no watashi o
During the times we spent together
kuyande shimau
Ah, once upon a time,
When the fate brought us all together
Ah once upon a time hito wa dare mo min'na
That was not to make us hurt each other
kizutsuku tame ni deau wake janai no
Thank you for your love
Even if we had to part once,
We'll meet again somewhere
Dokoka de aeru to wakaretakedo
I came to realize -
Tomodachi ni mo
Until the end of times,
koibito ni mo
Friends or lovers once
Can never return to being them again
modorenai koto dake wakatte ita
Episode 2
Exchange Game
Chairman of the U.S. Federal Reserve Board (FRB)
FRB Chairman...
People say with this man's every move,
the world's money start moving, too.
Just fishing so leisurely...
The catch today - two large Rainbowfishes.
Our fishing enthusiast seemed in high spirits
and went to bed a little while ago.
Tokyo, August 31, 1985
Got it. No abnormalities for today.
Good job. But the overall situation
is rather complicated these days.
Don't take your eyes off him, ever.
Well, goodnight for now, Birdwatcher.
Among companies comprising the Taihei Group,
as well as small banks and insurance agencies
there exist a dire demand for a precise advice
on the future development of the currency market.
So for the time being, I'm thinking of creating
a currency market consulting subdivision.
I'd like to ask Matsumoto to become the project team chief.
You can organize the team entirely to your liking.
Oh?
Will this really turn out well?
Predicting stock prices
is a breeze compared to the currency market.
There's a metric ton of factors that you gotta see through.
Just being a math prodigy would get you nowhere.
Instead, the flair for collecting data
and rich imagination are your only friends.
Well, we're yet to find out whether or not
Matsumoto possesses any of those qualities.
But I'm looking forward to seeing what
a Harvard Business School alumni's got in stock for us.
Thank you very much, Manager.
With your encouragement, I'm ready to accept the fight.
Business Headquarters Conference Room
I hope you don't mind me
getting straight to the point.
Companies comprising the Group, as well as a few individual members were offered a newsletter for internal business use.
Alternatively, they were offered
a customer advice service on a case-by-case basis.
Yukie, do you have the data
on the applications for membership?
Yes.
Despite the newsletter subscription
costing 10,000,000 yen annually,
the quota of 30 companies had already been filled.
Additionally, quite a few businesses expressed a wish
to receive case-by-case consulting services.
Oh, so the demand was that dire?
Considering the money our customers paid for this,
we have to supply them with data of corresponding quality.
Which means, the slipshod stuff
circulating on the streets won't do.
Hmm.
So we have to adopt a method for gathering Intel
that is profound, covert and advanced all at the same time.
Precisely so.
For Intel, particularly that concerning the market,
the less people have access to them,
the more they gain in added value.
If it's something everyone around knows,
you can no longer really call it an "Intel," can you?
Yes.
Well then, why don't we divide the areas of responsibility?
First, I'd like Manager Mikawa to find out what line
Ministry of Finance and Bank of Japan authorities adhere to.
Ueda will be in charge of work with our clients,
particularly - specialized currency trading institutions.
Okay.
Date will connect to the operational network of our dealing room, so as to directly monitor the currency market.
As for myself, with Yukie as my personal assistant,
I'll be in charge of monitoring
the Market Circles of the foreign markets,
starting with FRB and the American Ministry of Finance,
to New York, London, Zurich, and so on.
Ministry of Finance and Bank of Japan?
Quite the challenging assignment.
It's particularly important that you keep a close eye
on Ministry of Finance Secretary's every move.
Secretary?
That's because he is closely acquainted to the FRB Chairman,
and there exist a strong sentiment
of mutual admiration between the two.
If they come up with something,
they'll start deviating from this line.
Excuse me, but what exactly is FRB?
Hey, you...
Ah?
How did you manage to get into
the Business Headquarters without knowing even that?
I'm sorry.
FRB is an abbreviation, standing for "Federal Reserve Board"
of the U.S., also commonly known as just "the Fed."
It acts as the highest financial regulatory organ in the U.S.,
deciding on the monetary policies and supervising banks.
So, it's the same thing as Bank of Japan?
Well, I guess you could say so. But the effect it has on the world stands in no comparison to that of the Bank of Japan.
Just look at the first picture in the file.
That is their Chairman.
People say with this man's every move,
the world's money start moving, too.
Oh?
May I add, Sawako sure signed up
for one complicated assignment.
Well, it's what makes her so amazing, I guess.
Is currency market really that complicated?
Naturally!
The foreign trade turnover is $3 trillion a year.
But the currency exchange turnover in this term alone
amounts to $40 trillion.
$40 trillion?!
Unlike in previous days,
when the exchange rate was determined mainly
by the current balance of foreign trade,
nowadays, even if the marked is still somewhat tied
to crude oil price fluctuations,
there are also interest rates, price index, GNP,
and even policy interventions that may all affect the market,
rendering it extremely unpredictable
even for savvy currency dealers.
So it's all about being an expert?
Seems like I won't be of much help at all...
It's not like you to be whiny about your shortcomings.
Actually,
there's an acquaintance of mine
working in the Dealing Room of the Taihei Bank.
Would you like a tour after this?
I think you'll learn a lot by observing
the currency market operation from the forefront.
Yes.
I hope you also let me keep you company.
Sawako?
Now, how did I know you'd try to escape to here?
I'm sorry!
Yuki, what you've been discussing just now - I also want
to know the currency exchange bank's perspective on this.
You should definitely let me join you.
Okay.
Because we receive 10,000,000 yen a year in consulting fees,
Aoba Mutual Bank
we make absolutely sure
we don't put our clients at a disadvantage.
However, what conclusions you draw from our Intel,
what actions you undertake
is defined entirely by your own investment strategy.
Aoba Mutual Bank Executive Director
That might hold true,
but in a rural bank such as ours,
the proficient bond dealers are not thick on the ground.
So when we see another bank
buying up American government bonds, so do we.
Even so, we've been able to do business
with relatively good profits up until now.
There exists a 5% interest rate differential
between Japan and the U.S.,
So when you invest the money
collected from Japanese depositors in the U.S.,
you can make a decent profit with just that.
However, if the dollar suddenly collapses, the estimated value
of the actual amount of yen we have on hands will plummet,
making all the previous profits disappear into thin air.
Ueda, do you believe such a thing could really happen to us?
Yes. I believe such turn of events to be quite possible.
However, when will the dollar appreciation correction take place,
what would be the extent of ensuing compensation,
how low will it eventually fall -
nobody can tell you that for sure.
Please don't say such callous things.
After all, we all here are truly counting on you, Ueda.
Ah...
One yours!
Two mine!
Got it, one yours!
Okay, one yours!
Two mine!
Roger.
Right, one mine!
Those "One" and "Two" they're shouting are units of dollars.
"One" means $1,000,000.
"Mine" means buying, "Yours" means selling.
Oh... What an amazing place!
It's like we're on a battlefield!
This place is relatively quiet right now.
As we get closer to 3:30,
buying and selling becomes more and more lively.
Just before the closing time?
Yes.
There's this thing called position regulation, limiting the number of positions the bank can retain overnight.
To adjust to that regulation,
the banks start selling and buying assets more actively.
Position?
The banks cannot just sell dollars indefinitely,
neither can they buy them indefinitely.
The general principle is, you buy back the dollars
that you sold, and you sell back dollars that you bought,
arriving to a square. In other words, the change
in the number of positions has to be plus-minus zero.
However, making it a complete zero is often impossible,
therefore, you're allowed to carry over to the next day
a limited amount of trading assets.
And what exactly is that amount?
Presently, it's fixed on $100,000,000.
The combined turnover of transactions made here
usually amounts to $1 billion daily.
So the sum you're allowed to keep overnight
is only a small part of it.
These days, because of the time difference,
somewhere in the world, the market always remains open.
So Tokyo's position can be succeeded by London.
Conversely, it allows for New York and Tokyo markets
to be in coordination, right?
Yes.
That's what a 24-hour Market System is all about.
We, currency dealers, don't have the luxury of being able
to relax our nerves, neither in the day nor at night.
So everyone working here
needs a recreational vacation once every 3 years.
This isn't right...
By the way, Nakayama, in your opinion, when will
the strong dollar correction take place, and in what form?
A leading question won't work on me.
I know the news.
You opened a currency market consulting department.
This was something you should tell me.
September 16th, 1985
4:50 P.M.
Due to the strong dollar policy we've been upholding
and the dollar appreciation,
the U.S.-manufactured goods
rapidly lose in international competitiveness.
It also delivered a heavy blow to our agricultural exports.
As a result, the streets are flooded with unemployed men.
Both from Japan and from Europe,
we hear one voice after another,
U.S. Treasury Secretary
calling for abolition of our high interest rates
and dollar appreciation policies.
If this continues, our re-election is jeopardized.
President of the U.S.
The policies must be abolished.
I need you to make some decision.
Arrange a meeting with the FRB chairman.
September 17th, 11:20 A.M.
Which means, the Ministry of Finance Secretary
doesn't have any trips abroad in this week's schedule?
Not just for this week,
but for the next month or so, nothing in it!
With that girl Matsumoto as its nucleus,
Taihei have put together a "Currency Market Project Team,"
Goyo Trading, Business HQ Manager's Office
and now they scurry about in gaudy agitation?
We've nothing to fear so far.
They're merely scavenging any data
lower ranks of the Ministry of Finance can give them.
Hm. It's typical time of the year for companies to run about,
paying the import fees on their earnings in dollar.
Well, it's best that we also keep an eye
on what the upper echelon is up to.
Got it.
September 17th, Tuesday, 1:05 P.M.
Yes?
Sawako, it's from the U.S. A collect call.
Okay.
Yes? Matsumoto speaking.
This is Birdwatcher.
It's midnight on my end.
Our Fishing Enthusiast acts a little strange,
so I thought I should let you know.
What did you say?
Every week, our Fishing Enthusiast
goes on a round trip to Washington.
So I reached out to the pilot of his charter plane.
Turns out, he doesn't have anything planned
for the upcoming weekend - from 21st to 22nd of September.
And then, when I tried to inquire with the company,
managing Fishing Enthusiast's mountain villa,
I learned that he might not come there again this season.
At least, that's how his wife put it.
Ah... So suspicious.
The river in that area only has the fishing season opened
until September 25th.
This week is his last chance.
It's unlikely that a maniac such as him would miss it.
Understood, thank you.
The long-awaited storm is finally here.
You really didn't have to call a meeting
so early in the morning.
I will start with the conclusions.
For our tomorrow's newsletter:
"Towards the end of this week,
a multinational group of high-ranking financial officials
would be very likely to come together for a meeting,
to discuss the currency questions."
Such would be the announcement that I came up with.
When putting together the fragmented info
that was coming our way,
such was the only conclusion I could potentially arrive to.
Wait a minute!
Neither the Ministry of Finance Secretary,
nor Minister of Finance​
not even the Bank of Japan President
have any plans to travel abroad.
Besides, in all the previous instances,
whenever a currency meeting was about to be held,
there had always been some kind of a sign beforehand.
If we would only draw conclusions from precedents,
wouldn't our business be ultimately pointless?
The opponent is acting with utmost care, so as not to let
the Market Circles get a smell of what's going on.
Hey... If you plan to steer it with great swings,
such as this news,
the vessel, which is our consulting business,
will turn to shipwreck in no time.
Just diving headlong without testing the waters...
Manager! In a highly volatile world that is the
currency market, which waters do you consider safe?
Instead of this, I'd like to ask you
to tighten observation on our targets.
Starting today, attach a permanent lookout
to the Ministry of Finance Secretary's house.
Ueda, I've read the newsletter!
September 19th, Thursday. 10:45 A.M.
Holding on to large quantities of American Government Bonds
would be dangerous through this weekend.
Taihei Group companies were only advised to do that,
but I really think it'd be better if you sell
at least half of your holdings and convert it to yens.
Eh... I see.
I trust your judgment
and will take a chance on your company's Intel.
But if some other Intel comes to light,
please be sure to let me know immediately!
For a small-size financial institution,
this is a matter of life and death.
Very well.
For the moment, we're making every effort
to back up that Intel.
September 20th, Friday. 11:40 P.M.
Tomorrow, I'm going out for a private game of golf, so you'll have to excuse me for not meeting you in the morning.
Finance Ministry Secretary's house
With a lovely Ginza lady as your opponent, by any chance?
Playing golf with a Ginza hostess? Hm. A fine diversion for a man of his position. Very well. Dismissed for tonight.
The guy from Goyo received a dismissal already.
Ueda, let's pull out, too.
But Sawako told us to peer our eyes into it
until the morning.
Hm! It's been two nights already,
that we had to spend in the car.
Feel free to rest while I observe!
Good night, then.
Oh? Manager!
Ah! Yuki-san!
Provisions for the front line.
About time!
Hide!
Eh? Did he just pack his luggage and left?
Suspicious...
It's best that you call Sawako now.
Came back to pick up his suitcase? Roger that.
Keep a lookout on that position.
September 21st, Saturday. 7:05 A.M.
According to Ueda's phone report,
both Minister of Finance and the Secretary
got into the car, wearing golf uniforms.
There's no doubt their destination is New York,
via Narita Country Golf Club.
I guess that settles it.
If it wouldn't have been for a glimpse of that suitcase,
you could really think they're going to play golf.
The only question now,
how would their final agreement look like?
A decrease in American interest rates would be discussed
first and foremost, there's no doubting that.
Because American interest rates are high, every other nation
is concentrating its investments on the U.S.
The result is dollar appreciation.
If they manage to reach a groundbreaking agreement,
it would mean all the nations involved
will try to manipulate the currency market in cooperation.
In other words, a simultaneous intervention?
September 22nd, Sunday. New York.
It became an impediment to many economics of the world,
so a correction to excessive dollar appreciation is needed.
The U.S. had already stepped up
with one possible countermeasure.
However, this proposal is contingent
on the agreement and cooperation
between the monetary authorities
of all countries concerned.
The upcoming conference should become a forum
for the most frank discussion of this issue.
Even the U.S. are taking it seriously this time?
G5 conference held at New York!
US corrects high interest rate policy!
Agreement on coordinated currency market intervention in developed countries!
Just before the last weekend, the Taihei Group
converted half of their dollar holdings into yen!
What have you been doing all this time?!
General Manager, I hate to echo your words,
but in all such occasions up until now,
defying the currency authorities intervention was
the common sense, as a lot more profitable thing to do.
I don't think even a G5 agreement has the power
to reverse the dollar appreciation trend in one fell swoop.
Do you mean to say, you,
who didn't sell the dollars last week, the Goyo Group,
were actually holding back
so as not to take unnecessary risks?
Thanks for all your trouble!
September 23rd, Autumnal Equinox Day. 1:15 P.M.
Just now, Chief of Taihei Bank Currency Market Nakayama
got a phone call from the Bank of Japan.
He's meeting someone at 3 o'clock,
in front of the fountain at the Hibiya Park!
Oh? The foreigners are busy at work,
even when it's national holiday in Japan.
It seems, Bank of Japan is also taking it seriously.
I imagine, the currency market tomorrow
will turn into a dogfight
between the speculators and the currency authorities.
Today, our Bank of Japan
is to proclaim an unprecedented market intervention.
September 24th, Tuesday. 7:45 A.M.
Yesterday, in New York, the New York Federal Reserve Bank,
together with the West German Federal Reserve
Bank of Japan, Foreign Currency Division Chief
delivered on their promise
and put dollar-selling intervention into practice.
As a result of that,
the yen rose from 242 yen to 225 yen at one point.
Today, our duty is to inherit that baton
and solidify the ongoing trend for the yen appreciation.
Even if the total turnover of intervention
exceeds the $1 billion mark, it doesn't concern us!
I want you to sell the devil out of it.
Okay!
The price is approaching 229 yen 70 sen.
The dollar is put under a surprisingly strong pressure.
The billing companies sure are having a field day after this.
Bank of Japan begins its first round of intervention
any minute now.
Ah! Gone up a bit!
Yeah. It's Bank of Japan.
Only about 10,000,000 dollars this time.
Oh?
The yen went down again.
On Sydney market that starts trading first, the dollar appreciation is also 3 yens above the New York's level.
This is quickly turning into a forced hand market...
231 yen 20 sen.
Even if the Bank of Japan directly intervenes,
it's no big deal at all.
Ueda, even though the G5 prediction turned out true,
the dollar market price hadn't gone down one bit!
This morning, I tried selling more dollars.
But shortly after, just in time for the morning
trade session closure, I bought them back!
Presently, the market is going through the stage
of probing into the authorities' preparedness.
The trend is definitely changing in the afternoon!
Is that true?
Is that something I can fully trust?
Selling dollars is the only way now!
Sir! It's back to the 230 yen level!
Apparently, the authorities
are not about to give up on sporadic injections.
Regardless of dollars bought,
they keep flooding the market with selling offers.
Finally, even the oil companies started selling!
They're anticipating the dollar depreciation?
All right! The mood has changed!
Sell!
Sell more! More! Sell it all out!
It's over, at 230 yen 10 sen.
Yen appreciation compared to pre-weekend level
is at 11 yen 90 sen!
I hope you make sure to repair this damage in the future!
This new enterprise of ours took off pretty well.
This time, even you couldn't help
taking your hat off to Matsumoto, I believe.
Yes.
This 24-hour lookout
over Ministry of Finance Secretary's house...
Even if I thought that was going a bit too far at first,
eventually, it turned out to be a decisive factor.
Cheers!
The total trading turnover today
was over $4.7 billion.
Nearly one-third of those dollars
were sold by the Bank of Japan.
Our Foreign-exchange reserves
amount to about $27.5 billion,
while the combined global stock trading turnover
adds up to $150-200 billion a day.
The way the system works these days, the currency's strength is defined by the whims of its market price.
That's about all I can say.
The market's greatest enemy
is the market itself, agreed?
Huh? Yukie, how can you know that?
If you make a monkey out of me,
you do it to all Business Headquarters members!
Eeeh?!
Next episode
Trying to take advantage of Vatican's vast funds,
Taihei Finance and Goyo Trading are working in secret.
Then, one day,
the intermediary, Da Vinci Bank President
is found dead, floating in the River Thames.
At last, Matsumoto Sawako made up her mind.
Next time, in Illustrated Introduction to Japanese Economics:
Internationalization of Finance.
Please looks forward to it.
Episode 3
Internationalization of Finance
Driving down the midnight highway
Mayonaka no highway
Crossing through my memories
yokogitte yuku Memories
Just tonight, I ask you to be silent
Tada damatta mama ano hi~
Eye to eye, we stare at each other
Eye to eye mitsume teta
Some nostalgic love song
Natsukashī Love song
Slowly flowing out from the radio
nagareta From the radio
It's like fighting back
Tojikometa
this sadness, that's been locked away for long
kanashimi o tataku yō ni
Oh baby play for me!
Soul music
Sweet soul music
It's suffocating, let me hear it
setsunaku kika sete
Sweet soul music
I love you!
While you gently continue to sing
yasashiku utatte
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Raws by [unknown]