Bank of Japan Note - 10,000 Yen
Illustrated
Introduction to Japanese Economy
We were just passing by,
When suddenly we met
Meguriai surechigau
Just like headlights of this familiar city
That come and go
kono machi o ikikau Headlight
Once you had a dream
Anata no yume
That I failed to live up to
tsumetaku kawashita
My doings of those distant days
ano toki no watashi o
Are still torturing me
kuyande shimau
Ah, once upon a time,
When the fate brought us all together,
Ah once upon a time hito wa dare mo min'na
There was no one who could tell
That it'll hurt so much
kizutsuku tame ni deau wake janai no
Thank you for your love
Even if we had to part once,
We'll meet again somewhere
Dokoka de aeru to wakaretakedo
I came to realize -
Tomodachi ni mo
Until the end of times,
koibito ni mo
Friends or lovers once
Can't return to being them again
modorenai koto dake wakatte ita
Episode 1
Japan-US Trade Frictions
Welcome, Matsumoto Sawako!
Is she really coming on that plane?
Ah... Greeting people at the airport is just not my thing.
I shouldn't have agreed to this assignment.
Did Taihei Finance send you?
Yes...
I'm Matsumoto Sawako.
I'm so glad you decided to start your career at Taihei!
Leaving behind many of our male employees,
you now qualify as a super-elite,
a Harvard Business School graduate!
I've never met someone so amazing!
Not only that, you got a Master's degree
in Business Administration!
And what an astounding success the launch
of Hayate Motor Company's first factory in the US was!
I can't stress it enough how much I admire you!
I wonder what happened, it's not even the rush hour yet.
Ma'am, downtown is always like that these days.
I see... It'll take us a little longer I guess.
Yukie, I'd like to walk the rest of the way.
Let's get off here.
Detroit, Michigan. October 1980.
This year, the American automobile industry output
experienced a sharp decline,
compared to last year's 11,480,000.
Thus, Japan ascended
to the "world's number one" position.
The US now had to be content
with being number two.
We're boycotting the Japs!
That's right! We won't tolerate no dumping!
Exactly!
Impose import restrictions! Now!
We'll take our jobs back by force!
It's a Japanese car!
We'll show 'em!
Let's flatten the Jap's car!
Right, right!
Let's get it!
Here I go!
Watch out!
Central Motor Company chairman, Hoffman
It's me. Put me through to Washington.
Hoffman's play is pretty obvious.
General Manager of the President's Office, Showa Motor Co., Ltd.
He is scheming to stir a commotion big enough
to put pressure on Washington.
CEO, Showa Motor Co., Ltd.
This pressure is then projected onto our government,
who would eventually cave in to self-restrictions.
Keeping the appearances of restricting exports
of our own free will,
would serve to avert
any future political and legal repercussions.
Self-restrictions and the shortage of Japanese cars
would put a considerable strain on the international market.
The prices will naturally rise.
Without a doubt, that's what Hoffman is aiming for.
If the prices go up, the sales of the Japanese cars go down.
In turn, Central Motor Company, currently on the skids,
would be able to catch a breath.
So it's only a stopgap measure, after all.
Those guys are too busy
playing their zaitech-like money games.
Meanwhile, their production facilities
are neglected and operate ancient tools.
If you compare the number of personnel
needed to produce a single car,
the aggressive optimization had allowed us to reduce it
to less than one-third of what they need, and it's not over yet.
Those guys are afraid of their own shadows.
It's a problem.
But self-restrictions would entail
switching to local production, right?
Correct. The workers demand jobs.
That wish has to be fulfilled.
Until then, the unrest is only going
to get more out of hand.
Sir, our rivals at Kostar Motors
are ramping up their preparations steadily.
Hayate, who followed suit,
also switched to local production this year.
If our company doesn't do the same...
Still, we're facing the same old problem
as before, aren't we?
What I mean is,
just like we always did during desperate times,
we should take a plunge and act decisively.
Business Headquarters Office
The self-restrictions are finally placed.
The government couldn't hold out for any longer.
They set the next year's estimate
at only 1,680,000 cars produced?
Well, that was a one-sided battle all along.
Anyway, I'll go report it to the department chief.
Ouch...
Watch where you...
Department chief! We have just received a telex...
Self-restrictions, right?
I just received a call
from the executive director of Hayate Motor Company.
Oh, I see...
Matsumoto, in Hayate, they greatly appreciate
your mediation in arranging their local production.
Oh no... All I did was provide
some minor on-site assistance.
I appreciate your modesty, but for Hayate,
your early forecast of this development,
alongside your advice
on taking a plunge with local production,
proved vital, as a testimony to your keen foresight.
It gave them nothing short of several years of advantage
over two other major companies - Showa and Kostar.
Well, it's not every day that you see a woman
who graduated from Harvard Business School.
I bet their fascination with you lies with this factor.
Manager, what's it to do with her being a woman?!
Yukie...
At any rate, Showa Motors
made contact again.
Eh? Showa did?
They'd like to hear a lecture
straight from the horse's mouth,
recounting all the difficulties Hayate had
when opening a local production plant.
Which means Showa are also
earnestly considering switching to local production?
Their intentions are unclear.
Mikawa and Matsumoto,
on the evening of Saturday, would you be able
to meet with their president's manager?
I beg your pardon, but on Saturday,
I'm tending to some personal matters in Kyoto.
Listen, you!
Goyo Trading is running a monopoly now.
This is our chance to snatch Showa
from under their noses!
In here, I documented all the details
pertaining to Hayate's production relocation.
This notebook should suffice to sate their curiosity.
Kyoto
It all played out according to my calculations.
Soichiro Funaoka, Professor at the Institute of Economic Research,
University of Kyoto. (Sawako's mentor)
If the self-restrictions are placed,
the Japanese cars will rise in price by an average of $2,000.
Thus, even if the exports fall, that increase in price
would be enough to cover our losses.
No, we might even end up profiting from this.
And then, the American car makers
would also jump on the bandwagon of raising prices.
In the end, it's the ordinary American customers
who would suffer the most?
Well, that's more or less it.
It'll become a textbook example
of a joint US-Japan cartel.
But I shouldn't think it'll be a lasting enterprise.
What do you mean by that?
The exchange rates...
After 1970, the American foreign trade balance
went into the red.
Surplus      Deficit
Japan-USA Foreign Trade Profitability Chart
Blue chart - Japan
Billions of dollars
Red chart - USA
Since then, with every year passing,
the deficit had been deepening.
Year
(Note) Vertical axis is represented by a logarithmic function
(Source) Nomura Research Institute "Business World Observation May 1984"
At the same time, the budget deficit
had also been worsening.
So to fill this void somehow,
they relied on loans from other countries.
But as you well know,
a loan is something you pay back with interest.
Yes.
As a result, the American foreign debt
cannot be paid back now,
without printing out dollars, the world's currency,
in ridiculous amounts so as to cover the interest rates.
I.e. we'll see an outflow of dollars.
As a result, the dollar would depreciate,
entailing a major shift in the exchange rates.
With yen strengthening against the dollar?
Correct. One dollar, currently traded for about 200 yen,
will then drop to under 170 yen if not less.
And the decline might not end there.
But if that turns out to be the case,
Japan would be in favor
of switching to local production in the US, right?
That's what I'm getting at.
And then, the only remaining issue...
The surge of domestic unemployment?
The subcontractors are probably going
to be hit the hardest by that change.
If you're doing this research for Showa,
could I interest you with these records on subcontractors?
Are you...
Reference room manager, Yuki.
Ah, I apologize...
I never said hello
and just helped myself...
I work in Business Headquarters...
Matsumoto Sawako, isn't that right?
Yes...
You've already been introduced to me via a proxy.
Yukie...
Actually, I always come here when I need a break.
Oh my!
In the late 70s, I also had to deal with frictions
around the foreign trade of color TVs.
If we switch to local car production,
we'll be in dire straits, right?
Yes...
Actually, if that would help, I can get you
the records on the production relocation of color TVs.
You'd be my life saver!
Now, where was it...
Yukie, what do you think of manager Yuki?
He's a thousand times
as sharp as our manager Mikawa.
People say he had a bright future
waiting for him, apparently,
but at one point he had to take the blame
for some unfortunate happening
and was made into a mere by-the-window pen-pusher.
Two years have passed since the self-restrictions.
The appreciation of Japanese cars
allowed the American industries to also hike the prices.
The performance of the imperiled Central Motor Company
began to improve.
Then, as changes in the American monetary policy
caused yen appreciation,
Central Motor Company Shareholders' Meeting
the price of Japanese cars followed suit once more.
...and so, I'm proud to announce that the unjust
exchange rates, low wages, long working hours,
government protectionism,
and other foul means of Japanese profiteering
were met with international criticism.
Japan was left no choice but to radically alter its ways.
But above all, the dollar-yen exchange rate
is approaching a reasonable level,
weakening the competitiveness of Japanese cars.
In time, the conditions will arise,
where their manufacturers are left no choice,
but to step forth and switch to local production in the US.
And losing this battle on American soil
is out of question!
Furthermore, I expect
that large quantities of our "Central" cars
will soon comprise a significant part
of our exports to Japan!
We're not impressed!
Moving the factories to the US
would only result in a spike of unemployment!
Showa Motor Co. Workers Union President
Katsutoshi Sato
For us, simple workers,
it's all harm and no gain!
Be firm in your opposition,
for the sake of our union's survival!
Don't let them steal our jobs!
Not in a thousand years,
we'll be the martyrs to the trade frictions!
Isn't that right, gentlemen?!
At the board meeting this morning, a decision was made
that we start producing locally in the US.
Therefore, we ask you,
Goyo and Taihei representatives,
Goyo Trading Business Headquarters
General Manager Gondo                   Kunio Tsugawa
to come up with an optimal strategy
for relocating our production facilities.
I'd like you to consider all the possibilities.
Huh. Must be you're trying to make fun of us.
Where's the fun in competing against a softie girl
fresh out of school?
Tsugawa, please watch your language.
Okay...
Toda, we hope you don't go too hard on us this time.
No, we're the ones hoping for leniency today.
Do you mind if I ask just one thing?
Go ahead.
The problem of labor unions,
what do you intend to do about that?
You can trust us to deal with that issue
and devote yourself fully to developing the strategy.
Goyo's Gondo has a nasty record
of repetitively making fun of us.
This time, we must do our utmost to get the better of him.
Department chief, please trust me to deal with this.
In anticipation of this kinda scenario,
I was already secretly drawing up a strategy
for Hayate's factory relocation!
Oh, that would be rather handy.
I'll present them with a revolutionary idea
of taking over local plants.
Just let me draw up a report,
you'll see everything yourself!
Sounds good. Matsumoto,
what's your planned approach for this issue?
I thought I'd start with a research
on the subcontractors' situation.
Subcontractors?
What's the use of dealing with them
at this stage?
If you've nothing better to do,
I'd rather you help me executing my plan instead.
With all due respect to your vision,
Goyo Division is likely to have already made
the necessary arrangements with potential candidates.
But if we take a non-standard approach now,
Showa would be more inclined
to favor us in the future.
I believe it's the only viable strategy.
Indeed, cutting ties with parts subcontractors
is one more headache we need to deal with.
Very well. I want you to also
draw up a report in the nearest time.
Sure.
Use all the money you need.
Don't be picky with methods.
Just see to it that our cover isn't broken.
Make every precaution regarding that.
That's a no-brainer.
You and me have quite the history
of doing business together, after all.
Sato only has the union's backing, but has ambitions to run
for the upper house of the Diet.
We just need to get ahold of one good scandal.
Or fabricate one.
Whoa, whoa, now it's really heating up, isn't it?
Yeah...
After building up our trust with Showa for all that time,
I'm not giving them up to the likes of Taihei.
Ever since the self-restrictions were placed,
the plant had not expanded an inch.
And our future prospects are also less than bright.
Because of the strengthening yen, right?
After everything Showa has done for us,
speaking ill of them is the last thing I'd wanna do...
But we always end up being the ones to feel the crunch.
About that...
Showa is seriously considering
switching to local production in the US as we speak.
Ah... What was that just now?
Y-You can't be serious!
I was told the Showa's labor union
is vehemently opposed to it.
Why the one-eighty?
Well, that's all I know for now.
Even then, even if they build an assembly line over there,
what would they put on it without Japan-made parts?
It's us, the small subcontractors,
who make the Japanese cars so great and affordable!
Do you suppose they'll make us
send the parts there all the way from Japan?
That would've been reasonable, but...
The US Senate is about to reinstate a law that says,
unless over 50% of the car,
including parts, is made locally,
it's still considered an import.
But if that happens...
What do they suppose will become
of small companies like mine?
It can't be... I'm obviously too old to immigrate now!
Matsumoto, for us subcontractors,
this is a matter of life and death!
Isn't it within Taihei's power
to find us something else to do?
A new work for car parts manufacturers...
Taking over a poorly managed local company?
That's a gutsy plan, if I do say so myself.
Mikawa, if we choose your approach,
this job would call for some sharp practice.
Without going that far,
we'll never be able to win Showa over!
Especially if it results in the cheapest plan of all!
That may well be true,
but it also means
a huge initial investment would be required.
If Showa falls short of the investments required,
our company could look after them with our own funds.
And later, our company could also use it
to do business there.
You've thought of everything, haven't you?
All right, fly to the US immediately
and secure that property for us.
Got it!
Matsumoto, you got something for me too?
Yes. I was curious:
once Showa relocates its production to the US,
how would it supply the car parts there?
In particular, my research was focused
on how subcontractors would weather that storm.
So, what were your conclusions?
A few years ago,
we had similar trade frictions over color TVs.
During those, the Japanese manufacturers
were also switching to local production all as one.
As a result, the export of color TVs to the US
is now virtually nonexistent.
Electrical appliance manufacturers
moved everything abroad, including their parts divisions.
However, the subcontractors that were left behind
still made it through with little trouble.
Oh?
But that was because the lines
that were previously making TVs for the US
could be effortlessly converted to VTR production lines.
In the form of VTRs,
a terrific pinch hitter had entered the field.
Are you saying that no such pinch hitter
can appear in the automobile industry?
Exactly. Cars use considerably more parts than TVs.
The subcontractors also vary in size. And obviously enough,
they can't all follow the parent company abroad.
You were proactively urging Hayate
to commit to the local production.
Yet for Showa, you're skeptical about it...
By then, Hayate had much fewer subcontractors,
so they didn't run into a lot of trouble moving them.
I get it.
But then, have you any solution
for cutting this Gordian Knot?
Yes. Together with Yukie
and the reference room manager Yuki,
we can draw up a new business plan,
that'd facilitate a closer cooperation with the subcontractors.
I see. Please do that as soon as possible.
Okay.
A takeover of a local enterprise? I see.
Sounds very much like our Manager Mikawa.
But hey, stealthily buying out someone else's company...
Isn't it a bit too overbearing?
Especially when you have no idea
how people working there would feel about it.
Chairman Sato!
After opposing it so vehemently,
how come you suddenly changed your stance?!
How do we explain this to the union members,
who've always believed in the management's position?!
Well, I thought I explained this point to you
multiple times already.
Not even a trade union can exist in isolation
from the international economic environment.
What the... Don't tell me
you've made a shadow deal with the company!
How rude! One should know
what he can say and what he can't.
I think you'd be quite amused to see what's inside here.
What could it be?
Showa Motor Union chairman: spicy story!
This is a sham!
Too bad I couldn't care less whether or not it is.
But I bet a great many people would like
to see this jolly kind of article in the evening news.
After all, it's a scandal, concerning a big shot labor union chairman, aiming to run for the upper house of the Diet.
How is that not an attention grabber?
With all due respect to Taihei's efforts,
it has been decided that the production lines expansion
would be conducted according to the plan
proposed by the Goyo side this time.
What did you say?!
Are you saying our plan was in some way deficient?
No, it wasn't exactly deficient. It's just...
"Just" what?
Both proposals involved a takeover of a local enterprise.
They were similar to the point where both
chose North Carolina as a destination.
Goyo chose a takeover, too?
The key difference was in the cost.
On the Goyo side, it was an agricultural equipment
manufacturer about to go bankrupt.
What...
So the Japanese company
that bought up this manufacturer's shares was Goyo?!
Did it in the nick of time.
Well, regarding the alternative proposal...
The Subcontractors Strategy,
developed by Taihei's Matsumoto
was also deemed highly novel by our company's board.
Therefore, we hope for a productive future cooperation
with Taihei and their out-of-the-box analysis.
If you say it's so out-of-the-box,
you should start acting upon it ASAP.
Matsumoto, having helped myself to reading your report,
I'd like to subscribe to every word he said.
Showa is usually rather slow on the uptake,
so I'd rather have you working for us.
Gondo! We'd be in trouble if that happens.
Oh, it was just a "what if" soliloquy.
It was a bit hard to tell...
North Carolina, USA
I hear the company's new owners are Japanese.
They're going to turn this into an assembly plant
for Japanese cars. And they're going to keep us on.
I'd salute this new owner even if he's a monkey,
as long as I don't get laid off.
But I've heard that workers in Japan
are treated like slaves.
Aren't we all corporate slaves?
Well, if worse comes to worst,
we can appeal to the union. They'll do something about it.
Every time we rely on them,
we end up paying even more!
At any rate, we should let the Japanese know
that things won't be all that simple.
It's a shame Sawako and Mikawa got overlooked,
but at least we know our efforts weren't completely in vain.
Sawako, let's throw a big party tonight!
Yukie, nothing wrong with throwing a big party,
but really, this is a watershed moment
both for us and for the Goyo guys.
For Goyo too?
Right. Even after they set the factory up,
they'll only be able to talk about success when the cars
they make are on par with those assembled in Japan.
In the end, isn't it wonderful,
when people of different backgrounds, languages,
and skin colors work side by side assembling them?
I suppose...
However, a few years from now, when every single Japanese manufacturer switches to a local production model,
there'll surely come a time when supply exceeds demand
and a surplus of cars would form.
Sawako,
I have a strong feeling
it'll be your turn to shine once more.
I pray that your business style, born from
consideration for others, remains forever unchanged!
IMF - The International Monetary Fund
evaluated the consequences of the restrictions,
placed from 1981 to 1984 on exports from Japan to the US.
A detailed summary of the damage incurred
by ordinary American consumers is as follows:
Over these four years, the prices of all new
American-made cars rose by an average of 50%.
Had export self-restrictions not been placed,
they place the expected increase in price at just 27%.
As a result of this, the combined amount of money
overpaid by the consumers was over $17 billion.
Converted to yen at the exchange rate of that period,
it's about 4 trillion yen.
Which makes it a trillion yen yearly.
Episode 2
Exchange Game
Chairman of the US Federal Reserve Board (FRB)
FRB chairman...
People say with this man's every move,
the world's money starts moving too.
Fishing so leisurely...
The catch today - two large rainbowfishes.
Our fishing enthusiast went to bed
in high spirits a little while ago.
Tokyo, August 31, 1985
Got it. No abnormalities for today.
Good job. The overall situation
is still rather complicated though.
Don't take your eyes off him.
Well, goodnight for now, Birdwatcher.
Among companies comprising the Taihei Group,
as well as small banks and insurance agencies,
there exists a dire demand for the precise advice
on future developments of the currency market.
For the time being, creating a currency market
consulting subdivision is my plan.
I'd like to ask Matsumoto to become the project team chief.
You can organize the team entirely to your liking.
Oh?
Will this really turn out well?
Predicting stock prices
is a breeze compared to the currency market.
There's a metric ton of factors that you gotta see through.
Just being a math prodigy would get you nowhere.
Instead, the flair for collecting data
and rich imagination are your only friends.
Well, we're yet to find out whether or not
Matsumoto possesses any of those qualities.
But I'm looking forward to seeing what
a Harvard Business School alumni's got in stock for us.
Thank you very much, manager.
With your encouragement, I'm eager to join the fight.
Business Headquarters Conference Room
I hope you don't mind me
getting straight to the point.
Companies comprising the group, as well as a few individual members were offered a newsletter for internal business use.
Alternatively, they were offered
a customer advice service on a case-by-case basis.
Yukie, do you have the data
on the applications for membership?
Yes.
Despite the newsletter subscription
costing 10,000,000 yen annually,
the quota of 30 companies had already been filled.
Additionally, quite a few businesses expressed a wish
to receive case-by-case consulting services.
Oh, so the demand was that high?
With the subscription fee being that considerable,
we have to provide data of corresponding quality.
Which means, the slipshod speculations
circulating on the streets won't do.
Hmm.
So we have to adopt a method for gathering intel
that is profound, covert, and advanced all at the same time?
Precisely.
For intel, particularly that concerning the market,
the less people have access to it,
the more it gains in added value.
If it's something everybody knows,
you can't really call it "intel," can you?
Yes.
Well then, why don't we divide the areas of responsibility?
First, I'd like Manager Mikawa to look into the line
Ministry of Finance and Bank of Japan are toeing.
Ueda will work directly with our clients,
particularly - specialized currency trading institutions.
Got it.
Date will connect to the operational network of our dealing room, so as to directly monitor the currency market.
As for myself, with Yukie as my personal assistant,
I'll be in charge of monitoring
the Market Circles of the foreign markets,
from FRB and the American Ministry of Finance,
to New York, London, Zürich, and so on.
Ministry of Finance and Bank of Japan?
Quite the challenging assignment.
It's particularly important that you keep a close eye
on the Ministry of Finance secretary's every move.
Secretary?
That's because he is closely acquainted to the FRB chairman,
and a strong mutual admiration
exists between the two.
If they come up with something,
they'll start deviating from this line.
Excuse me, but what is FRB?
Hey, you...
Ah?
How'd you get into the Business Headquarters
without knowing even that?
I'm sorry.
FRB is an abbreviation, standing for "Federal Reserve Board"
of the US, also commonly known as just "the Fed."
It acts as the highest financial regulatory organ in the US,
deciding on the monetary policies and supervising banks.
So, it's the same as Bank of Japan?
In a way, I guess. But its influence on the world
stands in no comparison to that of Bank of Japan.
Just look at the first picture in the file.
That's Mr. Chairman.
People say with this man's every move,
the world's money starts moving too.
Oh?
That sure is one daunting task
Sawako is facing.
Well, I guess that's what makes her so amazing.
Is the currency market really that complicated?
Of course it is!
The foreign trade turnover is $3 trillion a year.
But the currency exchange turnover in this term alone
amounts to $40 trillion.
$40 trillion?!
Unlike in previous days,
when the exchange rate was determined mainly
by the current balance of foreign trade,
nowadays, even if the market is still somewhat tied
to crude oil price fluctuations,
there are also interest rates, price index, GNP,
and even policy interventions that may all affect the market,
rendering it extremely unpredictable
even for savvy currency dealers.
So it's all about being an expert?
Seems like I won't be of much help at all...
I'm not used to seeing you lament your shortcomings.
Actually,
there's an acquaintance of mine
working in the dealing room of the Taihei Bank.
Would you like a tour later?
The forefront view of currency market operation
could provide you with that much-needed insight.
Yes.
I hope you also let me keep you company.
Sawako?
Now, how did I know you'd try to escape to here?
I'm sorry!
Yuki, about that talk just now. I also want to know
the exchange bank's perspective on the matter.
You must let me join you.
Sure.
Because the consulting fees
go up to 10,000,000 yen a year,
Aoba
Mutual
Bank
we take every precaution
to ensure profit for our clients.
However, the conclusions you draw from our intel
and the actions you undertake
are entirely up to your own investment strategy.
Aoba Mutual Bank Executive Director
That might hold true,
but a rural bank such as ours
has no surplus in savvy bond dealers.
So when we see another bank
buying up American government bonds, so do we.
Even so, we've been able to do business
with relatively good profits up until now.
There exists a 5% interest rate differential
between Japan and the US.
So when you take the money from Japanese depositors
and invest it in the US,
you can make a decent profit with just that.
However, if value of the dollar suddenly nosedives,
so does the evaluation of the actual yens we have on hand,
negating all the previous profits if not worse.
Surely, you don't suppose
we could overlook that risk?
No. I believe such a turn of events
to be quite possible.
However, nobody can tell you for sure
when the appreciation correction will kick in,
what would be the extent of compensation,
or for how long it will keep falling.
Please don't talk so callously.
I mean it when I say we're all counting on you, Ueda.
Ah...
One yours!
Two mine!
Got it, one yours!
Okay, one yours!
Two mine!
Roger.
Right, one mine!
Those "One" and "Two" they're shouting are units of dollars.
"One" means $1,000,000.
"Mine" means buying, "Yours" means selling.
Oh... What an amazing place!
It's like we're on a battlefield!
This place is relatively peaceful now.
Chief of Taihei Bank Currency Market
As we get closer to 3:30,
buying and selling becomes more and more active.
Just before the closing time?
Yes.
Due to position regulation, the banks are limited
in the number of positions they can retain overnight.
To adjust to that regulation,
the banks start selling and buying assets more actively.
Position?
The banks cannot just sell dollars indefinitely,
neither can they buy them indefinitely.
The general principle is, you buy back the dollars
that you sold, and you sell back dollars that you bought,
arriving to a square. In other words, the change
in the number of positions has to be plus-minus zero.
However, making it a complete zero is often impossible,
therefore, you're allowed to carry over to the next day
a limited amount of trading assets.
And what exactly is that amount?
Presently, it's fixed at $100,000,000.
The combined turnover of transactions made here
usually amounts to $1 billion daily.
So the sum you're allowed to keep overnight
is only a small part of it.
These days, because of the time difference,
somewhere in the world, the market always remains open.
So Tokyo's position can be succeeded by London.
Conversely, it allows for New York and Tokyo markets
to be in coordination, right?
Yes.
That's what a 24-hour market system is all about.
We, currency dealers, don't have the luxury
of being able to relax our nerves even at night.
So everyone working here
needs a recreational vacation once every 3 years.
This isn't right...
By the way, Nakayama, when do you think the dollar appreciation correction will take place and in what form?
A leading question won't work on me.
I know the news.
You opened a currency market consulting department.
I should be the one asking that question.
September 16th, 1985
4:50 P.M.
Due to the strong dollar policy we've been upholding,
the US-manufactured goods
become less and less competitive.
It also hits our agricultural exports hard.
As a result, unemployed men are flooding the streets.
Both from Japan and from Europe,
we hear one voice after another,
US Treasury Secretary
calling for abolition of our high interest rates
and dollar appreciation policies.
If this continues,
your re-election is jeopardized.
President of the US
The policies must be abolished.
Please make a decision.
Arrange a meeting with the FRB chairman.
September 17th, 11:20 A.M.
So, the Ministry of Finance secretary
doesn't have any trips abroad scheduled for this week?
Not just for this week,
but for the next month or so!
In short, Taihei have put together a "Currency Market Project Team," with that girl Matsumoto at its nucleus,
Goyo Trading, Business HQ Manager's Office
and now they're actively prying into things?
We've nothing to fear so far.
They're merely scavenging for intel
from the lower ranks of the Finance Ministry.
Hm. The businesses are also hurriedly soliciting
their right to pay this fiscal year's import fees in dollars.
Well, it's best that we also keep an eye
on what the upper echelon is up to.
Got it.
September 17th, Tuesday, 1:05 P.M.
Yes?
Sawako, it's from the US. A collect call.
Coming.
Yes? Matsumoto speaking.
This is Birdwatcher.
It's midnight on my end.
Our fishing enthusiast acts a little strange,
so I thought I should let you know.
What did you say?
Every week, our fishing enthusiast
goes on a round trip to Washington.
So I reached out to the pilot of his charter plane.
Turns out, he doesn't have anything planned
for the upcoming weekend - from 21st to 22nd of September.
And then, when I tried to inquire with the company
managing Fishing Enthusiast's mountain villa,
I learned that he might not come there again this season.
At least, that's how his wife put it.
Ah... So suspicious.
The river in that area only has the fishing season opened
until September 25th.
This week is his last chance.
It's unlikely that a maniac such as him would miss it.
Understood, thank you.
The long-anticipated storm is here.
You really didn't have to call a meeting
so early in the morning.
I will start with the conclusions.
For our tomorrow's newsletter:
"Towards the end of this week,
a multinational group of high-ranking financial officials
would be very likely to come together for a meeting,
to discuss the currency questions."
That's the announcement I came up with.
When putting together the fragmented data
that was coming our way,
I couldn't possibly arrive to any other conclusion.
Wait a minute!
Neither the minister of finance, nor the secretary, ​
not even the Bank of Japan president
have any plans to travel abroad.
Besides, in all the previous instances,
whenever a currency meeting was to be held,
there'd always be some sign beforehand.
If we only draw conclusions from precedents,
then what is the purpose of our business at all?
They're acting with utmost care, so as not to let
the Market Circles get wind of what's going on.
Matsumoto... If you to steer it with great swings,
such as this news,
the vessel which is our consulting business,
will turn to shipwreck in no time.
Diving headlong without testing the waters...
Manager! In a highly volatile world that is the currency market, is there really such a thing as safe waters?
If you want to help,
tighten the observation on our targets.
Install a permanent surveillance
over the Ministry of Finance secretary's house.
Ueda, I've read the newsletter!
September 19th, Thursday. 10:45 A.M.
We recommend against holding on to large quantities of American Government Bonds through this weekend.
Such was the advice given to Taihei Group companies,
but personally, I think it'd be better if you sell
at least half of your holdings and convert it to yens.
Eh... I see.
I trust your judgment
and will take a chance on your company's intel.
But if some other intel comes to light,
please be sure to let me know immediately!
For a small-size financial institution,
this is a matter of life and death.
Very well.
For the moment, we're making every effort
to back up that intel.
September 20th, Friday. 11:40 P.M.
Tomorrow, I'm going out for a private game of golf, so you'll have to excuse me for not meeting you in the morning.
Finance Ministry Secretary's house
With a lovely Ginza lady as your opponent, by any chance?
Playing golf with a Ginza hostess? Hm. A fine diversion for a man of his position. Very well. Dismissed for tonight.
The guy from Goyo received a dismissal already.
Ueda, let's pull out too.
But Sawako told us to peer our eyes into it
until the morning.
Hmpf! It's been two nights already
that we had to spend in the car.
I'll leave this to you tonight.
Good night.
Oh? Manager!
Ah! Yuki-san!
Provisions for the front line.
About time!
Hide!
Eh? Did he just pack his things and leave?
Suspicious...
Better call Sawako now.
Came back to pick up his suitcase? Roger that.
Keep a lookout on that position.
September 21st, Saturday. 7:05 A.M.
Here.
According to Ueda's phone report,
both the minister of finance and the secretary
got into the car, wearing golf uniforms.
Though their alleged destination was Narita Country Golf Club, they're definitely going to New York.
I guess that settles it.
If it wouldn't have been for a glimpse of that suitcase,
you could really think they're going to play golf.
The only question now,
how would their final agreement look like?
First and foremost, they're going to discuss
a decrease in American interest rates.
With American interest rates being so high, every other nation is concentrating its investments in the US,
resulting in dollar appreciation.
If they manage to reach a groundbreaking agreement,
it would mean all the nations involved
will try to jointly manipulate the currency market.
In other words, a simultaneous intervention?
September 22nd, Sunday. New York.
It became an impediment to many economics of the world,
so a correction to excessive dollar appreciation is needed.
Plaza Hotel
The US had already stepped up
with one possible countermeasure.
However, this proposal is contingent
on the agreement and cooperation
between the monetary authorities
of all countries concerned.
The upcoming conference should become a forum
for the most frank discussion of this issue.
Even the US is taking it seriously this time?
G5 conference held in New York!
US corrects high interest rate policy!
Agreement for a coordinated currency market intervention in developed countries!
Just before the last weekend, the Taihei Group
converted half of their dollar holdings into yen!
What have you been doing all this time?!
General manager, I hate to echo your words,
but in all such occasions up until now,
resisting the authorities' intervention
was common sense, as it's a lot more profitable.
I don't think even a G5 agreement has the power
to reverse the dollar appreciation trend in one fell swoop.
Is that to say that by not selling dollars
last week, the Goyo Group
was actually holding back
to avoid unnecessary risks?
Thanks for all your trouble!
September 23rd, Autumnal Equinox Day. 1:15 P.M.
Just now, Chief of Taihei Bank Currency Market Nakayama
got a call from the Bank of Japan.
He's meeting someone at 3 o'clock,
in front of the fountain at the Hibiya Park!
Oh? The foreigners are busy at work,
even when it's national holiday in Japan.
It seems, Bank of Japan is also taking it seriously.
I imagine, the currency market tomorrow
will turn into a dogfight
between the speculators and the currency authorities.
Today, our Bank of Japan
is to proclaim an unprecedented market intervention.
September 24th, Tuesday. 7:45 A.M.
Yesterday, the New York Federal Reserve Bank,
together with the FRG Federal Reserve
Bank of Japan, Foreign Currency Division Chief
started selling dollars en masse
as agreed previously.
As a result of that,
the yen rose from 242 yen to 225 yen at one point.
Today, our duty is to inherit that baton
and solidify the ongoing trend for the yen appreciation.
Even if the total turnover of intervention
exceeds the $1 billion mark, it doesn't concern us!
I want you to sell the devil out of it.
Okay!
The price is approaching 229 yen 70 sen.
The dollar is put under a surprisingly strong pressure.
The billing companies are having a field day after this.
Bank of Japan begins its first round of intervention
any minute now.
Ah! Gone up a bit!
Yeah. It's Bank of Japan.
Only about 10,000,000 dollars this time.
Oh?
The yen went down again.
On Sydney market that starts trading first, the dollar appreciation is also 3 yens above the New York's level.
This is quickly turning into a forced hand market...
231 yen 20 sen.
Even if the Bank of Japan directly intervenes,
it's no big deal at all.
Ueda, even though the G5 prediction turned out true,
the dollar market price hasn't gone down one bit!
This morning, I tried selling more dollars.
But shortly after, just in time for the morning
trade session closure, I bought them back!
Presently, the market is going through the stage
of probing into the authorities' preparedness.
The trend is definitely changing in the afternoon!
Is that true?
Is that something I can fully trust?
Selling dollars is the only way now!
Sir! It's back to the 230 yen level!
Apparently, the authorities
will spare no coin to have it their way.
Regardless of dollars bought,
they keep flooding the market with selling offers.
Finally, even the oil companies started selling!
They're anticipating the dollar depreciation?
All right! The mood has changed!
Sell!
Sell more! More! Sell it all out!
It's over, at 230 yen 10 sen.
Yen appreciation compared to pre-weekend level
is at 11 yen 90 sen!
I hope you make sure to repair this damage in the future!
This new enterprise of ours took off pretty well.
This time, even you couldn't help
taking your hat off to Matsumoto, I believe.
Yes...
This 24-hour lookout
over Ministry of Finance Secretary's house...
Even if I thought that was going a bit too far at first,
eventually, it turned out to be a decisive factor.
Cheers!
The total trading turnover today
was over $4.7 billion.
Nearly one-third of those dollars
were sold by the Bank of Japan.
Our foreign-exchange reserves
amount to about $27.5 billion,
while the combined global stock trading turnover
adds up to $150-200 billion a day.
With the current system in place, the currency's strength is defined by the whims of its market price.
That's all I have to say.
The market's only master
is the market itself, agreed?
Huh? Yukie, how can you know that?
If you make fun of me, by extension,
you do it to everyone in Business Headquarters!
Eeeh?!
Episode 3
Internationalization of Finance
London, Thames Riverside
I love you, Diana.
Charles...
What's wrong, Diana?
I-In the river!
Mysterious body floating in the Thames River!?
Puzzling Drowned Body is Enrique, Banco da Vinci President!?
Manager's Office
Goyo Manufacturing, Business HQ Manager's Office
Manager, this seems serious.
What is it? You look hot and bothered.
Enrique has been found dead.
What?! How do you know that?
It's been some time since he last
made contact with us, and now - this mess.
"The man is believed to be the Da Vinci Bank president,
who had gone missing and a search request was filed.
Last seen 10 days ago in his Milan residence.
After that, he suddenly disappeared."
Shit... Even though they never mention
any traces of suicide or murder,
I can only believe that he was murdered.
Hm... Did Enrique cross paths
with someone dangerous?
No, his Banco da Vinci was among Italy's
leading financial institutions.
He was also an important figure
in Milan's business circles. Just...
Just... What?
Lately, internal power struggles plague Vatican.
Rumors of him being involved reached me as well.
What? Vatican?
Yes...
Da Vinci's still liable to our underwriting!
Taihei Finance, Business HQ Manager's Office
You were the one who suggested that we tap into
Vatican's vast funds that da Vinci operates!
Fly to London, Milan or wherever
and figure things out personally!
Okay...
How careless can you be?
But Manager, it wasn't my fault this time!
Yukie...
We're sorry.
What's with that attitude?
How can one be named after a beautiful river of Mikawa,
and still be a stinky creek?
Yukie...
Huh?
Ah!
Who's the stinky creek again?
No... I meant...
I should stick the documents together
and not crease them.
Ah, enough incorrigible gibberish.
Instead, book me the earliest possible
ticket to London.
Can you do that?
Yes...
Banco Da Vinci President Enrique?!
If it isn't Mikawa from Taihei!
Are you...
Where are you heading to?
L-Los Angeles. What about you?
Oh, just a short trip to Singapore.
Ah, here it is.
Um... Weren't you going to Los Angeles?
You said you were heading for Singapore...
Oh, I... Need to go to London as well.
Just a small detour.
Ah... That's an interesting coincidence.
It's the same for me.
You sly dog.
You sneaky fox.
A few months prior in Milan, Italy
I hope you can excuse me for using my own apartment
to discuss business with you,
but I absolutely wanted to introduce you
with the genuine Italian hospitality.
Banco da Vinci Chief Bond Dealer Gelsomina
Well, if someone told me
Banco da Vinci's chief bond dealer
could be this beautiful, I wouldn't believe them.
I appreciate your attention.
I hope for nothing less
than fruitful negotiations.
I can assure you we'll achieve that.
Our investment efficiency stands its ground
against any other bank in Europe.
Concluding profitable deals is our priority.
That's what I gathered
from the statistics you provided. One more thing...
In the current situation
of monetary revolution unfolding in the world,
what is the strategy your bank intends to employ?
The purpose of my visit today is to learn that.
I'd like to reassure you on that matter as well.
But before that...
Before that...?
In order to achieve a lasting business relationship,
don't you think it's essential
to build a good personal partnership first?
Why don't we make ourselves comfortable tonight?
A marvelous idea for the night.
There's also Gelsomina...
What... Gelsomina?
Could that possibly be
Gelsomina of Banco da Vinci?
Eh?
Then, don't you mean to say,
you're also going there because of Enrique?
In other words, you in Goyo too...
What do you know - apparently, we're going to London
for the very same reason, after all.
Damn you, Enrique...
Banco da Vinci, Milan
Banco Da Vinci President Enrique
I take it our chief bond dealer explained to you
our bank's conditions in all details, Signor Mikawa?
Yes. All in all, it seems like a sensible line of action.
After I consult with Tokyo, I hope we can come
to an agreement within the next few days.
All of our bank's regular customers are successful companies, prominent on the international level.
The safety of their assets is a given.
Our plans also include
opening a branch in Tokyo.
I hope that in doing so we will expedite greatly
a closer cooperation with Taihei.
We'll be looking forward to it.
While we're at it, President Enrique,
I was wondering if the rumors of your institution's
strong influence on Christian Capitals were true.
It is an unwritten rule among financiers
not to disclose anything specific about their clients.
But well, our bank made it pretty big
on the Italian market.
I'll leave the rest to your imagination.
For sure, by nibbling your way
into an organization that exclusive,
or appointing an exquisite beauty
on a position pivotal to the bank,
you've proven yourself
an outstanding bank president.
Should even you harbor a fondness for someone from our staff, that's none of my business, I suppose.
Susceptibility to the woman's charms
is innate to Japanese and to Italians alike.
Goyo Trading London Office
Ah... Tsugawa!
Did you learn anything new?
They've confirmed his identity.
It was Enrique, beyond any doubt.
Tentatively, the presumed cause of death is suicide.
A suicide, huh?
They're still feverishly gathering information in the City,
but no definite conclusion has been reached yet.
There's just that rumor, saying Banco da Vinci's
subsidiaries in Luxemburg and Liechtenstein
have hoarded large amounts of nonperforming loans.
What did you say?
In addition to that,
there's also a story that money was flowing to the mafia.
So... Did you manage to grasp
da Vinci's state of affairs?
Yes... We have the latest fiscal report.
But da Vinci has, beside its main body,
multiple holding companies
and foreign local affiliates.
With such an inscrutable spiderweb of subsidiaries,
nobody can grasp the actual state of affairs.
But if the City pulls all strings at once,
da Vinci would go under, wouldn't it?
All the bankers agree that in the event of a bank run
the bankruptcy seems unavoidable.
It's that bad?
We can't know for sure yet.
But if even just one of those rumors
flying around proves true,
that would seem quite possible.
Surely enough,
da Vinci has some backers, doesn't it?
Yes. You mean Vatican, right?
Though they go to great lengths to hide it,
the fact that Vatican is among that bank's
largest stockholders is undeniable.
However, the Vatican connection was apparently leveraged
to allocate huge loans to a paper company,
that were later written off as unrecoverable.
That's where the mafia comes into play...
So the chances of recovering our assets are slim?
Yes... Unfortunately.
However, it was a comparatively minor investment,
so our losses are sustainable.
Meanwhile, in the City's inner circles,
concerns are raised over a possible chain bankruptcy.
Damn you, Enrique...
By the time I was meeting with him,
his tail was already on fire.
He's had me
while feigning ignorance.
"Our losses are less than that of Goyo?"
Imbecile!
How does that make our own situation any better?!
It's inexcusable...
With this, the internal opposition to our company's current investment strategy is stronger than ever!
It hurts way more than any financial losses!
S-Sir...
Usually, I despise this guy.
But today, even I feel sorry for him!
Department chief.
Wouldn't it be premature to conclude
that nothing can be salvaged?
Hm?
I apologize for butting in,
but don't you expect the Vatican to try to come
to their relief, in one way or another?
The papal court operates vastly larger funds
than even Japan's national budget.
If it gets involved in a financial scandal,
resulting in a collapse of even one bank from the group,
it'll end up losing the trust
of the believers from all over the world.
Right... However, some influential British banks
are already cashing out their bonds.
If only 2 or 3 more banks follow,
it'll be the end of everything.
We still have a small window of opportunity,
before they are completely out of business.
If we play our cards right,
it may be enough to get things straight.
Matsumoto...
Very well. You can give it a try.
Something in your words inspires confidence.
I also want Mikawa to follow you.
However! We can't afford another blunder here.
Take every precaution before acting.
Okay.
I heard it from the news on TV yesterday.
They apprehended some big shot
of the Italian financial world involved in this affair.
I've also heard of this news.
May I add, that's one baffling affair.
Yes... Europe's financial world is in turmoil.
Add to that the mafia link and the murder.
A rumor is circulating
that it was the business circles' doing.
But you can't really blame Mikawa.
This Tsugawa from Goyo Group
got caught up in it too.
Seems that Enrique was one sly daredevil.
The world of international finances is murky waters.
It'd known stories of fraud
for as long as it exists.
While we're at it, how exactly
do you intend to sort out the da Vinci affair?
One of my Harvard Business School classmates
now works for a major American bank.
She had since become
the senior economist in the Manhattan Trust.
She is currently in Japan for a business trip,
so I thought I'd ask her for a bit of advice.
I see now.
Japan's Hokuto Finance conglomerate
plans to establish a subsidiary in the US?
I knew they wanted to branch out into the securities.
What I didn't know is that Taihei are also attempting
to tap into the international money flow.
Manhattan Trust Bank Senior Economist Anne Marie Taylor
But this time we encountered some unavoidable setbacks.
Is that so?
I think Taihei really did the right thing
by focusing their attention on Europe over the US.
Is that to say,
a financial enterprise founded in Europe
can get to work right away,
trading securities and providing banking services?
Yes. The ultimate destination of this financial revolution
is a world with no market restrictions.
Japan and the US are also on their way
to becoming very Europe-like in this respect.
And to expedite that process,
studying the European experience is not a half-bad idea.
Even if you say so, we're having to start from a complete zero.
Hey, Sawako. If Taihei are seriously committed to it,
I'm willing to lend you a hand.
The cobbler knows his last.
Our company is the perfect hub
for all kinds of information.
Manager, Banco da Vinci's
Luxembourg subsidiary declared bankruptcy.
Hm. This means the book is closed on the da Vinci Group.
The Milan headquarters still conducts business as usual,
but they're on borrowed time.
Looks like the moment is right.
Hm?
Tonight, I'm leaving for Milan.
Going to da Vinci personally?
They must be at sixes and sevens right about now,
with no time to meet small fry such as us.
No, actually, I thought I'd go there
to attend Enrique's funeral service.
It took them longer than expected to return the body,
but it seems, tomorrow they're finally going to bury him.
What? Since when do you care for his funeral?
He put one over on you, didn't he?
Thought I should pay my respects.
The Lord is my shepherd;
Cemetery on the outskirts of Milan, Italy
I shall not want.
He makes me lie down in green pastures;
He leads me beside still waters.
Here I pray that you guide his soul to heaven
and there grant him peace. Amen.
Amen.
Please pass this on.
Senorita, did you say "Matsumoto?"
Yes.
In the midst of this hubbub, you're the first one
to come see me personally like this.
Out of respect for this letter of introduction,
I'll hear you out.
Be mindful though,
what you expect me to do is probably impossible.
I don't wield the power
your introducer thinks I have.
Now, I'm all ears.
I hope coming all the way to Zürich for this
wasn't too much of a bother...
Zürich, Switzerland
Don't mention it.
For me, it's an unexpected but welcome vacation.
Besides, I'm more than happy to be of service.
Meeting with that man they call the Agent of Vatican,
would've been impossible without that Manhattan Trust
letter of introduction you gave me.
I don't know how to thank you.
"Give and take."
After all, I'm also counting
on your help in the near future.
Huh?
Thing is, starting next month, I'll be working
as a deputy manager of M.T. branch office in Japan.
I'm being transferred to Tokyo!
Really? I'll help in every way I can
once you're in Tokyo!
But that's still small potatoes
compared to what you're doing.
Word is, that man is a mafia bigwig.
So, how did it go?
Negotiations successful...
Or so I want to think.
We still have some practical odds and ends to sort out,
but presently, Vatican is in no shape to be bullish.
Which means, you're visiting their stronghold today?
Yes. To the head office of Göttfert Bank I go.
Gentlemen, our company's desire
is not the acquisition of your bank,
but of your talents.
In the financial world headed towards
liberalization and internationalization,
Japan is woefully behind the times.
It's you, tempered by rough seas of Zürich's finances,
with judgment that's sharp at all times,
whom I trust to guide Japan through it.
Therefore, I humbly ask you to give Taihei a chance.
Well...
Right...
Allow me to announce our decision.
Our bank's desire is not to help out Taihei Finance.
However...
It is our desire to make you happy
by any means necessary.
Thank you.
Would you look at this lady who made it big.
If you're ever tired of Taihei,
I'd be willing to take you in anytime.
Oh! So you've secured an acquisition
of da Vinci's subsidiary, Göttfert Bank?
Not just that, we're getting it pretty cheap!
Moreover, our unrecoverable da Vinci bonds
would be used to cover the part of the purchase cost? Hm!
Of all the da Vinci Group members, Göttfert is the one bank
that sustained the least losses in the recent affair.
That was thanks to its Swiss management
conducting a sound enterprise.
Its board is stuffed
with honest and conscientious people.
A bank that combines two functions
of a trust company and a securities trader in Europe,
willing to do business for us as a subsidiary
is a cherished dream of Japan's banking sector!
And yet, you got it all to ourselves!
The whole industry would eat their hearts out!
Taihei Finance purchases Göttfert Bank!
Laying the groundwork for a Merchant Bank?!
Shit... Matsumoto Sawako again!
Matsumoto, please have another glass with us!
Words can't express my gratitude!
I was lucky to pull this off.
I never expected it to actually go so well.
Our source in Vatican says
they're scrambling for loans.
Göttfert's gonna come out of this
with quite the profit.
Yes. To clean up after the da Vinci affair,
Vatican requires a lot of additional funds.
Some say they're now tens of millions of dollars in debt.
Ah, right!
Da Vinci's beautiful chief bond dealer already inquired
if we could hire her to work for Göttfert Bank.
She was so infatuated with Mikawa, after all...
M-Matsumoto!
Ah! He's blushing! Mikawa,
did you really have something with that lady?
I-I'd rather you refrain from speculations!
But you gotta admit, our company's zaitech efforts
will go a long way after this!
Japan's financial revolution was implemented
as a countermeasure to the first oil shock of 1973.
Triggered by the large-scale international issuance
of bonds and notes,
it served to promote
financial liberalization and internationalization.
The barrier was gradually lowered
between the banks and the securities companies.
That new fierce rivalry
roused financial world from the slumber.
Episode 4
Shares: A Market for the New Breed
The year is 1815. The news of Napoleon losing at Waterloo
was caught by the Rothschilds' House before anyone else.
But by selling British Bonds at the stock exchange,
they created an illusion of Napoleon winning.
The Bonds nosedived in an instant.
Realizing it was their time to act,
the Rothschild Family bought up the bonds,
thus laying the groundwork
for becoming the world's wealthiest family,
or so says the popular legend.
Why are you bringing up such an ancient story?
Well, when I went to Kabutocho yesterday,
I couldn't help feeling as if in a time slip,
so the Rothschilds came to mind.
All the extra money freed up across Japan by the lowering of interest rates last year began flowing into Kabutocho.
April 1987
Some estimates place the daily money turnover
of this place at 1.5 trillion yen.
That's how Japan achieved its current prosperity,
isn't that how saying goes?
The problem is, there's only a handful of actually
liquid stocks that everyone ends up buying and selling.
With all due respect, it's thanks to those stocks
that I'm able to take my seniors for a drive like this.
You trade stocks too, Yukie?
Only an idiot would let their money
gather dust in the bank.
I invested into what I use the most!
NTT stocks?
What I bought for 1,197,000 yen originally
now costs a whopping 3,180,000.
Net income — about 2 million yen,
with which I bought this car!
Yukie, how much money did you receive
from the company in paychecks during that period?
Oh, let me think, maybe just a fraction of two millions...
Ah...
Don't do this to me.
You're not allowing me any pleasant dreams at all!
If even you are trading stocks these days, we must do what it takes to adopt the Portfolio System ASAP.
What's that?
Market trends analysis that previously relied on manual labor would instead be performed using a simulation.
Computer software is the way to go
for composing a successful investment plan.
Oh? I didn't understand a thing.
The thought of someone making 2 million on stocks
without even understanding that is terrifying.
Mitsubishi Trust Bank
Right, buy it.
"Buy what?"
Hinomoto Steel Works, one million shares.
Eh? Tozai Insurance bought 3 million shares?
Fund Management Department, Goryo Trust
Then make it 3 million for us as well!
Yes?
Director Iida
If this places operates 1.2 trillion yen with just 6 people...
That makes it 200 billion yen per person.
200 billion?
We're no match for the New Breed.
Director, making fun of us in plain sight again?
For us, working here, handling 100 yen
and handling tens of billions of yen is the same thing.
Don't you worry about a thing.
And that's exactly what worries me —
you guys have no notion of fear.
Before dealing in stocks, we got a flair for it,
trading government securities.
That confidence is what scares me the most.
Well, this way please.
A Portfolio System?
In the US, that system had already been adopted
by the Merry Lunch Inc.
So far, with an outstanding record.
Of course, I've also been paying attention.
But the American market environment
is too different from ours.
This era, in which even a female office clerk
can make 2 million in a matter of just a few months —
do you believe it'll last forever?
That's a good question...
If we adjust the US-rooted software
to the needs of the Japanese market,
it'll surely be of much practical use.
Hm. Indeed, it'd take one look at our fund manager
to tell that he's but an amateur.
Ah... But didn't Goryo Trust assign its best fund managers
to you, their Institutional Investor?
Yes, it's embarrassing, even.
We may be the Institutional Investor by designation,
but really, we've only ever dealt in bonds.
Trust Fund = financial body, operating property and assets of its beneficiaries
It's been less than two years since we incorporated
the stock market into the Trust Fund.
Is it the same for other Institutional Investors too?
All they know is to take after government,
non-life insurance and private insurance firms.
Because they're all amateurs, they can't survive without relying on the info they receive from the broker-dealers.
Isn't it all the more reasons to embrace the Portfolio System that could prove so useful for the Japanese stock market?
Hm...
It's her, isn't it?
The elite female consultant from Taihei Finance.
She graduated abroad from Harvard, all right.
But back in Japan, she's but an ordinary woman.
Word is, she's actually quite the go-getter.
Huh. What good can a woman do?
Taihei Finance
Ah, Sawako!
Mikawa is acting like this now —
Business Headquarters
You'll be in trouble if the higher-ups find out.
Business Headquarters Manager Mikawa
Huh?
You've been to Goryo Trust, haven't you?
Yes. I went there to promote
the expeditious adoption of the Portfolio System.
And get on the couple
of young fund managers' nerves in doing so:
"Do you put more trust
in computer software than in us?"
The Portfolio System was created
by people vastly more experienced than them.
Not by a computer!
But you still need a permission from above...
Ah, Boss!
Mikawa, what's the outlook on the sales promotion
for that system we discussed?
S-Sir! I dispatched Matsumoto
to Goryo Trust immediately
and was in the process of receiving her report.
Report to the Department Chief!
Matsumoto!
Business Headquarters Department Chief Toda
The outlook is excellent.
I'm counting on you.
Your forecast was correct.
Here are last year's financial results
for the industry leader, Iwamizu Heavy Industries.
A slump on the maritime market
caused a drop in the shipbuilding division profitability.
And the aircraft division also went off track.
But it's over 10 billion in the black!
By collecting their convertible bonds
at a low interest rate of just 1.2%,
they made profit with zaitech manipulations.
Uchida Merchant Fleet,
Tokiwa Factory Complex, Hinomoto Oil —
everything outside the main business is in the black.
Isn't it comical?
Their earnings from side investments
are more than that from the main business
they worked so hard for.
In a way, it's the same as if the office lady was earning many times her salary by investing in NTT stocks.
So you know Yukie's story already?
Individual shareholders only account for 20% of the Tokyo Stock Exchange, so we gotta appreciate their existence.
Then who is making all that clamor over there?
Corporations, who are 80% of shareholders.
Yes?
It's for you.
Yes? Matsumoto here.
What's taking him so long?
He was the one who proposed the meeting...
My bad!
Our study tour lasted for longer than scheduled.
Study tour?
A showcase of Yamagami Brokerage partners.
Iwamizu Heavy Industries, Tozai Gas,
as well as Hinomoto Steel Works —
learning about the extent of lands owned by them
gave us all a useful insight.
And then, you bought their stocks
without a second thought, right?
Eh? Well, yeah...
Yamagami Brokerage played you like a fiddle.
They are pros, after all.
Well, we also know how to tell a good deal.
Wouldn't a computer be able
to handle such a simple task, then?
Hey, you...
When you gave the order to buy 1 million shares
of Hinomoto Steel Works,
but then learned that Tozai Insurance
bought 3 million shares,
you panicked and also bought 2 million more.
What now, eavesdropping on me?
Naturally, the broker-dealer phoned other
Institutional Investors and fund managers as well.
Yamagami Brokerage
Just for your reference,
Tozai Insurance and Goryo Trust
settled on buying 3 million shares each.
You want 3 million too?
Roger that!
...Which brings us to the events of today —
Hinomoto's shares becoming illiquid!
What are you getting at?
Buying penny stocks isn't scary
if everyone does that.
Because the ensuing loss isn't as bitter
when you're not bearing it alone.
All right, I'll propose it to the director.
Huh?
This "something... system" you're selling.
"Portfolio System."
Right. You bring it over
and put against us in a face-off.
If that fancy system of yours fails,
I'll have you kneel right before me.
And if the system succeeds?
I'll get a tonsure!
Manhattan Trust Tokyo Branch
That's our Sawako!
Anne Marie Taylor
And that's how you got the Goryo Trust
to order a Portfolio System from you?
Their Director Iida seems to have been inclined
towards adopting it since long ago.
To anyone familiar with the stock market,
it would come across as obvious that the current
market trend is going to cease one day.
Much like to the hardships of war,
the "New Breed" is oblivious to it.
Since the introduction of low interest rates
in autumn of 1985 to curb the strong yen,
the money that flowed into Kabutocho
amounts to 200 trillion yen.
The market capitalization of the listed stock
is 400 trillion yen.
Tokyo is on its way to surpass the New York's Wall Street,
becoming the #1 stock market in the world, right?
As for the US,
in three years from 1984 to 1986, the market capitalization
of the stocks in circulation dropped by 10%.
And the reason was, fearing an external takeover,
the companies were repurchasing their own shares.
Because the fewer your shares are,
the more each one costs.
Right, it was the same for Japan.
The number of stocks sold and bought
was relatively small.
Then, among all the stocks in circulation, about 70 to 75%
were exchanged through B2B schemes.
The market, therefore, descended
into a chronic shortage of stocks.
And if we look at the price-earnings ratio,
Japan is roughly four times ahead of the US.
For instance, said NTT shares
are reaching a whopping coefficient of 200!
But why does such an abnormal situation
only come into being in Japan?
There's a lot of residue money,
not being put to any use.
Come to think of it, my friend's uncle
works as a subcontractor for Iwamizu Heavy Industries.
Recently, when he came to pay off his debt...
Oh?
We have no objections to you keeping this money
and using it as you see fit for some more time.
Even if you say so, we don't need any more equipment
that we could spend this money on.
Our parent company is too freaked out by the strong yen,
so the work is tapering off on our end.
You're letting us down...
You're the ones letting me down!
Nobody ever gave me that look
when I'd come to return his money!
The president of Yonemura Real Estate
came to see you.
Very well.
Kid, finish with the formalities here.
Hm?
If it isn't Yonemura, the Real Estate maven!
Need acquisition funds, same way as last year.
Would you like a loan?
So, regarding the amount...
We'll lend you as much as you need!
Don't hold back when using it.
H-Huh?
Even if you invest into the equipment,
there won't be any job.
Even if you want to buy a house,
the plot would cost a fortune.
You can deposit the money,
but the interest rates are low.
All that money that has nowhere else to go
ends up accumulating at Kabutocho.
The average investment yield
of the stock is 34% in the US.
But it's only 0.5% in Japan.
Developing a Portfolio System that meets the needs
of the Japanese market is going to be a bumpy ride.
That's why I was hoping for some advice from you...
At the end of the day,
you appeal to our friendship again.
Think of it as of Japanese style of doing business.
When he invited me out, I thought,
"Sure enough, that'd be awfully awkward!"
So I said, "Why don't we invite Sawako with us too?"
Maybe I can learn something new from you
while drinking with you!
Oh, quit that farce, you!
So if you'd allow me...
This new product you're promoting,
"Portfolio System," right?
Straight to business!
That's right.
Surely enough, you know that the Japanese and the US markets operate so closely it's like they're tied together.
Yes.
Hence, the portfolio system takes into account
the American long-term and short-term interest rates,
commodities, oil and stock markets, etc etc,
predicting a whole assortment of indexes
to assist the fund managers
in making right investment decisions.
Long story short,
is it a system for minimizing the losses?
You can't expect our national money game
to go on forever like this.
But isn't it a good thing? Everyone is getting richer.
However, any game is bound to end, isn't it?
Exactly. Moreover, "game" implies
there would be a winner and a loser.
In this case, the game loser
will lose money as well, right?
Yes.
That includes the NTT shares too?
There's no such thing as risk-free stock.
Our Matsumoto never ceases to amaze!
Ah, here, let me pour you another...
I need to take my leave now.
I've got work to do.
Even this late?
Actually, just the right time to make a call to the US.
Thanks for the treat.
I hope you've learned your share, kid.
Hmpf! Just forget it and drink already!
Hello, Martin. I hope you're having
a very refreshing morning.
I just sent you the data on the New Breed Market,
which is overflowing with money.
Manhattan Trust Head Office
This data on the Japanese stock market
is absolutely fascinating.
Basically, whenever I input new data into the system,
I need but to slightly adjust its current state,
so it takes little to no time.
Sorry to trouble you, Anne.
Uh-uh. It's business.
Hey, Miss Sawako. You wanted to know
about the interest rate reversal, right?
Yes. Here, at Kabutocho,
they're gravely nervous about the US interest rate hikes.
So far, it's out of question for the US, right?
The stock prices always move inversely to the interest rates.
That would be so for any country.
If American interest rates spike, and the Japanese rates,
being directly linked to them, follow suit,
Kabutocho would come under the biggest ever bank run,
and the risk a of major crash would become very real.
Kabutocho is full of anticipation for when the violently fluctuating interest rates eventually reach the breaking point
and start climbing rapidly.
For the time being,
I don't register any trends suggestive of a spike.
You've nothing to fear.
Thank you. If you notice any suspicious trend,
please let me know.
Yamagami Brokerage
Sales Department
Presently, the stock market is jumping at its own shadow,
everyone is on pins and needles.
Could it be the apprehension
of the ghost of Rothschilds reappearing?
Must be exactly that.
When everyone is alarmed by the high prices,
and the international currency market
is shrouded in uncertainty,
nobody has any confidence
about making one move or another.
Then, why won't we let out
the ghosts of Rothschilds ourselves?
As far as I'm aware, the New Breed
is universally intolerant to the ghosts.
Goryo Trust Bank
Oh? Yamagami Brokerage placed an order
for selling a huge chunk of their large-cap stocks.
Yamagami selling so early into the month is a rare sight.
Hello? Is it true that your company is selling?
Just in case American interest rates
suddenly turn around and start rising,
we're converting part of our assets into cash.
Oh, really? You nearly spooked me there. Thanks.
It's a very strange move all the same.
Selling 34 million shares all at once...
Hey, they're suspending the trade again.
What's going on? Of 250 Ticker Symbols listed,
trading is suspended for 70 already!
Are we witnessing the advent
of a historical market crash?
In just under 50 minutes,
the market average is down by 1,000 yen already!
Saya, selling 300!
Hayate, 5,000 sold!
All 12 million shares of Hinomoto are sold?
Roger that!
Selling? Gotcha!
Sell! Sell everything!
Sell! Sure thing, everything!
If this continues,
everyone's combined losses would be immense.
Fund Management Department
Ah, Matsumoto!
Director?
The Portfolio System we've discussed before
is completed now.
Even if it's complete now, it's already obsolete!
The American interest rates are about to turn around.
The market average dropped
by 1,000 yen in 50 minutes.
May I use your phone?
New York
Ah, Sawako?
It's midnight on our end.
I'm sorry.
But the rumors of imminent reversal
in American interest rates are circulating like crazy.
Is there any truth to it?
Disinformation.
Nothing more than a false rumor from Practor Brokerage.
It was debunked soon after.
So, before being debunked, it was leaked to Japan,
where it took on a life of its own?
Thank you. May you have
the sweetest dreams tonight.
Ah, Sawako? Give me a minute.
What now? Even a 1,000 yen drop in market average
is nothing to be worried about.
It's just that when the market index median was at 15,600 yen,
the weighting was different
from that of now, at 24,500 yen.
But everyone is too afraid of the possible growth,
to the point where their judgment is hazed.
Sawako, our portfolio system says, "buy now."
The rationale is...
All right. I put my trust in your system.
Hey! Start buying!
Buy it all!
Director!
Hurry up! I assume full responsibility.
Yamagami Brokerage
Eh? Buying?
It's not funny!
Hm? Goryo Trust, huh?
Did the ghost of the Rothschilds
finally start possessing them?
Oh? The decline has stopped after a downfall of 1,066 yen.
Now the buying orders are placed one after another!
The first to switch to large-scale buying was...
Yamagami Brokerage?
Interesting. But does that mean
Yamagami were just aiming to sell short?
At the end of the day, the market average
only decreased by 182 yen 55 sen.
I see. So that's the best the New Breed can do?
Operation Rothschild ended with a great triumph.
Well, thank you again.
Thank you.
The system proved reliable beyond expectations.
But it was all thanks to the trust
that you put in our system.
What do you mean? It's just that I distrust the New Breed,
who are oblivious to the caution, even more.
How would you know
if we don't belong to New Breed as well?
Well, you can be pretty sure
we're not the "Old Guard."
Well, you made someone from the New Breed
reflect on his ways for sure.
Yes. 1,000 shares. Yes.
Damn you, Rothschild.
The ghost of the Rothschilds
was nothing more than an illusion.
However, it would still be premature
to pronounce the ghost dead.
Dormant again, the ghost is waiting patiently
for its next chance to strike.
Driving down the midnight highway,
Mayonaka no highway
Crossing through my memories
yokogitte yuku Memories
Just tonight, I ask you not to speak
Tada damatta mama ano hi~
Eye to eye, we stare at each other
Eye to eye mitsume teta
Some nostalgic love song
Natsukashī Love song
Slowly flowing out from the radio
nagareta From the radio
This sadness,
Tojikometa
Locked away for long
is breaking out again...
kanashimi o tataku yō ni
Oh baby play for me!
Soul music
Sweet soul music
It's suffocating to listen to
setsunaku kika sete
Sweet soul music
I love you!
While you keep singing gently
yasashiku utatte
Translation
Encoding & QC
Perevodildo
WOWmd