Lord!
Guide us, the Children's Crusade,
to the Holy Land of Jerusalem.
Lord!
Where is this ship going?!
Isn't it going to the Holy Land of Jerusalem?
Don't be stupid!
You're going to be sold as slaves
on the Barbary Coast.
This has to be a mistake!
The Pope in Rome ordered us
to go to Jerusalem.
I am the leader, Hans.
You've been sold by the Pope.
Wanna see the contract?
What?!
What's going on?!
Tell us!
Lord!
We believed in you. Is this how
you reward our loyalty?!
Lord!
Johann! Pierre!
Marco!
Michel!
I no longer believe in God!
For my friends who've been betrayed, someday...
Someday, I will take revenge!
I will become a fallen angel
and dispel our humiliation!
St. Michaela School Drifting Story
II
Part 1
Presented by Orphan Fansubs
The wind blows through the gaps in the clouds
And the radiance of freedom pours through
I gathered it with both my hands
And kept searching until I found my true feelings
While seeing gentle dreams
Even the days when I cried
While staring at the darkness
Those days no longer exist
Working hard as usual, I see?
Old Sage!
Has there been any change
in your wife's condition?
No, thanks to you.
Except for her eyes,
she's doing quite well.
I've obtained a good herb.
I'll come by later.
Thank you so much.
How peaceful.
How truly peaceful.
Yes. Since the Amakusa Restoration,
the world has seen no wars.
It's as if time itself has stopped.
Oh, no.
The eternal flow of time
rushes forth with certainty.
As long as there is no countercurrent...
What?
Oh, nothing.
Just talking to myself, that's all.
Say, isn't today the commemoration day
for those who served the cause
of the Amakusa Restoration,
the St. Michaela Girls' Crusade?
Oh, quite right.
Well then, I should also go offer them
a flower or something.
Excuse me.
Girl Crusaders of the Amakusa Restoration
This world, without national
or religious divisions...
Without wars among peoples...
This is the fruit of the Amakusa Restoration,
initiated by these Girl Crusaders
of St. Michaela School.
However, what of the erased history,
starting from the Restoration, through the Greater East Asia War and the Showa period?
Am I the only one that knows
this lost history?
The Restoration only succeeded
because they came from that future.
Thus, whoever remembers even a shred of the lost timeline must be terminated.
No matter who it may be.
Yuki?
Daisuke... Daisuke was killed in battle.
Yuki.
Calm down, Yuki.
Who's Daisuke?
Died in battle? There's no war anywhere.
The Shimabara Rebellion
was the last such thing.
You're right.
The Girls' Crusade overturned
the feudal government.
Then, the Roman Catholic Church and
the Holy Roman Empire were also destroyed.
That's right. No more religions
and no more nations.
No more rotten wars that pit
people against each other.
All thanks to "Amakusa Hans" Aiko.
I don't know what's gotten into me.
All I do is cause you worry.
But for some reason,
every year, when I hear the bell that marks the anniversary of the Restoration,
I get such a headache.
As if some unknown being
is shrieking deep inside my head.
But I'm all right now.
I'm so sorry.
Why? Why is it?
Edo Castle
Aiko, how's your wound?
Kozue!
Good. It's healed a great deal.
I'll be back to my old self soon.
That was an embarrassing mistake.
Not at all.
Since the uprising at St. Michaela School,
we've waged war in Amakusa,
then against the feudal army.
We fought non-stop till we finally
took Edo Castle here.
We all take our hats off to you
for charging into the battle first.
So it's no wonder you got hurt.
Nothing to worry about.
St. Michaela School, huh?
Even after all this,
I can still remember it like yesterday.
Sorry I'm late! I'm Mimura Aiko.
I'm the new transfer student.
You have some gall
for a new transfer student.
Where's your cross?
Dyed hair is against the school rules.
So are those shoes and socks!
Wearing pierced earrings is an outrage!
Everyone's all alike?
What about our personalities?
If you defy me, I'll have to discipline you!
Wow! An S&M show?
Hit me hard, harder, please!
Oh, harder! Right there!
Mimura!
Mimura Aiko!
Mimura Aiko, you have broken school rules on your first day and rebelled against the sister.
Therefore, in the name of the Girls' Crusade,
we are going to punish you.
In the name of the Girls' Crusade, we are going to punish you.
No way. You guys are kidding, right?
...punish you...
It must be a joke.
...going to punish you...
I couldn't believe how fierce Rika
and everyone were toward me.
That was my first acquaintance with Rika and the others.
No sooner did I join the college than I was on display as an example of bad behavior.
But thanks to that, I learned of the Dean's
right-hand man, Karino Daisuke,
and his conspiracy at St. Michaela.
And then...
Devil!
You've come to ruin the sublime mission of the Girls' Crusade. You're the Devil!
The Devil?
Does the Devil...
Does the Devil have...
these on her back?
Wing marks...
An angel?!
I confided everything to Rika.
I told her that the transfer student Mimura Aiko
is an alias for Hans, the leader of the Children's Crusade,
and about the tragedy of my fellow crusaders back in 1212.
Similar events are unfolding right now.
Using the name of God,
the Dean claims she's preparing you girls for stardom with the Takarazuka Revue.
In fact, it's a front for
a secret military mission,
organized by Karino Daisuke,
whereby you will be sent
to the battlefield as sex slaves:
the Michaela Project.
That's a lie.
If I showed you proof that I am Hans,
in spite of being a woman...
would you believe me?
A hermaphrodite...
Love is born out of freedom.
Forced celibacy is but a delusion,
made up in God's name.
Come on.
You're an angel?
I'm not the kind of angel
that's been blessed with the grace of God.
I'm a fallen angel, here to kill God.
Now I need your help, Rika.
Hans...
No... Aiko!
Thus began our battle.
D-Devil...
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
"Devil,"
you say?!
The Pope
betrayed
me!
I came here from a slave ship
in the Mediterranean, across time!
I am Hans Heilner!
Then, in the battle
against Shiro of Amakusa...
Well done on making it here.
I am Shiro Tokisada of Amakusa.
Why did you bring us here?
In this part of the world, I am God.
Fight alongside me. Paradise is near.
No!
We've come here to kill God. We won't tolerate any god, anywhere in the world!
Oh?
Let me show you the power of a god!
You fraud!
There is no God. Don't be fooled!
Rika!
Hans...
I love you.
At least...
I'm going to die after
experiencing a first love.
Thank you, Hans...
Aiko...
Rika... Rika...
Rika!
Rika...
Ikeda Rika...
Is that my name? I don't know.
Together with Hans Aiko,
Ikeda Rika revolted at St. Michaela
and died in Amakusa.
You're her departed spirit.
Died in Amakusa?!
I died?
Does that mean
I'll never see Aiko or Hans again?
I want to see Aiko, my first love...
Do you want to see her?
Do you want to see "Amakusa Hans" Aiko?
Who are you?
How is it?
Her eye is internally damaged.
Here, gramps.
If applying this doesn't heal it,
it might just be incurable.
I don't care if my eyes ever
return to normal again.
Oh, stop it.
You mustn't think like that.
Your condition, one might say, is psychological.
It stems from your own attitude.
My attitude?
There's something you don't want to see.
That's the source of your problem.
Something I don't want to see?
Right.
Old Sage, what could it be?
You shouldn't brood over it.
Right, Yayoi?
Yes. Sooner or later, you will remember.
Just be patient.
Do you think so?
I do.
Okay... May I ask you one more thing?
What is it?
The dead...
Is it possible to raise the dead?
Raise the dead?
It's not impossible,
but it certainly is a large undertaking.
I... I can communicate with the dead.
There's a certain teenage girl that I recalled.
Her name is Ikeda Rika.
Ikeda Rika?
One of the girl crusaders from St. Michaela.
She died as a martyr during the Shimabara Rebellion.
Yes,
one of the heroes of the Restoration.
Alongside their leader, Amakusa Hans Aiko,
she became a much respected figure.
Why on Earth did you recall her?
When I talk to her, I feel as if
I'm talking with the "me" of old.
She died before fulfilling her feelings
for her first love and was unable to pass on.
Though I've consummated my own,
there's another "me" inside.
She has lost her first love
and is crying, as it were.
Do you use a particular
mediumistic incantation?
Yes.
I've tried to revive her, but she only becomes an illusion and then disappears.
Because the spirit has no flesh.
Her consciousness is intact,
but her body is long gone.
So it's impossible?
When you don't have the actual body,
you provide a substitute.
For instance...
Here's something that could
become her body.
A soulless but mobile doll.
So I need to recall the spirit
and plant it in the doll?
Yes, but...
It is only a substitute body,
so the spirit won't live long.
Besides, Yuki...
One wrong move,
and your own soul could be taken.
I don't mind.
Humor my one and only wish, please.
A living and vital ghost.
Thy name is nothingness.
Out of nothingness cometh nothingness.
However, nothingness hath life.
By forces yet unseen,
I shall bestow life in thee.
Non cogito, ergo non cogito.
Non sum, ergo non sum.
If the night raineth and the morning cometh, then blood shall be poured out.
How much longer must thou
sleep on a lotus bed?
The evening of the Sabbath
hath now expired.
The dead, raise thyself slowly,
as it is thy wish.
Dear dream!
Ah... Dear dream!
How much longer wilt thou sleep
on the bed of Nirvana?
The banquet of Sabbath is all but through.
O devil, raise thyself slowly, as it is thy wish.
Ah... Dear dream!
Do you recognize me?
Wake up! Say your name!
Ikeda Rika...
Do you recognize the name
of Amakusa Hans Aiko?
Amakusa Hans Aiko...
The St. Michaela Girls' Crusade...
Aiko!
Mimura Aiko!
Daisuke!
I want to see her!
I want to see Aiko!
This is bad! Calm her down, Yayoi!
Okay!
Mimura Aiko...
Daisuke...
It was not a mistake.
My memory was not wrong.
Aiko...
Yuki, what are you plotting?
I want to recover the lost memory.
No, I want to know the truth.
You mustn't!
You were the one who told me to remember
what I don't want to see.
I would do anything for it,
even give up my soul!
But...
When should I surrender my soul?
"Time, be still. You are beautiful."
The moment you feel that way.
Time, be still. You are beautiful.
But I won't let you!
Yayoi.
Yes!
Wait!
You evil-natured woman...
What you wish to know
and are afraid to remember...
What lies in the turmoil
of conflicting emotions...
is the other history!
The other history?
This time, I'll have to fight you myself.
You know the other history, don't you?
Please tell me what really happened.
Please answer me, Old Sage.
I've gotten old.
Ikeda... Rika?
Ikeda Rika, can you hear me?
Ikeda Rika, do you recognize me?
Yes...
Kozue, what's on your mind?
The same thing that's on yours, probably.
That our mission isn't over yet.
When we revolted at St. Michaela,
our original plan
was to take the time tunnel in the chapel
and help Hans save
his fellow crusaders, right?
Back to Rome in 1212?
No can do. Aiko's still recovering.
I know that. She's spent.
We can let her rest here awhile.
Huh? You mean...
We can go without her.
Kozue, don't forget Aiko is Hans.
And now you're suggesting
we leave her here and go on our own?
The St. Michaela Girls' Crusade
has already proven its worth
through its success against the feudal government.
I... disagree.
I'm staying.
Very well. Whoever wants
to stay should stay.
I'll take my group with me.
What's the matter, Mayumi?
It's about Kozue and her group.
What about Kozue?
You see, they left for Rome.
For Rome?!
1212 AD
Rome
Bring it on!
Johann!
Pierre.
Hey, Pierre.
I knew you would volunteer too.
I'm Marco. Nice to meet you, Pierre.
Nice to meet you.
I swear I'm gonna be the first to get
to the Holy Land of Jerusalem.
Only if you can beat me.
Pierre...
Isn't Hans with you guys?
He's the leader.
He must've arrived ahead of us
to take direct orders from the Pope.
Really? He's the leader?
Of all the boys in the Holy Roman Empire,
Hans is the one most devout, after all.
Besides, he's also the most skilled!
By the way, let me introduce you to Francois
from the Kingdom of the Franks.
I'm Francois. I'm going to prove myself
just as worthy as you boys.
She's a peppy one.
I'd have to be, to enlist in the Crusade.
That's true!
My dear children.
On this very day,
I am overjoyed to receive you all.
As you already know, there have been many crusades to reclaim Jerusalem,
which has been taken away
from us by the Seljuk Turks.
Therefore, this time, we're going to rely on you children, who are still pure in your hearts.
One could say, you are angels who have
been blessed with the grace of God!
The adults have failed
to take back the Holy Land.
But not you!
You are angels, and therefore,
God's servants.
To prove it, you have wings on your backs.
Those with little faith may miss them,
but I can see them!
This Children's Crusade
is certain to succeed!
Go directly to Marseilles!
Marseilles is the gateway
to the Mediterranean Sea.
There, God will answer your pure prayers
and part the sea in two.
Yes, just as the Red Sea did for Moses!
Do not fear.
The Lord is with you.
The parted sea will lead you straight
to the Holy Land of Jerusalem.
It will guide you all.
Now, I will introduce you
to your leader...
Hans Heilner!
That's our Hans!
Hans!
That's Hans?
Our leader.
The Lord will always watch over us.
Together, we shall win the holy war!
In the name of love and the Holy Ghost,
may glory be with the Children's Crusade!
May glory be with the Children's Crusade!
Someone named Gonza wants to see Aiko.
It's been a while.
What brings you here, Gonza?
Yuki seems to have awakened.
She has?
Has she been here?
No.
I can't find her.
I thought she'd definitely
end up on this side.
Where could she possibly be?
I'll be damned!
You know?
Kozue's group is in danger!
Prepare to leave!
Aiko?
Get everyone ready.
We're charging into the Holy Roman Empire!
Oh?
Rika.
What are you waiting for, Misayo?
It's Rika. Rika!
No way. In Amakusa, she...
But look!
Rika! You lived?!
So when I came to,
I was being looked after by a fisherman.
That's why we couldn't find you.
It was a bloody war.
There were bodies everywhere.
Hard to tell who was who.
But I'm so glad to see you again!
Sorry I caused you such trouble.
But how did you get here?
Yeah, how did you get here?
I heard that after going back in time
to Amakusa, you overthrew the Shogunate.
So, I knew that Aiko, or rather, Hans would bring you here to save his fellows.
Sharp thinking as usual, Rika.
With Rika, we're unbeatable.
What a boost to our morale!
Absolutely!
Did you find Mimura Aiko?
She's not there.
She's not?
But Takemiya Kozue and her group
are headed toward the Vatican.
They are planning to join the Crusade.
I knew it. So that's why.
What do you mean?
If I combine your story with what I know,
the Amakusa Restoration
impacted the whole world,
because Aiko was Hans Heilner,
the leader of the Crusade.
The girls of St. Michaela must have led the World Restoration.
Miss Yuki?
What?
Why do you obsess about these things?
You need only do as I say.
But...
But?!
Ikeda Rika! You've died once, haven't you?
Don't forget you owe me
for reviving you!
Yes, ma'am.
Your second life won't last very long.
When your mission is complete,
I'll allow you to live freely.
I will infiltrate the Crusade as one of the soldiers.
You stay with the St. Michaela students.
Everything is my fault
for leaving it up to Daisuke.
If I myself had fought,
we wouldn't have lost the war.
Daisuke?
Miss Yuki?
I am Aaron.
I am a soldier of the Children's Crusade, Aaron.
Aaron?
Everyone, we'll finally depart tomorrow.
It's imperative that you act responsibly!
I've already relayed your order.
Don't worry!
Oh?
You're looking like a real leader, Hans.
I've been entrusted with the duty of bringing all of you to the Holy Land of Jerusalem.
Hans, did you know?
Support has arrived from Japan today.
Support?
They say they're students
of St. Michaela School.
All girls, to boot!
All girls?
Must be a courageous bunch.
Where's Japan?
It's an island nation in the Orient, they say.
Oh... Is it farther away than Mongolia?
Come to think of it, the one who came here yesterday is also from Japan, isn't she?
Excuse me.
I'm Ikeda Rika, from Japan.
I'm Hans Heilner.
How do you do?
Hans... You are Hans.
But, right now, you don't know me yet.
Rika!
You're here already?
Hi there.
We got separated on the way.
We were worried.
I knew we would find you here.
Just as Kozue said.
Allow me to introduce you to my friends.
This is their leader, Hans.
Hans Heilner.
That's Hans.
Hans before he came to St. Michaela.
The Hans who doesn't know us.
So you're Hans?
Wow! You know Hans?
That's incredible!
Word of Hans has even
reached the Orient!
Oh, I'm Michel.
Pierre.
Johann.
And Marco. Nice to meet you.
I'm Takemiya Kozue.
Aoike Kumi.
Hagio Misayo.
Yamato Watoko.
Well done coming all this way.
I must tell you...
We have come all this way
with the intent of dissuading you from going to Jerusalem.
In fact, you shouldn't
even go to Marseilles.
Why?!
It's a long, long way to Marseilles.
You would be faced with fever
and disasters.
Nonsense! We're prepared for all trials!
Hardship is the path we've chosen.
That is the path of love and tribulation
that the Lord preached!
Do you support us or not?
We do.
Then why?
If you insist on going,
we'll go with you, of course.
What are you trying to say?
Right now, this is all we can tell you.
Excuse us.
Go figure.
Some allies.
Aren't you going with your fellows?
N-No.
What could they be thinking?
Do you know?
Yes. Ah... I mean, no.
Who's there?
My name is Aaron.
I've enlisted in the Children's Crusade.
I have something very important
to tell Your Holiness.
Come in.
What is it you want to tell me?
Will you please trust me?
I'd have to hear you first.
In order to earn your trust,
I shall offer you my body.
Y-You...
You are...!
A hermaphrodite!
"An eye for an eye" is one
of the heathen's sayings, naturally.
But I find myself up against vicious treacheries of the Devil's own androgynous servant.
The Devil's servant?
The Devil is coming to hinder
the expedition of the Children's Crusade.
No matter what happens,
you must get them to Jerusalem.
Or, at least, to Marseilles.
For your own good...
Wh-What exactly do you know?!
Everything!
That is why
I am offering my body to you.
Wh-What do you take me for?
I'm the Pope...
I...
I know all about your secret pastimes,
Your Holiness.
My lips are sealed.
So, please, enjoy my body
to your heart's content.
My life is on the line.
The end justifies the means.
I trust you... trust you...
Even if I have to discard this body,
I will consummate my true love.
Daisuke, I promise you I will bury all the Aiko Mimuras of the world.
Yuki!
I won't let you have it your way.
Marco and his fellows,
and our own St. Michaela comrades...
I won't let them be sold into slavery!
Let's go, everyone,
to the Holy Roman Empire!
Yeah!
For the sake of this world I have finally built,
and as long as you don't kill me... and Hans,
let's fight, Yuki!
I've been waiting for your hand forever
Drowning and sinking in the depths of sadness
Freed from all doubt
I dream of the time when I could swim freely
I'm born again
Over the waves, beyond the sea,
the wind will blow me to the faraway land
Let the ship sail away in search of the future
You are best and best I need
Taking all the sadness
This is the bleeding heart
Now the echo starts to rewind here
Translation
Translation Check
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raw Provider
Brenda Foxx
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
imatu
ProxyMan