That's...
Karino Daisuke?
And Sister Yumiko?
Yuki, I regret to inform you
that my St. Michaela Project has failed,
because the academy girls rebelled.
To save Japan, I've joined a kamikaze unit
and am leaving for Okinawa tomorrow.
Daisuke...
The fate of the Empire depends
upon today's battle!
I have formed this special attack unit
to carry out a most heroic act of courage.
You must promote the tradition
of the glorious Imperial Navy.
Be an example of honor
for the next generation to follow!
Wipe out all of the enemy fleet,
thereby building the foundation
of an immortal empire!
Was that the end of Karino Daisuke?
But how on Earth...
Kumi.
Wh-Who's there?!
Aoike Kumi of St. Michaela School.
Now, at last, I shall...
I shall avenge Daisuke's death!
St. Michaela School Drifting Story
II
Part 2
Presented by Orphan Fansubs
The wind blows through the gaps in the clouds
And the radiance of freedom pours through
I gathered it with both my hands
And kept searching until I found my true feelings
While seeing gentle dreams
Even the days when I cried
While staring at the darkness
Those days no longer exist
Kumi!
Why?
Who did it?
Just horrible...
Miss Yuki...
Right now, I am Aaron.
You killed Aoike Kumi, didn't you?
I did.
But not Aiko! You're not planning to kill Aiko, are you?
Not so loud!
Come.
Ikeda Rika.
You seem to have forgotten
you're living on my terms.
I could easily banish you here and now.
Please spare me that, Miss Yuki!
Strip down.
Let me get it through to your body
that you're my servant!
Aiko...
You've surrendered your body to me,
but your soul is still reserved for Aiko?
Miss Yuki, if you kill Aiko...
Then what?
I will commit suicide right here
and take you with me.
Don't worry. I don't plan to do Aiko any harm whatsoever.
My objective is to send the Children's Crusade to Jerusalem, no matter what.
No...
Stop...
Send the Children's Crusade to Jerusalem?
Then why are you conniving against my comrades from St. Michaela?
Your objectives are the same!
Quiet!
It's just...
Yes?
Just as you love Aiko,
I too have someone I love.
Be on your way.
We're leaving tomorrow.
Yes...
Daisuke...
Yuki.
Before my departure,
I'd like us to have a wedding.
Daisuke...
Daisuke!
If only Aiko Mimura hadn't
come to St. Michaela,
my dear Daisuke would not have died.
All I have to do is kill Hans.
Then he can't reincarnate as Mimura Aiko.
Nor can he come into our time.
Please wait, Daisuke.
I'll do everything in my power
to protect your life.
Miss Yuki intends to kill Hans.
I must do something, or Hans...
No, rather, Aiko's life will be in danger.
Lord!
We pray that through your guidance we may safely reach the Holy Land of Jerusalem.
That voice... Hans?
I must tell him.
If we're destined to unite at some point,
I will swallow my shame
and use my body to convince him.
...so that the wind will be calm
over the ocean.
Lord, keep your loving hand
of guidance upon our journey.
Amen.
Hans.
Y-You are Ikeda Rika.
Wh-What are you doing here half-naked?!
One of my fellows has died.
A girl named Aoike Kumi.
What?
What is happening to us
will happen to you as well.
We are now also a part
of your Children's Crusade.
Someone is targeting you.
What are you driving at?
Won't you please cancel the expedition?
Not that again!
I've told you.
I was born for this mission.
About a year ago, someone stood
at my bedside and said:
"Go to Jerusalem."
And now I'm sure I heard the Lord.
Do you believe in God?
It is you, Hans, that I want to believe in.
Me?
You've taught me a way of living
that I could not have imagined.
When? I only just met you yesterday!
But we have met before.
To be precise, we will meet
hundreds of years from now.
We were lovers.
What are you saying?
That you've come backwards in time?!
Yes. I don't blame you
for not believing me.
But back in my time,
you were my first love.
First love?
We even consummated our love once, with our bodies.
If there is fate, if there is destiny, you need but to touch my skin to believe my heart.
It's immoral!
With unspoiled purity as our shield,
we the Crusade must rise up
and proceed toward the Holy Land.
How dare you!
I will protect your life with my own!
Get out, you filth.
Hans!
If you don't, I will!
Cover yourself!
What can I do?
What a disaster!
Hans and the Children's Crusade
have already departed!
What?!
Why did they?!
How would I know?
Regardless, we've got to follow them.
Everyone, ready your gear
and meet up in 30 minutes!
Marco, is everything okay
with your carriage?
Hi, Hans.
Your order was so abrupt.
We had to leave in a hurry.
I received a revelation from God.
We are protected by the Lord, after all.
Francois? You were supposed to be
in the carriage further back.
By the way, I don't see those girls from Japan
who came to support us anywhere.
Yeah... I'm sure they'll catch up later.
Not like we need their support.
We can manage fine on our own.
Right?
Recently, I've heard rumors
of bandits that prey on pilgrims.
Let them try if they dare.
We'll hand them their due
punishment, right, leader?
We'll spare no one that stands in our way.
That's right!
What's that?
What happened?
Bandits!
Get them, you bums!
No! Stop!
No!
Francois!
Dammit...
Stop it!
No! Stop!
Beast! No!
Please stop...
Lord...
Dammit...
Charge!
What?
That's the support from St. Michaela!
Don't you underestimate us girls!
We're the Girls' Crusade!
The veterans of a hundred battles...
...who wiped out the feudal army!
Aiko!
Mayumi?
We just missed them. The Children's Crusade left early this morning.
Kozue's group too?
They were led by Hans Heilner.
Aiko, that's you.
Let's go. I know the route
they're taking to Marseilles.
To Marseilles!
You're here at last, Aiko.
No, Hans!
Hans.
Leave me alone, please.
It's Francois!
How awful!
Don't just stand there!
Take her down!
Give her a burial!
It's against the Lord's word
to take your own life,
no matter how desperate you are.
Hans! Do you still believe in the Lord?
These trials are also God's will.
We will overcome all trials and surely reclaim the Holy City of Jerusalem!
Are you all right, Marco?
Yeah...
You're burning up!
Hans!
How's Marco?
We can't get his fever down.
Misayo is making an herbal remedy
with river water.
Thank you.
It's amazing how you predicted
the fever that's ailing Marco.
Rika?
This is Aaron.
He's been sent directly
by the Pope to aid Hans.
Perhaps you are God's messengers,
capable of prophecy?
Nothing like that.
We've come here denying God's existence.
Right?
Huh? Yeah...
Okay, it's done.
Just enough for now.
Rika, why don't you bring it to them?
Yes. May I, Misayo?
Yes. I'll be joining you
as soon as I make some more.
I've got to make enough
to get us to Marseilles.
Pretty handy, huh?
I'm like the medic of the St. Michaela troop.
You can save someone else's life,
but I bet you can't save yours.
Wh-Why?
Misayo!
Look!
Hey, look.
Misayo.
What happened?
Misayo has been killed.
The killer is here among us.
What do you mean?!
You suspect us?!
Misayo said, "The Children's Crusade,"
before drawing her last breath.
What?
Hey, let's stop this!
This is no time to turn on one another.
Rika? Are you taking their side?!
Watoko!
I won't tolerate any more insults from you!
Stop it, every one of you!
Marco, you should be in bed!
It's my fault.
If only I hadn't caught this fever...
Misayo would still be alive.
It's all my fault...
Misayo!
Marco...
Everyone, let's give Misayo a proper burial.
So we've failed to keep them from advancing,
and they made it to Marseilles.
Kumi's dead. So is Misayo.
If we hadn't left Aiko behind and gone
without her, maybe they wouldn't have died.
Watoko, what do you mean?
It's your fault, Kozue.
We should have waited
for Aiko to recover!
Too late now.
Kozue!
You punk!
We're here, and nothing can be done about it now, can it?
Aiko...
Everyone, we're almost there!
We're not far from Marseilles.
Hang in there!
Yeah!
I must avert Yuki's evil plot.
Or else, I will vanish from this world.
And the Amakusa Restoration, the world
without nations or religions, will never happen!
I can smell the sea breeze.
The sea...
The sea! Hey, it's the sea!
I can see the Mediterranean!
We finally made it!
Jerusalem is just beyond this sea.
God, our Lord, has indeed seen us
through our journey.
Thank you, Lord.
And thank you, Kozue and fellows.
And now, you're on your own.
What? Do you still hold a grudge against us?
Hell, no.
I'm afraid the Mediterranean won't part for you.
Nonsense!
There will be no miracle.
That's when you'll finally realize the Pope has betrayed you.
What?!
Rather, you've been betrayed by
the very religion you cherished.
It's a lie!
You're going to be sold to a slave ship!
Waving a contract with the Pope, the traders will take you all to Africa!
Are you mocking us?!
I've had enough of this!
Stop it!
We must pray.
A miracle will happen.
The sea will part.
We will get to the Holy Land.
As long as we believe in Him, the Lord will hear us and answer our prayers!
That's right! Hans is right!
Let us pray.
Our Father who art in heaven...
Our Father who art in heaven.
We the Crusaders have come here to take back Holy Jerusalem from the heathens.
Lord, please open our way
through the Mediterranean.
Amen.
Look! The sea is swelling!
The sea...
The sea is parting!
The way to the Holy Land
has been opened.
Let's proceed to Jerusalem!
To Jerusalem!
Wait!
Kozue, you have nothing more to tell us.
The sea has parted.
The promise has been fulfilled.
Those slave traders you feared
are nowhere in sight.
This can't be happening.
It's impossible!
This must be some sort of trickery!
Don't be deceived!
Listen carefully.
These women have only pretended
to support our cause!
Aaron!
Remember what they said?
If the sea doesn't part, it proves to us
that the Pope has lied about everything.
But the sea did part!
After witnessing a miracle,
why would they still deny it?
Because they are fallen angels
trying to destroy the Pope!
They're the Devil's servants!
What?!
Leave them to me to handle.
Hans, lead your fellows across the sea.
Rika.
Let's cross the sea together.
Only Rika has true faith in the Lord.
Let's go, everyone!
We're crossing the sea!
Yeah!
Kozue, forgive me.
I'm doing this for Hans... no, Aiko.
Aiko...
Watoko!
Eiko!
Kozue!
What about Kumi and Misayo?
All wiped out, most likely.
It can't be...
Yuki-san, I presume?
Right. I've been waiting for you,
Mimura Aiko.
You would disrupt the peaceful flow of time just for one man?
I wouldn't expect you to understand.
You intend to resurrect the dreadful Michaela Project once again?
The Michaela Project doesn't have to happen.
You're trying to resurrect the dark history
on behalf of Karino Daisuke, aren't you?
That means...
Daisuke belongs to me alone.
I will keep him from going to St. Michaela.
That is impossible.
It doesn't matter what you do.
In this timeline, the uprising at St. Michaela
will serve as a springboard
to the Amakusa Restoration, and ultimately the World Restoration as well, regardless.
Karino Daisuke will disappear again in the tide of a new history.
On the contrary!
It's you who will disappear!
Kill them!
Aiko!
They're no longer our Kozue and the girls.
They're only zombies,
manipulated by Yuki's sorcery!
Kozue...
Kill or be killed.
It's no use fighting back.
Iwadate!
Mayumi!
Now, Mimura Aiko, you're the only one left!
Be a good friend and follow
the others to Hell!
So that's it?!
Try manipulating them now!
Why, you!
Aaron!
Are you all right?
We were worried, so we came back.
Pierre, Johann, Marco, Michel...
Who are you?
Guys! It's me, Hans!
Pierre, Johann, Marco, Michel...
Rika?
Aiko!
What... You were alive?!
There she is. I'm finally seeing Aiko again!
Rika...
Aiko!
Everyone!
She is the leader of the Devil's support troop, the girls of St. Michaela, Mimura Aiko!
Destroy the Devil!
Stop! Don't do it!
I don't want to fight you!
Then stop resisting!
Michel!
You leave me no choice!
I'll just have to make you sleep awhile.
Hans!
Johann! Marco! Pierre! Michel!
Hans, let me explain.
There's a reason for this...
Did you do this?
Who are you?!
I'm Hans Heilner.
That's me!
Because you are me.
The Devil!
Stop!
You mustn't hurt me.
It'll be a catastrophe for everyone!
Please, Hans. She is you.
Y-You're...
Aiko!
I did it! I did it at last!
I've destroyed Mimura Aiko!
Daisuke, I'll fly over to you right away.
Daisuke... Daisuke!
Here I am, Yuki.
Daisuke!
Finally... we finally meet again!
With this, 735 years from now,
I will be able to live out my life with you.
That is impossible.
I have sunk to the bottom
of the southern sea.
No, you don't have to die this time!
We can go back to the time
before our wedding.
It's impossible, Yuki.
There, look at that.
B-But that's...
Indeed, it has begun.
The World Restoration.
The World Restoration?
You're not Daisuke!
Who are you?!
It's me.
My dear!
Then, Daisuke...
Karino Daisuke has disappeared.
Now that the World Restoration
has become a reality,
his existence has no place
in this particular space and time.
I can stop this vile World Restoration!
Yuki!
Your Holiness! You're unharmed.
You're Aaron!
I see. This is your doing.
Wh-What do you mean?!
The Children's Crusade that left for Jerusalem
has returned to attack us because of a contract
they found on some slave dealers' ship.
Th-This must be some sort of conspiracy
that you instigated!
I... I tell you, he's a hermaphrodite!
He's the Devil's messenger!
What are you doing?!
Stop it!
A hermaphrodite! How did this happen?
We mustn't keep it alive!
We must kill it!
You wretched creatures...
You should all burn in the fires of Gehenna.
F-Forgive me...
P-Please don't kill me.
Please spare my measly life! I beg you!
Die!
D-Devil...
Fool. It is you who will end up in Hell.
The Restoration has been completed.
That voice!
Old Sage!
So you were alive?
You've just sealed it yourself, dear Yuki.
You've now completed
the World Restoration.
What do you mean, Old Sage?!
All these events were preordained, Yuki.
From the founding of St. Michaela School, to the student uprising,
as well as the Amakusa Restoration,
all the way to the World Restoration.
All were merely playing a part
in the history of this world.
Now, Yuki. Try to remember.
How peaceful and plentiful was
the world post-Restoration.
But for Daisuke...
Don't be foolish.
Those who are tied to the dark history
are doomed to perish.
But, Old Sage, your explanation doesn't convince me!
Yayoi! You're alive?!
Mimura Aiko! Ikeda Rika...
No way...
There's no way! This is ludicrous!
Miss Yuki, even you can't touch Hans-Aiko now.
I have become one with Hans, completely.
Thanks to Rika and Yayoi over there.
We too have been rescued by Yayoi.
Somehow, I don't remember ever
being killed, though.
Well, I had to tweak time a little, you know.
Old Sage, who on Earth are you two?
Yuki, you even forgot that?
Yuki.
My dear!
Come on, Yuki. Try to remember.
Remember those who have lived deep
within the dark and oppressed history.
Gonza!
But your appearance...
Indeed, Gonza has reincarnated
for the better.
He is precisely the one true symbol
of the World Restoration.
And I suppose it's now time for me
to make claims on your life.
Old Sage!
"Time, be still. You are beautiful."
Don't say you don't remember
the pact we made that day.
But I have yet to meet Daisuke...
Yuki, just like Indra's net,
all the worlds are held together by
the reflections they cast on each other.
Now that we have fulfilled our mission,
there's no need for us to stay in this world.
You can understand that too.
But I only wanted... to be with Daisuke.
Old Sage, brace yourself!
Yuki!
Damn you, Mimura Aiko!
You still won't get out of my way?!
Rika!
In the end, I protected the one I love...
Aiko, I love you.
Rika!
This is the end of you, Yuki!
Daisuke... I'm coming to you now...
Time, be still. You are beautiful.
Daisuke!
Yuki!
Daisuke! Here we are at last!
We will be together forever now.
Rika!
Rika...
Aiko...
Rika, hold on!
I'll ask Yayoi for some medicine for you.
You don't have to.
Now that Yuki is gone,
my second life is about to expire too.
I have no regrets.
There is no greater joy
than to die in your arms.
Rika, my heart... will always
belong to you alone.
I'm happy...
Rika?
Rika!
I won't forget you, I promise, Rika.
As long as this world goes on,
you'll keep on living in my heart forever.
Forever.
Come on, here we go!
Yeah!
I've been waiting for your hand forever
Drowning and sinking in the depths of sadness
Freed from all doubt
I dream of the time when I could swim freely
I'm born again
Over the waves, beyond the sea,
the wind will blow me to the faraway land
Let the ship sail away in search of the future
You are best and best I need
Taking all the sadness
This is the bleeding heart
Now the echo starts to rewind here
Translation
Translation Check
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raw Provider
Brenda Foxx
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
imatu
ProxyMan