ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
There are times when a man must fight,
no matter how hard it gets.
My name is Aoyama Kenji.
For the sake of my pride and manhood,
I survived hellish training,
and now I’m stepping into the ring.
But even after all that,
can I really win a match like this?
Skit 8
A Fateful Showdown
Skit 8:
A Fateful Showdown.
Kenji! Do your best!
All right!
Kenpi! Go for it!
All those dreamy memories flooding back…
No good, I can’t focus on the match.
Kenji!
Oh, no...
Looks like it’s our turn already.
You seem bored, Gong Boy.
A high school girl?!
Ah, so this is what they call a gong?
I always wanted to try ringing it.
No, no! It’s my work, so you can’t!
Please! Meguru really wants to ring it now!
Huh? Stop! End of Round 1!
Huh? The gong already?
Wasn’t that a tad too fast?
Kenji! Get it together!
I burned my fire...
Until there was nothing left...
but pure white ash.
It just started!
You can’t burn out already!
Weird, has it really been three minutes already?
Hey, Gong Boy!
Good boy, good boy.
Hey! What are you doing?!
I'm so happy!
I got to touch Shinjo-san himself…
Shinjo Katsuya wouldn’t be shaken
by something like this...
Look at you, getting this big already. So cute!
Shinjo Katsuya would never
lose composure over this...
Never lose what?
I... I suppose I could wait
for just one more minute...
Ah, I'm so glad!
I’ll give you a special service.
Stand up, come on.
Good, good boy. Smooch...
Hey, Shinjo-san, what are you doing?
No, nothing...
Oh, my! You’re so manly
and well-endowed for someone so young.
Hey, what’s with this long break?
It’s already been ten minutes
since Round 1 ended!
Do you hate the breaks that much?
Not at all!
I love breaks, actually!
Thanks!
Kenji, focus!
It’s no use.
Even if his stamina recovers, he can’t win.
In martial arts, the difference between amateurs and pros shows most starkly of all sports.
M-Master?
Don’t worry, Hikaru-san.
Kenji-san gained a certain deadly weapon
during his week of training.
A deadly weapon?
"Name-them-all"         special moves quiz
[parody of "Galactica Magnum" and "Boomerang Telios"
special moves from "Ring ni Kakero" manga]
Hm, like the Galactica Magmag
or Boomerang Teriyaki?
"Name-them-all"         special moves quiz
Don’t shoehorn in more unneeded references.
Hikaru, just watch your beloved boyfriend
in his glorious form.
Hey, just to remind you, I’m still a man!
Oh, right! My bad.
You’re so cute I forgot.
Ugh! Enough dilly-dallying!
Match resumes!
Kenji, fight!
Kenji!
No good! At this rate,
my employee’s gonna get crushed!
Wait!
Unga Sisters appear!
Kenji’s secret weapon will come out now.
The ultimate weapon he gained...
is an unshakable will that won’t give in to temptation, no matter how hard we try to seduce him!
With that kind of patience,
he can withstand any punch!
You can do it, Kenpi!
Wait, hold on.
Hey, are you saying his
“deadly weapon” is just taking punches?
Bingo!
Huh? Even if he doesn’t go down,
he can’t win without attacking!
Crap!
We forgot that part!
What a tough guy.
Ioka, that's enough.
Finish him!
Okay!
Here comes the final punch!
Kenji, now!
Kenji!
Now!
Hikaru!
C-Cross counter!
One!
Two!
Now, let’s break down that exchange.
Okay, roll the VTR.
While delivering his finishing punch,
Ioka overextended, leaving his guard wide open.
So Kenji’s desperate right
landed clean into that opening.
Even Ioka, the champ, couldn’t take that.
It's a perfect hit if I ever saw one.
My! Boxing sure is scary.
And with that, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye...
It’s not over yet!
From the day we first met, my heart's been racing.
For Ioka-kun, his own punching power backfired.
Wow! It’s just like in a real boxing anime!
That's because the timing
for Hikaru’s cheering was perfect.
Huh? You knew about the cross counter?
Not at all, I just went for it.
Why do I feel this way? Oh why? Fate is a question...
Five…
Six…
Stand up! You've got to get up, Kenji!
Kenji-san!
Kenji!
To be continued