ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
When I found out my roommate Hikaru
was actually a girl, my mind went totally blank.
Then Sister Rika showed up to take Hikaru back,
and now my life’s in total panic mode.
Now you see the truth about this man.
His partner doesn’t have to be you,
it literally doesn't matter to him.
Kenji!
Yes, nice... Oh, my!
Goodbye, Kenji
Skit 12
Skit 12:
Goodbye, Kenji.
The truth is, Kenji-san actually
prefers girls like me, right?
Kenji!
You wouldn't agree to this,
unless it's with me, right?
Isn't that right?!
Eh? W-Well, I...
Hikaru-san, no hogging allowed—
sharing is caring!
Kenji!
That’s not true, right, Kenji?
You said you’d love me even if I were a guy.
So now that you know I’m a girl,
you’ve gotta love me even more, right?
Did I actually say that?
Come on, put this
overconfident woman in her place!
Say something like, “I only love Hikaru,”
or “I hate big-breasted women.”
B-But actually, I kind of like them well-endowed...
Do you really hate me?
Oh, Lord! Your body’s talking
for you again, and it can't lie.
N-No! This is merely what we call a courtesy boner—
you know, like polite laughter.
You know, I'm a people person, so it happens for me automatically—be it a smile or a boner.
Oh, Christ...
Look—is this really merely for courtesy?
Now you understand, right?
L-Like hell!
Hey Kenji, I’m better than her, right?
Huh?
Move!
Then... what do you call this?
What are you doing?
Why is it that with Rika you blow up
the solar system, but with me it’s just a tent?
Well, love or not, sometimes it stands,
and sometimes it simply doesn’t.
Kenji...
Kenji, you idiot!
Ah... Hikaru!
I’ll go. You stay here.
Wait, Hikaru-san.
Let me go! I hate you, Rika-san!
Men are just all like that.
You’re still young, so you don’t understand yet.
But I’ll make sure you do.
Hikaru, a girl...?
I mean, she did look like one
from the start, but still...
Rika-san, where’s Hikaru?
She said she needed to cool off a bit.
She’ll be back soon, don’t worry.
I see.
Well then, while the kids are gone...
let’s pick up where we left off.
H-Hey, R-Rika-san, I...
No talking.
Kenji-san’s kisses are so indecent.
Ah... is that so?
If I hadn’t shown up, you probably would’ve done it with Hikaru-san, huh?
Well, maybe...
So sorry to interrupt, darling...
Kenji-san, come here.
R-Rika-san!
Ah! Don’t rush me!
R-Rika-san, Rika-san, here I come!
And once again, the whistle of fate
blows with deep emotion.
Hang in there!
Farewell forever, my womanless youth!
Let’s dig in!
Uh... Hikaru?
What?
Uh, well...
It’s fine, you don’t have to explain yourself.
I don’t really mind.
You don't mind... what?
After all, we two were always just roommates.
Rika-san, will you go back to the convent
and apologize to Papa with me?
Y-Yes.
See you, Kenji.
B-Bye, then.
"We two were just roommates"?
Is that really it?
Hikaru-san, are you really not bothered by it?
Not at all. I learned a lot,
and it was kind of fun.
Every time your gaze meets mine, my heart skips a beat.
Hikaru-san...
I feel it deep inside, a spark running through me.
Kenji, you idiot!
I want to know your fingers...
To be continued