ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
I snuck into the convent to bring Hikaru back,
and as you can see,
my situation's tighter than it's ever been.
Wait!
Hikaru!
The police? That’s too soft!
Skit 15
Heaven and Hell
Skit 15:
Heaven and Hell.
What do you think you’re doing?!
Wh-Where am I?
The reflection room.
It’s where we lock up rule-breakers.
Maki-senpai!
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
Aoyama-kun, you haven’t changed
one bit since university.
Well, Maki-senpai...
Who'd think you were all
fire and energy back then!
Then I got my heart broken,
and my outlook on life changed.
Anyway, hurry.
Right... S-Sure!
What are you doing?!
We’re breaking out of here!
By tomorrow, they’ll hand you
over to the police!
Maki-senpai, why did you
send Hikaru to live with me?
She was miserable being cooped up here.
I figured if I offered you someone to split the rent with, you’d take her in without hesitation.
It's Maki.
Hika—
Thanks, Maki-san.
I guess it worked out.
Yeah.
Hikaru, so you’re the one who rescued me?
Hikaru...
Did it hurt?
Y-Yeah, one punch and I was out cold.
You hit even harder than Ioka.
But, um... Do you feel a little better now?
Of course not, what am I thinking...
My hand...
Huh?
Hikaru?
It... hurt.
Really bad.
Won’t you come back
to live with me again?
Kenji...
Hikaru?
Kenji, you thought I was a guy all along, right?
Yep.
Then the second you found out I was a girl,
you tried to hit on me.
Th-That’s not it!
Didn’t I tell you?
Whether you're a boy or girl, I still...
Actually, I’ve always believed in platonic love.
P-Platonic love?
Rika and the others were saying...
once a man and a woman get physical, they just start tying each other down and lose their freedom.
Th-That’s not true!
They're just overthinking it.
In reality, sex isn’t something
you should be taking so seriously.
Good! Then you don't mind
if we don't do it, right?
Kenji, you’re such a gentleman!
Th-That’s right.
Born and raised a gentleman.
My lady, thank you for this beautiful evening.
To part now would be too cruel.
Until the clock tower chimes,
let’s cherish these fleeting moments of grace.
Do not give in to worldly desires.
Goodbye, my fair lady.
Oh? Kenji, what's wrong?
Huh? Ah, never mind. I was just thinking,
it's nice to talk about love like this sometimes.
Kenji, you're so stoic!
A man can't survive unless he's tough.
But if you're not kind,
you don't deserve to live.
Hey, I feel like a dunce!
Hey, so then, does it mean you wouldn't mind
preserving our pure relationship for life?
This might actually be pretty cool!
F-For life, like...
until we die?
Abstinence
Kenji, what's wrong?
Are you with me?
Enough already.
Huh?
You don’t have to beat around the bush.
You just mean... you don’t like me, right?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Maybe it'd be better if I was still thinking of you as a boy, like before.
Then, we could at least stay friends.
D-Don’t be stupid, I told you I was kidding.
It’s not like I could ever hate you.
You don’t have to force yourself.
The concept of lewdness
is simply too foreign to you.
That’s not true!
Sometimes I think about lewd things too.
Hikaru, you... lewd things?
But for me, it's not sometimes—
it’s all the time.
Even right now,
I’m thinking about you and me...
Oops, I shouldn't fluster you
more by finishing that.
Sorry, forget I ever said something.
Kenji...
Well, then... take care, okay?
Wait!
Uh?
It’s fine, if that’s what you want.
Y-You mean it?
Kenji...
Hikaru!
You sure about this?
Yes...
Kenji, I love you.
Hikaru...
Now I can finally be one with you.
Here I go.
Yes.
Hikaru!
Hikaru! Open this door! Hikaru!
Do you hear me? Open up!
To be continued