ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
You’re late.
I’ve been waiting forever.
Wh-Who is he?
You owe me a kiss of apology for being late.
Wh-What?
In my family, it’s tradition to marry
the person you share your first kiss with.
Ah… so he’s my prince!
Hikaru-chan!
Right, sorry.
Wait, then who was the girl I just kissed?
I’m Aoyama Kenji—an aspiring manga artist,
currently working at a girls’ high school.
My girlfriend Hikaru goes to the same school,
but if anyone finds out, I’m done for.
Skit 21
Palpitation at the Infirmary
Skit 21:
Palpitation at the Infirmary.
N-Nooo!
We can't!
No! It's my first time!
Ah! Amazing!
Omie-san, what’s wrong?
What’s amazing?
U-Uh, um, it's...
I—I’ve got such a terrible fever! I'm red-hot!
That's true. Your face is bright red!
Y-Yeah! It's the fever!
So hot! Amazing! Amazing!
Amazing! Amazing!
Teacher, I’ll take her to the infirmary.
INFIRMARY
Looks like the nurse isn’t here.
Oh right, the thermometer.
Sorry for the trouble, Hikaru-chan.
Hmm, where could it be?
Ever since that kiss,
my body’s been burning up...
Found the thermometer!
Huh?
Isn’t this Kenji’s tie pin?
Delivery slip for the new medicine batch.
Huh? H-Hello! You’re Saito Hikaru
from Class 2-D, right?
She’s asleep, so we don’t have
to pretend to be strangers.
More importantly,
why does Omie have your tie pin?
Wait, but that means...
The one I kissed in the dark was this girl!
I—I dropped it in the hallway earlier.
Oh, so it was her who picked it up?
Really, so that's what it was?
Right, right...
But if Hikaru finds out I kissed this girl...
Well, now, delivery, delivery...
Aren't you afraid of being exposed?
E-Eh? E-Exposed for what?
That tie pin—isn't it the one I gifted you?
It’s engraved “From H to K” on the back!
If anyone sees it, they’ll figure out our secret!
I see...
Right, you’re totally right.
Ah, really worrying...
But you look way too relieved.
A-Anyway, let’s just grab the pin.
Hey!
Don’t you dare touch a girl’s body so casually!
I’ll do it! Okay...
Wh-What now?
You’re hopeless.
I just can’t watch this.
Ugh. I'm always getting stuck
doing things I don't...
SQUEAK
I’ll handle it!
Wow! So soft...
How did she get them to be that big?
Compared to mine...
Grow big... Come on, grow big!
No, focus! This isn’t the time for that!
Oh geez, Omie's really sensitive, isn't she?
Kenji, out!
Sorry, Omie-san.
You’re kinda busty,
so I can't avoid touching your skin.
I'm sorry! Just hang in there a sec, okay?
Oh? Where’d it go?
POP!
H-Hikaru-chan!
N-No, it’s not what it looks like! I'm just...
Wh-What is going on here?!
Ah... I can’t tell her about the tie pin...
Omie-san!
Watch out!
W-We can't, Hikaru-chan!
You’re walking the path of sin!
It’s not what you think!
I was just trying to get your temperature.
And then you suddenly wake up.
Huh? Really, that’s all?
Of course! Do I look like the type to do that?!
Right, you're definitely not that kind of girl.
Phew! That was close.
Hey, did I make any weird noises?
Huh? J-Just a little...
Ahh... Omie Haruka, humiliated for life!
All my dignity, gone in an instant!
Ah... My life is over!
Don’t worry.
I won’t tell anyone.
Hikaru-chan...
Moments like that happen.
I get it. I’m a girl too.
Anyway, I’ll head back to class now.
Get better so you can join us for PE, okay?
Hikaru-chan...
Hang in there, Omie-san!
Thank you, Hikaru-chan...
Next up, Saito Hikaru!
Okay!
After our date, I called you on the phone,
So cool!
Not bad!
So you're good at sports too, Hikaru-chan!
Telling you, "Come over right now," though I knew it was selfish.
Not really...
Hikaru-chan... so cool!
THROB
Just testing your love a little.
SKIP A BEAT
Oh, no, what’s this sudden palpitation?
To be continued