ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I'm Aoyama Kenji.
The other day, I ended up kissing Haruka,
after mistaking her for Hikaru.
The man who stole my first kiss,
though I don’t even know your face or name,
I, Omie Haruka,
long to meet you again someday!
But back then, I had no idea
that’s what she was thinking.
Skit 24
Haruka in Danger!
Skit 24:
My name’s Kyomoto Masashi,
PE teacher at Inran Girls’ High.
Today’s the gymnastics test!
Loosen up while you can.
Okay!
I can’t get this right!
Kyomoto-sensei, please help me!
No fair! I need Sensei too!
Hey now, mess around
and I’ll dock your points.
Geez, Kyomoto-sensei is always so cool!
Yes, on campus they know me as the cool,
nihilistic, hardboiled, pretty-boy teacher.
But the truth is...
Whew, it's driving me crazy!
The scent of pheromones wafting from schoolgirls—that’s what I live for!
I became a teacher
at a high school for girls just for that!
ENCYCLOPEDIA
Futarigurashi Tip Corner:
“Pheromone” comes from the Greek—phérein meaning “to carry,” hormôn meaning “to stimulate.”
Combine the two and you get “pheromone,”
a substance that travels
out of the body to excite others.
Cut the nonsense explanation!
Just breathing in this fragrance feels like my soul’s
strolling through a garden in paradise!
Ah...!
What's this exceptionally strong
pheromone scent?
Omie-san, does it hurt?
Y-Yes, a little...
Ah, what’s wrong with me?
Ever since that kiss the other day,
my body’s been burning up...
No doubt about it—this pheromone scent
comes from a girl in love! For sure!
There’s a poor soul, whose body and soul are writhing in the agony of unrequited love!
And she’s waiting for me!
Omie-kun, are you sick?
“A-Am I sick”?
Just look at my healthy and ripe young body—
do I look sick to you?
W-Well, if you’re fine, good.
Okay, we’ll start with the mat test.
First up—Saito Hikaru!
Yes! Here I go!
You nailed it, Hikaru-chan!
Amazing!
You’re such a natural athlete!
Nice, nice!
Hikaru-chan is the best!
I wanna give her some private lessons someday...
Next—Omie Haruka. Here I go!
Watch out! I dropped my pen on the mat!
Th-This feeling is forbidden...
Ah, but it's so irresistible!
Ah, that's it, I'm feeling it!
You okay, Omie-kun?
You’re acting really weird today.
What happened?
This fragrance! Could she be the source
of all those love pheromones?
Please worry not, it’s nothing!
Still, let’s take you to the infirmary.
O-Okay...
A girl in love becomes hypersensitive.
From here on out, I’m...
Animal Kyomoto!
INFIRMARY
To all sixty-five million Aoyama Kenji fans out there—thanks for waiting!
The main character’s finally here!
Even if I’m just slacking off during work hours
and napping in the infirmary.
No screen time lately—so boring...
Ah... Crap.
Whoa, what’s going on?
Omie-kun, are you okay?
Y-Yes.
Oh? You’re drenched in sweat.
Y-Yes, I get all sweaty sometimes, it’s such a pain...
I’ll wipe you down.
N-No, it’s fine! I can do it...
Look, you’re soaked.
Wh-What are they doing?
Something wrong?
T-Teacher, please, it’s all fine!
T-Teacher, I'm set...
Oh, more sweat?
I gotcha covered.
Ah, no... Stop!
Don't be shy.
If I don’t wipe you down, you’ll catch a cold.
Huh? "There" as in... THERE?
And now for the most important part...
Ah... No!
No way!
Whoa, she’s dripping wet...
This depth, this suction—amazing!
This girl’s something else!
Who the hell are you!
No matter how horny you are,
when a girl asks you to stop, that's a no-go!
You’re... the new office clerk!
Ah, Haruka-chan? You okay?
Y-Yes, thank you very much!
Eh?
Wh-What’s wrong?
That tie pin—yours?
Eh?
Shit! I forgot and put it on as usual!
So? Yes or no?
Oh, it's over! I'm fired!
L-Look, I assure you it's a coincidence
and I can explain it in full...
Eh? Ah?
I’ve been looking for you this whole time!
H-Hold on a moment...
To be continued