ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
The only way for you
and Hikaru-chan to be happy...
is to have lots of abnormal sex.
Abnormal sex?
Skit 18
Let’s Go Abnormal!
Skit 18:
Hang on, Kenji-san, I’ll make you dinner.
Ah, don’t trouble yourself.
First, slice the cucumber.
Can’t see the cucumber past my boobs.
All right.
Target acquired.
Boobs tied up, cucumber found.
Okay, dinner’s ready...
Huh?
Suneo-chan, where’s Kenji?
Huh? He said he’s going
to his part-time job after all?
Come on, why didn’t you stop him?
Will that fortune come true?
Oh please, I just made it up, obviously!
If those two split up,
I can go after Kenji myself.
I’m such a bad girl.
No way, I don’t believe it.
To think I’ll be cursed
unless I have abnormal sex with Hikaru?
No way I’m believing that!
Unless you keep having abnormal sex,
misfortune will keep following you.
No way...
["Wonderful" is the late night variety show that ran on TBS
from 1997 to 2002, the Futarigurashi anime also first aired as part of it;
Azuma Mikihisa was one of the regular hosts]
Did you catch yesterday’s Wonderful?
Yeah!
Azuma Mikihisa, man.
Seriously?
Kenji?
H-Hey. Done with work already?
So unless I please her in some abnormal way,
we’re doomed to fail, huh?
I don’t care what happens to me,
but if that’s what Hikaru’s into, I’ll go all in!
Love is Wonderful
I really do bring bad luck to guys.
Stay back!
I...
I'm not the kind of man
who can make you happy.
What are you saying?
No matter what kind of man you are,
I’ll stay with you.
[Chiaki Hara & Mikihisa Azuma were hosts of "Wonderful" at the time;
they also voice themselves here]
Chiaki...
Mikihisa-san...
I'll never forget that smile, Chiaki.
Your smile is what keeps me going.
Never forget that smile...
Chiaki...
I love you.
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
Hold me, Mikihisa-san.
Hold me hard, tight!
Chiaki...
That hit the spot.
Feeling warm now?
Huh? Your eyes are red.
You weren’t crying, were you?
O-Of course I wasn’t crying.
Come on, really.
I wasn’t...
Kenji!
Wh-What’s wrong?
Will you...
Will you still love me despite the way I am?
D-Despite the way you are?
Abnormal sex!
Hikaru, so you really are...
Kenji...
You can be any way you want,
but you’ll still be my Hikaru.
Really?
Now smile—your smile’s what keeps me going.
You’re saying the same thing as the TV.
What are you doing?
Don't worry, it's fine.
Hikaru, if that’s what you want,
I’ll go along with any kink!
No matter what kind of man you are,
I’ll stay with you, Mikihisa-san!
R-Right, no matter what kind of man Kenji is,
Hikaru will stay with him.
Hikaru, do you like it this way?
Yeah, I love it!
So Iyona-chan was right after all!
We're going to have some fun now, right?
Y-Yeah, something amazing’s about to start.
Yay! Can’t wait!
Eh?
I-Is that also necessary?
O-Of course, didn't I say it's gonna be fun?
If that’s what Kenji wants...
Yeah, should be really fun.
I—I know, right?
No!
On second thought, no!
I'm sorry, Kenji.
I’m not mature enough
to enjoy this kind of thing yet.
But you want to do this
because you love me, right?
I’m sorry, maybe when I grow up?
N-No! I don’t even like
this kind of stuff myself!
Really?
Of course!
Then why are you doing it?
W-Well, there are... reasons...
After our date, I called you on the phone,
Hey, if we keep living together,
you might get cursed with bad luck, you know.
So what? We’ll crush that fate with our love!
Telling you, "Come over right now," though I knew it was selfish.
Kenji...
Hikaru...
I glared at the clock, certain you'd show up,
K-Kenji, are you okay?
Stay with me!
Guess I have to back off for now.
Just testing your love a little.
But one day, I’ll be back for sure!
I’ll be back!
To be continued