ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji, 24,
an aspiring manga artist.
I went undercover on an AV set to rescue Hikaru,
who got scouted as an actress,
but somehow they made me an actor too!
Script change:
a second woman appears,
trying to steal the man...
played by me!
Now, let’s keep rolling!
Skit 33
Ppolaco the AV Actress
Skit 33:
Ppolaco the AV Actress.
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
“Ball Torsion Loving Girl.” Ready... action!
Wonderful
Grand Circus
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Wonderful
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Grand Circus
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Grand Circus
Wonderful
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Wonderful
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Wonderful
Grand Circus
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Wonderful
Grand Circus
Ball Torsion
Loving Girl
Wonderful
Grand Circus
What are you doing, Kenji?
Wonderful
Grand Circus
Step away from that woman!
Wonderful
Grand Circus
T-Troupe Chief!
[For the entirety of this skit, "ball" can be read as "balls"]
I’m the one who polished
your ball routine to perfection!
Have you forgotten that debt?
Please, don’t blame him.
It’s my fault for falling in love with this ball!
This smooth surface... This curvature...
How could I not love it?
It’s because you loved my ball
that I’ve learned to handle it so well.
Aw, how lovely!
No! That ball is mine!
Ah...
Do you dislike women like me?
N-No, of course not...
Good. Such an honest boy.
Now roll this ball for me!
Y-Yes!
He's always like this
when he sees a pretty woman!
Ah... So good!
That rattling sound is irresistible!
I’m glad you’re enjoying it!
All right, Kenji.
Let me roll your balls this time.
Mwah, what a nice smell...
Kenji...
Crap.
I won’t betray her!
I’m a woman who sold her soul
to the devil called cinema.
How could I fall
for a second-rate actor like you...
Next scene!
[Okuhida is famous for its baths (yokujou), "lust" is also "yokujou";
"tanima" is both "valley" and "cleavage"]
Okuhida Desires: Petals of the Valley
"Okuhida Desires: Petals of the Valley."
Ready, action!
Okuhida Desires: Petals of the Valley
Wait, Lady Hikaru!
Why must you go?
Are you still upset that I laid down my spear?
Wasn’t it you, Kenji-sama,
who betrayed me?
I loved the way you thrust your spear...
[Innuendo: pierce me now]
If you still love me, then thrust it now!
Right here, right now—thrust, thrust, thrust!
I can’t.
All I have now are these twin blades.
So stabbing is what you prefer
to thrusting after all.
No! I like both thrusting and stabbing!
That’s all there is to it!
Enough. Farewell, Kenji-sama.
Ah... Lady Hikaru!
Beyond the checkpoint lies Okuhida.
East and west, day and night,
the moon over the Takase River
weeps farewell tears!
Lady Hikaru!
Do not cry.
Sister Kunoichi?
That girl’s just a civilian.
She lives in a different world from us shinobi.
Even without your spear, you still have a sword and a sheath to hold it.
Huh?
Come on, quick.
Draw your blade and slide it in.
Quickly, now!
When drawn, it drips with icy frost.
From its tip, droplets of silver fall.
Behold, the legendary blade—Murasamemaru!
Yes, faster! Faster! Let me take
your Murasamemaru into my sheath!
Bon appétit!
Be more careful, Hikaru-chan!
Sorry, Director!
Crap! I completely forgot Hikaru is still here...
Violated Atmosphere
“Violated Atmosphere.” Ready, action!
Please believe me!
It’s all a misunderstanding!
Oh, sure. You’ve always been a playboy.
My love isn’t a lie!
If I ever betray you, you can take my life!
I love you, Hikaru!
Kenji... me too.
Are you ready for docking?
Yes, Kenji.
Hikaru...
Kenji, come to me!
Thrust your shuttle into my docking hatch!
Here I go, Hikaru!
Hikaru!
Kenji!
The Ikeoo-type space station has arrived,
much to your amusement!
You’re docking with me, rocket!
Come on! Aren't you eager to commence
a heated, intense docking with me?
Come on, hurry up...
No fair!
That rocket’s supposed to dock with me!
Ha! A tiny station like you
could never satisfy that huge rocket.
Kenji, you’d rather dock with a young,
brand new station like me
than with that run-down old one, right?
Uh... well... I mean...
Get out of my way, you!
Your fate is to burn as a shooting star!
Down you go!
Ugh! Hell no! Take this!
Why don't you both calm down?
If you disturb the cosmic peace with such a clamorous quarrel, the stars will punish y—
Back off, you little brat!
You stay out of it, old hag!
Did you just call me old?!
Exactly!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?
Director, are you okay?
This is what happens
when you don’t listen to me!
No fair! You provoked this yourself!
What is Sato doing?!
Sorry!
I-It's on fire!
Put it out, quick!
What? AV means adult video?
For a minute there,
I thought we were cooked.
It was crazy, but kind of fun, wasn’t it?
I wouldn’t mind trying it again sometime...
Hey!
Then you're lucky to have me right here!
Director!
I’ve got a brand-new script right here!
This time, I want to sign you both together!
Let’s take on the world together!
Run!
Ah... No, wait!
Publishing
Who was the boy who drew this again?
It was Aoyama Kenji.
He might be useful.
To be continued