ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
I live with my girlfriend, Hikaru,
who goes to the same school where I work.
But if someone finds out, I'll get fired!
Skit 23
Battle of the Beauties
Skit 23:
Battle of the Beauties.
Hikaru’s come down
with a fever all of a sudden!
Hey, Mr. Clerk?
Oh, trying to play dumb, huh?
All right, then.
Everyone, listen up!
This man went to the video rental store yesterday
to enjoy some very naughty...
What is it?
Hey, Mr. Clerk, you're Hikaru's neighbor, right?
Eh? Ah, right, sort of.
I wanted to go check on our Hikaru-chan!
You’ll take me there, won’t you?
So this is Hikaru’s place, huh?
Hang on, Hikaru-chan.
Omie Haruka is here
to bring you love and comfort!
That’s strange, she’s not answering.
Maybe her fever’s too bad for her to get up?!
Oh?
Hikaru-chan, you home?
Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru-chan, are you okay?
Oh no, you're burning up!
Hikaru-chan...
Wow, I didn’t think Hikaru-chan
lived in such a shabby place.
All right then, I’ll get going.
Yeah, thanks.
Now what do I do?
Haruka!
What are you doing?!
Ch-Chisato!
Don’t tell me you’re trying to take advantage of Hikaru-chan while she’s sick and helpless!
Wh-What?!
You’re one to talk!
Huh? Chisato-chan, Omie-san,
why are you both here?
U-Uh, Hikaru-chan...
Y-Your pajama’s slipping!
Oh no, you saw my flat chest!
S-So cute...
36.7 degrees.
Looks like your fever’s coming down.
Hope you get better soon.
What the hell! Why is she here?
I thought I’d finally
get Hikaru-chan all to myself!
I wish you'd come down with a fever instead!
Ah... So hot in here…
I think I’m getting a fever too…
Chisato-chan, you okay?
Oh, no-no, Chisato,
you should go home and rest right now!
I know—should I call you an ambulance?
Sorry… I must’ve given you my cold.
I’m burning up, can’t move…
Hikaru-chan, can I stay over just tonight?
Huh?
Wha—
Oh, no, now I’m feeling feverish too...
What? You too, Omie-san?
Yeah, so get lost, you.
Hikaru, I’m home!
Kenji!
Ah! That must be Hikaru's brother!
Yay! Can’t wait to see what he’s like!
Crap, if they find out we’re living together,
I’ll get expelled and Kenji’ll get fired!
Hikaru, I’m home!
Huh?
Oh, well now, you must be my sister’s friends.
Y-Yes!
Sorry to impose!
It's her!
Blast! If she remembers
what happened that day, I’m toast.
Say, would it be quite all right
if we stayed the night?
Well, if you need it,
I suppose that’s fine.
Wow, really?
Thank you!
I’m so glad!
Hold up, what exactly are you cooking here?
There, take a look at that.
She’s wearing it even on her pajamas!
No, no! Focus, Kenji, focus!
But if I just play with it a little...
So sensitive!
Oh, this is unreal!
So soft!
I-If I just take it one step further...
Kenji?
H-Hikaru?
If you don’t leave soon,
you’ll be late for work.
Was she half-asleep?
No good! I must resist temptation
and complete my mission!
Only then can I call myself
a real man, Aoyama Kenji!
If only I’d grabbed it sooner…
C'mon, just let me...
No, there’ll be another chance.
Don’t rush, Kenji.
Wait for the right moment.
I waited till morning...
Thanks for having us, it was fun!
We’ll come by again!
My once-in-a-lifetime chance…
Huh?
I swiped it while we were changing.
I'll give you all my smiles.
O-Oh, good.
But why was she keeping this thing
like it was some kind of treasure?
Now, cast your magic...
Ah! It’s gone! Gone!
Gone! It’s gone!
That was my only clue to my fated darling!
To be continued