ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
I work at the high school
that my girlfriend Hikaru goes to.
However, the girl I accidentally kissed the other day, Haruka, is onto me—
the situation is both thrilling and scary.
Skit 25
The Last Date Is with You
Skit 25:
The Last Date Is with You.
To think we’d meet again today...
This must be fate—God’s doing!
Come on, let’s hurry!
Wh-Where to?
My very first date!
Oh?
Wait, that’s...
Omie-san! Kenji!
Uh, well...
Sorry, but we'll have to stop you here.
I’m the Omie family butler—
servant to Lady Haruka.
Ah... First time I’ve ever skipped school.
Wait here, I’ll go change.
Haruka-chan!
Skipping work to go on a date with a student?
You’re fired!
Fired
After all the trouble
I went through to get you this job!
What's worse you're dating someone
other than me? Unforgivable!
We're done!
That’s it, we’re done!
No way! if I lose both my job and Hikaru,
I’ll be nothing but human trash!
ME - (JOB + HIKARU) = HUMAN TRASH
Uh... Wow, even saying it out loud hurts.
Well, I can think of that plenty later.
Right now, I gotta head to school alone...
Mr. Clerk!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I’ve never worn something like this before.
Looks nice...
Well, let’s go now!
Y-Yes.
After our date, I called you on the phone,
Telling you, "Come over right now," though I knew it was selfish.
I glared at the clock, certain you'd show up,
Ah! That was so much fun!
Next, let’s ride the Ferris wh—
Just testing your love...
Were you actually scared?
No, it's all right.
I wasn't scared at all, totally!
Sorry, I forced you to go
through all these rides with me...
Not at all! I actually had fun.
So, so much fun!
Mr. Clerk...
I have to tell you something.
Tomorrow, I have to be in England...
Milady.
We’ve come to collect you.
It’s nearly time for your flight.
Come on, we must hurry!
Oh, but...
Milady...
Hey, are you sure?
Looks like this Ferris wheel ride will be our last.
Mr. Clerk...
W-Wait, Haruka-chan...
Please, give me one last memory!
When you saved me in the infirmary,
I realized what a kind person you really are.
No, I always knew it.
Ever since you kissed me in the storage room...
You’ve been my prince.
Please, make me yours!
Haruka-chan...
Mr. Clerk...
I'm touched by the sentiment, but...
Why not? We’re all alone now.
We’re inside a moving Ferris wheel, you know.
If only it’d just stop for half an hour or so right here,
maybe I could make a memory with you...
Mr. Clerk...
Uh... We sincerely apologize.
Due to a system inspection,
the ride will stop for up to thirty minutes.
No way!
It’s a sign from God!
Now no one will see us!
Mr. Clerk...
C-Crap, wh-what do I do now?
Get ready! The fight is on!
Mountain of Desire
River of Reason
Whoa would you look at that—
Mountain of Desire
River of Reason
the River of Reason pinned the Mountain of Desire
against the edge of the ring!
Mountain of Desire
River of Reason
No! I can't give in to temptation now.
I already have Hikaru!
No time to waste...
Come on, hurry...
The River of Reason still pushing forward...
Ah! The Mountain of Desire throws him out of the ring!
The Mountain of Desire wins the bout!
Eh! Whatever happens now, I’ll take it!
Ah...
Hikaru!
Congrats, Kenji.
It’s a little gift to celebrate your employment.
Mr. Clerk?
I’m sorry, Haruka-chan.
I already have someone I love.
Eh?
That’s why I can’t return your feelings.
Mr. Clerk...
Ah!
The inspection’s complete.
We’ll resume operation now.
Milady, we’ve been waiting for you.
Kenji!
Hikaru!
D-Did she see everything?
I already heard from them what happened.
You were just helping Omie
make a nice farewell memory, right?
Kenji, that’s so sweet of you!
Y-Yeah! Exactly!
Just a nice memory to take with her!
I see... So the girl he likes is Hikaru, huh?
That’s fine. If it’s someone
as wonderful as her, I can accept it.
Hikaru-chan...
Omie-san,
we’ll meet again, right?
Yes, I’m sure we will.
From the day we first met, my heart's been racing.
Did you settle things for Mr. Clerk?
I explained everything to the principal.
He won’t get in trouble for skipping work.
Why do I feel this way? Oh why? Fate is a question
Good. Thanks.
Milady, your expression
has softened so kindly.
Oh, but that's thanks
to a very special friend, I’m sure.
Goodbye, Hikaru-chan, Kenji-san!
To be continued