ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
My roommate is Saito Hikaru—
a real girl through and through.
I came here to bring back Hikaru
who left me behind, and ended up sneaking into...
no, not a secret garden,
but the convent of the Pheromone Church!
Hikaru, believe me!
These tears running down my face
are tears of joy from seeing you again!
They’re definitely, absolutely
not tears of happiness or anything like that!
Kenji? Why is he here?
Skit 14
Encounter with Father
Skit 14:
Encounter with Father.
Welcome back, Padre.
I trust nothing unusual
happened while I was away?
You’ll be pleased to hear,
your daughter has returned.
Hikaru?
Padre?
Hikaru!
Hikaru?
Hikaru! Where are you, Hikaru?
Hikaru!
Miss Hikaru’s in the bath.
The other nuns are in there too,
so please wait until she comes out.
No! No, no, no!
I have to see Hikaru right now! Right now!
There, there.
Please, just bear with it for a bit longer.
Once it’s about Hikaru,
Padre turns into a different person.
Kenji, did you come to take me back?
S-So happy...
Oh? You're so modest, Kenko-chan.
Cumming!
Hey, don’t say that,
you’ll make her self-conscious.
It’s fine.
You don't mind at all, do you, Kenko-chan?
Kenji, you idiot.
C-Crap!
I came to bring Hikaru home.
I can’t lose sight of the mission!
See, massaging them like this improves blood flow and helps your breasts grow.
OINK!!
Wow, so cute! Let me try too.
Yeah, me too, me too!
She’s feeling it—so cute!
What bliss...
Ah, who'd think it's possible in this life...
He's disgusting!
Huh? Wh-What's that?
Hikaru!
Papa?
Huh?
Storage
room
H-Hikaru! I’ve missed you so much!
Papa.
There’s something I need to know.
Huh?
Why did you raise me as a boy?
Hikaru...
If you’d told me the truth from the start,
I wouldn’t have had to suffer this much.
I see. So the time has come to tell all?
But before that, I must ask you one thing.
Huh?
You haven’t fallen
for any man out there, have you?
Kenko-chan’s so cute!
Right?
Eek! A man!
Well? Is there a man you like or not?
I—I...
don’t. There’s no one I like.
I see. Good.
But... But suppose there was
a man I love—what then?
His life would be in danger!
Padre!
Huh? What is it?
An intruder!
Kenji!
Who are you?
Surely some kind of sinful deviant!
That must be it!
I see... So you really won’t forgive me
after all. Guess that’s fair.
I’ll ask one more time—who are you?
That’s right. I’m a deviant!
[Talking with ostentatiously strong Osaka accent]
My word, this here’s a garden of ladies!
For a pervert like me, it’s heaven on earth!
Sure had myself a helluva time,
I’ll say that much.
I can’t drag Hikaru into any of this.
Kenji... you’re doing this for me?
Take me away—police, whatever!
My life ends here!
Surely a man of God wouldn’t hand someone over to the police so easily, right?
Turn him in to the police!
No way...
Wait!
Hikaru!
The police? That’s too soft!
Hikaru...
To be continued