ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
To rescue Hikaru, who lost her memory,
I infiltrated Yukanoue Mai’s private villa.
At last, I’ve reached the final door.
What could be waiting on the other side?
Eh, no turning back now!
Skit 29
When Love Burns
Skit 29:
When Love Burns.
Hikaru! You here?!
Aoyama-san, I’ve been expecting you.
Let us toast to the courage
that brought you this far.
Cheers!
It's good stuff!
I’m glad you like it.
No!
I didn’t come here for drinks,
I came to take Hikaru back!
Take her back?
That girl doesn’t even remember you.
She’s happier now, aiming to become
a rhythmic gymnastics star—with me.
Her dream is the Olympics.
To grasp a woman’s happiness
without relying on men.
Aoyama-san, you work as a clerk
at our school, don’t you?
Our school strictly forbids relationships
between staff and students.
If I report this to the principal,
you’ll be fired.
And Hikaru will be expelled.
FIRED
EXPELLED
Fired!
FIRED
EXPELLED
Expelled!
But I don’t want to do that.
How about we get to know
each other a little better?
Leave Hikaru-chan to me.
Let’s have some fun together,
just the two of us.
The thing about men
is that they're this easy to manipulate.
And if I scream at just the right moment,
that video will be all the proof I need.
I’ll have him thrown in prison,
and I’ll be free to coach
Hikaru-chan all by myself!
[Parody of "Space Battleship Yamato" (1974)]
Energy output: 360%!
Launch!
Roger!
Ignition!
WHOOSH
I'm at my limit...
Fine then, Aoyama-san. Come here.
Hikaru, I’m sorry!
Now’s the time to scream!
Ready—go...
No!
Hikaru...
Hikaru-chan, I—I told you to stay in bed.
C-Coach, that man...
That's right, he was just trying
to violate me a moment ago!
How could you do such a terrible thing!
Hikaru...
Why do you care?
You don’t even know this man!
I don't understand…
I don’t know why, but somehow I feel so sad.
You’re just tired.
Come on now, go to bed.
Hikaru!
Yukanoue-sensei, let me through!
Hikaru-chan!
Yukanoue-sensei!
Aoyama-san?
Hurry, while you can!
Why are you helping me?
Just go, run!
Aoyama-san!
I never thought there were men like this...
I always thought all men were cowardly,
selfish, and vulgar creatures.
Go and leave without me!
I’ll save Hikaru!
Don’t be stupid—you’re too hurt!
Aoyama-san!
Hikaru, are you okay?
Kenji!
Hikaru!
Hikaru, did you remember me?
Yes, Kenji!
Hikaru!
Kenji!
Kenji! Kenji!
Stay back!
Hikaru! Get out while you can!
It’s not too late for you!
No!
You idiot! You're gonna die!
That’s fine!
As long as I’m with you, Kenji!
Hikaru...
If we die, we’ll die together.
We’ll see each other again in heaven, right?
If you become an angel
and come take me away, then sure.
Kenji…
Hikaru…
Rosa-chan!
Are you both okay?
Aoyama-san!
Hikaru-chan!
You’re safe now.
Come on, we have to run!
Kenji!
Aoyama-san!
Stay with us!
Kenji...
Hikaru!
Thank goodness you’re awake.
I thought we lost you.
Everyone...
Aoyama-san, Hikaru-chan,
please forgive me.
I was once an Olympic candidate myself.
But the day before the trials,
my boyfriend dumped me.
OLYMPICS TRIALS
The shock ruined my performance.
After that, I couldn’t trust men anymore.
But forcing that hatred onto others was wrong.
Please forgive me, Aoyama-san, Hikaru-chan.
It’s all right.
What matters is that we’re all safe now.
From the day we first met, my heart's been racing.
What about the girls
from the gymnastics club?
They’re fine—they made it
back to the boat ahead of us.
The whole ship’s buzzing
about you and Hikaru-chan!
No way, really?
Why do I feel this way? Oh why?
That’s embarrassing...
Our relationship...
If it leaks, I'm fired...
and I'm expelled!
To be continued