ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
RAW    The walked forest
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji,
currently in hardcore boxing training.
My roommate is Saito Hikaru,
who looks like a girl, but really is a boy...?
And then there are these girls...
We heard everything.
I don’t get what’s going on,
but they’re definitely cute and curvy!
Skit 6
The House of Abstinence (Part 1)
Skit 6:
The House of Abstinence.
(Part One.)
Who are you guys?
[= "lucky woman"]
Unga Iyona.
[= "luck will rise"]
Unga Akeru.
[= "luck will come true"]
Unga Kanau.
[= "luck will come around"]
Unga Meguru!
Together, we are the Four Unga Sisters!
We just happened
to overhear your conversation.
Our real job is fortune-telling.
We guide lost souls toward salvation.
These girls are my apprentices.
And as for myself, besides being a fortune-teller,
I am also a licensed boxing trainer.
A boxing trainer?
You’re Kenji-san, right?
You’ve got an important match coming up in a week, I hear.
Would you like to leave your training...
to us until then?
Sure, sure, I'm all yours!
Hey, what’s going on here?
You just pop outta nowhere talking nonsense!
I’m Kenji’s trainer, remember?!
Tell me, can you make Kenji
strong in just one week?
Well…
Because we can.
We’ll turn Kenji-san into a real man in a week.
I get that you’re worried, but trust us for now.
Then it’s settled!
Let’s set off.
Set off?
All packed?
All right, let’s go, Kenji-san.
Whoa, hey, hold on!
Kenji!
Don’t worry, Hikaru-san.
See you later.
We’ll meet again ringside in one week!
Kenji!
Glance…
E-Excuse me, why’re you going this far
for a guy you just met?
When I see a man giving it his all,
I just wanna support him in any way I can.
Well, thanks!
Nice place.
Hikaru would’ve loved it if I brought him here.
Do you like it?
My dad owns this lodge.
Oh, really?
Kenji-san, take your clothes off.
Eh?! That fast?
No objections!
Here, change into this.
Ah, I see…
F-Feels kinda stiff, though.
You’ve only got one week till your match.
Normal training won’t be enough
to bring out your hidden potential.
My hidden potential?
Kenji-san, are you ready
to endure any kind of pain with me?
Yeah, I guess so.
Well then...
K-Knew it!
Let’s dig in!
What the?
Those trunks are wired to a bell that rings whenever that part of your lower body becomes active.
Your hidden potential is your “horny power,”
beyond normal human limits.
H-Horny power?
But you must never let it out.
Stay calm, and channel that pent-up
horny power into your fights.
Right...
Until you can resist any kind of arousal,
you can’t leave this mansion.
Ah, no... I don't think that's possible...
Come on, Kenji-san, pour all your dirty thoughts
into that punching bag!
I see. So I’m supposed to burn off
all that pent-up energy through training.
I mean, I’ve gone 24 years without a girlfriend.
There’s gotta be a lot
of pressure built up in here.
But is this really all the power I’ve got?
Good work. Break time.
Oh, thank—
It’s tasty.
But you must keep hitting the bag
till the bell stops ringing, okay?
Must hit!
I'm beat...
Oh, no, this is just the beginning.
Huh?
Kanae-chan!
Oh, my, what amazing reaction speed!
All right, go for another round of training
until that sound stops.
Kanae-chan, I’m sorry...
N-No, we're only supposed to be training you!
I can’t help it—my body’s moving on its own!
Somebody stop my hands!
Oh, no... Stop... We cant!
I’m sorry, Kanae-chan!
No, Kenji-san!
Kanae-chan!
N-No, this is only special training for the match!
Stop!
Stop
I called you after our date
Geez. I knew it would come to this.
M-Meguru-chan, right?
and asked you to come right away.
Yes. From here on out, your training will be handled by me—Unga Meguru!
You looked at the watch and said...
To be continued