ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
RAW    The walked forest
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Hey, hurry up and get over here!
If you keep teasing me like that,
I'll find myself someone better.
I'm Aoyama Kenji, 24 years old.
Dropped out of college, and working part-time while studying to become a manga artist.
So goddamn noisy! Don’t start making out
the second you walk in the door!
Think of your poor neighbor who has to hear it,
you damn sex junkies!
Don’t get jealous just because
you can’t get laid yourself!
This drawing completely lacks realism!
Have you tried to at least
get yourself a girlfriend?
Your art’s not sexy at all!
At all...
Dammit!
I didn't choose to not have a girlfriend!
Somebody, please lend me some good luck!
Ah, he's here.
Starting today,
I’ll be living with someone.
My new roommate’s a younger brother
of my college senior.
I’ve never seen his face, but if he’s paying
half the rent, I don’t care who it is!
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for taking me in starting today.
Uh, excuse me?
My ideal type!
What the hell are you jumping me for?!
I don’t swing that way!
Huh?
“Boku”?
[Male form of "I"]
Wait, are you the senior’s little brother?
Yep. Saito Hikaru, sixteen.
I may not look it, but I’m all man!
No way!
Skit 1
Boy or Girl?
Skit 1.
Oh, so you’re a manga artist?
That’s great art.
I really admire people who can draw.
Huh?
A guy?
You’re still not buying it, are you?
What's there to buy?
You're a girl every step of the way.
And your voice doesn't sound one bit manly!
I... I just haven’t gone
through a voice change yet!
And that face—if you’re a guy,
why are you wearing makeup, huh?
Everyone says I'm prettier this way!
Or… do you think it doesn’t suit me?
No, it’s not that.
Makeup! Makeup!
He’s seriously cute.
Even among girls,
you hardly see one this cute.
Oh, jeez! You’re still doubting me!
Well, yes, but...
Just once, okay?
W-Wait, wait!
At least let me throw down a futon!
Futon!
What are you doing?
N-No way!
Yes, of course, I understand.
Hey, what did my sister say?
She said, “Don’t you dare
bully my brother.”
So don’t try anything, okay?
Ever again.
I know that!
Who’d wanna bully you anyway?!
Ah... The sex junkies couple next door.
The eternally bothered perv next door.
Finally found himself a girl?
What?! Sh-She’s cute!
What’s wrong?
I lost!
Hey, tell me.
I... I win!
Though… does that even count?
Kenji, I made special hamburg steak tonight!
Kenji, you want it extra chilled or not?
Uh? No, warm's fine.
Ugh... It’s stuck too tight.
Huh? Let me try.
You're a strong man!
Flattery’ll get you nowhere.
What the hell am I doing
flirting with a guy?
You can have the bath now!
Ugh... I can't stand it!
Just face the other way, okay?
My bad.
He’s a guy, but all his habits
are totally like a girl’s.
Should I try to land a kiss?
Ah, get off it…
What am I even thinking?
Making love to an underage boy?
But…
my mind...
I'm losing my mind!
Kenji!
No!
Hikaru!
Stop it!
I told you, I’m a guy!
Seriously! Are you drunk already?
I drank too much, it seems.
Truth is, I’m almost sober.
From the day we first met, my heart's been racing,
But it’s kinda my fault too.
I dress like this, after all.
N-No, it’s my fault.
I’ve been living without any women around for too long.
I lost control.
Huh?
Hikaru.
Hey, am I just in your way here?
Why is this happening so fast?
Fate is a question.
You don’t have to worry.
I’ll get used to it soon enough.
Oh, Kenji, you’re so kind!
Yep, I’ll get used to it.
In no time.
Wh-What the...
Ah, if this is what they call love...
So sexy!
This is perfect!
Perfect, I say!
Guess I owe it all to that kid.
To be continued