ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I'm Aoyama Kenji. I'm 24
and dreaming of becoming a manga artist.
The girl I live with, Hikaru,
has been scouted to be an AV actress.
Even I haven't slept with her yet, so there's no way
I'm letting someone else have Hikaru!
I'll sabotage this shoot no matter what,
even if it costs me my life!
Skit 31
Infiltrating the Filming Set!
Skit 31:
M-Man, that girl’s too cute...
My heart flutters just watching her!
When this video drops,
I’m buying it myself!
Go ahead, envy me all you want.
You’re just nobodies
whining from the sidelines.
Hikaru belongs to me and me alone!
I wish I could bed a girl that cute at least once!
Maybe if I ask her nicely, she’ll let me?
She’s doing AV anyway, right?
Maybe we should all try asking together later.
No way! Absolutely not!
Even I haven't done it yet!
No, I mean...
She shines even more through the camera!
This girl’s gonna be a real star someday.
All right, that’s a wrap on the image scene!
Next, we move indoors.
Okay!
Sugar Baby Sato, you warmed up?
Aye!
Is he even human?
That guy kinda looks like Kenji.
I wonder what we're filming next.
Feeling nervous, Hikaru?
Not at all! I’m actually super excited!
I’ve been in this business a long time,
but I’ve never seen a rookie
this relaxed before a bed scene.
You’re gonna be big, kid.
Yay! I’m gonna be big!
By the way, what’s a bed scene?
Director, we’re ready to roll.
Good. Set the camera.
Name?
Saito Hikaru.
What do you do for a living?
Nothing.
But I’m gonna be the best
AV actress in the world and make a fortune!
And what’ll you spend all that money on?
Living expenses, of course!
You have to do AV
just to pay your rent these days?!
That really makes me want to support her.
I’ll buy two copies of the video now!
You know what kind of work
AV actresses do, right?
Yep, sure do!
They sing and dance to the music
on TV and in music videos, right?
By the way, how many men
have you been with?
Been with?
Let’s see… I've lived with my papa,
obviously—we're a family.
Then there were some male teachers
who took classes at school...
Not that kind of "been with!"
I'm asking how many guys have you slept with?
Eh? AV actresses
even get asked that kind of stuff?
How many men?
Louder!
Zero!
No way!
She’s a virgin?
Whoa! I’m preordering three copies!
Listen, there’s nothing to be afraid of.
Just trust me and do exactly as I say.
Okay.
Now close your eyes.
A sleeping girl awakens by a man’s touch
and transforms into a woman.
With this film, I’ll make history by winning all twelve categories at the International Porn Academy Awards!
Oh? You’re fired up too, huh?
Aye!
A little snack to give you energy before work.
Thank you.
Everyone, help yourselves.
Oh, good timing!
I was just getting thirsty from all this tension.
Huh? Are we changing again?
Wait, what? I must undress
even with all the guys in the room?
But the director said to trust her.
Relax, relax, relax!
This is bad. Really bad!
What? We're changing the underwear too?!
Hold it right there!
What is it, Sugar Baby Sato?
S-Something’s wrong with my stomach...
M-Me too!
It worked!
Q-Quick, get out of there!
What’s going on?!
Start shooting or you're all fired!
E-Even so, there’s nothing
we can do about food poisoning.
Ugh! You’re all useless!
What’s gotten into everyone?
Hikaru!
Ah, Kenji! What, decided to tag along?
Talk later! We’ve gotta get out of here!
What? But we’re not done filming yet.
If I leave now, it’ll break my contract.
Listen, AV is not what you think it is...
No matter how great the lead actress is,
we can’t shoot without a male actor.
At this point, any guy will do.
Hm?
U-Uh, is something…
You'll do.
Wh-What?
You’ll be her partner!
You’re the only man left standing.
Get ready at once!
Eh?! W-Wait a second!
No time to argue!
So Hikaru’s the AV actress,
and I’m the AV actor?!
To be continued