ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Today we’re visiting the home
of the explosively popular manga artist
[e ga kirei = "beautiful picture"]
Egaki Rei, known for her gorgeous art
and captivating stories.
Wow, what a lovely house!
Mangaka
Egaki      Rei
Oh, please, it’s embarrassing—
I didn’t have time to clean properly.
That artist Egaki Rei
is such a stunning beauty!
She’s got style, and that sensual vibe...
Uh? You say something?
Ah, sorry, keep working.
O-Okay...
Kenji looks so cool
when he’s drawing manga.
Yes, Aoyama speaking.
Ah, the editor?
[Parody of Mitsumori Akira, the author of "Let's Nupu Nupu,"
another show from the TBS Wonderful block]
Huh?! Mutsumi Akira’s
production studio hired me?
Skit 34
Gateway to Dreams
Skit 34:
Gateway to Dreams.
Right now?
Yes, I’ll head over immediately!
Kenji!
Hikaru!
I did it!
You did it!
That's it—I got hired!
They’re taking me in as an assistant!
That’s awesome!
I’m so happy for you, Kenji!
From here, it’s a straight shot
up the ladder to the major league!
Soon I’ll make things easy for you too.
You’re going to be a great mangaka, Kenji.
I believe in you.
Hikaru...
Hey, what kind of manga
does Mutsumi Akira draw?
Uh...
No looking!
Wait... erotic manga?
Publi
shing
Mutsumi-sensei will be here any minute.
Just hang tight.
O-Okay.
Man, I’m nervous.
I wonder what kind of person Mutsumi Akira is.
Wh-What was it... Egaki Rei?
Interested in my body?
A-Ah, no, I mean...
It’s fine. The charm of the manga you draw
is born from that very desire.
Y-Yes...
I haven’t introduced myself yet.
I’m Egaki Rei, the manga artist.
And my other name is...
Mutsumi Akira.
This is my workspace.
Bright lighting, neatly organized references,
and beautiful assistants!
Quite the impressive setup, isn’t it?
Mizuki-san, show Aoyama-kun around.
Yes, ma’am.
Well then, do your best, Aoyama-kun.
Y-Yes!
Let's go, rookie.
This way to the workspace.
Huh? Isn’t this it?
This is Egaki Rei’s studio.
Mutsumi Akira’s studio is in the basement.
The basement?!
Sensei doubles as mainstream artist Egaki Rei,
and underground erotic illustrator Mutsumi Akira.
No one in the public knows, of course.
I see... Well, that sure came as a shock to me.
Sensei’s basically a manga demon.
Her talent overflows so much,
she needs two identities to contain it.
I’m Egaki Rei’s chief assistant, Mizuki Kana.
Good luck down there.
Eh... Thanks...
M-Man, it feels totally different down here.
Excuse me...
Wh-What is this place, a cave?
U-Um, I’m the new guy, A-Aoyama Kenji.
You can draw butts, right?
Huh?
Our butt artist got sick
and ended up in the hospital.
We need someone
who can draw cute behinds...
S-So this is Mutsumi Akira’s studio...
How did they learn to draw this well?
Don’t stop. Keep working.
Yes, ma’am.
What’s with this pathetic bust?
How do you manage to ruin
my linework like this when tracing?
Retake!
Screw up again
and you’re demoted to errand boy!
Y-Yes, ma’am!
Mizuki wasn’t kidding—
she really is a manga demon!
Listen up.
If you’re not aroused by your own art,
you’ll never arouse the reader.
Whether it’s a major love story
or fourth-rate porn, it’s all the same.
You’re all still amateurs.
So at least draw with heart.
Here...
You can do it, right?
None of them get it...
Ah, s-sorry, I was in the process
of drawing a butt, and needed a reference...
Then...
how about this?
Such drive... even I’m overwhelmed.
This boy’s the real deal.
Hikaru, wait for me. I’ll make it big
and make you happy, no matter what.
Kenji sure is late...
To be continued