ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
RAW    The walked forest
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Translation       Perevodildo
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I'm Aoyama Kenji, living with a boy
named Hikaru who looks just like a girl!
I’m not into guys, but...
b-b-but... but damn it,
I’m seriously losing my mind!
Skit 3
Our First Fight
Skit 3.
Our First Fight.
Stop it, Kenji!
We’re both guys, remember?
Shut up! You’re way too cute for a guy!
Cow...
S-So you really are...
Sorry for lying.
The truth is, I’m actually a girl.
Right...
I suspected it all along.
I’m... I’m normal after all!
That’s right.
So now you don’t have any reason
to turn me down, right?
It’s like a dream...
Wow, looks delicious!
C-Can I eat you out next?
With you, I don't mind.
Ah, and now, with every emotion swelling inside me, the whistle blows.
[One massive reference to the launch scene for Galaxy Express 999]
Kenji!
Good luck!
Congratulations!
Farewell, my womenless youth!
Hikaru!
Ow...
A dream, huh.
He's sleeping.
Wide open.
Seriously, what kind of sleeping pose is that?
Ah, wait...
No! He’s a dude!
Wait... is he really a dude, though?
What am I thinking?
The day he moved in...
Just once, okay?
But I never actually saw for myself.
Don’t get excited! I just need to confirm
if he’s really a dude, that’s all.
God, my reaction’s pathetic,
if I say so myself.
If he’s a dude, I should be seeing
some balls and a bat soon.
Maybe if I just touch...
Stop! Don’t touch me!
Okay, okay...
Deviant! Pervert!
What the hell are you thinking?
D-Don’t get the wrong idea!
I just wanted to make sure
you’re really a guy!
I already told you I am!
If you keep wasting time thinking about stuff like that instead of working,
I wouldn’t be surprised if you never debut!
Shut up! And who do you think’s the reason
I can’t get any work done?
Oh, so now you’re blaming me
for your own failures?
So that's how you are, Kenji?
Ever since you showed up,
my life’s been a total mess!
Oh, spare me! Hearing that from a guy
who can’t even cook, wash, or clean by himself!
I bet you’re just thinking
that once I’m gone, you’ll be free to stare
at magazines like this all day long!
Honestly, you’re impossible,
with all the lewdness on your mind!
You're infringing on my privacy now!
Kenji you perv!
Look who’s talking!
You’re the cross-dressing freak here!
Get out!
Fine, I’m leaving!
Freedom!
Now this room is my kingdom alone.
I can do whatever I damn well please!
I can leave the bathroom door wide open,
lift one leg and fart whenever I want,
air-dry my son with a fan after a bath,
and no one can stop me!
Quiz: Common Sense of the World.
A girl runs out of her house
alone at two in the morning.
What happens next?
There’s only one possible answer.
Wrong!
Hikaru’s a guy!
Where are you going at this hour?
You’re one to talk—
what are you doing out here?
I can do whatever I want!
Just don’t blame me
if some drunk creep hits on you!
Fine then, I’ll just go back inside, happy?
What's that?
Ah, crap!
The bathtub is smoking!
Kenji!
...your eyes and every gesture
Jeez, what if the place caught fire or something?
Guess you really can’t manage without me.
I want us to become one—forever, just the two of us
You spend all day drawing manga,
so your brain gets filled with nonsense.
Let’s try doing something
more fun sometime, okay?
Sweet heart
Huh? “Something more fun”?
To be continued