ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
RAW    The walked forest
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji, 24 years old,
aiming to make it big as a manga artist.
A freeter.
My roommate’s Saito Hikaru.
A sixteen-year-old...
boy...?
Skit 2
Do You Like Miniskirts?
Skit 2:
Huh? So, this is supposed to be based on me?
Wow, I feel like I turned into a girl or something!
And what did the editor say?
He told me to make it look sexier.
I see. So it’s still not sexy enough?
Well, no matter how cute you are,
a guy’s still a guy.
Hmm… Maybe it’s my flat chest?
But Kenji,
poses like this don’t bother you, right?
Since I don't have boobs.
Guess I can’t beat real girls after all.
You’re a guy, that’s why.
All right then...
How about this?
Or this one?
Or maybe this?
Okay, maybe I got a little carried away.
Hikaru.
Huh?
You keep saying you don't swing that way,
but deep down, you totally are, aren’t you?
Wha...
You’re trying your best to provoke me!
Well, I’m not falling for it.
I’ll make it big, get rich,
and live a pure youth!
Don’t say stupid stuff like that!
I’m just a healthy, normal guy like you.
A perfectly normal guy, all right.
Then try to withstand my Three-Inches-Below-the-Bellybutton Attack!
One inch...
Two inches...
Three inches!
More, more...
H-Hey, I was joking!
You really were into it, weren’t you?!
I told you, I was joking too!
Don’t take everything seriously, geez!
You can’t joke like that, man.
I know you were actually getting turned on by it.
Spot-on...
Don’t let that shake you, my heart.
Your goal’s to make it big, get rich,
famous, and score hot girls, remember?
A fork in the road?
Dream world?
Another world?
Hey, should I make spaghetti
with meat sauce or Italian-style?
Hm? What’s wrong?
Crap, what was I just thinking?!
Kenji, you’re such a weirdo.
Don’t call me weird! If you’re calling me that,
I’ve got no hope as a human being!
Come on, don’t take
every little jab so seriously.
Even jokes don’t work on me anymore.
Let’s eat.
How is it? I tried adding wine to the sauce.
It’s great! Way too good.
But he’s still a guy...
Just so we’re clear, if I ever have
to introduce you to my friends or neighbors...
I know.
I’ll say I’m your little sister
so nobody gets any weird ideas.
Sister?
Yeah, don’t worry about it.
I’m used to being treated like a girl, so it’s fine.
I wouldn’t even mind posing as your girlfriend.
That’d probably be even better...
But for appearances’ sake,
sister sounds safer.
Besides, I’m working at the same place as you.
Same place?
Why’d you purposely pick
the same part-time job as me?
Because they said lunch is free there.
Just like I thought—it suits you perfectly!
Now I’m feeling pretty confident.
Hey, what do you think, big bro?
Huh? Yeah...
Not too shabby, all right.
Just that? I thought it was pretty stylish.
Too perfect.
My lifelong dream is to marry a girl
who looks good in a miniskirt.
If only I could marry her…
My beloved wife, I’m home!
Welcome back!
Dinner first, bath first, or maybe...
me?
Of course, you!
But on the other hand,
that would make this idiot my family.
I can’t handle calling him “big brother.”
Still,
no one rocks a miniskirt like her!
What am I supposed to do?
Hey, big bro,
how about like this?
Yes!
Even cuter that way.
Then what if I also show a bit more like this?
Ugh, it's too much!
Hey, Kenji...
If she weren’t your sister,
what would you be doing right now?
Dream world...
Another world...
Ah, my dream...
Where the hell did my pure youth go?
I can’t take this anymore!
To be continued