ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Uh... Hikaru?
What?
You don’t have to explain yourself.
I don’t really mind.
Rika-san, will you go back to the convent
and apologize to Papa with me?
Y-Yes.
See you, Kenji.
"We two were just roommates"?
Is that really it?
Skit 13
The Secret Garden
Skit 13:
The Secret Garden.
Finally made it.
Hikaru!
Father’s out right now.
I see. Then why don’t we take a bath first?
You must be tired, Hikaru-san.
Yes.
Wait here a moment.
I’ll go drop my things off in my room.
Maki-san?
I’m sorry, Maki-san.
You even helped me sneak out,
and now I’m back already.
Did something happen
between you and Aoyama?
Yes.
Well, he's a perv, all right.
But he’s a good person, so I thought
living together would work out for you two.
No, Kenji’s not the problem.
Hikaru-chan?
Hikaru-san! Where are you?
See you, Maki-san.
Ah!
Don't worry.
Yours will start growing up too soon enough.
Who said I'm worried about stuff like that?
I'm not asking you to forgive me for exposing Kenji like that, but I promise I’ll work to make it right.
It’s fine. I’ve already forgotten that idiot.
Huh, weird. When did I get this bruise?
Wobbly...
Right, back then...!
R-Right, must’ve been a mosquito bite.
I’m getting out first.
The teachings of the
Pheromone Church tell us this:
Man does not live by pleasure alone.
Nor by the flesh alone.
Now, let us pray!
Hey, did you hear?
About Hikaru-chan?
BATHHOUSE
Yeah! Did you know she came back?
And it seems she finally realized she’s a girl.
BATHHOUSE
Whoa...
About time.
It's a mystery how she
didn't realize it until now.
We only helped keep the secret
because Padre said so.
“If you drink enough mushroom soup,
you’ll grow a pee-pee!”
What a cute little myth!
But poor Hikaru-chan.
I wonder how Padre plans to explain it all.
Whoa! I got more than I ever hoped for!
It's the Garden of Eden!
Keep calm. Lose control here and it’s all over.
Um... Hikaru...
No, not that.
Ah, why was Hikaru-san raised as a boy?
We don’t know anything about that either.
Hey, haven’t seen your face before. You new?
Eh? A-Ah, y-yes.
Name?
Uh... Aoyama Kenko, sister.
Whatever. Just hurry up and strip.
I-It's a paradise!
No good! Calm down. Stay calm!
Hold it together...
I have to endure...
What’s wrong?
You’re crouching down.
Uh, nothing...
I just feel a little lightheaded.
Are you unwell?
Oh my, a nosebleed?
Should I take you to the infirmary?
No need. It's just a natural reaction.
I’ll be well soon.
Hikaru!
Ah, Hikaru-chan! Long time no see!
You vanished all of a sudden—
we were so worried!
Why’d you leave?
Uh, well...
Ah! Your boobs! You’ve got boobs now!
Whoa! So cute!
And your butt’s getting rounder too.
Let me touch something...
H-Hey, stop...
Wh-what the...
See?
You’re extra sensitive now.
Got someone you like, perhaps?
N-No way!
Bad girl. This is what we do to liars.
N-No, stop! That tickles!
Hold it! I mean, don’t go further.
Who are you?
Come on, everyone.
If you don’t bathe soon, you’ll catch a cold.
Aren’t you joining us?
Oh, I-I’ve got business with Hikaru-chan.
No fair! You just want her to yourself!
Yeah, you too.
Get undressed and get in the bath.
Eh?!
Help her undress, everyone!
No...
Oh, geez...
After our date, I called you on the phone,
Kenji!
Ah, I swear I can explain this...
Oh, so that’s what this is about?
Eh?!
Telling you, "Come over right now," though I knew it was selfish.
A flat chest is nothing to be shy about.
Eh?
That’s right! You’ll grow up
soon enough, just like us.
I glared at the clock, certain you'd show up—
Eh?
Come on, let’s take a bath together!
Uh, w-well... Wait, h-hold on...
Just testing your love a little.
Hey! Stop! Damn it!
Kenji? Why is he here?
To be continued