ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
My name’s Aoyama Kenji,
24, an aspiring manga artist.
That mysterious female teacher, Yukanoue Mai,
roped Hikaru into the rhythmic gymnastics club by force.
Then she took the whole club
off to some training camp.
Worried about Hikaru,
I went after them right away.
Skit 27
Dangerous Amnesia
Skit 27:
Dangerous Amnesia.
So the training camp's on that island?
Kenji’s probably worried sick...
Hikaru, hang on! I’m coming!
Wow! Can’t believe we get to train
in a place like this. It’s unreal!
Oh? That’s one daring
high-cut suit you’ve got there.
Oh, really? Says the girl
with the even skimpier bikini!
Yikes!
Oh, geez... Everyone’s so bold!
You there, listen up!
We didn’t come here to play!
Kyaa! Amazing! So daring!
What’s with those plain swimsuits, girls?
Beauty is our weapon.
How can you compete
dressed with zero sense of aesthetics?
D-Doesn’t that hurt, Teacher?
Not "Teacher."
It’s "Coach!"
Y-Yes...
If you can’t bare your whole self,
you’ll never move anyone with your performance.
God's creation of woman shines the prettiest
and brightest when she’s being looked at!
Do you understand, Hikaru-chan?
Yikes...
Uh, um… well…
That swimsuit makes you
look plain inside and out.
A rhythmic gymnast can’t afford that.
Y-Yes, ma’am.
Now change into this.
Coach, isn't there anything else?
Hikaru-chan, it looks perfect on you.
Really?
Yes! I knew at first sight you had potential.
Guess I’ll join the girls, then...
Is she serious?
That’s some hardcore ’80s taste.
I’d rather go naked than wear that.
Girls’ fashion sense is impossible to figure out.
One more important rule.
Only women on this island.
Having men around
would be a total distraction.
While you're here,
forget all about them and focus on training!
Now, let’s begin practice.
Music start!
All right, everyone—dance!
Whoa!
So cool!
Keep dancing! No cheap tricks.
Use your whole body
to express the joy of being watched.
Forget everything else—just dance!
This is a deserted island, after all!
Wow, amazing!
My body’s moving on its own!
What is this feeling?
I’ve never felt like this before!
Man, chasing that cruiser was rough.
But to see high school girls in leotards,
it’s well worth it!
No! I'm here to make sure Hikaru's safe.
Heavenly!
Feels great!
This—this is what I’ve been searching for!
Right now, I feel true happiness
as a human being with all my heart!
Ah… I’m so glad I was born,
Dad, Mom, and God...
thank you for bringing me into this world!
Oh, God!
River of Reason
Snap out of it!
Reborn!
Right! Hikaru! Where’s Hikaru?!
Hikaru's on fire!
Wh-What?
Even though we live together, watching her secretly like this is arousing in a whole other way!
Hikaru, once again, you’re the best!
Lovely, Hikaru-chan.
Truly beautiful.
But beauty that perfect
can be dangerous too.
Wh-What’s that?
What's this? Something’s moving.
Ah! It’s getting in!
That shell’s still alive.
Looks like the heat awakened it.
Ah... no!
No!
Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru, are you okay?!
Oh, crap...
Hold it! Who are you?!
Crud...
Ah!
It’s that clerk who’s close with Hikaru-chan!
Why are you here?
Don’t tell me you’re Hikaru’s…
Oh, whatever are you talking about?
I'm just Perry the Platypus, obviously!
Spare me your lame excuses!
Oh, gosh...
Ah, she figured me out.
Guess I’m fired for real this time.
Hikaru...
Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru, are you okay?!
Who…
Eh?
I don't get it.
Who are you?
Wh-What are you saying?
We live together!
No… I can’t remember anything.
Hikaru...
Is this amnesia?!
Well now, that turned out rather convenient.
Arise, Yukanoue Imperial Guard!
Big-Bust Task Force—Beauty Rangers!
[Parody of Kyoryu Sentai Zyuranger (1992)]
Big-Bust Task Force Beauty Rangers are here!
Eliminate that man!
Yes, ma’am!
One-two!
Hikaru! It’s me, Kenji!
Hikaru!
To be continued