ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Eh? You’re not coming home again tonight?
I can’t help it.
Deadlines keep piling up one after another,
I barely get any sleep.
I see.
Got it.
Do your best at work.
Sorry. Once I wrap things up,
I’ll come straight home.
Well, then...
Bye-bye!
It’s been half a month since Kenji left.
Please come home soon, Kenji you idiot.
Skit 35
Temptations of Slavery
Skit 35:
Temptations of Slavery.
Won't you... go give this to Sensei?
Chief... You should rest a bit.
We’ve got tons of work, so come back soon.
Ah... Sure.
At this rate, when will I ever see Hikaru again?
No, I’ve got to hang in there.
Don’t lose heart, Aoyama Kenji.
Sensei, I brought the manuscript.
Huh? That sound...
Th-This is Sensei’s...
most sacred smell!
I’m so glad I became her apprentice!
Oh, my...
I'm cockroasted!
I-I'm sorry, I don't know
what's gotten into me...
It’s fine. Without a little depravity,
you can’t draw a sensual manga.
Right...
This coffee is my special blend.
How many sugars?
Huh?
You look surprised—is it because
I seem different from usual?
N-No, it’s just...
I mean, at the office you’re always like...
Clumsy! Useless!
You idiots should just go back to
whatever neck of the woods you came from!
...and that kind of stuff.
I turn into a different person when I work.
Everyone probably thinks I’m a horrible woman,
but I just don’t want to publish half-baked work.
Th-That’s not true.
Sure, work’s tough,
but I really appreciate you, Sensei!
Thank you.
You’re a kind guy.
Oh, no...
Thanks for the coffee.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Oh, by the way,
do you have a girlfriend?
Eh? I do...
Oh, I see. Thanks.
Aoyama Kenji, huh...
It's like a dream—Egaki Rei herself
treated me to a coffee!
And on top of that...
Sensei, I’m sticking with you for life!
And as soon as I master my craft...
Welcome home, Kenji.
I missed you!
Hikaru!
I’ll do it, Hikaru.
Just you wait for me!
Aoyama-san, got a minute?
Y-Yes?
Actually, I’d like your help with something.
Help? Mizuki-san, you're the chief
of the editorial team,
what kind of help might you need
from a rookie like me?
Aoyama-san!
M-Mizuki-san?
I’m drawing a love scene,
but I can’t get the feeling right.
If we try it out for real, I think I’ll get it.
Y-You can’t be serious...
Please, help me out, Aoyama-san.
Aoyama-san...
[Parody of Ultraman's chant]
Kenji, don’t do anything rash!
H-Hikaru?!
N-No, Mizuki-san, I can’t!
It’s all for the sake of manga!
H-Hikaru, I’m sorry!
That’s enough!
I'm fired after all!
Thanks for the hard work, Mizuki-san.
Not at all.
Eh?
Here.
Huh?
This is my storyboard.
The scene where a man who has a girlfriend
gets seduced by another woman.
W-Wait, does that mean what we just did...
I asked Mizuki-san
to put on a little act for you.
Now you can draw a realistic scene about
the emotions of a man who has been seduced.
Y-You’ve got to be kidding...
What are you waiting for?
Get to drawing, chop-chop!
Damn it, I never agreed to be part of this act!
Making a fool out of me...
What do we have here?
A man gets seduced but doesn’t waver at all?
He thinks of the girlfriend he loves
and rejects temptation without hesitation?
Bullshit! No matter how in love you are,
if a sexy woman’s right in front of you,
you take her! That’s how men are!
Fine. I’ll wreck this thing.
This is what you get for making fun of me!
A man always takes what he wants!
Change this, and this! And this too!
How about that?!
What’s the meaning of this?
You rewrote my storyboard
without permission?
S-Sorry.
At this rate, I can’t let you stay as my assistant.
This time, fired for sure!
It was short, but thanks for everything.
Where are you going?
Huh? But you said I was fired.
Yes, as an assistant.
But this draft turned out
even better than originally intended.
I feel it deep inside, a spark running through me.
You’re more than qualified
to be my full-fledged partner.
Partner?
I want to know your fingers, your lips even more.
From now on, you’ll also draw manga
under the name of Mutsumi Akira.
Want to give it a try?
Tomorrow, yesterday, forever...
Hikaru!
Hikaru, I’m finally debuting!
Oh?
Hikaru!
Huh?
Not here...
Hikaru...
Where did you go?!
To be continued