ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji.
My roommate is Saito Hikaru.
He looks like a girl,
but he's a boy...?
Ah least that’s what I thought until...
BOOM
Girl!
Ah, fireworks!
Summer’s really here.
Guess he found out.
Skit 11
Hikaru’s Past
Skit 11:
Hikaru’s Past.
Kenji, are you okay?
Now, don’t you get excited so easily!
Nosebleeds don’t wash out easily, you know.
I sliced up an apple. Want some?
Guess that backfired.
Hey, Kenji, am I really a girl?
Come on, you’re still playing dumb?
I mean, how can I believe
something like that out of nowhere?
Wait a minute, you seriously think you’re a guy?
Well, why, exactly?
Guys have something you don’t.
Ah... Hold on, when you first
came over to my place...
Ah, that? Oh, that was just me
sticking my finger through my pocket.
See?
So it was a silly little trick after all...
I was embarrassed at not having my willy grow at sixteen, so I just tried to act cool.
Not having it grow, huh?
Well, I mean, when we’re kids,
boys and girls look the same, right?
If you drink a lot of milk, your boobs grow,
and if you drink a lot of mushroom soup,
your willy grows.
Now, hold on, what kind
of education did you get?
Now that I think about it,
I don’t know anything about this kid.
All I heard was that she’s
my university senpai’s younger brother.
I don’t know where she lived before,
or why she left home.
Hey, am I really, truly a girl?
Yeah, you’re a girl.
Nothing else you could be.
Then...
can you make me feel like one?
Feel?
Hey, don’t yell it like that!
It’s embarrassing.
Embarrassing? Why?
Why? Well...
I mean, even if you ask me that,
how do I actually make you feel it?
Huh? Well...
That’s a pretty tough problem.
How on Earth could I make you feel that?
Uh, but what if...
F-For example, you know...
doing naughty stuff.
Oh, I see. You really are bright
between the ears, you know.
What?!
Hikaru.
When he looks serious like this,
Kenji’s actually pretty handsome.
Serious...
But his lower half ruins it all...
Wh-What's that? An earthquake?!
C-Calm down, get it together, Aoyama Kenji.
She's only a b-b-beginner.
I just need to t-t-take the lead a little, and then...
Kenji.
Come closer.
Ah! My leading role...
[tachiba = position (literally "place to stand on/pedestal"]
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
LEAD
ING
ROLE
Thank you for having me.
What are you, a newlywed wife?
H-Hi—Hikaru, I, uh...
Let me see again!
O-Okay.
N-No, don’t look too closely.
Adorable!
When did I suddenly start talking like a girl?
Hikaru...
From the day we first met...
All right, that’s enough!
K-Karin-san!
What are you doing,
barging into someone’s house like that?
I should’ve taken you back sooner.
Taken me back?
You still don’t understand, Hikaru-san?
Y-You are Sister Rika!
What? You know her?
Yes. I’m a sister from the Pheromone Church,
where Hikaru was born and raised.
I apologize for keeping that from you, Kenji-san.
Hikaru, you didn’t recognize her?
Well, I’ve never seen Sister Rika
in casual clothes before.
Now then, let’s go home, Hikaru-san.
Padre is worried about you.
Y-You know, I’ve figured out
something amazing!
W-We’ll talk about that later.
For now, get ready to leave.
No, listen! You might not believe this,
but I am actually a girl!
Oh... Oh? That’s wonderful.
But you said you wanted to become a girl,
so that works out nicely.
Anyway, let’s pack up and go.
Wh-What?
Rika-san, did you perhaps
already know I was a girl?
Oh, no! I’m sorry.
That’s awful!
Hey, you two—what the hell is going on?
Explain to me, from the beginning!
Then why did Papa raise me as a boy?
Your Papa was raising you...?
Well, your guess is as good as mine.
Ignored...
If I’d known I was a girl,
I wouldn’t have had to suffer so much...
Give me back my youth!
One more time...
What the hell is going on?
Explain everything from the start!
I’m not going back to the convent!
You're not allowed to do that!
Can someone please remember I exist?
I... no, we are trying to start a new life!
"We"?
That's it—finally, it’s my turn!
For the third time—what the hell’s going on?
Explain everything!
Huh?!
Kenji-san...
Hey, hold on!
Please...
Now you see the truth about this man.
His partner doesn’t have to be you,
it literally doesn't matter to him.
Kenji!
Yes, nice... Oh, my!
To be continued