ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Living Together
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Kenji, I love you.
Hikaru...
Now we can finally become one.
Here I go.
Yes.
Hikaru!
Hikaru, open up! Hikaru!
Can you hear me? Open this door!
Skit 16
The Great Escape of Love
Skit 16:
The Great Escape of Love.
Hikaru, I’m coming in.
Hikaru.
Wh-What is it, Papa?
Something wrong?
What are you doing?
N-No, nothing!
I was just praying.
It’s been a while, so I thought
I’d do it properly, dressed as a sister.
I see.
That deviant managed to escape.
I was worried he might’ve
sneaked into your room.
I-It’s all fine.
As you can see, it’s just me here.
I—I can't breathe...
I see.
Well, if so, you can leave now.
I’d like to finish my prayer.
You can pray later.
More importantly,
let’s finish what we were talking about.
Huh?
What’s wrong? Sit down.
No, I prefer standing.
All right.
What I wanted to tell you
is why I raised you as a boy.
I know it was wrong to deceive you.
But it’s not like I lied because I wanted to.
You see, you were born with a destiny
to bring misfortune to the man you love.
Wh-What’s that supposed to mean?
You were born on a beautiful starlit night.
Three wise men
came from the East and said this:
“This child is born
under a mysterious star of fate.
Any man who falls in love with her
will face an avalanche of trials in love.
If his love is true, he’ll survive them.
But an average man of weak heart
may perish before that happens.”
Wh-What the hell...
That’s why, Hikaru, I raised you as a boy.
So that's what it was...
Do you understand now?
But if someone truly loves me,
we can both be happy, right?
W-Well, that’s true, I guess...
It’s already time for evening prayers.
Hikaru, come to the chapel with me.
Eh?! Like this?
I’m going to reintroduce you to everyone.
As my daughter now.
What’s wrong? Come on, hurry.
I—I just wanted to take in
the sight of the convent again.
M-My back’s killing me!
This too is God’s will.
From now on, please accept her
as a woman, one of us.
Kenji, you okay in there?
Can you breathe?
Kenji!
The smell of Hikaru’s pheromones...
is irresistible!
This is insane!
One more thing.
We’re gathered here praying
for the happiness of all people.
To help those who suffer
and those less fortunate.
Hikaru, can I kiss you?
What are you talking about?
How are we supposed to kiss like this?
Like this.
Might as well enjoy it while we can.
Idiot! This is not the time!
Oh, Hikaru!
By helping those in pain,
we find brotherly love within ourselves.
And through it, we too can be happy.
Many of you have committed mistakes in the past.
But now, you are children of God
who love and help others.
Be proud of that, and live
with your heads held high.
The escaped deviant
may still be hiding in the convent's premises.
You might find him lurking
in the most unexpected place.
I ask all of you to be on your guard.
Don’t push your luck!
Hikaru, what’s the meaning of this?
I'm sorry, Papa!
They’re getting away! After them!
Crap, we can’t escape...
All because you're such an impatient fool!
From the day we first met, my heart's been racing.
Hikaru-chan, Aoyama-kun, this way!
Huh?
Over here, quick!
Maki-san!
Hikaru-san, this way!
Rika-san?
Here, get in this bag.
Why do I feel this way? Oh why? Fate is a question
Rika-san, Maki-senpai, thank you.
Thanks!
Hikaru-san, hang in there.
Aoyama-kun, make sure
you keep Hikaru-chan happy!
I beg for more sweet kisses, and yet they get stolen.
Maki, Rika!
Has Hikaru been here?
No, she hasn’t.
The only one who came by
was the garbage truck.
I... I see.
Every time your gaze meets mine, my heart skips a beat.
IN PROGRESS
Ugh, it stinks. Especially compared to how nice it smelled earlier.
I feel it deep inside, a spark running through me.
Oh, stop it, you perv!
But do you think that “trial of love” thing
that's about to crash down on us is actually real?
I want to remember your eyes, your moves so gently,
and become one with you, forever just the two of us
Eh, whatever.
Sweet heart.
To be continued