ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
My name’s Aoyama Kenji.
I’m gonna get stronger...
Much stronger.
I will get stronger!
Stand up. You've gotta get up, Kenji!
Kenji-san!
Kenji!
Skit 9
The Mysterious Visitor
Skit 9:
The Mysterious Visitor.
Get up, Kenji!
At this point, that’s our only option.
Wh-What do we do?
Kenji’s strength comes from that unconventional “horny power.”
All right...
I need your help too, girls.
Okay!
Seven!
Kenji-san!
Get up!
Ah, if nothing else helps, then so be it!
I-Incredible!
I'm so glad I joined this gym!
Wh-what the hell are these people?
Pop!
My, so impatient, aren’t you?
Well? Are you impressed?
Go for it!
Kenji, get up! Come on!
Hikaru-san, you take yours off too!
Eh? But, um, I...
Now’s not the time to be shy!
But I’m a boy!
So you’re fine with Kenji losing?
Eh? N-No way!
I-Ioka’s getting up!
Kenji...
Fine!
Kenji, get up!
Hikaru-san, one last push!
A new star is born!
No-o-o!
Stop! Hikaru’s mine!
Ten!
Kenji!
Huh?
Kenji! You won!
Every time your gaze meets mine, my heart skips a beat.
Hikaru!
You’re all here to celebrate with me? I did it!
I feel it deep inside, a spark running through me.
Yahoo! Finally, that pointless match is over!
At last! Wanna do it on the mat, babe?!
I want to know your fingers...
D-D-Did I really win, though?
How does a roasted turkey sound?
See? The meat around the thighs
is all so tight and tasty!
Stop that!
Ah... Did I miss the mark?
That’s not what I meant!
Hey, now, what's your deal,
getting turned on by a guy?
Hey, thanks for earlier, Kenji.
You tried to help me out, didn’t you?
I was really happy about that!
Oh? Ah, you mean at the gym?
That was just me getting pumped up
from seeing Hikaru naked.
I should be the one thanking you.
I only won because of you.
Wh-Why'd you stop moving just now?
Oh... B-But what about you?
This silence is heavy...
Jeez, why am I getting
so nervous with another man?
Still, at that moment, he really seemed like a girl through and through to me.
A girl...
Coming!
Y-Yes?
H-Huge!
I’m Karin, your new neighbor starting today.
I came to say hello.
R-Right, nice to meet you.
Here, a little something to celebrate our meeting.
Kenji, who’s at the door?
Hi, Hikaru-san.
Hello...
How does she know my name?
Oh, so you live with your little sister?
Yep, my oh-so unapproachable little sister.
What the hell! I was planning to throw
a nice private celebration for just the two of us.
Hikaru, forget cooking for now,
come sit with us.
Hey, is she really staying over?
Well, she said her futon hasn’t arrived yet.
What can we do?
Besides, a party’s better with a pretty girl
than just two boring guys, right?
Kenji-san...
I think I’ve had too much to drink...
Ah, yeah, I’m coming!
That makes sense...
Any guy would be happy
when a gorgeous woman shows up, right?
I can't sleep...
K-Karin-san...
I get cold easily, let’s warm each other up.
K-Karin-san, I'm at your service...
Big bro, I’ll warm you up.
Hikaru-chan, you were awake?
Oh, is this for real? Two beauties
on either side... I’m in heaven!
Though, isn’t one of them a boy?
Hey, is your sister asleep?
She’s out...
Coming through!
Wobbly...
Oh, I can't hold back anymore!
Hanazono                    Tunnel
Hanazono                     Tunnel
Hanazono                      Tunnel
Hanazono                       Tunnel
Hanazono                        Tunnel
Hanazono                          Tunnel
Hanazono                            Tunnel
No entry!
What's your problem?!
What was that?
We were just getting to the good part!
Oh, really? What are you thinking,
making out with another woman next to me?
You always intrude at the worst possible moment!
Looks like it's going according to plan.
To be continued