ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it-a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
I fled, I ran away,
Calling the melody of grief-
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
Hikaru-chan!
Hikaru, are you okay?
I'm Aoyama Kenji.
I followed Hikaru all the way to this deserted island where a rhythmic gymnastics camp takes place.
I don’t get it…
Who are you?
After hitting her head,
Hikaru lost her memory!
Hikaru, please, remember me!
Skit 28
Big-Bust Task Force: Beauty Rangers
Skit 28:
Ready—go!
Well, he looked tough enough,
so he won’t die that easily.
As long as we’re around, we won’t let
anyone stand in Mai-sama’s way!
We are...
the Imperial Guard...
of Princess Mai—
the Beauty Rangers!
Now do you understand?
You’ve been a rhythmic gymnast all your life.
You and I were preparing
for the Olympics together.
But that guy before looked like he knew me.
He’s just some creep.
You only need to trust me.
Okay.
That’s right. Never trust men.
There she is.
You're the one we're supposed
to keep a lookout for!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I’m just a passing sea turtle, ma’am.
Excuses are useless!
[Parody of idol Moritaka Chisato]
My name is Moritaka Shikato.
This is what happens
to those who defy Mai-sama!
I am Maten Roza!
Prepare yourself, you human trash!
Ah!
Rouza, shake him off!
I can’t use my whip with you in the way!
I know! I will now...
What are you doing, Rouza?!
Hurry up and pull him away!
No way she's letting go of such delight that easily!
Come on! What are you, a suckerfish?!
He's getting away!
No weapons!
Hikaru, I swear I’ll make you remember me!
You too, huh?
What a fancy villa!
Didn’t expect a bath this big!
But that was a real shock earlier, wasn't it?
Hey, Chisato, Chisato!
Was that guy really Hikaru’s boyfriend?
I don’t really know either.
A peeper!
Just a little farther now.
A—A kitten?
[Meaning "Don’t underestimate me!"]
My name's Namenja Neeyo.
Too bad, but I’m not a kitten.
[Meaning "Qi (energy) Girl"]
My name’s Kiko.
Prepare yourself!
Here I come!
[Basically, he can focus well on moving objects]
Secret technique: Kinetic Vision!
Where are you looking?!
Why are you still looking there, dammit?!
Now, surrender!
If you do, we might just spare your life.
Guess I’ve got no choice.
Time to get serious.
That’s Brubruce Lee's specialty!
This is my final trump card!
Earth Stasis!
Earthly Cower
Sowwy
Please, let me go!
Earthly Cower
Sowwy
Or so you'd think...
[Distraction technique in Sumo, literally "fool the cat"]
Deadly technique: Cat Scare!
Ah! Madam Neeyo!
Then I have no choice...
Ultimate Move: the Butterfly Waltz!
Ah, your panties ripped!
Huh? Really?
I—I can't breathe...
N-No! Your Qi is too strong!
It’s surging through my whole body!
That was delicious...
Ah, no... I mean dangerous!
This must be the room.
Hikaru!
Kenji! You came for me!
Kenji!
Hikaru, so you remembered me?
Kenji, I’m so happy!
[Feminine form of "I" as opposed to hikaru's usual "boku"]
"Watashi?"
What’s wrong, Kenji?
You’re not Hikaru.
Wh-What are you talking about, Kenji?
I can tell! Where is Hikaru?
You win.
You’re the first person to see through my disguise.
I’m Omomuki Satori.
Hikaru is in the room further inside.
But...
Mai-sama truly hates men
from the bottom of her heart.
She might really try to kill you
if you go any further.
K-Kill me?
You’re still going?
Heh! No turning back now!
To be continued