ther
ther
ther
ther
Blasphemboys present
Living Together
Melody of sorrow,
Memory-echoing melody.
Translation       Perevodildo
If colors could name it—a creamy hue
Typesetting      Perevodildo
In this town where the wind
blows the dust through the streets.
Editing         Paul Geromini
RAW    The walked forest
So I hold back my tears,
I fled, I ran away,
Special thanks     TougeWolf
Calling the melody of grief—
That innocent one, that person.
With a smiling face,
You send me spinning again,
And the sorrowful melody revives.
I’m Aoyama Kenji, a 24-year-old freeter,
dreaming to make it big as a manga artist.
My roommate, Saito Hikaru,
turned out to be a girl after all!
But my happiness was short-lived,
because right after that, Hikaru went back
to the convent in her hometown.
But only a couple of hardships later,
I finally managed to bring her back!
We even... Even...
made it all the way to our first kiss!
Skit 17
The Embarrassingly Happy Boob Fortune-Telling
Skit 17:
The Embarrassingly Happy Boob Fortune-Telling.
We can finally be together now.
Yes.
What’s wrong?
Still thinking about what your dad said?
Any man who falls in love with her
will face an avalanche of trials in love.
Kenji, don’t tell anyone about me, okay?
H-Huh? Sure...
Hikaru...
Kenji, take me.
Here I come, Hikaru!
Kenji, are you okay?
Kenji, you sure you don’t wanna see a doctor?
I’m fine. And I don’t have
any extra money to blow right now.
I already called in sick for my shift.
Huh?
S-So that means we still
have the day all to ourselves?
Exactly.
Hey, Hikaru...
Kenji...
Hikaru...
Ken... ji...
Come on, who is it this time?!
Why is it always
right when things are getting good?
Hello, Kenji-san, Hikaru-chan.
Long time no see!
Iyona-san?
What brings you here all of a sudden?
I just moved in next door today,
so I came to say hello.
Nice to see you again!
Iyona-san, we're also glad
to have you next door.
Great! Well then, see you around.
Ow! What was that for?
Don't ask me!
Hey, Hikaru, where are you going?
I think I’ll go to my job today after all.
When are we ever gonna have sex already?
Ah... Just seeing Kenji-san again
after all this time,
I could feel his bottomless
horny power once more.
Ah! Just remembering it
makes my body tingle!
All right! Time for more special training today to win over Kenji’s heart!
Suneo-chan, music start!
My boobs are my life,
one touch and they tell all!
Man, I really am Unga Iyona.
When Iyona faces west,
boobs point to the east.
When Iyona faces east,
boobs point to the west!
When Iyona faces down...
Ha! Her boobs...
Ah! I thought I was gonna die.
Yes?
Hello!
Kenji-san!
You came for a good time already?
A-Ah, no...
It's not that!
You’ve entered a streak of female-induced abysmal luck starting about a month ago.
A month ago?
That’s when I met Hikaru.
So what her dad said
might actually be true...
If you want to know how to change your fate,
I’ll need to perform a deeper reading.
P-Please do!
Then...
I’ll use my specialty:
Boob Fortune Telling.
B-Boob fortune telling?
Yes.
Now, gently massage my breasts, please.
Boobs!
No! Control yourself.
Okay then, I’ll take your word for it.
Whoa, so heavenly soft...
Wow! Feels amazing! Heavenly!
I’m feeling it...
No! It's not the time to enjoy myself!
I've gotta focus on my work.
That feels good...
N-No!
This is only for fortune-telling!
I’m only doing this to see
what lies ahead for me and you!
Kenji-san! Don’t lose focus.
The result’s almost here.
Y-Yes!
Iyona-san!
The reading is complete.
There’s only one way
for you and Hikaru-chan to be happy.
And that is...
To have a lot of abnormal sex.
H-Huh?
Normal sex can’t satisfy Hikaru-chan.
You must make love to her in ways
so embarrassing she can barely stand it.
Even if she resists, push through.
Otherwise, misfortune will keep following you.
Abnormal sex?
To be continued