Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
In the dawn of Japan's modernization,
a time of great political upheaval,
the waves of life swept two lovers
away in opposite directions.
But even if a flower's life fades away,
love is eternal.
And so, the lovers' unfulfilled wish was passed on to their grandchildren, who were to be married.
Little did they know this High Collar Lady
had other plans.
Love is a willful sailboat, they say.
Scared by the recent turn of events,
Ranmaru, who is one year younger,
convinces Benio to elope together.
Episode 3
A Romantic Hangover
I made her favorite, grilled chicken, again. Hopefully she'll eat it.
Going on a hunger strike
isn't good for her health.
Young Lady, I made grilled chicken!
Let's see...
Oh my! Sir!
What's wrong, Nanny?
Did you find more cockroaches?
The young lady,
s-s-she's ran away!
To my dear Father
What?!
S-She eloped?
Who did she run away with?
She went with Ranmaru!
Ranmaru?
That's a good one.
I'm not joking!
What are you going to do?!
If Second Lieutenant Ijuuin
loses face because of this,
I'll commit seppuku!
My lord!
Don't do that, please don't do that!
I think we've gone far enough.
Shinagawa ward, 1st Street
Huh? We're still in Shinagawa?
Tokyo is quite a big city...
I'm getting kind of hungry...
Come to think of it, I am too.
I'd love some grilled chicken right now...
I thought eloping would have been a more romantic experience...
I'd eat anything,
but no store is open at this hour of the night.
And it's pitch black.
I-I'm scared, Benio!
Calm down, Ranmaru, are you
gonna be afraid of the dark forever?
A monster!
W-Who are you calling a monster?!
W-We don't have any money,
and we don't taste good!
Please, spare us!
What are you talking about?!
You dumbass!
Stop being violent!
Stop acting like you're a man!
Actually, I am a boy...
W-What?
Ah, I see, you've got a typical "high collar" lady here with you.
If you keep dilly-dallying,
some stranger might pounce on you!
Like this:
Take this!
Amazing!
W-Who you think you're dealing with?
Take a look at this goldfish tattoo! Don't look down on the notorious Rickshaw Ushigorou!
Prepare to be taught a lesson!
Benio!
Take this! And that! You swine!
Stop it, please! Stop fighting!
Don't hurt Benio!
Oh my, look at that. Looks like
he was the one that got hurt.
And he got beaten by a girl!
I may not look it, but I've trained hard,
so don't think you can take me lightly!
So cool!
Huh, you want some more?
Come on then, I'm in a bad mood today!
Color me surprised!
I've never lost to anyone before,
and to a girl, of all things, too!
I have to admit,
you've beaten me!
Boss!
Wh-What did he call me?
B-Boss...?
Yes, I want to be
your henchman!
Henchman?
You've gotta be kidding, right?
I beg you!
Listen, we were in the middle
of eloping together.
I won't interfere!
Boss, you're the strongest man I've ever met!
Wh-What was that?!
I mean, you're the strongest
woman I've ever met!
So please, even though you've never been a boss,
and I've always been a lone wolf,
I want to humbly serve you,
and cater to my boss's every need!
C'mon, Boss! Eat and drink
to your heart's content!
Sounds fun!
I'm in! First of all,
let's have a toast!
If any occasion to grab a drink,
one drinks to the occasion!
Well, let's take a little break
from your elopement.
Come on, let's go
with the first cup!
First of all, let's make
our oath official.
B-B-Benio!
Me, too!
Bottoms up, Boss!
It's the good stuff!
W-Well, it's not like modern
girls can't drink Sake.
Right, there's only a little bit here.
I shouldn't be scared of this!
That'dth the spirit!
That hit the spot!
Benio!
Oh, looks like you can
hold your liquor, Boss.
Gulp!
Now that's what I like to see!
You're gutsy!
You be gusty, heh.
More! More!
Here you are!
B-Benio... W-What
about our elopement?
Whaya'?
I speak drunkard,
so I can translate whatever she says.
Whaya'?
"What?"
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
'Dja say, Ranmaru?
"What did you say, Ranmaru?"
This is awful,
her eyes are totally glazed...
Hammers mark the city rhythm:
whack, whack, whack!
Streetcars scurrying about:
packed, packed, packed!
Benio is actually drunk!
Once more!
Huh? D-Didya call me?
Hammers mark the city rhythm:
whack, whack, whack!
Streetcars scurrying about:
packed, packed, packed!
Is there some more sake?
More?
More.
Come on, bring out the good stuff!
This was supposed to be our elopement!
Gosh, no, no, no!
Hanamura
Young Lady!
Benio!
That's enough.
She might as well be disowned now.
So are we going to
stop looking for her?!
W-Well, actually...
Oh, is that so? I'll look for
her all night, if I have to!
Let's just go for
another thirty minutes.
Young Lady!
Hammefsark the ciry rhyrhn:
wyack, whack, wyack!
Stfeetcars sdurrhing about:
lacked, packrs, padked!
I wonder if Benio even
knows what eloping is...
According to a Kabuki story,
Umekawa and Chuubei...
ran away, hand in hand,
following the path of their love...
under a moonlit sky...
That's what you'd call a true "honeymoon"...
Come on, encore!
Hammeark ciry rhyrw:
ack, ack, wyack!
Stfeefcars sfurry round:
acked, packrs, padked!
How did it come to this?
Ugh...
Hey, let's go to the next bar.
Don't push it, they're all
gonna lose soon anyway.
Oh, come on, we're soldiers, after all.
Man, you two really are hopeless.
Let's go in, then.
There's an empty table.
B-B-B-Benio, Benio, listen!
'Dya wan', Rambaru?
"What do you want, Ranmaru?"
Gimme more Sake.
Look, that's not the
problem right now!
That laughing guy!
That high collar tomboy!
It's pretty strange, though.
What are you doing here,
of all places?
Th-That's my line!
Oh, you know her?
Oh, I got it! My father sent you to take me back home?
B-Benio, do we have to go home?
Boss, what's the matter?
What's going on here, Benio?
Too bad, I'm never
going back home!
Oh, come on, calm down.
Don't touch me!
I'm halfway into
eloping with Ranmaru!
R-Right!
Don't think you can stop us!
Oh, eloping?
So you mean that you're
in love with Ranmaru?
U-Uh... O-Of course!
What a liar!
He bought it!
That's wrong!
It's not a lie!
I truly love Benio!
Hey, lovely maiden!
Eloping isn't any fun
if you're both girls!
C'mere, let's knock
back more sake!
C-Come on, girl!
I-I'm a boy!
Oh, that's fine by me.
Ah, Benio!
Get your filthy hands
off Ranmaru, you drunk!
You've done it now!
Hey, bastard!
What are you
doin' to my Boss?!
What's wrong with you?!
You take this, this, this!
Ushigorou!
Take this, and that, and some of this!
Darling, I was convinced I had taught our
daughter how to be a woman, but still...
Take this!
You too!
And a little of this!
Looks like fun!
Let's join in!
H-Hey, stop that!
Hey, please stop this!
Ah, Benio!
What are you whinin' for?!
It's your fault we're in
this mess, help us out!
Huh, did something
hit my head just now?
I'm not in my element...
S-Second Lieutenant,
please make this stop!
I got it, I got it.
Uh, are you actually
going to make this stop?
Yeah, yeah, don't worry!
Why, you little—
Watch out!
Why don't you stop
meddling for once?!
Not a chance,
I'm so good at it.
Why, you—
Dammit...
For God's sake, what the hell is
wrong with tonight's customers?!
This is bad, the cops are coming.
Hey, Ijuuin, we'll take care of this.
You hurry out the back.
Alright, thanks.
Let's go, Benio.
I-I don't care!
Why don't you mind
your own business?!
You hit me...
I've never been hit in my whole life,
not even by my own father.
You're right, I slapped you.
Any man who hits a woman
can never call himself a man!
I did it because
you wouldn't listen.
What do you think would happen to your father,
an army major, if his daughter was arrested?
Come on, let's hurry!
Boss, please, wait!
Benio!
Hey!
Uh?
Huh?
Wh-What?
Hey, we were just drinking some
sake and messing around, right?
Yup!
Ouch, ouch...
Are you alright?!
Benio...
Wh-What...
What in the world am I doing?
Holding the Second Lieutenant's hand like this...
I shouldn't feel anything for him.
In fact, I should even hate him.
And yet, with his face
this close to mine...
My heart feels like it's
beating out of my chest.
It's like I'm dreaming...
My feet are floating...
Is it the sake that
smells so good?
What is this smell?
Everything...
Everything is straight out of a dream.
Throb
My head hurts!
A clear sign of a hangover!
How could a lady indulge in
alcohol before she's married?!
You damn idiot!
I feel all dizzy...
Why did you do such
a disgraceful thing?
Uh, could you lower your
voice just a little bit?
Shut up!
You'd better be grateful for what
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin did!
Ijuuin?
Didn't you realize you
were about to get arrested?
You moron!
Hey, you, what are
you doing to my boss?
Who the hell is this guy?!
Oh! I forgot all about him.
He's my henchman.
Henchman?
Yeah, that's right.
Ushigorou, that's my father.
Master, this is your father?
Allow me to do the honors.
I'm your daughter's henchman.
My name is Rickshaw Ushigorou.
I'm pleased to meet you!
Wh-What...?
The daughter of an army major
adopting yakuza manners...
So shameful, right?
What will her fiancé
think about this...?
It's too bad, it was such
a great marriage deal.
Isn't it better like this?
I never wanted to get married
from the very start.
Now he'll probably reject me.
He said he's not going
to change his mind.
Wh-What was that?!
I couldn't even try to explain
why he's the way he is.
But you should be thankful there's a man
who still wants to marry a tomboy like you!
Despite all of this,
he hasn't given up?
Think he's got a few screws loose?
Maybe he just doesn't put
a lot of thought into marriage.
At any rate, if I don't do anything,
I'll end up getting married.
My high collar lifestyle will be gone for good
before I ever get a chance to fall in love.
I'm told that Ranmaru
has been sick since then,
and I'm not allowed to visit him.
I'm sorry, Ranmaru.
Yo, Boss!
How ya doin', Boss?!
Boss, would you allow
me accompany you?
It's just one bad thing after another.
Boss Benio's ride
Make way! C'mon, people!
Make way for the boss!
Very unconventional
company for a young lady.
Is that rain or are those tears that fall on
the way to this sacred garden of learning?
Either way, she's running head-first
into the High Collar lifestyle!
Boss Benio's misadventures go on,
as her henchman, Goldfish Ushigorou,
causes turmoil in her all-girls school.
On top of all of that, she learns about
her friend Tamaki's unrequited love,
who just so happens to be
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
Ah, love, the root of every pain.
There's no end to Benio's troubles.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"A Messy Asakusa Opera"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
amicus
darkcart
ImAWasteOfHair
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
Ziusudra
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
amicus
darkcart
ImAWasteOfHair
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
Ziusudra