Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Even after all the efforts Benio made
to return to her father's lovely old home,
she discovered that her old-fashioned father
was less than thrilled with this development.
She concludes there's no way
out of this impasse.
Thus, she had to leave the same way she came.
Meanwhile, Shinobu comes to fetch her, but as fate would have it, they miss each other by mere minutes
and end up straying further apart.
Benio keeps drinking more and more to drown her worries in alcohol, until her brawler side shows through.
But her dangerous choice of an opponent is a disaster—
Shinobu's direct superior,
who holds Shinobu's future firmly in his hands.
Episode 18
Scoring Grudges is Dangerous!
Fight!
We've a fight here! A fight!
This woman's raising hell!
Raising hell? Could it be Benio?
Excuse me, please let me through.
Aren't you the ones who bumped into me?!
Shut up!
Y-You dare to raise a hand against me?!
You saw it, right?
Officer, sir, please be my witness!
They're the ones who resorted to violence.
Y-You whore!
Stand and answer for what you did!
Oh, really?
Make way! Make way!
What's this, eh?
T-Those two are picking a fight!
This officer saw it all—he can testify.
Damn you...
Then you four will come to the station with us.
No, I c-can't.
I'm in a hurry, you know.
Please don't be so cold,
I need you as my witness!
Benio...
Where are you now
and what are you doing?
You're going to answer for this.
Answer for what? You were the one
so drunk you tumbled into our table!
I-I'm sorry, she's a bit of a mean drunk.
No I ain't!
I can't be a mean drunk!
Mean drunk...
What's that?
You lowlife, think you can
talk your way out of this?
Shinagawa Police Station
Can't you understand even after all I've said?
At any rate, you see, I'm in a hurry.
You'll have to excuse me now.
Well then...
Why would someone in a hurry get off his horse?
You had a reason for stopping to watch this brawl,
so what's the story?
Eh?
Y-You see, I, uhm...
I still have more questions for you.
So you're staying here for little while longer, understand?
Sh-Show some respect when talking an officer of the Imperial Army's 1st Division!
Well now, don't be so stiff.
Here. Wipe your face with this.
Lt. Colonel​, that is a dust rag!
Wh-What?
Apologize at once for making a fool of me!
Shouldn't you be the one apologizing?
1st Division or 1st Multiplication,
what license is that for being a nuisance?
Can't you drink quietly?!
I am quiet, though.
I await your apology.
For that and being such an insufferable snob!
You lowly brat,
you're speaking to an Imperial soldier!
Here they go again!
What's so special about being a soldier?
Even my dad...
Even Shinobu!
Even Shinobu...
Shinobu is a soldier, too.
Shinobu, you idiot! Idiot!
I never figured you for the maudlin type, Benio!
What a vulgar woman!
Precisely!
She may be a woman,
but she's affronted the Imperial Army!
She obviously had it coming!
Loud and clear! Cider and beer!
B-Benio! Shh! Shh!
Let them bring it on!
Even all five at once!
When did you become so many?
How cowardly! A whole army against a single girl!
Oh... Oh no!
Our Boss may be incredibly strong,
but she's drunk and up against five men!
Moreover, those are professional soldiers,
so there's no way she wins!
I gotta run right now and bring the lieutenant!
Ah! W-Where are you going, Ushi?
No-no. You can't do this to us!
Listen up, Ranbuddy.
If you're a man and in love with Boss,
you'll defend her with all you've got!
Play for time!
E-Even if I wanted to...
Hey, wait up!
I'm just a pretty boy...
I have nothing!
Hey-hey, Ushi! C'mere, Ushi!
Oh geez...
Sounds swell. Sounds swell!
Oi! Give it!
I need to be smashed if
I'm going to get through this!
You've finally come round?
Good thinking, Ranmaru.
Ma'am, refill!
Refill!
Oh?
Ouch!
Now she's done it!
Alright!
Fine by me. Bring it on!
C'mon!
Bitch, think you can get away with this
just 'cause you're a woman?!
Let's do it!
My, I didn't mean to.
I guess I'm a violent drunk too!
Wow! Way to go, Ranmaru!
You've got my back!
Take that!
You also had it coming!
Ah! Don't hurt me!
B-Benio...
Stay close, Ranmaru.
Dammit. They're pretty tough for women.
You can't escape now!
Sorry for detaining you for so long.
Goodbye.
Go!
Benio!
Where... Where is she?
Fight! Fight!
Hey! We've got a fight here! Come see!
What's your problem, jerk?!
You wanna fight? I'm all for it!
You bastard!
Another false alarm.
Still, why do I think of Benio
whenever I hear that there's a fight?
It's a bad habit. I need to lose it.
W-We're surrounded!
What are we gonna do, Benio?
Come on! It's just one girl!
Take her on! Forward!
Benio!
Take this!
Yay! I'm seeing stars! I'm so happy!
Out already?
Take this! And that! And this! And that!
Ah!
That's it! Keep going!
How did it come to this?
It's gonna cost someone a pretty penny...
Room divider: add 50 sen!
One smashed stool.
And add 10 sen for ten smashed flasks...
Hey, it's just me, your friend Ushigorou!
Hey, don't ya understand me?
Boss is in big trouble!
Why can't ya understand? Oh geez...
Please let me pass! I beg you!
Y’all never'll understand, won't ya...
They're barking...
Could it be that Lady Benio has come back?
We've gotta give her a warm welcome!
Hm. That's for sure!
Ah, I can't wait!
My dear, you seem quite fast for your age!
Shut it, I've gotta be the one who opens the door!
Hey! What insolence!
You dare to defy your lord?!
No, but opening the door is my job, after all!
Benio...
Benio!
Benio, isn't that you?
Benio, are you hiding somewhere?
Benio!
Hey, hey!
It's about time you stopped getting so upset at the sight of me!
I serve Boss! Don't you understand who Boss is?
B-O-S-S!
Oh, I know!
Boss's scent is something you've gotta recognize!
Let's see... Here.
Take a look.
Oh dear me! This is Ranmaru's loincloth, isn't it?!
My bad. It won't happen again.
Let's see.
Here it is, it's this one! This!
Look.
There, you see it now?
Boss is my priority!
I've gotta talk to Shinobu, pronto!
It's important!
We got a deal?
Then why don't you...
Let me pass?
Ah... I get restless if I don't keep busy.
I probably shouldn't be saying this,
but this mansion is so tidy without Lady Benio around.
It's urgent! Urgent!
That racket...
I can't deal with this!
What? Benio?
Y-Yes.
She's surrounded by five soldiers.
I came for Shinobu...
Where is he?
Shinobu went out to look for Benio.
No way!
At such an important time...
they missed each other by this much?
Whatever, I'll do it!
It's a battle! I might be old,
but I'm still a Satsuma samurai!
It falls to me to protect our family's first lady!
Bring me my spear! Ready the horses!
Let's go! Let's go, I said!
Dear!
If you do that, you'll sprain your back again!
A battle is at hand!
My country needs me!
I must go!
Dear!
No! Get off me! I gotta go!
No, don't go!
Oh my!
There! Move out!
After me, men!
I got a little carried away...
I'm really not sure
if we can rely on this geezer at all...
Ladies and gentlemen,
it seems we've as good as lost already.
I'm counting on you, Ushigorou!
I have to make it to the battlefield!
Good gracious,
I wonder what kind of battle he thinks it is.
Is he still that obsessed
with proving his mettle as a samurai?
We have to hurry up, Ushigorou!
Hang in there, Benio.
I'll come to your rescue soon enough!
Ushigorou, off we go!
Hut, hut, hurrah!
Dear!
Are you hurt, Milord?
Imbecile! Hey, wait!
After him!
You! Wait for me!
Lord...
Wait, Ushigorou!
Huh?! When did I lose my passenger?
Slam!
Please stop it, everyone!
Take this!
Hey! Stop embarrassing yourselves!
How long can it take for five soldiers
to defeat a single girl?
Weaklings!
Easy for him to say!
He's only been watching so far.
I'm worn out...
Taking on five at once isn't very fair, after all.
I need five times the energy.
You go from the right, I'll be on the left.
Alright. This time for sure.
Do it! Do it now!
Like hell!
Now!
I got her!
W-What are you doing? You monster!
You already know it!
We'll take it out on you now!
B-Benio's in danger!
Hands off Benio!
Piss off!
Ranmaru...
Wh-What's going on?
Boss!
Benio! Are you safe?
Count!
Fear not!
With your soon-to-be grandfather here,
not a hair will fall from your head.
Let's do it! C'mon, let's do it!
Gramps, what's wrong?
I sprained my back...
What's up with this infirm geezer?
What? I may be old,
but I still have the heart of a Satsuma warrior.
Age has not blunted my mastery one bit!
Prepare yourselves!
With all my experience, I step forth!
A-Are you alright, Liutenant Colonel​?
T-That geezer is out of his mind.
I'm going.
Me too.
Me three.
Roll call over!
I may have aged,
but I'm still the head of the Ijuuin family!
I'll teach you a lesson!
What? Ijuuin?
Benio, where are you?
Ranmaru and Ushigorou are probably with her.
Check out this fight!
Another one?
Hold on, did you say "Ijuuin" just now?
So what of it?
You feeling weak in the knees?
Ushigorou's rickshaw!
Wait a minute.
I've got an earful for you, Count Ijuuin.
Hm. If you're scared,
get on your knees and beg for mercy!
Show him none, Count!
Grandfather, Benio!
Hm?
Sh-Shinobu!
Oh, it's you, Shinobu?
Would you care to explain this to me, Grandfather?
How come you're here...
And, moreover, dressed like that?
Ranmaru, are you hurt?
Ranmaru...
I may be a coward, but I was prepared to die for her.
If you really want Benio's hand in marriage,
you'll need to be able to protect her at all times!
If you can't do that,
I'll never let you have her!
Ranmaru,
now's not the time for that...
Huh? "Ranmaru"? Is that maid who I think she is?
Or did I mishear it?
Hey, hey, hey, Ranbuddy, come this way.
I need to tend to your wounds.
Okay...
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
Y-Yessir!
What's wrong with you?
Shinobu! How can you stand at attention before that awful man?
That's right!
Even if he outranks you,
you don't need to obey an asshole like that!
Grandfather, Benio,
this man you've been fighting
happens to be my direct superior.
Lieutenant Colonel Innen
of 1st Division Headquarters.
Good grief, no wonder he's only qualified for short division.
Lame!
A worthless man is worthless regardless of his rank.
S-Second Lieutenant Ijuuin,
do you know these civilians?
Yes. This woman is my fiancée.
In other words, Major Hanamura's daughter?
Yes.
To be engaged with such a vulgar
and unfeminine woman...
Maybe you should reconsider things,
Second Lieutenant?
You're the one who brought
five guys to deal with a girl!
You're a disgrace to all men!
Speaking of which,
whatever on earth happened to you and your men?
A number's been done on you.
Nothing in particular!
So I thought.
After all, there is no way a single woman...
could mess up a squad of imperial soldiers that badly, right?
Yes. Of course one couldn't.
More importantly, as a soldier yourself,
you ought to teach your fiancée some manners!
Huh?
Outrageous! W-We're leaving!
Yessir!
Oh my, leaving already?
Damn that bastard Ijuuin and his nosiness.
He's a soldier, yet he's physically weak
and lets his hair grow long.
I've always felt that he's up to no good.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen is really furious now!
You know things are about get real nasty
when he has that look on his face.
So scary!
Rejoice, the enemy has been routed. We've won!
You can lose a battle but win the war.
The obstinate and vindictive Lt. Col Innen
still intends to have to the last laugh.
You'll pay for this.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Our High Collar Lady, who's made an enemy of the entire Imperial Army,
is yet to learn that scoring grudges...
is dangerous!
Right after declaring victory
against the soldiers,
and too drunk to walk, High Collar Lady
gets to have sweet, sweet dreams
while carried on Shinobu's back.
This in turn brings peace to the household,
and even the elderly couple is touched.
But all the while, behind closed doors,
Lt. Col Innen is plotting something...
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady: "Fleeting Happiness."
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan