Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Benio didn't come home after school,
so the Ijuuins were understandably worried.
Concerned for her safety,
Shinobu went to look for her personally.
However,
Benio's father stopped him in his tracks, demanding an explanation of his relationship with Kichiji.
Meanwhile,
through listening to Kichiji's life story,
Benio realized how caring Shinobu really is.
And now she's gushing with joy, ecstatic.
But the world is smaller than we think,
and the unlikable Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen
runs into them again.
Yet another humiliation at the hands of Benio only serves to throw more fuel into the fire of his vendetta,
which now roars with a ferocious strength.
Still unaware of this,
for how long will our High Collar Lady
be able to retain that carefree smile of hers?
Episode 23
Heaven Yesterday, Hell Today
Hammers mark the city rhythm:
whack, whack, whack!
Streetcars scurrying about...
I'm back!
Benio, we wouldn't want anyone
to see you in this state.
Let's hurry to your room, okay?
Huh, what's the buzz?
Let's drink some more!
I'm so happy!
Oh, come on, Benio!
Don't be a killjoy!
To learn that Shinobu's is not a playboy...
And on top of this...
If I know that you're going to be the one with the Young Master, I should be glad to give up on him.
Didja hear that?
She said it!
Come on, Benio!
Right, Ranmaru?
Welcome back, Lady Benio.
Huh?!
Whoa!
Oh no! We've been spotted!
W-What a disgraceful look!
I'm happy! And I love everyone in this house!
So many nice people in here!
And I love my dear Kisaragi, too!
Eh?!
B-Benio, that's a bit too much!
Cheers to this beautiful life in the pink!
Hi there!
My favorite person in the whole world.
Good to see you in high spirits, Benio.
Oh? Shinobu is right here!
Why are you wearing nothing but pajamas?
If you wanted to set the mood,
you'd be better off wearing a negligee.
Unless you're just messing around...
N-Nobody's messing around!
What about you,
what are you even reading this late?
A Russian-Japanese dictionary.
Russian? Russian...
Yes.
Russian. Right...
You know there's been
a revolution in Russia, right?
Emperor Nicholas II was overthrown,
and now they're in a protracted civil war.
Y-Yes... Kind of...
So the USA and Japan are considering an intervention
to quell the insurrectionists.
Huh?!
Don't tell me...
You're going to Russia?
Who knows...
I doubt they'll dispatch the troops stationed in Tokyo, though.
Geographically, it makes more sense to dispatch the Kyushu and Hokuriku garrisons there.
Don't go...
Huh?
U-Uhm...
Do you love me?
Benio.
Ah!
What in the world did I just say?
It seems the alcohol went straight to my head.
I do love you.
Wha... Even if I am a careless, average girl,
who goes berserk when drunk?
Shut up! Shut up, you idiot!
I love you.
He is so close to me...
He is getting even closer!
Oh, alright.
Well, good night then.
Benio!
Maybe she didn't understand?
I just confessed my love, yet she was completely unmoved...
At this rate, I'll lose all of my confidence.
I feel weird, like I've just been told
something important...
Oh my, Benio!
You still haven't changed?
I can't remember what he said...
Watch out!
Whoa! She has a terrible fever! This is serious!
Somebody, please!
Somebody!
Strange, huh?
I still can't believe it.
I know, right?
What might have happened to Lady Benio?
She's never had a fever before...
How could such a healthy girl develop a fever?
Maybe something happened
that shook her to the core.
That must be it,
something we don't know about.
Good grief...
I slept so well!
Ah, it feels great!
That reminds me,
just what happened yesterday?
He's been helping me in any way he could,
and was there when I needed encouragement.
He is a truly caring and chivalrous man.
Your marriage will be the one
that stands the test of time.
Yes, I remember now!
Yesterday was an amazing day!
Hooray!
And alley-oop!
Good morning, Lady Benio.
Morning!
Hey, wait a second there.
Here. These silk stockings are for you!
Whoa, so wonderful!
Is this for real?
At the time, nylon wasn't invented yet
and wearing silk stockings was every girl's dream.
Whatever, while we're at it...
You can have these too!
Really? You're so kind!
Good morning!
Good morning, Benio.
Morning.
Oh, Benio, you look rather happy this morning.
Did something good happen to you?
Yes! Countess, please find
somewhere to put these on display.
Why, thank you, Benio!
Benio, what's this "good thing" that happened?
Uhm, you see... Actually, I...
wanted to express my utmost gratitude to both of you for raising Shinobu to be the lovely person he is today.
Oh, I see!
It's all because I raised him right!
Oh? Yet it seemed to me like you barely did any raising.
Ah, no, actually...
Oh, would you look at this!
It laid an egg!
My, congratulations!
Benio, hurry up with laying some of your own!
E-Eggs?!
No, no, my bad. Not eggs,
great-grandchildren!
A new spring is about to come to our home!
The spring I've been awaiting for all my life...
Hold up, Ushigorou. I want to stop by my old home before school.
Alright! But are ya sure we have the time, Boss?
It's not a big deal if I'm late by just a few minutes.
Alright, gotcha!
L-Lord, Young Lady is here!
Wh-What? Again?
How do you do?
Good morning, Father.
Hey, Benio, what did they kick you out for this time?
Oh, cut it out! I came this morning
to tell you some good news for a change!
I don't believe it.
What really happened?
Father, I...
I would like to extend my thanks to you.
H-Hey, Benio, where did that come from?
You've always told me how Shinobu
is a truly noble person
and that I should trust him unquestionably.
Today, I can finally say
that I'm convinced of his greatness.
I express my admiration for your keen eye!
I see!
So I take it that things
are finally going well with the lieutenant?
Yes!
Oh, no!
I'm late for school!
I'm off!
She never changes, huh?
But aren't you glad that she now stands firmly
on track to marriage?
My dear, you can rejoice now.
It seems that Benio
is finally at peace with her destiny.
Praise be the Lord, praise be the Lord!
The year is 1918 - Japan is on the verge of a historic decision to dispatch troops to Siberia.
July 1918
Stop... Turn right!
Start marching!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin Shinobu coming in!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin, uh-huh,
there are orders for your transfer, uh-huh.
Huh? Transfer?
Attention!
Imperial Army Second Lieutenant Ijuuin Shinobu,
As of today, you are seconded to the 12th Army Division, 14th Infantry Regiment, 3rd Battalion,
as a field commander of the 2nd Platoon, uh-uhm.
Yessir!
Where is 12th Division stationed?
Kokura in Kyushu.
Kyushu?
A long way from here...
But why this sudden reassignment?
Within the next week,
you need to finish your work
and depart for your new post. Uhm, hm.
Yessir!
Atonashi School for Girls
First you obey your husband,
then you obey your son,
this is the only correct path
a Japanese woman can take.
Good morning, everyone!
Hmph...
Oh, my!
My apologies!
Ha-Ha-Hanamura!
Yeah, yeah, I got you,
Standing in the hallway isn't half-bad either.
Stand up!
Bow!
You'll be here all day long!
Eat it!
Excuse me?
Alright, she's gone now!
Gosh, she's so annoying!
Benio, what happened?
You provoked the teacher again, didn't you?
Yes, I just wanted to share
a bit of my happiness with her.
Oh? Did they appoint the date
for your marriage?
Come on, Benio, what was it?
Pretty close, but not quite it.
It's amazing, Benio!
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you!
Thanks...
Ah, by the way, girls, how about you come to the Ijuuins' place this afternoon?
I'm holding a small party to celebrate
and you're all invited!
Wonderful!
Benio, so you're getting married soon?
Yeah!
Be sure to come, all of you, okay?
What's with that noise?
Ugh, I can't see well...
I hope it's not infectious.
Hey, so they're transferring you to Kyushu?
Sounds hella sudden.
Yeah...
Hey, you!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen!
Heard you're going to Kokura, huh?
I hear the guys there are having a hard time
scrambling the expeditionary force,
so you better get used to dealing with rural roughnecks,
not well-behaved Tokyoites.
I wonder how long will our noble boy last?
Will, I'll be going.
Watch yourself, kid.
That was snide of him.
I can't stand him at all!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen is well-connected in the Army High Command, so please keep your guard up.
Don't tell me...
That self-important mop-head...
Out of sight - out of mind -
that is my priority.
Can you imagine how will that schoolgirl react...
Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
Major Hanamura, sir?
Come with me for a second.
Is it true that you're being transferred to Kokura?
Yessir.
That's ridiculous...
You're the only one getting transferred
in our entire division.
There are no other personnel changes.
But the division commander
received an official order...
Just when Benio finally came
with some good news this morning...
What's going on?
Major, what's wrong?
Father, are you alright?
You've just called me "Father," haven't you?
This is wrong...
Let's see, how many people
would probably be coming...
Oh, you can place it there.
Okay.
All of my classmates have enormous appetites,
so make sure to prepare lots of refreshments, okay?
Okay!
Lady Benio, there is a call for you.
Really? Who is it?
Hello, it's Benio!
Huh?! Transferred?
Hey, Benio!
Hey!
Hello?!
He's going away...
Shinobu is going away...
It's so stupid...
Simply ridiculous!
You're being transferred!
You're being transferred...
How did it come to this?
They're sending him so far away...
Yes. Shinobu told me just now...
Get yourself together!
O-Okay... But dear...
It's for the country...
Our country!
He's going away...
Shinobu is going...
...far, far away.
Benio!
Have you heard the news?
Shinobu's getting transferred!
I'm so happy!
This means the odds look good for me again!
Oh? O-Oh...
How cruel! Didn't you say yourself
that you don't want to see his face anymore?
I mean, yes, I did that, but...
It's just that my hand moved on its own!
Silly hand! Silly! You must not do this!
I wonder how it could have happened!
Silly!
Lady Benio, your friends have come
to party with you.
Tamaki...
Benio.
We took you up on that offer!
Come on, show us your future husband
and the love nest you've prepared!
We wanna hear all the cheesy stories you got!
This is a little something from us to celebrate!
It's not much, but I'll prepare something better
for your actual wedding ceremony!
Come on, accept our presents, Benio.
Thank you. These are all great presents...
But... I can't have them.
Benio!
I can't look at Benio,
she's so pitiable!
Did something happen, Ranmaru?
It's Shinobu...
They're transferring him to faraway Kyushu!
How come?
There's a call for you, Lady Benio.
Hello, it's Benio.
Oh, it's you, Father?
Is that you, Benio? Have you heard
about Shinobu getting transferred?
Yes...
Something about that doesn't feel right to me.
Doesn't feel right?
Could it be that you did something
to incur the wrath of Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen?
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen?
I don't quite remember... Innen...
Wait, wait, wait!
Soldiers this, soldiers that -
it's nuffin' to be proud of, you!
A-Actually, Father, could it be that this Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen has...
Face the shape of an upside-down onion,
lifeless eyes with a sinister look in them,
lips the shape of the Mt. Fuji,
a stupid mustache
and to top it off, eyebrows that look
like a line of dots - is that him?
How harsh!
Good to know that descriptive powers
run in the family.
Well, he does have a face like that, anyway.
Just as I thought!
Does this mean that it was he
who masterminded Shinobu's transfer out of spite?
Uhm, well, I can't
rule this possibility out...
In any case, given the circumstances,
we'll have to postpone the wedding...
That's not what you should be saying!
Benio! What are you going to do now?
Hold up! Hold up I said!
This is all so sudden...
I don't even know
what I should put in his suitcase.
Such a shame...
Oh, Lady Benio!
Where are you headed?
I am now going to meet
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen of 1st Division.
Things have taken a turn for the worse:
yesterday was heaven, but today has become hell,
and she needs to let that anger out somehow.
Our High Collar Lady is armed and dangerous and she's willing to put her life on the line!
High Collar Lady isn't having any more of that.
Even as a single woman, she's not afraid
to take on the entire 1st Division of the Imperial Army.
This is a real emergency!
News spread like wildfire -
from the Count to the servants,
to the geisha Kichiji,
the Violet Band from Kanto family,
even Benio's teacher and classmates
enter the great coalition to help Benio!
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"I Can't Stand Martinets!"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan