Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
It's pitch-black!
Yeah! It's pitch-black!
One more time!
It's pitch-black!
I can't hear you!
In the past, people rode on the backs of animals, or were carried around.
Let me go!
Nowadays, trains magically take people wherever they want to go!
All the smoke makes the tunnel...
pitch-black!
Episode 1
Benio's Seventeenth Birthday
It's the seventh year of the Taishou Era,
and people are fascinated by
Romanticism, the trend of the times.
The heyday of Taishou Democracy.
Hanamura
That stings!
Y-You're too rough, Benio!
Why are you hitting me so hard?
What do you mean, Ranmaru?
You're a boy, right? Now, en garde!
W-Wait, hold on a second, Benio!
A duel waits for no one!
You sadist!
If you can still run like that,
then you can fight!
S-Stop, stop, I give up!
You give up?
Weakling.
Ranmaru, once more!
That's enough!
Enough already, Benio.
But we just started training...
Ranmaru is going to be a Kabuki actor,
he doesn't need fencing practice.
T-That's right, sir!
You shut your mouth!
Father, you know Ranmaru lost his
mother when he was young, like I did.
But it's made him such a weakling.
So, to fill that void his mother left,
I'm determined to make a man out of him!
U-Uh, Benio, isn't it about time
you went to girls' school?
I believe it is.
You'd better get going.
Oh no!
Phew, that was close.
Thank you for the lesson, Master.
Wide open!
Must I keep repeating myself?!
Eyes on your opponent!
Sir!
It's no bed of roses, is it?
No bed of roses?
No, far from it.
Benio is amazing.
Yaoya Oshichiya, Agemaki Dayuu...
There are so many wonderful Kabuki women.
But even so, none can ever,
ever compare to how divine Benio is.
I mean, why else would I
practice so early every morning?
What are you trying to say?
Oh, it's nothing!
I've got to keep a closer
eye on those two.
Our Late Sister
Akizuki Sumire
But she's already 17 years old, too.
Even I have to admit, without her mother,
she's turned into quite a tomboy.
What am I to do with her...?
I'm heading out!
The cherry blossoms
are in full bloom!
The swaying heat haze,
the water of Koishikawa...
Half boots on my feet,
maroon trousers,
and a ribbon fluttering on my head...
This is the life of a teenage student.
It's actually my seventeenth birthday.
Good things are bound to happen!
No! No! Go away!
Ow, that hurt...
What's up with this guy?
Oh, forgive me.
Do you need a hand?
No thank you, I don't need it!
This was nothing.
Smmmmack!
Oh...
Wh-What's your problem?!
Didn't anyone tell you it's not
good etiquette to make fun of ladies?!
It's people like you that stop Japanese women
from getting ahead in the world! Good day!
What's up with that
high collar student?
Oh well, oh well.
Oh well, oh well,
A high collar girl's thick head is like a shellfish stewing in its shell...
Atonashi
Girls'
School
Goodness, Benio.
What happened to your feet?
Nothing!
Hey, did you hear what I did yesterday?
I went to a Rossi opera in Asakusa!
It was incredible!
"Love is like a sweet flower in a field!"
Whoa, I wish I'd been there, too!
I'm so jealous!
So what was the plot about?
C'mon, teach us the lyrics!
Ladies!
The bell has long since rung!
Do you plan on chatting the whole day away?!
These youngsters sure are rowdy...
Stand up!
Bow!
Righteous path towards wifehood
Today, ladies, I will teach you
how to sew a lined kimono.
But before that, let's see your yukata projects I assigned to you last week.
Oh, drat!
Oh, to hell with it,
I'll just use the excuse I used last week!
What did you say?!
You didn't do it?!
It completely slipped my mind!
It completely slipped your mind, you say?
Is that right, Hanamura Benio?
It really did!
So, it "slipped your mind" like it did last week,
and the week before, and the one before that!
Are you telling me you've been
forgetting it every single time?!
Stand there with those buckets!
Ladies, having such a shameless attitude
will keep you from shining as the proud, envied and educated mothers of Japan!
I forgot about my
homework, too, ma'am!
Kitakoji Tamaki?
Be quiet!
I'd expect this much from Hanamura,
but from an honor student like you...?
That's right, I forgot.
And another thing, ma'am.
If we are to become independent, then shouldn't
we be able to pick our own husbands?
To quote Hiratsuka Raichou:
In the beginning, women truly were
genuine, and shone like the Sun.
Righteous path towards wifehood
We, as women, are not to be "chosen" by men,
we are the ones who do the choosing.
That choice is ours,
and ours alone.
Benio ❤️ Kazuo
I will not hear another word of your propaganda!
Stand out in the hall, now!
Righteous path towards wifehood
Tamaki?
Can she be anymore monotonous?
All she says is that we should
become "mothers of Japan".
What a joke.
I refuse to marry a man,
just because my parents say so.
I didn't think you'd speak like that,
Miss Silk-Stockings.
Oh, please. Nobles are
regular people, too, you know?
Tamaki! You did do
your homework after all!
You did all that for me?
As I've said,
that teacher bores me.
Ah, Tamaki is such
a strong-willed girl...
On top of that, she's kind,
beautiful and wise.
I can't help but admire her!
I won't marry someone just because my parents want me to, either!
Is that so? Then let's promise
to choose by ourselves!
It's a promise!
Flatly refusing arranged marriages,
looking for a blossoming romance
that will shine for the rest of their lives.
All of this is in the spirit of these new Taishou Era "High Collar Girls."
What are you doing?!
Be quiet already!
So harsh!
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Hey, Tamaki, how about
a bowl of anmitsu?
Sorry, I've got a date today!
Take care!
She's the same age as us, but while we're
eating anmitsu, she's going on dates!
Hey, I saw her in Ginza with a university student the other day!
He seemed like the artist type!
So bold! Especially when people still think boys
and girls should be separated after they turn seven!
My, how that sounds lovely!
I'm sure of it, soon I'll be in love,
just like Tamaki!
What's with her?
Oh, so very lovely!
What's with those looks?
Should be obvious.
These are looks of disdain.
Haven't you noticed the
big difference between you and Tamaki?
What are you saying?
What difference?
Oh, the ignorance!
It's about your beautiful chest.
Itsy-bitsy
Who cares?!
It's not that big of a deal!
My ideals are shapely!
Yeah, it's all about my ideals!
Oh my! The anmitsu
went to her brain!
Must have.
Wh-What was that?
My ideals... are... my ideals...
Well, for instance...
What's wrong?
I think I am tired, after all.
I'm going home.
She wasn't in a very
good mood today.
Maybe we shouldn't have
compared her to Tamaki.
Well, she is flat,
there's no denying tha—
Oh, you're still here?
I forgot this.
How dare they mock me.
It's all been downhill ever since I met that guy.
Sho-Sho-Shojo-ji Gardens...
What are you supposed to be?
Boozy the Kid. Ring a bell?
Honestly. I'm running into
nothing but oddballs today.
It hurts!
That'll teach you for
being such a tomboy!
It hurts...!
Oh, what would I say to your mother if she were here?
I'm at a loss for words!
She says that all the time!
The creepy old no-chin hag.
Hold it, Young Lady!
I even told her today
was an important day...
Ranmaru? Ranmaru!
So pretty!
Even a boy like Ranmaru
can look so pretty...
I must be unattractive after all.
Like she was saying, like how all my friends
make fun of me. Is it my fault for being like this?
Oh, Benio!
Are you busy practicing?
No, don't worry!
Well, that's all for today!
We were only halfway done, sir.
That's enough for me,
I have to play with Benio!
It seems our young teacher
is head over heels for his neighbor.
Also, what's so good about that girl?
I wonder sometimes...
Glare
Run!
A kite?
Kites are cool, but isn't
that kind of a boyish thing?
So what?
You're one, too, aren't you?
Look how high it's getting!
It's way up there!
Benio's still so innocent.
After all these years, she hasn't changed one bit.
Easy does it.
What an unlucky
place to land on, Benio.
Stop, you'll break the thread!
What a mess...
Well, in that case.
Since there's nobody around...
Let's do this...
S-Stop it!
Benio!
Stop what you're doing!
It's fine!
Nobody's going to come here!
It's dangerous!
Oh, quit your worrying!
Alright, now!
Get down!
Once more!
Leaves falling at
this time of year?
That smug guy from earlier!
Well, well, we meet again!
You better not be stopping there!
I could say the
same thing to you!
Shut up!
How hurtful!
I told you to go away!
Oh no!
Good heavens!
Don't look at me!
Benio's gonna die!
What am I going to do with you? Do you high collar types always climb trees?
Th-That's none of your business!
Why does something weird
happen when I meet you?
Y-You want to laugh?
Go ahead, laugh then!
Ranmaru, let's go home!
Hanamura
Oh, Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
I've been expecting you.
Hello, Mr. Hanamura!
So this is where you lived?
W-Why is that guy here?
I didn't know he was Dad's guest...
I assume Benio showed
you the way here.
She's a daughter worthy
of a major like you.
She resembles her late mother,
such unparalleled beauty.
That's the impression I get.
Oh my!
Actually, he's our
neighbor, Ranmaru.
Huh? You're telling
me that's a boy?
That means the other one's...
That chucklehead
Second Lieutenant...
Young Lady!
That's edible seaweed!
The tea leaves are over there!
Here you go.
Well, look at that,
I'm following etiquette after all.
Second Lieutenant, go ahead.
Of course. Thank you.
My lord! Did you really serve them
those mugwort rice sweets, young lady?
Yeah, so what?
They're a week old already!
They're probably all moldy!
Oh, just a minute!
I'm begging you, stop joking around today!
And be a little more careful, too!
Why should I, Father?
Well, that's because...
You'll find out soon enough.
Oh, while you're at it,
why don't you show him the garden?
That's fishy...
Father's probably hiding something.
Huh?
I can't believe he just
got up and left. How rude.
Where has he gone?
Oh, there he is!
He's sleeping so peacefully!
What gives?
Well, then.
Just a little closer...
Don't get too fired up,
it's my turn to laugh at him.
Here I come!
It's cowardly to catch
people off guard!
A true warrior must always be watchful,
even while asleep!
I won't forget this!
You started talking without thinking.
Stand up!
I said stand up!
Now then, let's duel!
What a bother...
That's it! I'm done with
your teasing! Here I go!
Y-You...
That sound...
It couldn't be...
I've got him!
No, stop!
Stop right this instant!
D-Don't you know Second Lieutenant
Ijuuin is going to be your fiancé?!
You're going to get
married to him!
Yes! Marry!
Wh-What did you say?!
There! Ten points!
Are you kidding me?
Him taking ten points off me is too much...
This can't be real!
It's like a nightmare!
And so, our High Collar Lady discovered
she was engaged to Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
What sort of man is this
blond Second Lieutenant?
Thus, a romance in
the Taishou Era began...
The Second Lieutenant's engagement to Benio
was agreed upon three generations ago.
In an age bound by convention,
will she have her own way,
or one laid out for her by her parents?
In a time where life
is too short for love...
And let's not forget Ranmaru...
What will be High Collar
Benio's next move?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Eloping"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it gets so hard to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
when he goes away, I want him to turn around,
to give me a loving glance one more time
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Editing
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing, TLC
QC
darkcart
ImAWasteOfHair
MartyMcflies
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo
TougeWolf