Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Now that they've ascertained
that Shinobu's is Japan's #1 bridegroom,
even Benio's father shed some tears of happiness.
Benio, also brimming with joy,
invited her classmates to the mansion.
However, fate loves irony,
as Shinobu is about to be transferred,
rendering a seemingly heavenly situation hellish.
Lt Col Innen clearly pulled the strings
that led to this devilish intervention in fate.
But the orders are not up for debate.
Still unaware of all of this,
Benio's classmates arrive to celebrate...
That was the last straw for our High Collar Lady,
so she prepares to storm the garrison herself.
Bloodshed seems inevitable today.
Episode 24
I Can't Stand Martinets!
Please wait, Lady Benio.
Don't be so hasty!
She's right.
Stirring things up will only make matters worse.
They're not the kind of people you can reason with!
Dialog is impossible!
Lady Benio!
Let me go!
Wait!
Benio!
What is it, Ranmaru?
I-Is it true that you're storming
the army headquarters?
What does it look like I'm doing?
Don't do it, Benio!
Out of my way!
You're my only allies here, aren't you?
Now, after me!
Benio!
Don't try to stop me!
Shinobu's deployment to Kyushu
is part of one big conspiracy,
I can't possibly let this slide!
Anyone who gets in my way,
be it the Imperial Army or whoever else...
will be chopped in half just like this tree!
What are your worries,
riverside willow?
What are you waiting for... Huh?
What's up with the belligerent outfit, Boss?
Perfect timing.
Ushigorou, I need a ride.
Yessir!
I'm happy to follow my boss through fire and water
and 'til the end of the world!
So, where are we headed?
Imperial Army, first division.
Huh?! W-What did you just say, Boss?
We're mounting an attack
on the 1st Division headquarters.
Ushigorou!
Can you even call yourself a man?!
N-No, it's because I'm a man that I
know exactly why this is dangerous.
B-Boss, I don't know all the details,
but I know damn well
that you don't wanna antagonize the Imperial Army.
Shut up!
We're done.
Our Boss-Henchman alliance is over!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, come.
Boss! Assaulting them on your own
is biting off more than you can chew!
Boss!
Oh, there's no stopping her now!
I gotta do something 'bout it.
And this!
Dear, stopping Benio should be done
with words, not spears!
Silence!
I'm not planning to stop her.
If anything, I'll go back her up!
Not again!
Don't "not again" me!
It's not hard to understand how Benio feels.
I'll stand by Benio's side,
come hell or high water!
Shinobu is my grandson, which makes his bride Benio
my cherished granddaughter too!
Anyone who gets in the way
will meet my spear!
Like this!
What's going on?
What is this?
Get out of my way!
This is serious!
Really serious!
Huh?
Ma'am, the wedding ceremony
is just around the corner.
I can't wait for the day to come!
Hey!
Nanny! Nanny, t-t-this is serious!
Ah... Whenever you come here, it doesn't bode well, so I don't want to listen to you!
How can you say that?
A father and his daughter are about to cross swords!
Huh? Cross swords?
Yes, exactly!
Tell me, Ushi, what is going on?
Gladly. If memory serves me,
Lord Hanamura is in 1st Division, right?
That's true.
What about it?
And that's why I'm saying
that they're about to cross swords!
You see, Boss went to assault
their headquarters!
Huh?!
How come?
Ma'am...
It seems the wedding ceremony
is still a long way off.
Wait, Lady Kichiji!
Hey! This is real bad!
Boss went...
1st Division...
Ushi, please explain things calmly.
Yessir!
Milk bar
The wife sympathizes with her husband,
while the husband yearns for his wife.
Both parties come to each other's rescue.
That's what being a couple means.
Understood? Then keep it in mind.
Sorry to barge in, but...
Ugh!
This disgusting man again!
I can't stand him, I'm going home!
What's with her?
Ah, Tamaki, I was looking for you!
What's the matter, Ushigorou?
Hear me out! Boss is...
Boss is in a pickle big time!
Benio is?
What was that?
Hanamura is up to something again?
Ma'am, call from the 1st Division.
Yes, thank you.
Hello?
Hello, Major Hanamura here.
It is a pleasure to hear from Benio's father.
The Ijuuins are listening.
Oh, you're just who I needed, Countess.
I wanted to make sure Benio didn't do anything silly.
Well, about that...
She might just be about to do something silly.
Wha-Wha-Wh-What did you say?!
For this reason, I wanted Shinobu to intervene,
as he is the only one who can stop her!
Unfortunately, the lieutenant is not here.
Huh? Where is he, then?
Presently, he left for Toyamagahara with his unit
to conduct his last drill as part of the 1st Division.
Dear me! And you can't summon him back?
Please understand,
the Imperial Army waits for no one.
Even if it's just a military exercise,
the expectations are set as high as in a real battle.
One should be prepared
to be sent into battle any moment.
Ready...
Shoot!
Charge!
Keep going! No retreat! Keep going!
So cruel, sending Shinobu to Kyushu...
I sincerely believe that your marriage
will be the one that stands the test of time.
No, I can't just let him go!
I will... I will...
Shinobu!
Where are you going?
Just you wait, Innen.
You'll regret bullying my dear Shinobu!
He can't get away with it!
Yes, we'll deal with him!
Yes, sounds good.
Mission: aid Benio!
We'll show them!
Good! Let's go!
Thank you, everyone!
That's the spirit of classmate camaraderie!
Here we go!
Hey, hold on a spell... Hold on...
A man's left behind by his party.
Let's admit him to our circle now!
Shut up!
Goldfish Ushigorou is the manliest man alive!
Sticks and stones may break my bones, you hear?
Oh, really?
Yay!
Ushigorou, you're amazing!
Our hero!
Seeing you up close,
I'm having second thoughts.
T-Teacher...
May I ask where the five of you
are going all together?
You see, we...
You're going to assault the 1st Division
headquarters, aren't you?
Teacher, please let this slide.
Please!
Not happening.
Teacher, we're begging you!
No, that won't do!
Times like these are when having a good leader is crucial.
And I'm prepared to take that role upon myself.
Huh? You're coming with us?
Yes. The tyranny of the military must be stopped!
The true victims of any war are always women!
We must protest against militarism!
Eternal devotion to motherland
Alright, everybody!
After me! Fight!
Fight! Fight, fight, fight!
Talk about unlikely alliances...
Okay, I'll be going now, Mama.
Sure thing.
Sister, we heard that someone
is stirring things up in the city!
Which gang are we fightin' this time?
The local army garrison.
Huh? Army...
Sis, if that's a joke, it's a rotten one.
This battle is not a joke. In fact,
I am in part responsible for it happening.
So I'll fight them to the death, if necessary.
T-To death?
It's my duty to protect those two's happiness.
Now, with that cleared up,
move out of my way, everyone.
Sister...
I just can't sit back and watch after seeing your determination!
We'll defend whoever's happiness,
even if the world considers us just parasites.
We've never did anything
for the good of the world or others before!
Please allow us this once-in-a-lifetime chance
to be useful to someone!
We'll back you up in any way we can.
We'll back you up!
Then, is that to say
you're entrusting your lives to me?
Certainly, Sister!
Ma'am, once again, this wedding
became the stuff dreams are made of.
It's time for me to go there
and defend Lady Benio to the best of my abilities.
Just for you, I'll be sure to leave a big bump on Innen's forehead.
Enough, just let me go!
Ah!
Dear...
Huh?!
Bring Sublieutenant home
W-Why are you all standing there?
Count!
We'd all like to join your cause.
Before all else,
Benio shares our blood.
We can't just stand here and watch idly
as she risks her life!
But remember—we're going up against
the Empire of Japan itself.
I'm aware of that.
I already went to my wife...
Go there and show them all!
...and had my farewell cup!
And we are on Lady Benio's side because
we also oppose Young Master
being transferred far away!
Bring him home!
Bring the lieutenant home!
Please!
Even if you forbid us,
we'll take matters into our own hands!
Come on, let's go!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
H-Hey, wait!
Are you seriously gonna leave without me?!
I'm the warlord in this house!
Get back! Ah...
Hey, stop!
Hold on, hold on!
Hey, you!
I'm talking to you, can't you hear?
How do you expect me to react to your "Hey, you!"
when I was already in a bad enough mood?
But even putting that aside, I've just about had enough of men who wear sabers!
Hey, easy now, no need to get so worked up.
Actually, I stopped you because of your dogs.
Dogs?
Yes, dogs.
I'm sure you're aware that rabies
has been on the rise lately.
Huh?
You did vaccinate these dogs
against rabies, did you?
If you did, you must have the certificate.
I'd like to see that.
I have no such thing.
Just as I thought.
In that case you must follow me to headquarters now
and get them properly vaccinated!
What?! I've no time for that!
Listen, you, without that vaccine,
they might get rabies at any moment!
It'll be too late to act when that happens.
Prevention is the best medicine!
What about tomorrow?
Folk always promise to get it done tomorrow
and run off, but never actually do it!
Just come with me!
W-W-What are you doing?!
Don't complain!
What's this? Civil disobedience?
Come on, let's go!
Hey, you're not getting away!
Stop!
Let me out! I told you to let me out!
Imperial Army 1st Division HQ
Hey, don't forget about me!
Bring the men out already!
I want a man!
You can come out.
We're done vaccinating your dogs.
You really didn't have to throw me into the cell
for something this trivial!
You could say you got off lightly!
Just look at what you've done to us with your naginata and those dogs!
O-Oh, sorry about that!
Benio sure is taking her time.
You don't suppose she's made a detour
to eat anmitsu or something?
Geez, just as all these people are waiting for her!
Ah! Here she is! Boss!
Where were you, Benio?
That's unfair, Benio!
Young Lady!
Oh my, why did you all gather here today?
Are we on some kind of strike?
Lady Benio, we've all come here to aid you
in your storming of the headquarters.
Huh?! What did you say?
Hanamura, you have the worst grades
among my many students.
That said, your courage in telling off those selfish military men as a frail girl is nothing short of admirable.
On one hand, having a student such as you
has brought me nothing but indescribable grief,
but, on the other hand,
it is also an indescribable honor!
Now, let's storm this joint together!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Teacher, everyone else... Thank you.
You've made me so happy.
All these people came here for me...
But I can't accept it—my opponent is the Imperial Army
and I can't drag anyone down with me.
Up until now, I've only ever acted
out of selfishness.
So please forgive me this one last selfish act!
I can only go there by myself!
Shinobu...
If it's for Shinobu,
I'm prepared to die as well, right?
Shinobu...
Shinobu! I...
Shinobu!
Shinobu...
It's a certain day of a certain month of the year 1918,
and our traditional woman Benio is about to storm a garrison all by herself!
Although this event was never written
in any history book or official document...
But to set the record straight:
our High Collar Lady really did that, all on her own.
I'm going in and confronting Innen face to face!
In the next episode
There goes the High Collar Benio,
forcing her way through worthless guards and demanding the despicable Lt Col Innen to come out.
Perceiving the danger High Collar Lady presents to his life,
Lt Col Innen is desperate and even attempts to flee.
1st Division HQ is in total chaos!
See in the next episode of
Here Comes the High Collar Lady,
"Don't Go, Shinobu!"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan