Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
This is no Shakespeare play,
but to stay or to leave—that is the question
for our High Collar Lady.
Ignorant of how she feels,
Ranmaru and Ushigorou
launched a spirited all-out offensive,
rendering the poor hard-working
head maid Kisaragi down for the count.
But it appears Shinobu had finally unmasked Ranmaru, even if he keeps playing dumb.
Our High Collar Lady struggles to guess
what Shinobu's true intentions are.
It's just one worry after another for her.
Back off! It's my turn this morning!
No way! I'm polishing it today!
It's my duty to look after
Young Master's belongings!
Let go! Young Master chose me to do it!
No, me!
Cut it out!
If you both want to polish them so badly,
why not polish one each?
You're right.
Hey, that could actually work.
Good morning.
Ah, hello!
Hey, take a look at this!
Mine is shinier!
Lies! Mine is sparkling!
No it isn't!
Are you sure you should trust others
to take care of Shinobu's things, Benio?
Hey, Benio, are you listening?
Humph! I'd rather be taking care
of my buddy right here
than of someone like Shinobu!
Right, right, I understand how you feel!
Attagirl!
That sublieutenant doesn't care about me in the slightest...
To hell with him!
Episode 14
Two Bewildered Flowers
L-L-Lady Benio!
Ah, p-please don't worry!
I'll reassemble it at once.
Let's see, this looks like a foot, I think...
Lady Benio! Forget about this junk and show at least some solicitude for Young Master!
Humph! Who cares about him...
Lady Benio!
It's fine, it's fine.
Then, I'll do it myself.
Young Master, here you are.
Oh? How pretty.
Your pads also didn't flee to your back today. Nicely done.
I remember and appreciate
your samurai-like lenience.
Oh...
Oh, where are my gloves?
My, what negligence!
Someone, hurry up and bring them here!
Yes, ma'am!
Ah, wait.
Lady Benio!
Finally done!
Huh? Oh, did you say something?
It's your job!
Bring Young Master's gloves here at once!
All right. What's the big deal
with just bringing the gloves?
Let's see. Ah, here they are.
Actually! I wonder how he'd react
if I gave him two right-hand ones!
Yes, let's give it a whirl!
She is rather late.
Why is it taking so long?
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Here.
Yeah, thanks.
Huh?
Later.
Please return soon, Young Master!
How boring. He didn't even
try them on before leaving.
What is this about?
I felt like playing a prank on Shinobu, so I gave him two right-hand gloves! Look, here are the left ones.
Brilliant as usual!
Boss! With a little luck, that might embarrass him big time!
How?
If I recall correctly, Shinobu is supposed to be a standard-bearer.
Now that I think about it,
my father once mentioned that too.
Hey, what's a standard-bearer?
Attention!
Salute His Majesty the Emperor.
At ease.
He's the one holding the flag!
Soldiers!
Yessir!
Prepare!
In the regiment, only the most accomplished young officers can become standard-bearers.
But to be one, you need to wear your white gloves at all times!
So if someone like that forgets his gloves...
Yes! Exactly what you think of!
You fool!
His district commander will have him for breakfast!
And since your father is Shinobu's direct superior,
he's also getting the shaft for sure!
Huh? It's that big of a deal?
Can't be any other way around!
Yahoo!
Now Benio is getting the boot for sure!
That's it!
Banzai!
Hip hip, hooray!
What am I gonna do?
Shinobu, that's not what I had in mind.
Sorry, Shinobu!
I'm sorry, okay?
Boss, what's wrong?
You've been sighing so gloomily all day!
Ah... It's nothing.
Your glove mischief should've taken effect by now.
With this, you'll be able to bid your farewell to that mansion, Boss!
Why did you stop all of a sudden?
Look what we got...
What do those three want?
Hey hey hey!
This is a public road,
so why don'tcha get out of our way?
Don'tcha yell at me!
You're that lady who's engaged to sublieutenant Ijuuin, right?
We are...
the most influential gang
in the whole Kanto district!
Say our name out loud,
Lilac Band!
Lilac Band...
W-We're so sorry...
Ah! Stop, stop! Ushigorou, stop!
Ushigorou, stop!
Oh, so then you guys must be
the part of the Lilac Theater Troupe!
Right, our beloved troupe!
Pam-pa-bam...
When the lilacs...
When the lilacs
bloom again,
Bringing back the thrill...
Idiots! You think it's time to be singing our theme song?!
Sorry.
How funny!
Stop laughing!
I have nothing personal against you two,
but I gotta make a living somehow.
Like it or not, we'll have to hurt you a bit.
Huh?! What do you mean by that?!
No arguing! Get off!
B-Boss...
I see. So you want to fight me?
Looks to me like you ain't deaf.
Ushigorou.
Well, I did get off, so I'm no longer responsible
for whatever happens to you next.
Fight with your fists,
not your mouth, you brat!
Bitch!
B-Boss, don't underestimate them.
These guys rule the streets down here!
So what of it?
Provoking me today was a bad idea,
so I'll use them to let off some steam.
Fine! I'll be facing you!
Get!
Ushigorou!
Remember that it was you who started all of this!
What? Ya gon' teach me?!
Die!
Ouch...
Way to go!
Come! I don't have all day!
This wench! I went easy on her 'cause she's a woman!
Time to get serious!
Bitch!
You're not getting away with it!
B-B-Boss!
I'll be fine, Ushigorou.
I don't really know why,
but I've not been this excited in a long time!
Rot in...
hell!
Head!
You little...
Belly!
Why, you...
Butt!
Let's dance!
You're done!
Boss!
Ta-dan!
Finally.
Straight to hell.
Hey, say your prayers!
You think I'll let yakuza scum like you
get the best of me?
Shaddup!
Die!
Stop!
Sister Kichiji...
What is wrong with you,
going three against one?
But we were concerned about you...
Don't do things I haven't asked for!
I don't remember ever hiring you for this!
Yes, but...
Silence!
Begone at once!
Wow. She's pretty.
And also so strong-willed!
Boss, are you okay?
I apologize, milady,
these thugs keep troubling my acquaintances.
Oh, it's nothing.
I am a geisha from Yanagibashi,
Kichiji of the "House of Flowers."
Huh?! So you are the Sister Kichiji?
Yes.
I take it you are Hanamura Benio?
Y-Yes...
I see.
As I thought...
Ah... How do you know me, though?
You see, I happen to be in love...
To be in love?
With Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
Of course, it's purely one-sided.
But now it's clear to me that I stand no chance of getting his attention.
Not if you are his fiancée.
Oh, it's not like that. A-Actually,
we aren't officially married yet...
Besides, Shinobu is not really interested in me...
What are you talking about?
It is plain to the eye
that you have the upper hand.
Compared to you, what am I?
A geisha cannot dare to dream about ever being with a nobleman.
However, I did start to think about breaking off his engagement, if only I get a chance.
That is, until I unexpectedly met you today.
Young Lady.
Take good care of Sublieutenant!
Ms. Kichiji!
Ugh, that shameless womanizer!
Shinobu had also been fooling around with that geisha behind my back!
Unforgivable! Un-bloody-forgivable!
B-Boss!
That hypocrite!
A single sneeze...
I hope it's not a cold.
Lord Ijuuin!
You've come so suddenly... I don't suppose
it's because something happened to Lady Benio?
Well, I'd be lying if I said
that nothing at all happened to her.
Oh, this is unbearable. To think that she would lose her chance for such a great engagement!
I won't forgive him.
I won't forgive him!
Not in a thousand years!
Oh!
Welcome home.
Benio, what's wrong?
Ranmaru, today's the day.
Help me pack my things.
I've already done that in foresight.
Huh? Are you a clairvoyant?
With you, even the telepathy
is not impossible for me.
Alas, I was just kidding.
Anyways, I'll get your things now.
Ah, hold on!
What is that pile?
Ah, this?
Can't you tell? It's today's share of love letters for Shinobu.
Ugh...
It's like this every day!
I've never seen such a playboy before!
Author, seriously?!
Even you...
Dear Shinobu
I'm head over heels for you~
♥Waki
I'm not staying here for a second longer!
Ugh... He's late, isn't he?
Okay, we can go now.
Ah, wait a second.
I wanted to tell Shinobu
just one thing before we leave.
Huh? You still can't let go of a man like him?
Not that. I just wanted to give him
a piece of my mind.
Fine. A piece it is, then.
Hey, I'm back.
Shinobu!
Did you get into trouble because of the gloves?
Are you hearing what I'm hearing?
I mean, that was very inconsiderate of me.
I didn't embarrass you before your unit, did I?
Ah... We actually just laughed it off.
Yeah, it turns out
the world is full of scatterbrains,
so another officer happened to bring two left-handed gloves today.
I exchanged my right glove with his left one,
and we both made it through alright.
Thank god!
Lady Benio!
Shinobu!
Moreover,
can you guess who this officer
with two left-hand gloves actually was?
None other than your father!
Which was probably a slip-up on your Nanny's part,
because her mind was preoccupied.
Nanny's?
Yes.
Ever since you left, your Nanny must've been feeling lonely, and that was slowly consuming her.
That's how she made that slip-up.
Nanny...
So,
on my way back, I stopped by at your house to comfort your Nanny for a bit.
Your self-aggrandizement...
I-I-I'm not falling for it!
I know all about his womanizing exploits!
Ah, by the way,
Nanny asked me to give something to you two.
Here, this is for you, Ranmaru-not, Ranko.
That's quite a lot.
Are those all love letters?
You've gotta be joking.
It's just the fan mail.
I never answer to any of these,
but they still keep writing them.
This is getting bothersome.
I feel you, every day is like that for me.
I have no idea who's sending them,
it's all one-sided.
What? One-sided?
Hm! He's so pretentious!
And these are for Benio,
one from Nanny.
To Benio
from Saburou
To
Young
Mistress
Ah, it's from Sabu and Hiroshi.
Who are they?
Two kids in my neighborhood.
I see.
Ah, I didn't expect a letter from them.
Dear Benio, let's climb trees
together again sometime!
Climbing trees?
What did Hiroshi write?
"Benio, when are you coming back?"
I can't wait to climb a tree!
I'll never forget the trees we climbed together.
- Hiroshi.
What is this?
He only cares about climbing trees!
The letters for me are completely down to earth.
Fan mail is stupid!
To hell with these!
No need to turn away when laughing!
Oh, my bad.
Are you gonna keep on laughing forever?
I already know your true colors, and about your affair with Ms. Kichiji from the House of Flowers!
Y-You've met her?
Your expression changed!
You're...
wrong on her account, Benio.
Please, don't misunderstand this.
Spare me your lame excuses.
I hate people like you
who play with women's feelings.
I-I-I hate you...
Out!
Get out!
Both of you!
B-Benio!
Out, out!
What should I do?
After all,
I'm just a nominal fiancée,
shanghaied into a loveless marriage.
This is too much to bear!
Being made into a figurehead wife
who resigned to her husband's adultery
without hope of ever getting a divorce,
working herself to the bone just to quietly
perish in the most miserable way—
For some reason,
children are the only thing
we have a lot of
such is the sad fate of womankind.
Yes, I've decided!
Down with this house!
Oh?
To Young Mistress
A letter from Nanny?
Young Mistress, how are you?
As for myself, I am living peacefully, all alone with your father.
He has never expressed any anxiety about you.
I understand how you might be feeling,
but please never consider returning home.
Actually, I have never had the wish
to see you again either.
So I beg you not to come back home,
no matter what happens.
Never, never come back home, please.
Nanny...
In our world, things always have two sides to them.
You should still try to loosen the knots on the tangled thread of a heart that's been smashed to pieces.
And if you succeed, it'll bloom again...
But with which flower?
During the airing of old family possessions,
something slips from Ranmaru's hand and breaks,
and, oh goodness, it was a precious plate!
The Count obviously snaps out and draws his katana.
Thus, to give the remaining nine plates the same fate,
Benio decides to break all of them! Big trouble!
Next time on "Here Comes the High Collar Lady":
So Long, Old-Fashioned Mansion! Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Minty
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Minty
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Minty