Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The more Benio read the first letter she'd gotten from Shinobu, the more her feelings overflowed.
Ah, how sweet, yet sorrowful.
But just when she sat down and tried responding to it,
she ended up falling into the arms of Morpheus.
Meanwhile, Shinobu once again fell victim to Innen's plotting
and found himself in a platoon full of rogues,
who waste no time in starting a fight.
The garrison commander
soon realizes what's happening,
and immediately confronts Shinobu
to know the cause.
If Shinobu says the truth, he'll be safe, while Onijima will be punished.
What is he going to do in this Siberian do-or-die situation?
Episode 28
A Battle for Men, a Battle for Women
Hey! Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
I want to know what the cause of the brawl was!
Answer me!
What you saw was not a brawl, Major.
We wanted to be ready for upcoming battles, so we decided to practice.
H-He's lying...
Yeah, things are going differently
from what I'd expected.
Since we're always here,
we've long been itching for some action.
I see, training for real combat, then?
Yessir.
So it wasn't a brawl?
Absolutely not.
Alright. If you guys are craving action that much,
then I'll grant your wish.
Your unit is getting transferred to the front line in the nearest future!
Front line?!
Front line?
You'd better be ready to get moving! Understood?
To the front line...?
Seems like it.
I'm sorry this is what it came to.
You don't have to worry.
What?
Everyone! We'll follow Second Lieutenant to the depths of Hell or wherever else he goes, am I right?
Yeah!
Guys...
Platoon commander!
We're to blame for getting the wrong idea about you.
When we heard that a Tokyo officer would take the lead here, we thought we were being made fun of.
However, because I spoke too much, I ended up sending us all to the front line.
So what? Besides, it's true that we're itching to get some action.
I, the unworthy Sergeant Onijima, will always be by your side!
We're with you, commander!
You won't be alone!
Yeah, I'm not backing off either!
We'll follow you anywhere!
Guys... Everyone got themselves a drink?
Commander!
C'mon. You need to get wasted too. Wasted!
This sure feels good!
Let's celebrate the eve of our departure!
Now we'll finally get to show the world what outcast rogues like us are capable of!
Yeah, he's right!
Oh, well. Wherever I go, I end up getting entangled with heavy drinkers, be it Benio or this platoon.
Besides, that fight we had today...
Whichever way you look at it,
it was Benio's style.
I'm going to the front line tomorrow...
But I'll come home safe and sound.
Benio, I'll always find my way back to you.
Here you go.
Let us have a sip.
It was truly delicious.
Mhm...
It's bitter!
I've had enough of this...
You don't have to force yourself, Benio.
Oh no, this is still nothing.
Since Shinobu is out there fighting on the battlefield, behaving like a proper wife is the least I can do.
And, in the meantime, I'll become so beautiful that he won't believe his eyes when he sees me again.
I'll have turned so ladylike by the time he returns home safely!
Kitsch!
I'll become more and more ladylike!
Oh no! I've once again beheaded a flower!
Ah... She'll never learn, it's hopeless.
W-W-What happened here?
What?
You can't breathe because of your face mask?
I must be ladylike... Ladylike...
In 1918, young noble girls used to learn
nursery rhymes such as "The Canary's Song" and "The Drummer Raccoons' Song".
The canary forgot its songs!!
What was this noise?
It broke the windows!
W-What was that just now?
Huh? Just a children's song?
So it wasn't a cat getting strangled to death?
Ugh!
But man, Benio sure has changed so much lately.
I wonder where her old self has gone.
This is all for love...
It's for Shinobu...
S-So now you're that
head over heels for him?!
No, never! I just can't accept this!
Ah! Keep your cool, Ranmaru!
She leaves me no choice but to lead an okama's life!
W-What should I do, Ushi?
If that happens, I'll poke my eyes too.
Huh?
A ball?
We've just received an invitation,
so you might as well go entertain yourself.
We all need a change of pace every once in a while.
A ball?
A letter of invitation
Yes, we want you to have more experiences,
and get to know all about the world of the nobles
while you wait for Shinobu to come back.
Precisely. This will be your classy debut to the high society. I'll accompany you there.
Yes, that makes sense.
The weather is looking to be just right.
Playing ball sounds like a wonderful idea.
Huh?
It's been a while since I last played ball.
She's hopeless...
Oh, my, this looks so good on you!
Benio,
back in the day, this was my go-to choice when I had to dress up.
Benio, are you ready?
Yes, Count. Shall we go out?
Ah! Oh! Ow-ow-ow-ow!
I hope we'll be alright...
Don't worry, don't worry!
We're now headed to the ballroom!
Hip hip hooray!
I can't help but wonder whether Benio will do fine.
Go ahead.
Right, thanks.
Hey, Ushi.
I'm worried about those two
going out on their own.
I'm a bit worried too.
I can get you there if you wanna follow.
Well, well, now let's see what I can come up with.
We're setting off! Now floor it!
Today, all the soldiers of the Ijuuin platoon are being deployed to the front line.
Soldiers, attention!
To your left!
March forward!
I feel sorry for them -
they're going to the battlefield.
I wonder if any of them will survive.
Whatever. It's a motley crew of scoundrels.
Nobody's gonna miss them
even if they all get wiped out!
Hello, is it Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen?
Yes, it's me.
Well, as per your request, Second Lieutenant Ijuuin's unit has just departed for the front line.
Oh, really? Good to hear.
Are you satisfied now, Lieutenant Colonel​?
Just to be sure, you sent them to the Siberian front line, right?
It's not just the front line, it's straight up Hell out there.
No one's ever made it out alive.
Splendid. Splendid. Just splendid!
Oh? They're dancing already.
So chic!
We've arrived.
You're on your own now, okay, Ranmaru?
Leave it to me, Ushi.
Noble gatherings are my forte!
I'm sure that back in the Meiji era
it was even more lively.
Am I right, Count?
These dances look pretty different from the loach-catching ones.
E-Excuse me, count.
So what you're saying is that
this is your first ever ball?
'Course it is!
Called it!
I forced myself to wear a dress like this in order to appear more ladylike...
but it is a pain to walk in it!
Whoa! Ah... B-B-Benio!
Your legs! Your legs are bare!
Come on, you just need to bear with it.
Shinobu... I'll be doing my best
until the day you come back!
Everyone, stop!
Hey, is everybody here?
Is everybody here?
First squad: no one missing!
Second squad: everybody's here!
Third squad... Oh!
We're missing one!
Private Kobayashi isn't here!
Huh? Kobayashi?
Sergeant Onijima,
take command of the platoon.
Kobayashi! Private Kobayashi!
Kobayashi, where are you?!
Private Kobayashi!
That's Kobayashi!
Hey! Hang in there! Hey!
There, please stay strong!
C-Commander, please leave without me.
If you're exhausted and alone here,
you'll be dead in no time!
I cannot walk any further!
What's wrong?
I've had a fever for two days already...
Why didn't you tell me? I would've let you stay in the hospital!
I could never stand still when all my buddies are out there facing death!
You've got a family waiting for you back home, haven't you?
Not quite. I've always been an orphan. There's no one waiting for me.
There has to be someone, at least one person.
Now that I think about it,
back when I was in reform school,
there was a teacher who was really kind to me.
Don't you want to meet him again?
Well, I...
Hey! I can guarantee you that he's waiting for your safe return to Japan!
It's for him that you have to stay strong!
R-Roger!
Stand up!
There. There, let's get up.
Hang in there!
Now, hop on the horse.
There!
And up!
Onijima...!
Kobayashi's my friend, after all.
I just couldn't stand still.
Onijima!
Didn't I tell you to take command in my stead!
I don't remember acknowledging
that command, though.
Commander, it's unsafe to stay
in a place like this!
Onijima, hop on the horse and take Kobayashi to safety. Quick!
I don't think I'll do it.
Hey! This is an order from your superior!
Doesn't matter who's the superior out here.
It's unfair that only one gets
to ride in the saddle.
Wouldn't you agree, commander?
Alright, you tell me then—what’s your draw method of choice?
With these.
Fine! Let's use them to decide.
Come on, roll them!
I'll go with odds!
Fine, I bet on the opposite.
Okay, ready now?
Yes.
Hey, this is odd, right? Or is it even?
Tsk, would you look at that!
Man, it sure feels bad to lose to a beginner who doesn't even know the difference between odd and even.
And... up!
See you.
Go!
Commander, don't become the wolves' dinner!
Now then, to decide my own fate...
Should I go with even or odd?
Oh my, it's you, Benio!
Wow, Tamaki!
How in the world did you
end up in a place like this?
It's part of my diverse training program.
Training?
Now I see. It's something you're going to do until Shinobu returns.
However, you really shouldn't have come here.
Everyone in here is staring at you with contempt.
Contempt? Huh, why? What'd I do?
You know what you did, Benio.
Shinobu was the idol of this high society.
Among both young and adult noble women,
there isn't anyone who hasn't fallen for him.
In other words, there's no shortage of women
who would've loved to marry him.
Really? I see...
Also, you must know that they aren't as noble when it comes to words.
I hope you'll be able to endure that pressure.
Oh my, would you take a look at who
the missy Tamaki is talking to, madame?
Pathetic! It looks like she chose an antiquated dress for tonight.
You never know,
she must be but a country bumpkin.
Oh my! Look, that's her.
The girl that came with Count Ijuuin!
Huh? Shinobu's betrothed?
So that girl is his fiancée?
I would've expected her to be astoundingly beautiful in order to match Shinobu.
I'm so jealous, I'm way prettier than her!
Our dear lady-killer Shinobu sure has a fancy taste in women, doesn't he?
Well, that’s fine too. How should we punish her for getting ahead of us and stealing our Shinobu?
Let's walk up to her!
Everyone, let's give her a warm welcome!
Ugh, I see it now,
everyone is staring at me.
Well, if it isn't Count Ijuuin! What a truly rare sight.
Oh no, I just wanted to introduce my granddaughter to the high class tonight.
Well, what do you know,
we were talking about her just now.
We couldn't help but notice
what a gorgeous and refined lady she is.
You sure have guts, I heard everything you said about me!
Would you like a drink?
Yes, thank you.
Wow, this juice is so delicious!
What about you?
Here.
Thank you.
Huh? Isn't this champagne?
You're right.
This is bad!
Even if it's a refined alcohol...
Benio will go into a frenzy!
This is just juice, so I can drink however much I want, right? Hic!
Ah, B-Benio, that's not...
Just at the right time, Ranko.
Y-Yes?
Go get me something to drink.
Yes, right after I...
Right now!
O-Okay...
Oh, darn, I've lost sight of my platoon.
Who goes there?!
It's just me, Second Lieutenant.
Oh, so it's you, Onijima.
I got Kobayashi to safety. Now, get on.
Oh, thank you.
I thought you ended up in a wolf's belly.
Why would I?
Even dogs wouldn't want to eat me.
You can have your precious dices back.
Second Lieutenant, I'd like you to keep them.
They'll bring you good luck.
Having them saves you from illness and misfortune.
If they have such capabilities, you should be the one keeping them.
Keep them, Second Lieutenant.
Not a chance! You take them back.
I told you I'll follow you
to the bitter end, remember?
Second Lieutenant, we've got company.
Yeah. So we're surrounded...
Albeit unknowingly,
Benio broke her oath of abstinence!
Might this attract the gods' fury and bring calamity on Shinobu?
What will you do now, High Collar Lady?
The night takes hold for both of you.
Next episode preview
Shinobu and Onijima are surrounded by a large enemy force.
Could this have been caused by Benio, who broke her oath?
In the hostile land of Siberia, what fate will Shinobu face?
Meanwhile, Benio is doing Benio things
and her wild drunken side
brings chaos to the ballroom!
Next on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
In the Thick of the Siberian Battle.
Don't miss it!
Episode 29
In the Thick of the Siberian Battle
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon