Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The time has come for our
Romantic Era High Collar Lady to leave the nest,
as her fate takes a new, unexpected turn.
She indeed has to learn the ways of marriage,
as required by etiquette,
and now nobody can stop her,
but now she'll have to face a warrior in the flesh...
If this is just a dream, it's definitely a bad one!
What do you want?
Hey, you!
Are you the shogunal vassal's daughter?!
What's this...
Don't stall, answer!
Oh, I got it, I got it.
What did you get?
This is the pomp coming with a festival!
Or maybe it's for the promotion of a new doll.
You insolent!
Does this seem like a decoration to you?
It hurts just to look at...
You're the shogunal vassal's daughter, aren't you?
You're an enemy of the emperor!
An enemy??
Are we going back to the days
of Meiji Restoration now?
This feels pretty anachronistic.
Even if you're a woman, I won't hold back!
Get ready!
You butcher!
Episode 7
Count, forgive me!
Hey, calm down, come on!
Please, relax! I am a good guy too!
Help me!!
You butcher!
Huh? Is this Boss calling out for help?
There's no time to wait!
Go-go-go-go!
Make way, make way!
Cut it out!
I told you to calm down, you damn...!
Don't you dare run away!
I am going to skewer you!
Stop running away!
Are you kidding me?
What else am I supposed to do?
I got you!
Wait!
Oh, Darling,
I'm not sure if I trust this strict count.
Benio is now being taught to be ladylike,
but I wouldn't expect her to be very dedicated.
Yahoo!
Hop!
Here we go!
Wait!
What's wrong with this house?
Sure, my goal was to raise hell and get kicked out.
But this is too much!
Take this!
Wait!
If only I had a katana,
he wouldn't stand a chance!
If only I had a katana... Katana, katana...
There's one!
Even if it's just this, I'll cut the work!
Stay still!
It won't move!
En garde!
If that hits me by chance...
Say your prayers!
No! I'll end up murdered!
Boss!
Milord!
Did someone say "Milord" right now?
Yeah, now that you mention it...
Hmm, could she be referring to this mansion's landlord?
Boss, I doubt so.
Nowadays, only princes,
counts and barons get called that way,
but I don't suppose this is the case.
It's likely that there could be a count.
Really?
In that case, could it be...
As mad as it sounds, this stuffed samurai doll is...
Yes,
he is Count Ijuuin.
And I am Shinobu's grandmother.
I'm pleased to meet you, Benio.
So, you're saying...
that this guy is a count?
Milord, I'm so sorry.
T-That girl is out of her mind, treating me like that!
To be fair, it was your own doing,
what in the world were you trying to do,
dressed like that?
Enough! Just shut up!
In any case, I'll never allow a marriage
with the daughter of a shogunal vassal!
Understood!?
I'm done here.
I'm sorry,
I had no clue that he is a count...
I'm sorry too,
he is a genuinely good man,
but he's a little headstrong.
"A little headtsrong" is quite the understatement.
Anyways, you didn't get injured, right?
Hey-hey-hey, that's enough! Shut up and listen,
won't you!?
I don't care if he's a prince or a count,
he was still trying to murder one of his guests!
Oh,
about that...
Remember this!
If anything ever happens to Boss Benio,
I'll show you what this goldfish tattoo truly means!
So crude!
Whadja say!?
What on earth are you saying to ma'am?
You are just an oaf!
Ouch!
Moreover, why are you making such a racket
with your rickshaw over here?!
Get out of our sight right now!
I'm beat...
Thanks for coming here, Benio.
Yeah...
It's not going well.
You truly resemble your grandfather, Benio!
Your thick eyebrows,
your stiff lips,
all of your masculine features.
Masculine features?
This stings!
At last, my long-time love...
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually turn into one again...
...will be finally fulfilled, thanks to you.
My happiness...
My first love...
Shinobu...
Will the day we marry ever come?
Impossible!
He'll marry me!
Phew...
Help!!
No! Ah! Not like that!
Help me, please!
Leave me alone!
Boss! Boss!
Boss, I'm afraid of dogs!
Calm down, please!
Ushigorou isn't a bad person.
Is it so hard to understand?!
Good boys, you can listen to me.
Just like you are protecting the people who live here,
Ushigorou is trying his best to protect me.
It looks like they've got it.
Thank you.
They have never been affectionate to strangers!
She'll be a big thorn in the flesh!
Right, this is surely a strange feat.
Oh?
Young Master!
Something incredible just happened:
Benio tamed Tenmaru and Chimaru with no trouble!
Just what I'd expect from Benio.
Benio, welcome!
Get along with her, you two.
It looks like dogs are way smarter
than people here, am I right?
There, there...
Hey!
Tenmaru, Chimaru,
Look after Boss Benio while I'm not here!
I got it, I'll go away at once, don't worry!
Boss, take care!
Benio, who is that man?
Oh, Ushigorou? He's my hen-
Aaah! No way!
What did you say?
Sorry. He is my-
He is Lady Benio's devoted manservant.
Really? I'm sure I heard him say "Boss".
Well, to make it short,
in Benio's family they use
this word instead of the usual "Sir," grandmother.
Oh, I see.
You're finally here.
Hello.
Honestly, knowing you, I didn't expect your coming.
On top of it...
This get-up!
There he goes again snickering.
Also, I bet you've already caused some mischief,
I regret I wasn't there watching.
Unfortunately, I am not an Asakusa spectacle!
I'm pleased to see that you two are already
in such a playful mood!
Ah, it's not what you think!
Come on, don't be bashful.
Shinobu, do not add to it.
Yes, Grandmother.
Oh?
That guy is such a grandmother's good boy...
Must be because she brought him up.
It's good that he respects elders,
but I hope he's independent too.
Benio, Ms. Kisaragi is going to assist you
all the way through.
Leave her to me, ma'am.
Since the count is from Kagoshima,
we follow those traditions,
I know that it's difficult, but please get used to them.
I'm going to teach her,
with great attention until the wedding day!
Blood curdling!
Shinobu, please show Lady Benio her room.
Sure.
Uhm,
so your grandfather is from Kagoshima?
Yeah, you've already met him, right?
Yes, that old-fashioned madman.
Deep down, he's not a bad person,
he's just a little stubborn and proud.
Take this!
He's way too harsh!
I could've died in a matter of minutes!
No, it's that...
...he just wanted to intimidate you a little.
Why does he resent me?
He doesn't seem to like
that your ancestors were shogunal vassals.
During the Meiji Restoration,
they and the Satsuma Domain fought to the bitter end,
even though they were both Japanese...
That happened moons ago,
it's inappropriate to fuss over it now!
Ah, please calm down, I apologize.
I admit that even I didn't behave properly at all, still...
I can picture this!
Hey you, just stop laughing!
My apologies.
So, to sum it up, after your grandmother
bade farewell to my grandfather,
she met and married your grandfather,
who was a samurai from Satsuma.
That's right,
after that,
since they had a son and your grandparents too,
their promise fell on grandchildren.
So we are the chosen ones...
More or less, but don't mind about it now.
Benio?
Ushi...
Hey, Ushi!
Where's Benio?
Don't you understand?
She's now on the Ijuuin family's bucket.
Hey, don't jump to conclusions yet!
They are still not officially married yet!
Well, kind of.
Ushi, why are you so battered?
Two enormous lupine dogs attacked me.
What about Benio? She didn't get injured, right?
It ended in a blink of an eye.
So Benio...
No, the dogs.
The dogs?
That's right, even though they shredded my clothes,
the moment they saw Boss,
they became docile in no time!
At this rate,
even the Ijuuins could become
as affectionate to her very soon.
No, no, that can't be!
Benio went there to try to break her betrothal!
Well, I'm doubtful about the viability of this plan,
destiny could be already written.
Well, it's here.
Beautiful... It's just like a foreign princess's room.
And he's like a prince...
Hey, what's that I'm thinking, all of a sudden?
There's also a great panorama from here.
I'm sure you'll like it.
You must be tired, so I'll take leave.
It truly is a marvelous room!
I hate both Shinbou and this house, though!
I only like my new room!
Lady Benio.
Uh...
Dinner is ready.
Please dress up.
Do I need to get changed only to eat?
These are our mores, so follow them and dress up!
Stop it!
What?
Stop, let me go!
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Hurry up and get dressed!
I don't- want to- just- let me- go-!
It was tough, but we made it with style.
It was just because you forced me!
At any rate,
I'm starving now, I'd love a good dinner.
Alright, I'll eat all of it
and lick the leftovers!
Western style? I don't know these manners!
I don't know these manners...
Wherever our High Collar Lady goes,
it turns into a symphony of laughter and romance,
but don't give up,
destiny has many things in store!
Our High Collar Lady, not knowing western manners
is catapulted into a clanking table.
Despite being on the verge of tears,
the kind Shinobu gave her a glimpse of a sweet dream,
incessantly disrupted by her table mates!
What is Benio going to do?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
I won't weep 'til I win! Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Ziusudra
Perevodildo