Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The Colonel may very well
be the devil incarnate,
as he deliberately let Benio
take the hostage’s place,
without ever intending to pay the ransom.
But don't underestimate our High Collar Lady,
as she managed to break herself out.
However...
she still ended up getting caught
by the bandit leader and is now in dire straits!
No! Don't do it!
Shinobu, help me!
The moment she shouted
the late Lieutenant's name,
the bandit leader unexpectedly
revealed himself as Sergeant Onijima.
Benio is desperate to get some answers out of him,
but the grief-stricken Onijima
couldn't bring himself to tell her.
Hey... Why won't you tell me anything?
Does this mean Shinobu really died?
I wasn't there for him...
I just left him there,
all alone in that blizzard.
As we were running, a shell landed right next to me.
My leg got hit and I couldn't keep going.
He was the only one
who came back for me.
Hours later I was still
going through the area, looking for him.
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
Commander!
Eventually, I crossed the border into China.
I deserted.
I just couldn't fight for an army
that abandoned such a decent man to his fate.
That was when I ran into the mounted bandits.
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
Episode 39
The Everflowing Song
of Mounted Bandits
It was all my fault!
I couldn't return the favor!
I'm sorry, Benio.
No, this happened because
I foolishly provoked Innen.
It's my fault that Shinobu
was sent to certain death!
Innen? You mean the officer who's running the outpost in the village?
Yes...
I see. Killing the lieutenant
wasn't enough for him,
he also betrayed you—
he never intended on paying that ransom!
We'll show him how small the world really is!
Listen up, men!
We're attacking the village at dawn!
Yeah!
Roll out!
Wait, Onijima!
I'm coming too!
Let's go!
What a truly fortuitous day!
Oh, that's right!
Did you call, Sir?
Urgent orders.
Get everyone into battle position right now!
Yessir!
But Sir, who are we fighting?
Don't you understand?
You think those mounted bandits
will just sit around
twiddling their thumbs
after getting no ransom, huh?!
When the bandits are angry,
they always attack the village in retaliation!
Then plant an ambush there
and wipe them all out for good!
Go!
Emergency call-up!
Emergency call-up! Emergency call-up!
All personnel in battle formation!
Hey, soldiers!
Hey!
What do you want?
What's all this fuss 'bout?
Y'all suddenly started rushing all over the place.
We're going to ambush the mounted bandits.
We'll set a trap.
Hey, hold it!
I couldn't care less 'bout the bandits, but what'll become of my boss, who they're holding hostage?
Why would I know?!
Come on...
Hey, what'll become of Boss?!
Tsk. Drat. That scumbag Innen
is surely plotting something again.
I guess it falls to me
to negotiate with the bandits.
Alright!
Ushigorou the Goldfish, who is scarier than any demon, is getting outta here!
Peace in the world
The bandits won't stand a chance.
With this, I'll gain another medal
and my promotion will be even nearer!
Whoops, a true warrior
must take care of himself.
Good. With this, my beautiful curls are preserved.
I need to be attentive to my beauty. Yessir.
The dangers of the battlefield are for the soldiers to handle.
As they say, a wise man stays away from risks.
Good night to me.
Stop!
What's wrong?
It's strangely quiet. Way too quiet.
Evening to you, sirs...
Yes?
Huh?! J-Just who are you?
Please allow me to introduce myself!
Right! A great honor!
Thank you very much for your kind attention.
I am a humble man from Kanto.
You probably know where it is.
No, no, no! Go home at once!
Don’t you know what they say—
“Vast is the Kanto Region?”
I come from Musashi Province
where the Sumida River flows,
you must’ve heard of me—
Ushigorou the Goldfish!
Huh?! It's Ushigorou!
Eep!
As it happens, I am also the henchman
of the highly renowned High Collar family.
Ushigorou! Get out of the way!
Move, you hear?! Get out!
Yes, I am that Ushigorou the Goldfish.
A pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Goodbye!
Over here! Over here!
"Over here?"
Oh! Boss!
H-Hey! Hold it!
Hey! Boss! I'm here, I'm here, Boss! Piss off!
Hey! Hold him back!
This actor is clearly off his rocker!
Whoa!
Whaddya want from me?!
Here, a gift for y'all!
P-Put that down!
Please put that down!
What are ya weeping 'bout?
Such a weakling! Take this!
Y-Y-You bastard!
I've had enough of you!
Get down now!
Alright! Try and shoot me if ya want, you fool!
Do ya at least know where it comes from?
W-Why should I know that?
Well, how can I put this, basically, "fool"
was originally a medical condition,
like when you're hit on the head
so that's what's gonna happen to y'all!
I've heard enough of this mumbo jumbo,
just come down already!
Ouch!
Who the hell are you?
Ushigorou!
Oh, Boss! You're safe!
I'm so happy you're well!
I'm happy to see you too, Ushigorou!
Man, it looks like even bandits
have diverse taste when it comes to girls!
So you want to die after all?!
That felt good...
Hey, Ushigorou or whatever it was,
what were these guys doing out here anyway?
Security is way tighter than usual.
Yeah, well, you see...
Innen sent them here to set a trap and kill all the mounted bandits.
Sheesh, he always plays so dirty!
We'll pay him back handsomely for this!
It seems I forgot to close the window.
Wh-Who's there?!
Y-You there, r-reveal yourself!
Hello there, I am here to inform you
that it is currently 4 AM.
This is when the earthly world
and the afterlife converge.
It’s a time like no other.
I came for vengeance...
Oh poor me, I was murdered in cold blood by bandits and now I haunt this place...
Begone... Begone, whatever you are!
Oh, you shouldn't be talking like that...
Shoo! Shoo! Begone! Begone!
Oh my, why so inhospitable?
Begone once and for all!
S-So it was you!
Since I've been exposed,
there's no turning back now, Akechi!
Y-You!
How in the world did you manage to survive?
Sorry, not sorry!
Who'd die for such a trifle?
But when I return to Japan alive,
I'll make sure to cover your exploits extensively!
R-Right, that wasn't very nice of me.
I beg your forgiveness.
Humph! It's too late to repent!
No, I do mean it.
I'm so sorry. Would you please marry me...
...in your wildest dreams?!
Wow! How sly!
Can you blame me? In this case,
I’ll just have to kill you myself.
Say your prayers!
Save me, Shinobu!
THUD
Oh?
Man up, everyone!
Our target is the headquarters!
We'll avenge Second Lieutenant Ijuuin
once and for all! There!
The mounted bandits are attacking!
You keep destroying my life!
My status, my position, my reputation.
Everything is in ashes now...
You think that excuses anything?
It's all your fault my Shinobu is gone!
Shinobu...
Oh crap, I've lost it!
How the tables have turned!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Stop running away!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
I want a man...
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Huh?
Hey! Stop!
Ushigorou!
Ushigorou the Goldfish...
makes an entrance!
Everyone, gather round!
Man, they really didn't have
to make such a mess out of it...
Well, we've probably
wrecked this place enough.
Benio, where is that Innen now?
Lying right there.
So you're that asshole?
Wake up!
What should I do with you?
Let's use him up to make some dumplings!
What about turning him into soup?
Let's boil him and bake him!
How about we tear
all your limbs apart one by one?
Onijima, while I despise Colonel Innen
as much as you do,
you must realize
that even if you kill him now, it won't...
bring Shinobu back.
Hey! My boss showed great compassion for you.
You better be grateful, Innen!
Yessir! Let’s all say “I love you!”
and sing a song about it!
Man, what should we do?
Even the Colonel has a screw loose now...
Who am I?
I have no memories of my past at all.
Shinobu, where are you now?
I'm willing to face any kind of fate
if it's for your sake.
You said that to me once.
But now you're gone.
How foolish of me.
I came all the way here,
yet all I could do was confirm that you're dead.
If anything, I'd be better off following you...
That's right. That's what I'll do.
Shinobu, your Benio will be by your side again
in just a moment—this time, forever.
At least I'm leaving this world without any regrets!
Suicide note
Farewell, everyone.
My journey ends here.
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Thank you very much for following our High Collar Lady faithfully all this time.
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase...
Here Comes the High Collar Lady
The End
Ah! Boss, how could you?!
Let me die!
I'll kill myself and nothing's gonna stop me!
Suicide note
If not the washing basin...!
Endure... Endure...
Suicide note
Benio!
Inhale
Hiccup
Benio! Benio!
Our favorite sake jug!
Why did you save me? Let me die!
Lights out
She went from a basin to a sake jug, huh...
Benio. Benio!
Who is it? Who's calling me?
Shinobu!
Shinobu, so you survived after all?
You lied about your death, didn't you, Shinobu?
Who is she? Who is that woman?
Shinobu! Wait!
Where are you going, Shinobu?
Wait! Wait, Shinobu!
Shinobu! Shinobu...
You’re finally awake?
My head hurts so bad! I feel awful.
Of course you do. Be grateful
you didn't get acute alcohol poisoning.
That means... I didn't die?
The Manchurian wasteland...
It connects directly to Siberia,
where Shinobu rests.
The malinka flower...
It's a small, yet enduring flower.
They bloom early, don't they?
In the middle of this wasteland
it can't do anything but hope to grow.
That's what makes it especially beautiful.
Don't you dare think about dying ever again.
He wasn't the kind of person
who'd want you to follow him.
We both know what he truly was like.
Thank you, Onijima.
You're right, he wasn't like that.
Whether Shinobu is alive or not,
it doesn't change the fact that I still love him dearly.
Live, Benio. Keep on living for me as well!
I'll keep on living, Shinobu.
And I'll never...
I'll never forget you!
If you follow this road,
you'll get to the station.
Got it. Thank you for everything.
Take care. Well, goodbye now.
Bye.
Ah, wait a minute.
What is it?
If you ever get tired of Japan,
you can come to Manchuria anytime.
And...
And?
Never mind.
Well, adieu!
So, shall we return to Tokyo?
Yessir!
I was about to say:
"If you ever manage to forget Shinobu..."
What do you know,
guess I got a crush on her! Poor old me.
Boss?
Thusly, the play is once again set in Tokyo.
Benio leaves Manchuria with nothing
but the confirmation of Shinobu's death.
"I had no business coming here. Goodbye, Manchuria, and my dear Shinobu," she thinks to herself.
as the burning red sunset stings her eyes.
Next episode preview
Upon returning to the flowering Tokyo,
Benio finds the Ijuuin family in shreds.
How could she ever tell them about Shinobu's final moments?
But even if he is now gone,
her love is unchanged
and she decides to stay with them.
Our High Collar Lady holds back her tears and carries on, stronger than ever.
See in the next episode of
Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Shinobu Lives on in My Heart."
Episode 40
Shinobu Lives on in My Heart
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan