Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Having found out that it was the evil Lt Col Innen who orchestrated Shinobu's transfer to Kyushu,
High Collar Lady loses it. Her sight is set on the Imperial Army 1st Division Headquarters.
The news reaches Kichiji,
who also arrives at the site with an army of helpers,
namely the Kanto Lilac Family.
War makes strange bedfellows,
thus, even the nagging teacher decides to personally lead her students into battle.
Not to mention Nanny,
who joins the supporting army as well.
But we ought not to forget
about one more important character:
Of course it's none other than the indomitable count,
determined to test the military's mettle!
Despite that, our High Collar Lady
resolves to storm the place on her own so no one else comes to harm.
Episode 25
Don't Go, Shinobu!
Hello! Hello!
Hanamura Benio has just arrived!
Innen, come out!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
Ouch!
I am Hanamura Benio and
I need to speak with Lt Col Innen!
Go inform him!
Who do you think you are? Hey, if you want a meeting,
apply for one in writing like everyone else!
Si
Silence!
Sil
Sile
Silen
Silence!
Oh no!
I... I've lost...
I've lost
Come out, Innen!
Wait, civilian! Hey!
Let me go!
I told you to wait!
What's all this ruckus?
Innen!
Hey, hold on!
Visitors Reception
Let me go!
Hey you, civilian.
In order to have a meeting, you need to write your name and your address on this visitors' register.
Shut up!
My name and address?
I don't have time for formalities!
This should suffice!
Headquarters office
L-Lieutenant Colonel​... I-Innen!
What is it?
Y-You've got a visitor.
Why are you trembling
over a simple visitor?
Y-You see, it's a schoolgirl
named Hanamura Benio and...
What? Hanamura Benio?
Uh?!
Hanamura Benio?!
Sh-She's right there, Lieutenant Colonel​.
Innen! Where are you?!
Ah... Hanamura...!
Next one can start!
Good! Next one step forward.
Hey!
Come out, Innen!
Wh-What's with her...!
U-Uhm, I-I....
Let's see...
T-Tell her I'm not here! Got it?!
Uhm, didn't you just say
that she's a simple visitor?
Idiot!
Not in her case!
Anyways, tell her I'm away!
I'm away.
Where are you, Innen?
Hanamura Benio's here!
Sh-She's here!
Innen! Where are you?!
Uh-uh, uh...
Oh crap, Division Commander!
Uh...
Oh well...
I have no business with you two!
Get out of my way!
Sir!
Uh...
You, lady. Do you need anything here?
Oh well... uh..
I'd like to meet Lieutenant Colonel​
Innen face to face.
Really?
Uh-uh, alright.
Huh?
Then, follow me.
Okay.
Is Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen here?
Uh-huh.
She's coming this way?
God... Buddha...!
No!
Where are we going?
Uh, it's this way. Come with me.
Well, I guess he's not here.
Uh...
Phew...
Whoa!
Out of the frying pan, into the fire!
H-H-Help me!
Have a seat.
O-Okay.
So, what's your business
with Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen?
Uh...
Well... You see...
"Uh-uh...
"Alright..."
What do you mean by that?
Oh, that's just a bad habit of mine.
Yeah..
You can pay no mind.
Uh-uh, oh well...
What a weird grandpa.
Uh, what about some tea?
Uh-uh.
Yes, please.
Okay.
Alright...
Oh, do you make tea yourself?
Yeah, your own tea is the best
for when you need to concentrate.
Yeah... I also have
coffee, black tea, cocoa,
coarse tea and green tea.
Coffee
Candies
Tea
Sweets
Anything
you could ever wish for, uh-uh.
Then I'd like some coffee.
Uh-uh, alright, but you'll have to wait
while I make some great coffee for you, uh-huh.
I'm ready to be spoiled!
That broad is something else!
She just waltzed in and attacked a military base!
Huh?
Oh! It's​ Innen!
I remember that bastard's face!
No!
Geez...
Here, here!
Thank you.
Not bad.
So, what was your business
with Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen? Uh-uh.
Well... You seem like a reasonable person,
so I guess I can tell you.
Uhm. Feel free to tell me, uh-uh.
Well, then. Where do I start...
It seems like this is taking a while...
What might have happened to Benio?
I don't suppose she has met the firing squad yet.
Ah, the soldiers are back!
Oh! Shinobu! Good timing.
Platoon, at ease!
What's all this commotion, Grandfather?
Huh, so Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen
did such a thing? Uh-uh...
That's right. I can't really blame him
for holding a grudge against me,
but Shinobu had nothing to do with any of it!
I see. I understand what you mean, uh-uh...
So now he's being transferred all the way to Kyushu to answer for my mistakes...
Still, it has already been decided, uh-uh.
Already decided or not, I just can't back down!
Whoa!
I want to talk to your superior!
Your superior!
Right, uh...
Yes? This is the 1st Division commander, Oukouchi.
Uh-uh?
What?
Uh-uh, yeah...
Division commander...
A lieutenant general?
Uh-uh... uh-uh.
Uh-uh, got it. See you later. Alright.
Oh, young lady!
You see... actually... I...
Ah, no. No... You forgot this. This! Here.
Chief, I beg your pardon.
Shinobu!
Oh, Benio!
Here you are, Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
I was waiting for you.
I apologize, Chief.
Please forgive my fiancée's disorderly conduct.
No, she was just worried about you.
No need for a disciplinary action here. Uh-uh.
Yessir!
While some shady meddling
obviously took place,
the personnel change
is already set in stone.
You'll go there, won't you,
Ijuuin? Uhm.
Certainly, Chief.
Good.
Well. You've got yourself a nice fiancée there,
make sure to treasure her, got it?
Yes, thank you.
Uh...
We have many officers in our great army,
but in times of emergency,
they couldn't stop this one-woman army
from taking the place by storm.
It's not every day that you see
a girl so masculine, uh-uh.
Huh?!
If I may.
Let's go, Benio.
Uh-uh... uh-uh...
The Imperial Army heads to Russia!
The time nears to announce dispatch of troops
The Imperial Army is going to Russia. The time is finally near to announce the dispatch of troops.
Breaking news, everyone!
In 1918, fearing that Russia
might fall to communism,
Japan on August 2nd and the U.S. the day after, both declared that they would send troops to intervene.
Wow, to Russia?
Just as the Great War ended...
The Japanese Army in particular
saw this as an opportunity to advance northward.
In their blind confidence,
they repeatedly funneled in more troops.
The masses were deeply concerned that their husbands and sons would be sent to actual battlefields.
That same day, Shinobu,
who was about to be transferred to Kyushu,
had breakfast with his family one last time.
Will you be fine there, Shinobu?
I'm so worried that they might
send you to Siberia too...
Don't worry! The Nagoya regiment will be the first to be dispatched.
However, you're the only child
of our family, Shinobu.
It's not like you to be so worried.
By the way, where's Benio?
Oh, where might she be indeed?
Hey there!
Ijuuin!
Oh, so nice of you to come.
A little bird told us you're leaving.
Do your best, buddy.
Sure.
So, where's Benio?
Where is your lovely fiancée we've all missed?
Well, she should be here somewhere...
Lady Benio.
Lady Benio? Lady Benio!
Now then, where might she have gone?
Lady Benio?
Lady Benio!
Found her?
No.
Boss!
Where are you?
Benio!
It's worked before.
Found her?
No, nothing!
Boss!
Boss! Feeding time!
Huh?!
Hey, get out of here, y'all!
Tenmaru
But it's so comfortable here!
A man...
She's nowhere to be seen.
I wonder...
Are you as sure as you can be?
Yes, we checked every corner.
Let's think of a place where Benio could go.
Does anybody have any idea?
Ah!
She might be there!
Saddened with Shinobu leaving, Boss went drinking to drown her sorrows! That's it!
It's not entirely unlikely.
No, I have another idea.
She's drowning her sorrows
in anmitsu, not alcohol!
Don't be silly, it's alcohol!
No, anmitsu!
It's alcohol!
Anmitsu!
Alcohol!
No! You're both wrong!
It's somewhere completely different.
She might not look like one, but
deep down Benio is a tender-hearted girl.
She's definitely offering a hundredfold prayer.
After all, she's the same person
who kept a night vigil when I was sick.
You may be right.
But I'm thinking...
She might be busy gathering stitches for a senninbari
to wish Shinobu well in the war.
Best of luck in your battles
"Senninbari" is a stomach band stitched a thousand times by a thousand people
in order to wish the soldier a safe return.
I'm sure Benio barely has time for anything, when she has so much to do to ensure her husband's safe return.
Pardon the intrusion.
Ah, Father!
Lieutenant, make sure to watch yourself, okay?
Yessir.
By the way, where's Benio?
That's what we're trying to find out.
There's not a trace of her anywhere.
What?! N-now, of all times?
Yes...
I need to go out for a moment.
What's wrong?
Why are you barking, you two? Huh?
Benio!
What are you doing, Benio?
It's dangerous up there!
You shouldn't have climbed so high.
Come on down now!
B-But Shinobu, it's my fault
that you're being transferred to Kyushu...
You don't mind if I join you there?
N-N-No! Don't, don't!
I don't want anybody to come here!
Just leave me alone!
Too late.
Why were you crying, Benio?
I mean... I mean, it's all my fault!
I... have always caused you so much trouble,
but I never thought it would come to this!
Enough worrying about that already.
I've chosen to spend my life with you,
so I'm willing to face with you
any curveballs fate throws your way.
Shi...
Shinobu...!
Don't joke like that!
I've loved you ever since we first met.
Watch out!
Anyway, Kyushu isn't all that far away.
So you shouldn't think that this reassignment is for the rest of our lives.
When your school vacation starts,
make sure to pay me a visit.
Now that I think about it,
Kyushu is famous for its alcohol, too.
Kuma-shochu, for example.
Yes, yes! I'll visit for sure!
Look at who's finally smiling.
It suits a high collar lady like you.
What is it, Ranmaru?
Shinobu, I call for a truce.
Eh? A truce?
Yes, until you return.
I'm not giving up on Benio!
But for the time you're away,
I call for a truce.
And while you're away,
I'll keep protecting Benio any way I can.
This is a promise between men.
Watch yourself, Shinobu.
Stay safe, Young Master.
Shinobu.
I'll be going, then.
Benio.
Shinobu...
Benio, take care of my grandfather and grandmother while I'm away.
Not just them,
Tenmaru and Chimaru too.
O-Okay.
Bye, then.
I was too embarrassed to say it,
even though I thought about it all night,
"I'm sorry for being so stubborn up until now.
But the truth is that I also...
love you.
Please try to come back as soon as possible.
I'll be faithfully waiting for you..."
Heh, I've become quite
mature and womanly, haven't I?
Why are you blushing?
Ijuuin Shinobu, banzai!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai!
So please, come back home safe.
Next time you come home,
I'll tell you everything.
So please, stay safe any way you can.
When the time comes, I'll tell you...
that I want to be your wife,
from the bottom of my heart.
It's often said that meeting inevitably leads to parting,
but who would've thought
that it would happen so soon?
It's no surprise that even our brave High Collar Lady is shocked.
Will today's tears give way to a smile tomorrow,
High Collar Lady?
To be continued
Benio tries to be feminine,
and learn to behave like a proper wife,
while waiting for Shinobu's return.
But unexpectedly, Shinobu is transferred from Kyushu straight to Siberia.
Thinking that this could once again be the result
of Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen's meddling,
our High Collar Lady starts to plan a new raid.
See in the next episode of
Here Comes the High Collar Lady,
"Quit Drinking and Behave Like a Woman!"
Episode 26
Quit Drinking and Behave Like a Woman!
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan