Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
People or heirlooms—that is the question,
or so it would sound if this was Shakespeare.
The furious Count gets this close
to making good on his vow to slice Benio open.
With his wits and good timing,
Shinobu deescalates the incident.
But Benio's already fed up. She bids farewell to everyone and leaves of her own accord.
For once, the Count's stubbornness is met with condemnation from his family.
Shinobu is chosen to be the messenger,
sent after Benio to bring her back.
I'll take my leave then.
Even so, Benio is not out of the woods yet, as her strict father is not happy with her latest escapade.
Do you know why I gave you this?
This is deplorable!
You've gravely offended the lieutenant!
If I may say a word,
it is Shinobu who is deplorable!
I despise that womanizer!
Womanizer?
Yes. Every day, our mail was flooded with piles this big, all love letters.
Then there's that geisha from Yanagibashi he's really close with.
What? Geisha?
Yes. On top of that, she's even prettier than me!
I can't believe that someone like him would do such things.
Don't you trust my words, Father?
Silence! An imperial soldier would not stoop so low
as to indulge in that kind of behaviour!
You keep saying soldier this, soldier that. You really think soldiers are all heavenly beings, huh?
And don't slam the table at me!
What do you call what you're doing right now?!
Shut up! Silence!
You dare slander the army?!
Do you trust just about anyone
over your own daughter?!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Like father, like daughter...
Ah, Benio...
My one and only Benio...
Episode 17
Wandering Petals
W-W-What are you doing?
Come this way.
P-Please don't hurt me!
You need to be more discrete.
Father and daughter finally arguing again—
just let them work it out between themselves.
It'll probably take them a while
after all this time.
Ma'am, you are hearing the lovely sounds of a fresh father-daughter quarrel.
You're still the daughter of a soldier!
I'm your daughter!
What?
What? Didn't you say you're no daughter of mine?
Ah, the people in this family seem to enjoy their arguments a great deal.
I don't remember saying that!
What a nice evening.
Listening to this commotion really makes me feel at home.
Oh,
if it isn't Ushi.
Just in time, I need you to take me somewhere.
Sorry, I don't want to go anywhere tonight.
Is there a reason for that?
Idiot!
Yep! I'm busy listening to the soothing melody
of this father-daughter quarrel!
Huh? Don't make up silly excuses!
C'mon, give me a lift,
I'll give you a good tip.
Tsk. Fine, then.
Okay, up we go.
There, you can start going now.
You still can't understand?!
You're the one who can't understand!
What?
Are you defying your father?!
Master! Master Ranmaru!
Oh, Ken, it's been a while.
Not just "a while"—you've neglected us completely. There hasn't been a lesson in ages.
Please put yourself in our shoes!
My bad, my bad,
I've simply been too busy.
Welcome back, Master!
Oh my, you're beautiful as ever!
Hey, hey, when will we rehearse?
Wait, wait.
No need to rush things like that.
I'm not going anywhere anytime soon,
so we'll have plenty of time to practice.
So we'll be rehearsing this month
according to our normal schedule?
Of course!
Then we must get in touch with the theater at once!
Give them a call.
Yessir!
Then we must get our costumes ready too!
Yes, I'll leave it to you.
Yessir!
Hey, Master, since we're all finally reunited tonight,
shouldn't we celebrate it with some pomp
and sake on the side?
Good idea.
Then, can you go get some takeout
and buy drinks from the liquor store?
Sure!
Young Master, Young Master!
Oh my, what is it?
Great news: they gave us permission
to use the Imperial Theatre on the 31st!
T
Th
The
The I
The Im
The Imp
The Impe
The Imper
The Imperi
The Imperia
The Imperial
The Imperial T
The Imperial Th
The Imperial The
The Imperial Thea
The Imperial Theat
The Imperial Theatr
The Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre w
The Imperial Theatre wa
The Imperial Theatre was
The Imperial Theatre was o
The Imperial Theatre was op
The Imperial Theatre was ope
The Imperial Theatre was open
The Imperial Theatre was opene
The Imperial Theatre was opened
The Imperial Theatre was opened i
The Imperial Theatre was opened in
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 19
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 191
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911.
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911..
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911...
What the hell are you waiting for?
Isn't Benio your fiancée?
Then go bring her back!
Restaurant
Here we are!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen, watch your step!
I'm not drunk! Not drunk at all!
Hey, watch out!
Didn't we warn you?
Are you alright, Colonel​?
I'm not the type to tumble after a little alcohol.
To the next bar!
Let's go to yer watering hole this time, boys.
Yessir! Please let me show the way.
Oh! A horse! I wanna ride that horse!
Stop that fellow!
Surely, you can't be serious!
That'd be unlawful!
I am serious.
And don't call me Shirley.
Ah! That's Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
What, Ijuuin?
Hey, Ijuuin!
Gimme your horse! Stop!
Oh, yikes.
Stop there!
Gimme your horse!
Okay, go!
Stop!
You!
Hey, you!
I apologize!
H-Hey you!
Is that any way to treat your superior?!
How insolent!
An officer can't behave like that!
Did you forget about the chain of command,
you moron?!
Huh?
Oy-oy-oy...
Hey, isn't this where we started?
Hey, Ushi! Aren't we circling around the wall?
Didn't I tell ya that I don't wanna leave this place?
Here we go!
Perhaps it's best that I get off this wild ride?
It's because of your pampered upbringing
that you lack the necessary patience now.
No, I have plenty of patience.
No matter what kind of man Ijuuin Jr. is, as his bride, you must dedicate every ounce of patience to him.
Golden Bat paper roll cigarettes
went on the market about ten years prior, in 1906,
and cost four sen per 10-pack.
At home you obey your parents; as a wife,
you obey your husband; and as an old lady,
you obey your sons.
This is the line of thought that the women and children of Japan must abide by.
You're so old-fashioned, Father.
Go back to the mansion.
Ijuuin Jr. must be worried about you.
Oh no... This anachronism is inherent to my own family as well as to the Ijuuins.
Benio, go back!
Does that mean you don't care what ordeals
I'm having to go through?
Benio.
Once a woman leaves her home,
she shall never set foot in it again!
Father!
Period! No objections!
Understood.
I'm leaving.
And never coming back!
Oh, Lady Benio,
knowing that you'd probably want to celebrate
and have a lavish feast tonight, I was wondering
if I should boil some white noodles.
I won't get to taste your noodles
ever again, Nanny.
Huh? Why so?
I got kicked out.
From this house as well.
Eh? What are you saying?
W-W-Wait just a second!
Why does it always have to end up like this?
Wait here, don't be so hasty!
My dear, there was nothing else I could do.
It's for her own sake
that I'm sending her back to the Ijuuins'.
Lord, don't be so hasty!
Wh-What do you mean?
Aren't you the one being hasty here?
Ah... B-But weren't you about to commit suicide?
Do you take me for a fool?
With a daughter like Benio, no amount of lives is enough if you kill yourself after each of her escapades.
You have a point.
Ugh! How insulting!
Alright, if this is the way it has to be...
You'll not see me ever again!
My young lady, please stop it...
Not happening.
Well then, take care, Nanny.
And take care of Father, okay?
This is just the worst...
Hey, Master,
it's been a long time, hasn't it?
Where were you?
Now that the feast is ready, and we have a solid plan for next month's performance,
won't you make a toast, Master?
Alright, then.
Let's raise our glasses...
to everyone's health, to the actors of Fujieda School,
and to the success of our next spectacle.
Cheers!
Oh Lord!
Ranmaru!
T-This is terrible!
Goodness, what happened, Nanny?
You look dismayed.
Th-The young lady has fled the house again!
Stop her, Ranmaru!
This is a disaster! I gotta go too!
Sorry, everyone, I'm leaving!
Why's that?
B-But where to?
Well, I don't really know myself.
What about next month's show?
You're just gonna have to do it without me.
But I already booked the theater...
And I had already ordered the costumes...
And think of all this food going to waste!
See you, then. Bye-bye!
Oh, come on, Master...
Please wait!
I'm at a loss...
Benio!
Nanny, why did you do that?
I didn't actually mean
to take Ranmaru away from you...
I just wanted to stop Lady Benio.
Wait!
Ugh, to hell with it!
I can't take this anymore!
What the hell? He thinks he can order me around just cos he's a soldier?
Like hell I'm coming here ever again!
I regret nothing, you rotten dad!
Benio!
Sorry for the wait!
We can go now.
Sure.
Young Lady!
And she's gone...
Ushi! It's bad! Really bad!
What is it, Nanny?
The young lady and Ranmaru have run away from home again! Hurry up and stop them!
Great! That means Boss needs me again.
Hey, mister, this is your stop.
Gimme my tip and get off.
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
You've not moved me one inch from where I got on!
And you have the nerve to ask for a tip?!
No refunds...
And off you go!
Boss!
Ushi!
Lord...
I might've gone a bit overboard.
Y-You really didn't have to bring it to this.
We went too far, it's hard to know when to stop with her.
I was happy to see Benio back myself,
but in the end, I know that for her own good
she must return to the Ijuuins' mansion.
Sir...
What could that be?
Excuse me!
So he came for her after all!
Oh, it's you, Lieutenant.
I apologize for the late visit.
Commander Hanamura,
what happened today was the result
of my own indecision.
No, it wasn't solely your fault.
Is Benio here?
Hm? Hasn't she come back to your place yet?
N-No, I mean she left for your place a while ago.
Sh-She must not have arrived yet.
She only left a short while ago, after all.
I'll check now.
Excuse me, I'll need to use your telephone.
Ah, hello, please put me through
to the Ijuuin residence in Otowadai.
Yes, Ijuuin.
Hey, Boss, this is the wrong way.
It doesn't go to the Count's mansion.
Who said we're going there?
Ah, I see.
Then, in the event that Benio returns,
take her to her room and let her rest.
I'll be back shortly. That's all.
She's not back yet.
N-No, don't worry. She's got to be going there.
She's got nowhere else to return to.
You think so?
Well then, I'll check any places she may have gone on my way home.
I appreciate that.
Yessir. Nothing to worry about.
Ah... Say, Lieutenant...
Yes? What is it?
You see, Benio told me that in Yanagibashi she encountered a...
geisha, or someone like that.
Ah, if that's what this is about, I assure you
there's no cause for concern, Major.
So I thought.
I'm glad I never doubted you.
Thank you for your trust.
Benio jumped to conclusions without consulting me and kept silent about it.
I'll be sure to talk to her about it once I get a chance.
Right. Good to hear.
Then, I'll be leaving.
Lieutenant!
Huh? Is there something else?
Take good care of her.
I know how difficult she can be.
N-Not at all!
Benio turned out to be just the kind
of person I thought her to be.
On the contrary, I sometimes think
that I'm not worthy of her.
Lieutenant...
Thank you.
Hey, Benio, what are we going to do?
Gimme a minute, I'm trying to think.
You've been thinking for a while, haven't you?
Well, you know I've slammed the door in both houses now.
I can't go back to either.
It's too late to return home, after all the stuff I said.
But, I've also had just about enough of that mansion.
Why does it always end up like this for me?
I'm sick of it.
Uhm, Boss Benio,
how about we use this occasion
to go somewhere festive,
with lots of drinks?
You're right! That's a great idea!
I was also considering drowning this affair in drink.
Ah... Please, no!
Benio can't control herself when drunk!
Then you can go home on your own.
Ah! I don't deserve this treatment!
Ushigorou, let's go!
Aye-aye.
Hooray! Lessgo, lessgo!
C'mon, Ushigorou, lessgo!
Abuse after abuse...
Why is it always me?
I can keep you company!
What's wrong with Shinobu?
That womanizer...
Right, right, right, right.
On top of it, Father also took his side.
Drinking can fix anything!
Pour me another one!
Here. Sorry for the wait.
Alright! Another one!
Sure.
That's the spirit, Boss!
Ushi! Don't make her drink any more!
Idiot! Alcohol is the broom that sweeps away sorrow!
Screw Shinobu, screw Father,
screw all the soldiers, dammit!
They're so noisy!
Lt. Col, are we leaving already?
Don't speak nonsense. We're just getting started.
I was going to take a leak.
Ugh...
Whoops!
The hell you doin'?!
W-What was that?
I sat on something.
My cap!
You bastard!
How dare you do this to a soldier's headwear?
A soldier? What of it if you're a soldier, huh?
What?
She's got the drunken eyes.
T-T-This is dangerous!
Ijuuin's a soldier.
Father's a soldier too.
And then there's this nasty guy!
Bitch, you're talking to the imperial soldier...
What's with this little thing?
Okay! One, two, three...
What did you expect to achieve
with a sword that blunt?
My precious saber...
Soldiers this, soldiers that...
It's nuffin' to be proud of!
Our high collar lady is dauntless,
but she had chosen a dangerous opponent this time,
as this man is none other than Shinobu's superior,
and holds the lieutenant's fate wholly in his claws.
But well, they say ignorance is bliss.
It's also true that no one knows what the future holds,
but no one does it quite like our High Collar Lady.
The Imperial Army is no match
for blooming Benio in a drunken frenzy,
so she mops the floor with five grown men.
"Boss is in danger!" -
Ushigorou dashes out to call for reinforcements,
but Shinobu gets bogged down in another brawl
while the changed Count
fights the public nuisance with all his might.
Benio's surely incurred a lot of grievances tonight!
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady: "Scoring Grudges is Dangerous!"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon