Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Benio came to an elegant ball—in name only—and got surrounded by deeply jealous women,
then accidentally broke her vow of abstinence.
Meanwhile, Shinobu and Onijima
fought to decide who'd get to sacrifice himself to save the other.
Back at the ball, Benio once again
brought chaos in her special fashion.
With the High Collar Lady around, no event is safe from ending in a grand brawl.
Serving as a decoy,
Shinobu went on a one-man assault.
His selfless act moved Onijima,
who has now regained consciousness
and is desperately calling out to him to no avail.
Commander! Commander!
Commander, where are you?!
If you're still alive, answer me!
Episode 30
Shinobu's Final Battle in Scattered Petals!
Tokyo
Way to go! All-out assault!
How dare you?! Take this!
What's this?
Do you understand now, Akechi?
All-out assault! Kyaa!
See you again, boys of the detective club...
Commander!
Here they come. Alright...
I must avenge the commander by myself.
It's my squad!
Onijima!
Commander...
Commander!
Onijima, so you've also made it out alive after all...
I was dead sure there was
no hope for you, Commander!
Hey, everyone!
The deputy commander is safe too!
Hooray!
What a relief!
I thought it was too late.
You're safe and that's all that matters.
Right. When I left you to rest in that trench
and attacked the enemy by myself,
I thought I'd never get to see you again.
That was when I heard...
Platoon commander! Deputy commander!
We've come to your rescue!
Worried for you and me,
the entire platoon rushed to our rescue.
Commander!
Hang in there!
Private Kobayashi...
Commander, you're safe now.
I see. That's good!
Deputy commander! We might be hopeless good-for-nothings...
but we'll stick together unto death.
Am I right, boys?!
Yeah!
Commander...
We've decided to entrust our lives to you,
so we'll follow you to the end!
However, I can't let you die in vain.
I'll do whatever it takes to protect all of you!
Hey, gimme one.
Here, your change of clothes.
Thanks.
Sheesh, it sure has turned chaotic.
And it's all because Benio showed up.
As always...
I am nothing but a burden on Benio.
What's wrong, Ranmaru?
What I want to say is...
Benio is doing her best to become more ladylike, but I led her astray...
Ranmaru...
Do you love Benio that much?
I see. But, Ranmaru, you have to understand...
Benio loves Shinobu now.
Yes...
I'm well aware.
Seeing how excited she is when she receives Shinobu's letters,
how impatiently she waits for his return...
I, on the other hand...
can't help but chase hopelessly after her.
Even though I know full well that she'll never turn back for me...
I keep trying to satisfy
my unquenchable thirst!
Ranmaru...
It's fine. Even if my love
will never be reciprocated.
I know that you may think of me
as an idiot for doing this.
Pure child. What a pure child you are.
Shinobu, you need to come back soon.
Please make sure to return home safely.
If you don't, we won't have any outlet for our feelings.
Can you see them, Second Lieutenant?
We are... deep into enemy territory, aren't we?
Why should we defend this place to death?
Benio, have you picked up kendo again?
Yes, I suppose.
Good grief...
I sure hope I'll never have to face you.
Acting all that feminine just isn't in my nature, you know?
My shoulders got stiff.
I guess I should stop forcing myself.
I am who I am, after all.
Well said! That's the Benio we all know and love.
Oh, I have an idea.
Say, how about we practice together again?
For old times' sake, Ranmaru.
Th-Th-Thanks, but I'll pass.
G-Goodbye!
What about you, Ushigorou?
Oh, right! I've just remembered that I have an urgent matter to take care of.
How dull.
Pardon me!
Shinobu, you haven't sent me any letters lately.
The last time I've heard from you was when you got sent to the front line.
No, I shouldn't worry.
You promised that you'd return home safely.
You told me that you will return.
The enemy seems to be drawing closer.
That sounded like a 70mm howitzer, didn't it?
You've become quite used to explosions, haven't you, Commander?
We've been on the front line for two months, after all.
How does a toast sound?
Yes, sure.
I still find it strange that someone like you ended up in a place like this.
We are an infamous unit
composed entirely of outcasts.
It was only a matter of time before we got sent to the front.
Someone like you must have left
a lot behind back home.
First from Tokyo to Kokura and now to Russia.
They've been harsh to you.
Don't you have a pretty girlfriend?
That's right.
Thought so.
You got any pictures of her?
C'mon, lemme see what she's like.
Huh?
A pug-nosed girl!
In the flesh, she's nothing like this photo.
She's irascible and quick to fly off the handle.
But deep down, she's kind, magnanimous, indomitable, and has a strong sense of justice.
She'd never leave someone in trouble.
Commander,
why did you get sent all the way here?
It was all my fault.
Shinobu...
Come home soon, okay? Please...
Oh?
Mrs. Kisaragi.
Grandfather and Grandmother don't seem to have any appetite at all.
Receiving no news from Young Master must have cast a gloom over them.
I don't think it's possible for them to enjoy their meal at times like this...
I'd prefer it if they had
at least a slice of bread, though.
A slice of bread, you say...
One, two, one two.
We absolutely gotta let them win!
Roger that!
We'll begin now.
Ready!
Idiot, I told you we're not allowed to win!
Ah, my bad...
Ow, ow...
What, you're crying
at the sight of some anpans?
Yes. It reminded me of Young Master.
It goes back over twenty years.
Young Master had lost his appetite
because of a cold,
so I brought him some anpans to eat.
He loved them at once.
From that moment onward,
we had our little secret
and I would make anpans
from time to time only for him.
Commander, this is our entire ration for breakfast.
Crackers from emergency rations?
Kobayashi, do we really have to use them?
Yes. We don't have a single grain of rice left.
Commander, the others haven't made any complaints about food,
but we definitely won't last long like this.
I'm aware. In normal circumstances, we would've been resupplied two days ago.
But we haven't heard anything at all.
Commander!
Th-The enemy!
What?!
Before I knew it, there was a large formation of cossacks surrounding our position!
What do we do, Commander?
Commander!
Alright, let's move out of here.
We'll evacuate and run to headquarters.
But, Second Lieutenant, we were ordered to defend this place to the death.
Get ready to move! Leave everything you don't need behind. Hurry up!
I'll take responsibility.
Commander...
Why haven't we been sent any provisions in three days?
Headquarters is to blame for this!
Keep going, everyone!
Keep it up!
We'll soon reach headquarters!
Oh! I can see the building!
Okay, one last push, everyone!
Alright!
Tonight we'll finally fill our stomachs!
This is strange.
There are no lookouts stationed.
No flags flying, either.
Commander, there's nobody here!
Everyone's left, not a living soul here!
Wh-What did you say?!
(Top Secret)
Siberia Invasion Plans
Dammit! Those high command
bastards stranded us!
Rather, they've used us, burdens that we are, as a decoy for their retreat.
Just what you'd expect! Tsk!
They didn't even send us any supplies!
Listen, everyone. In a situation like this, the best we can do is save our own lives.
It's all or nothing now.
We'll break out of the encirclement
and try to rejoin with the rest of the division.
We'll do this by running through the forest.
Our only ally is the dark of the night.
Let's go!
Listen well: forget about defeating the enemy.
Run for your life, just run.
We're not fighting for the fate of Japan here.
This is just an intervention war.
So we can't let ourselves get killed in vain!
We're fighting to survive and return home. Got it?
To survive.
And return home.
They're coming.
Commander, the same goes for you.
You have to survive to return to your Benio.
Ura!
Platoon, charge!
Crap! My leg!
Oh! Hey, wait for me!
Did everyone make it?
Yes, we're safe.
Commander, Sergeant Onijima is not here.
What? Onijima?
All right, you guys can leave without me.
Wh-What are you going to do?
I can't leave Onijima behind.
Don't do this!
You'll face certain death.
We'll return to Japan all together.
Get moving!
Commander!
Onijima! Where are you, Onijima?
C-Commander!
Onijima!
Stop! Don't come here!
Leave me behind!
How can you be so reckless?
You'll just end up dying too!
Hang on, Onijima!
Stop, Comman⸺
Commander! Behind you!
Commander!
White... White petals of Malinka...
White... White Malinka...
The symbol of Shinobu's safe return.
I'll be waiting... I'll be waiting!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
Shinobu's portrait cracked...
Don't tell me something bad happened to him...!
Commander!
Where are you, Commander?!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
You're such a fool...
Didn't I tell you
that you must return to your girlfriend?
Commander! Why...
Why did you sacrifice yourself for me?
The snow falls on the Siberian landscape
as Sergeant Onijima, moved by Shinobu's sacrifice, sheds manly tears.
The moment Benio is notified of his death in battle,
there'll surely be no end to her tears.
Episode 31 of Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"No Tears Left to Cry"
Shinobu's promise to return home safely is broken
once Benio is informed of his tragic death in battle.
The grief obstructs her throat to the point she can no longer wail
and clogs her eyes
to the point where she has no tears left.
Her love for Shinobu pours out of her heart
and her intense feelings form a tempest.
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"No Tears Left to Cry."
Episode 31
No Tears Left to Cry
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan