Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Shinobu's unit, deployed to the front line, found itself marooned by the headquarters
and forced to face off a whole battalion of cossacks with a single platoon.
Having vowed to bring everyone home alive, Shinobu returned to look for injured Onijima,
recklessly jumping into the smokes of the battlefield all alone.
Although repeatedly called on, he never returned.
What is the tragic fate
awaiting our High Collar Lady?
Episode 31
No Tears Left to Cry
Commander!
Sergeant Onijima!
Hey! You found anyone?
No luck!
How'd it go?
It's no use!
They're nowhere to be found.
Let's give up.
This could only mean that both Commander and Sergeant Onijima have died in battle.
Our enemies are not just the partisans and the Cossack cavalry.
We mustn't take wolves and this blizzard lightly either.
Even Napoleon himself was defeated by Russian snow.
Come on, let's march back!
Never!
I'll try once again, even on my own!
Kobayashi, I understand how you feel,
but we've exhausted our options.
Let's go home now!
I'm not going anywhere without our commander!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin is the only one who has ever treated outcasts like us humanely!
I'd rather die alongside someone like him!
You go home without me!
I'll go look for him alone!
Kobayashi!
Commander!
We're not gonna leave you one!
Come on, let's give it another shot!
Commander!
Kobayashi!
It's autumn already.
Yes, just look at all of these ginkgo nuts.
Found one already!
I could ask Kisaragi to make some
omelet with it today!
Yeah, or roast them and eat them here.
Yes, nice idea.
Let's put them on the bonfire.
This brings back memories, actually.
Don't you remember when we used to go to the botanical garden to gather ginkgo nuts?
Of course I do. We'd go there all the time.
One for Ranmaru, one for me.
Two for Benio, two for me.
We'd keep going until we'd get so full we'd have a stomachache!
The stench of the ginkgo nuts would stick to our kimonos, too.
Yeah. Nanny used to scold me for that.
Why can't we just go back the way we were?
Ranmaru...
Sorry. I'm doing nothing but troubling you by talking about this.
Not at all. Thank you.
I wonder when Shinobu's coming back.
After all, 13,000 people are making their return on October 18th,
while some of them have already come back.
Army performance in Russia was far from stellar
and, with recession around the corner,
the expeditionary forces were repatriated en masse from October to December 1918.
Good question. I'm sure he will also be back in no time, though.
That day, I'll bring many bottles of vodka for us to drink.
He made me a promise. He swore that he'd be back.
Lady Benio! Lady Benio!
Oh? Good timing, Kisaragi.
We've just finished roasting ginkgo nuts.
This is not the time for that!
C-Countess has just collapsed.
Huh?!
How come?
Countess?
Let's all just hurry home. Quick!
Stay strong, Countess.
What?
Shinobu... Shinobu...
Countess?
Watch out, you're too close.
You'll end up falling into the pond...
Countess...
Shinobu...
My Shinobu...
This way, please.
She's been muttering for a while, I hope she'll be fine.
I'll inject her a sedative.
At times like these, resting properly is the best one can do.
Lady Benio.
Yes?
There are some visitors that wish to meet you.
I don't want to leave Countess's side right now...
But you see, they said that it's urgent.
There's also your father among them.
What? My father?
Who could they be?
Long time no see, father.
Benio, these men are Shinobu's subordinates.
Oh, so you are Lady Benio.
Are you the fiancée Second Lieutenant told us about?
Yes...
W-We're extremely honored to meet you!
The pleasure is all mine.
Second Lieutenant used to talk about you all the time.
My Benio is ever so kind and cheerful...
He'd never get tired of talking like that about you.
Cheerful...?
Shinobu...
Here.
Our unit was sent to the most dangerous front line before the other ones.
Being a gathering of rogues, we've always been treated poorly by our superiors
and on the final day of our assignment, our headquarters left us to our death.
We got surrounded by a Cossack formation.
Platoon, attack!
We desperately tried to make our way out and ran for dear life.
However, Sergeant Onijima,
our deputy commander, got injured,
yet we couldn't afford
to wait for him to catch up with us.
Shinobu has told me a lot about him in his letters.
Commander couldn't leave him behind.
So he said to us...
We'll return to Japan all together.
Get moving!
We couldn't stop him
and, with those words,
he ran among bombings all alone.
He was the only one of us
who returned to look for Sergeant Onijima.
Despite our selfish superiors having abandoned us to our fate,
Second Lieutenant just refused to leave even a single one of us behind...
I... I'd never met a commander like him!
Even if we are just lowlifes,
he declared he wouldn't let anyone die in vain.
He's the only one to who's ever treated us like human beings.
Throughout our lives, people have always regarded us as nothing more than pests.
Only Second Lieutenant was different,
protecting us like he was our big brother.
And now he's...
Shinobu...!
Shinobu!
Shinobu! Shinobu!
Whoa, Benio!
Hang in there, Benio!
Father, I don't understand
what you all are trying to say...
What in the world are you trying to tell me?
Benio, I don't want to believe it either,
but Second Lieutenant Ijuuin... died in battle.
Shinobu... is... dead...?
I'll return home for sure...
Shinobu! I thought you promised you'd be back!
Shinobu...
Countess, here, please sit on this chair.
I am Count Ijuuin, the owner of this mansion.
Sir!
We've heard many great things about you!
Good. Well, at ease, boys.
It's been a long time, Count.
I'm here today to express my condolences for Shinobu's passing.
Please tell us everything about Shinobu, even minor details.
We'd like to, but every memory wrings our hearts even more.
Hey! Don't forget that you're still imperial soldiers!
Leave the tears to women and children!
As men, you must never...
Never lose your composure! Never!
At first,
we all had hastily assumed Second Lieutenant
was just another spoiled heir of a rich family
and belittled him.
However, we soon realized he actually was more human than anyone else.
That's obvious! It's our family's trademark, after all. So what's next?
I have a tattoo on this arm,
which has always been enough for me to be respected,
but that wasn't of any help when it came to letters from home.
While everyone else received them from their loved ones in Japan,
I, being an orphan,
was always the exception.
That was when Second Lieutenant introduced me some White Russian orphans
who lost their parents during the revolution.
He offered me to become their Japanese teacher.
A, i, u, e, o!
Truth be told, I didn't even finish elementary school myself.
Even though many in our unit had high school and even university diplomas,
IVAN
NIKOLAI
NATASHA
KOBAYASHI
he still chose someone like me, completely unbecoming of a professor.
So, in the beginning, I was at a loss.
But, thanks to this, when we were leaving for the front line,
the kids came to see us off, waving small Japanese flags.
In that moment, I vowed to sacrifice my own life for them.
Thanks to Second Lieutenant, I found my new little sisters and brothers in Siberia.
It was him who granted an orphan like me with a reason to live for.
We may never meet again...
but, whenever I close my eyes, I see those Siberian children...
and I feel like I'm there with them.
Only someone like him could make this happen.
Shinobu was very much like that...
Dear, a Satsuma warrior
shouldn't be crying before the survivors...
I'm not crying!
Who're you taking me for?!
I'm just sweating from my eyes!
From that day onward, Countess has been sleeping for days on end due to the shock.
Meanwhile, Count has shut himself in his room.
When he comes out every now and then,
his eyes are clearly red and swollen.
Why? Why did it have to be Young Master?!
Our immeasurably kind Young Master...
The whole household spends its days crying.
No one can bear the thought of you being gone.
No one can bear the thought of living
while you’re gone.
Shinobu...
Benio, Shinobu's funeral is tomorrow.
I see.
Why...
Why won't any tears come out?
I can't cry.
My throat is obstructed by grief
and I can't speak.
My eyes are clogged
and I can't shed any tears.
I can't stand this pain in my chest...!
Ah... The very thought of your love...
It's like being desperately trying
to get out of a whirlpool.
All of these emotions are about to tear my chest apart...!
I'll come home for sure. I promise. Safe and sound.
Didn't you tell me so?!
You have to come back!
You must come back, and then at least
I could tell you about my feelings!
It's a lie. It has to be.
It can't be true that you're gone.
Hey, what's with that woman?
What a weird girl. Why is she out in this rain without an umbrella?
I don't believe it.
I don't want to believe it.
Why? Why didn't you come back?
Why... Didn't you appear before me
like you always did?
Boy, let me tell you about your father
who went to Siberia, where flowers bloom...
We might never meet again
for this could be my final moment.
At the battle of Nikolayevsk...
That's why they were left behind...
That's when that a partisan stabbed you
and you drew your last breath...!
Shinobu!
Shinobu! Shinobu!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You sure have a lot of energies, huh?
Gonna leave without even
apologizing, eh, young miss?
Army uniforms...
Precisely. As you can see, we are imperial soldiers!
Whoa there. Hold on.
Who said you can just leave without saying anything?
How about you hang out with us for a while as a token of apology?
Right, what do you say?
Come now!
Now you've done it!
Is that a way to treat an imperial soldier?!
You're too impertinent for a woman!
What am I doing?
Then tell me, what have you done for Shinobu?
You sent him to his certain death while you were twiddling your thumbs!
I won't forgive you!
Anyone or anything that played a role in taking Shinobu away from me won't get away with it!
You broad...
There's a fight!
I-It's a fight! They're fighting!
S-She fought them!
Wow!
A woman is thrashing four soldiers by herself!
Someone stop them! I beg you!
We'll need an ambulance if this keeps up!
There's no way that she can win in a one-to-five.
You got this wrong! It's the soldiers who'll need it!
What?
We got beaten up...
See? It's what comes after that's scary. Hospital bills don't come cheap these days.
Oh, Boss! Let's hurry up to get out of here, okay?
Hey, you!
They're already here, Boss!
Come on now! Hurry up!
Who did this?!
Who made such a mess of these soldiers?!
Well, it was me.
No way you did it with that face of yours!
Oh... that hurt...
Ueno Police Station
Are you ever gonna open your mouth?!
What's your name? Where do you live?
Who's gonna answer in your place?!
How in the world did a woman like you manage to beat up five imperial soldiers?!
Ugh, at least show some remorse!
You'll stay here until someone more mature comes for you.
Sheesh, we're in a pickle...
Even if she brings Count up,
she'll just give him and Countess,
who are already grieving, more to worry about.
Boss may be foul-mouthed, but there's no way she'll mention Count.
In other words, this means no one's coming for her, so she'll never get out.
But tomorrow's the day of Second Lieutenant's funeral...
Wherever Benio looks,
be it to the West or to the East,
there will always be a cold wall before her.
All that comes to her feverish mind
is Shinobu's gallant image.
But this doesn't change the fact that tomorrow his funeral will be held.
Why is she refusing to utter the Count's name in order to leave this police cell?
Next episode of Here Comes High Collar Lady
Various relatives of the Ijuuin family, who gathered for Shinobu's funeral,
start shameful fights when discussing how to share their fortune.
Benio declares her eternal and unchanging love for Shinobu,
donning her white dress and cutting off her black hair afterwards.
Ah, how is she going to live from now on?
Next time on Here Comes High Collar Lady:
I'll Cut my Black Hair to Consecrate it to You.
Episode 32
I'll Cut my Black Hair to Consecrate it to You
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing & translation checking
Special thanks
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo
Golden time Anime (vk)