Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
In life, things never
seem to go your way.
Even during your all-important
romantic elopement,
you could stumble onto a shady man or
even the fiancé you were running away from.
And even if you end
up starting a bar brawl,
you can still sneak away,
hand-in-hand with the Second Lieutenant,
and leave a maiden's heart
with a romantic hangover.
Benio's high-collar life goes from bad to worse as she's taken to school at breakneck speed!
Here I go! Make way, make way!
What's wrong with that guy?
Here we are!
Here we are, Boss!
Come on, give me your hand.
Come on!
Boss, what's wrong?
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Didn't we swear an oath?
Come now.
Boss, you forgot your bag!
- Good morning!
Good morning!
How are you?
Boss!
Whoops, excuse me, sorry...
Please, wait!
Boss, you forgot your bag!
Ushigorou?
You can leave now.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're my boss.
I'll be by your side,
through hell and high water.
A ma— A ma— A ma—
A man...
Episode 4
A Messy Asakusa Opera
Teacher, hang in there...
I didn't think I was
that scary-looking...
Ushigorou, this is an all-girls school.
Men aren't allowed inside.
Aren't allowed inside?
So you're telling me that no man has ever set foot in here?
Yes, that's right!
But you know, half the
world is made up of men...
What a waste...
Just get out of here!
Hurry up!
Okay, call me if
you need any help!
I'll be there before
you know it!
Phew, that was close.
What... just happened?
What do you mean?
I was sure there was
a man in here just now.
A man...
A man?
A man!
I need a man...
Shut up!
T-Teacher, isn't it time
to start the lessons? Isn't it?
For you to want to start classes...
That's not like you at all, Hanamura.
Well, I'm a student too, after all.
Sometimes even I
feel like learning.
Righteous path towards wifehood
Stand up!
Bow!
Sit down!
Oh, my...
Ushigorou isn't a bad guy, deep down.
Then again, he's one more
thing I have to worry about.
Well then,
get your homework out.
I-I forgot again!
I was about to run away from home,
so I didn't think I would come to school ever again...
What?! You forgot it again?!
Uh, yeah, but...
What on earth are people like you going to do with their lives?!
It's not about what
I'm planning to do, uh...
It's just a lot of things
happened in the meantime, so...
Don't lie to me!
I know you did this on purpose!
This is the final straw,
I'm going to inform your father!
Hey, hey, whatcha
doin' to the boss?!
You old hag, how dare you
threaten the boss like that!
Stop it, Ushigorou, stop it!
Don't you dare lay
a finger on my Boss!
Stop it!
That's an order!
Cut it out!
Yeah! I'll let you go this time,
but if you mess around with my boss,
I won't let it slide!
If you'll excuse me.
He's finally gone.
I had to use my authority as
his boss to make him stop...
Look, he's still there.
That's crazy,
is Hanamura part of the yakuza?
What should I do?
The stress just keeps piling up...
Hanamura,
people like you...
Sorry 'bout that.
Oh my...
Huh? You were eloping?
Ranmaru is your
pretty neighbor, isn't he?
I knew you had it in you!
Stop it, you don't
know the whole story...
Is the guy your parents chose so awful that he made you run away?
It's not like that...
There's something about
him you dislike, right?
I want to fall in love...
and then I want to get married.
That's what I want.
I understand how you feel.
Oh, what happened?
You don't look so happy.
That's not like you.
Is that so?
It's kind of obvious.
So, what's bothering you?
Now it's your turn to talk!
But...
Please!
Even though we're classmates,
you've always been more mature than me.
Tell me about yourself, please!
Very well.
To tell the truth,
there's someone I like...
He's a childhood friend.
I've liked him since we were kids,
and I thought I'd get
to marry him one day.
But he's never
shown me any affection.
Not being loved
by those you love,
and being loved by
those you don't.
Things never seem to work out.
On top of that,
he already seems to be
preparing to get married.
Rude of him, isn't it?
But, Tamaki, aren't you always
going on dates with boys?
Yeah.
I was hoping that if I did,
I would find someone better.
But it's no use.
I just can't give up on him!
What does his fiancée look like?
What do you think?
Who knows?
If she's smarter, prettier,
and has a better personality than me,
then I can let him go.
Don't you think so, Benio?
Yeah, I guess so.
But if she's not,
then I won't back down.
Not at all.
Yeah, yeah, that's the right thing to do!
Never give up!
You have to snatch
him away from that girl!
I'll cheer you on!
Thank you.
I have to meet that girl,
no matter what.
I'm sure she pales in
comparison to you, Tamaki.
I hope so...
But I wonder, what kind of boy
made you fall head over heels for him?
I want to meet him!
Do you want to come with me?
I'm going to watch the
Asakusa Opera with him today.
Are you sure you don't mind?
By all means.
Since it's you,
I don't mind you seeing him.
I wonder what kind of guy wouldn't be
attracted to someone as wonderful as Tamaki.
Things are about to get wild!
What will happen when these three people
finally understand what's going on?
Opera as we know it began
in the Imperial Theatre.
It took root in Asakusa
in the 6th year of Taisho,
and the Asakusa Opera took
things to a new height.
In particular, the Boccaccio Opera, centered around the cross dressing girl, was sparking in popularity.
There are so many people!
With the Opera Craze going on, it's been very popular lately.
Hey, Tamaki!
Where's your beloved?
Oh, right.
Oh, there he is!
W-Where, where?
Hey, where is he?
Look, he's over there!
That guy?
Yeah, him.
Hey... Huh? You...
Oh, do you
know each other?
Wait...
Benio, are you
Shinobu's fiancée?
But if she's not,
then I won't back down.
Yeah, yeah, that's the right thing to do!
Never give up!
S-So t-the Second Lieutenant
is the guy Tamaki is in love with?
This has to be a joke!
You're telling me that...
Of all people, Shinobu's fiancée is Benio,
the most unusual girl in school?
No way!
My delicate heart...
can't take such a shock!
Tamaki!
Wait, please wait!
Tamaki, what are you doing?!
Running away won't solve anything!
What a mess this turned into...
So you and Tamaki are friends?
It's so strange, watching her
act like that all of a sudden.
It's my fault...
Don't worry about it,
she's always been like that.
She said she just had to see this opera, so she invited me today.
Opera Boccaccio
It would be a shame to waste them,
so would you like to go with me?
What? Are you saying
I'm your backup plan?!
Come on!
Nanny.
Nanny!
Oh, Ranmaru,
are you feeling better now?
Not really,
but I'm worried about Benio.
Is she here?
She should be back from school by now,
but she's still not home.
The young lady is
always causing trouble!
Worry after worry, I'm going
to start losing weight over it...
Really? I wouldn't have guessed...
Oh!
It's you, Ushigorou.
Where is the young lady?
What? She's still not here?
That's strange...
She's not here?!
Being her bodyguard, I thought you would know where she is!
I'm glad to hear you say that,
so I'll go looking for her now!
Wait, Ushi, I'll go too!
Ranmaru,
aren't you still sick...?
It doesn't matter. I have a bad feeling that
something's going to happen to Benio...
I have that bad feeling
about her every day!
How did it come to this...?
My friendship is in jeopardy...
Tamaki, I'm so sorry!
What should I do?
And he's acting
so nonchalant now,
like nothing happened
between me and Tamaki...
Um...
Did you really not
notice it at all?
About Tamaki...
You see, Tamaki...
Rice crackers, caramels, and red bean buns!
To tell you the truth, she...
Oh, would you like a red bean bun?
Who cares about a damn bun?!
Now's not the time to
be talking about food!
What about lemonade or dried squid?
What do you want?
Let's see... I'll go with a red bean bun,
a lemonade, and dried squid!
And Kintarou candy, too!
Sure, here you are!
W-Well, I missed my chance.
I-I just can't help it
when food is involved.
Here I go! Let's go-go-go!
Make way!
Ushi, stop here.
Yes, sir!
She's wearing the
same uniform as Benio.
You kabuki actors sure
know your clothing!
Hey, girlie, hold on a minute!
May I ask you something?
Oh, you're Benio's henchman
we saw at school.
And I take it you're Ranmaru?
Oh!
You're well informed!
Then that makes this easy!
You happen to have any
idea where the boss could be?
If you're looking for Benio...
Please tell us if you know.
She's at the Asakusa Opera...
Something's wrong.
My woman's intuition could
tell something was wrong.
Come on, let's get a move-on!
Here I go!
I can't believe my friendship
with Tamaki could end over this...
I need to think of something...
Love is full of kindness
A flower in the meadows
Tamaki loves Shinobu,
Not even under summer sun
and I am Shinobu's fiancée,
b-but I don't feel anything for him.
Letting itself wilt
There's an easy fix to this, then!
Permeated with warm thoughts
Hey! Shinobu!
Uh? What's the matter?
Rushing through my chest
I have a proposal...
A proposal? What is it?
Let's cancel it, our wedding, I mean.
Not ever transfixed in doubt
Huh?!
Louder!
Not even as winter comes
In my young heart,
And here I was wondering
what you wanted to say...
This is no laughing matter!
You are the only one
Damn you, you're
always laughing at me!
More, more!
Play louder!
Tamaki really loves you a lot!
She loves you!
Huh?
Did you say something?
It's about Tamaki!
Louder!
Huh? You want to eat tamarind?
Tamaki said...
she is deeply...
in love with you!
Uh-oh... Everyone heard that...
I swear, audiences these days...
Love is full of kindness
A flower in the meadows
Not even under summer sun
Letting itself wilt
Permeated with warm thoughts
To learn that Tamaki likes me,
all of a sudden...
Rushing through my chest
What? Can you raise
your voice a bit?
Not ever transfixed in doubt
It feels so sudden...
Not even as winter comes
Don't you feel bad, though?
Huh?
Don't you feel bad, though?!
In my young heart,
W-Well...
Tamaki has always loved you,
so wouldn't it be better
if she married you?
You are the only one
There's no way I could do that!
How dense can you possibly be?!
Hey, it's getting interesting over there!
I should be the one
saying that to you!
W-What was that?!
I don't feel that way!
And then you come here and say...
I mustn't give up.
I'll get their attention back with my talents...
Love is full of kindness
Oh, so you're saying that you don't
care about my friendship with Tamaki?
A flower in the meadows
No, I'm not saying that...
Then what are you saying?
Go ahead, tell me!
Not even under summer sun
That's right,
you said it, go for it!
Oh my, aren't those
my red bean buns?
Letting itself wilt
Hey, you red bean bun thief!
Permeated with warm th—
I'm gonna kill them! Kill them all!
I'll kill the whole lot of them!
Hey, please, calm down,
Prima donna!
I'll kill 'em! I'll kill 'em!
Take this!
UFO!
Where do you think you're going, after causing all this mess?
Never come back!
Huh?!
Here I go!
Go-go-go-go!
Boss!
Benio...
Please, hang in there, Boss!
Red bean buns... red bean buns...
Why do twists of fate follow high-collared girls wherever they go?
What does fate have
in store for tomorrow?
Tamaki's unrequited love and getting to know Shinobu's story led to a lot of sad moments.
Benio, upon realizing it,
decides to quit the high collar lifestyle.
And to ruin her potentially loveless marriage,
she decides to throw a spanner in the works.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Godspeed, Bride in Training"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it gets so hard to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
when he goes away, I want him to turn around,
to give me a loving glance one more time
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Editing
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing, TLC
darkcart
ImAWasteOfHair
TougeWolf
amicus
MartyMcflies
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo