Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Our High Collar Lady is working hard
to provide for the Ijuuin family
and is now worthy
of the title of "modern woman."
Unexpectedly, she found Tamaki,
now a reporter for a newspaper.
At first they had a toast
and cheerfully chatted about many things,
but afterwards they stumbled across a UFO:
was it a hallucination, a dream or real?
What's more, an alien who looked
exactly like Shinobu was on it.
When she awoke with a splitting hangover,
she chalked the whole thing up to a drunken illusion.
But the very next day, the dream turned into reality
when an airship from Russia landed.
Who is going to get off it now?
Episode 42—The End
Oh, Taisho Romance!
So it wasn't a dream after all...
Ah, what a relief!
Oh, thank goodness...
What are you waiting for?!
Interview them already!
G-Got it!
The two who landed are prominent figures
of the exiled Russian nobility.
They are Maquis Mikhailov and his wife.
Fleeing the red terror
of the revolutionary government,
they have applied
for permanent residence in Japan.
Our peace-loving country
is more than glad to warmly welcome both of you.
Whoa! Look at how handsome he is!
I wonder if all Russians are that good-looking.
Ah... I can't see! Fine...
If that's the case,
I'll just crawl from below.
So it wasn't a dream?
Sh-Shinobu's perfect double...
What's wrong?
Hey! Don't push!
Shinobu...
Hey, you!
Show some respect!
Now then, this way please, Marquis.
Wait, Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
What in the world are you talking about, huh?
The marquis started studying Japanese
in anticipation of his arrival,
but he still doesn't understand it fully!
I'm sorry.
It's just that he strongly resembles
someone I knew, so I called him that on a spur...
For the time being, the couple
is going to stay at Earl Tanukikoji's house.
Words came out of my mouth
before I could realize what I was doing...
Malinka?
Why is he the spitting image of Shinobu?
Marquis Mikhailov...
Please tell me, Onijima.
What happened to Shinobu?
He was severely injured,
yet I didn't come to his rescue
I just left him in that Siberian blizzard!
It was all my fault!
I couldn't return the favor!
I'm sorry, Benio.
My Shinobu died...
Yes, it's all a mere coincidence...
"Malinka?"
Didn't Marquis say "malinka"
the very moment he saw me?
Malinka...
Malinka!
Shinobu?
Shinobu! Are you there, Shinobu?
What was that,
instead of interviewing them?
Huh? Editor-in-Chief...
You see, that Marquis Mikhailov
isn't really a Russian aristocrat.
What do you mean?
He is the spitting image
of Ijuuin Shinobu, my betrothed!
Besides...
What are you talking about?
He doesn't look Japanese by any means.
Yes. Shinobu is half-Japanese.
His traits make it hard to tell his nationality.
That's ridiculous! So what you're saying is that your betrothed is still alive?
That person is definitely Shinobu!
Okay, I understand.
So you want to look into
Marquis Mikhailov's background?
A headline like "Exiled Russian Aristocrat Actually Japanese" would certainly be a scoop.
Editor-in-Chief!
Hooray! Editor-in-Chief!
Thank you, thank you!
Follow me!
Today calls for a celebration!
You’ve earned two circles of kielbasa!
Both you and me have been waiting
for Shinobu's return for a really long time.
With those bright, graceful hair
and mysterious hazel eyes of his,
could it ever be anyone
other than my Shinobu?
No! He positively can't!
Still, why couldn't he recognize me?
No wonder!
After many years of hard work,
there's no sign of the feminine charm I once had.
It's no wonder
he didn't realize who I was.
Back in the day, I besotted him
with nothing but my naturally pretty face...
Makeup will save the day!
Some wrinkle-reducing set
and white powder will do!
Oh? Now that's unusual:
Boss is preening herself before the mirror.
I bet there would be no use
in telling you to stop right now!
Eek! No! It slipped off!
You want something?
A-A scary tanuki monster!
Doctor, we've lost him.
Uh?
At any rate, I'll go to sleep for now.
I'll learn everything
during the interview tomorrow.
That said, why does Shinobu...
refer to himself
as Marquis Sasha Mikhailov now?
And to make matters worse,
he even has a wife...
What does that woman Larisa
want from Shinobu?
Oh no, I can't sleep.
Why? Why did he marry her
despite being already betrothed to me?
I can't wrap my head around all of this.
This here is Earl Tanukikoji's mansion.
Such a chic place for a tanuki.
Please inform Earl Tanukikoji.
Certainly.
Here I am, it's me, Tanukikoji.
Wow! He's an actual...
Shh!
Y-You see, we'd like to interview
Marquis Mikhailov and—
No can do!
Their excellencies are tired
and refuse to meet any press.
N-No way!
There has to be...
Now shoo, shoo!
Cheapskate!
Seems we won't be able
to meet them in a proper way.
If we're left with no proper options...
Oh, I know what to do!
Good morning!
Your order is here!
Too easy!
Oh? You found out?
Right, I beg your pardon!
Sheesh, some people can be obnoxious!
Was it a magazine reporter, Mr. Tanukikoji?
Oh no, you needn't worry.
I've just driven them away.
We appreciate it. For the time being, we're not ready to be seeing anyone.
Of course! By the way,
have you made any progress in Japanese?
Yes. Marquis and I
have been studying all day long.
Shall I try reading for you?
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone...
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
But it will eventually turn into one again.
Oh, Marquis, your pronunciation is impeccable!
Wow, your learning rate
is nothing short of stunning!
Damn it, they're keeping a close guard.
I wonder why are they
that opposed to an interview.
We're so close... Just behind that window
there's the one who might very well be my Shinobu...
You call yourself a bride of that Marquis Mikhailov,
so what are you going to do about that?
Even if we don't know all the details, the current Marquis seems to already be properly married.
If you try to intervene now,
you'll do nothing but hurt yourself.
Are you going to keep pushing despite that?
I...
I never thought about what I would do next.
I just wanted...
I failed to convince myself that Shinobu died in Siberia.
I kept believing he was still alive.
So if he is indeed alive, this might just be
my one and only hope to hold on to.
That's the only way to overcome my regret
of not having confessed my love back then.
That's all I need.
If Shinobu is still alive,
no matter under what name...
I can't possibly forgive that.
No matter how he came to this, forgetting your betrothed to live with another woman...
That's unforgivable. No person
should ever have to suffer through this.
Editor-in-Chief, did you just...
No, no, never mind.
Hey, I need to be serious!
What was I going to say just now?
Wasn't it... Wasn't it...
Oh my, is something wrong, Editor-in-Chief?
Stay strong, Aoe Tousei.
What was I hoping to achieve
by hiding and running away from women?
Perhaps it was out of fear that women
would bring chaos to my orderly and noble life?
B-But that's so... So... So...
My! So sometimes you cry too,
Editor-in-Chief!
Were you that moved
by my heroic determination?
Ugh! No! No, I'm not, you hear?!
Please wait, Young Master!
Wait!
Wait for us!
If only we could join you...
Benio!
Ranmaru?
Caught you!
Help me!
We did it!
Look! I got his underwear!
Hang in there, Ranmaru!
Ah! How cruel of them!
I can't go out like this!
Man, they sure had no mercy at all!
Fans can be truly morbid!
Ranmaru, you can change into this.
Okay...
So? Do you think it suits me?
Oh?
Isn't that Shinobu?
You even keep his photos
on your desk at work?
Oh no, that's a Russian marquis.
Huh? A marquis?
No, this is definitely Shinobu!
I'd never forget my rival in love, alright?
This look, this feel.
He does seem a little haggard indeed,
but I can't be wrong!
As an actor,
I have an eye for these things!
Is there really no room for mistake, Ranmaru?
Do you believe that
Marquis Mikhailov is Shinobu?
Mikhailov? Where have I heard
this name before...?
Oh, I know!
We should go to that park.
They're holding a welcome party there!
Oh, is that true, Ranmaru?
Please! Take me to that party,
won't you?
I-I can't. The party is hosted by the government
and they won't let anyone in except those concerned.
Oh, really? Fine by me.
If that's your final decision,
why don't I publish
this nostalgic photo of yours?
Whoa, it really is you!
That'd make the headlines for sure!
I-I'll take you there...
That's my good boy, ever so obedient!
I’m counting on you all today. Let’s make sure
we leave a good impression on our foreign guests.
Hey, Ranmaru?
Uh?
Are these really the only roles they had?
It can't be helped—lots of other actors
in today's show are making do with minor roles too.
Playing a princess
would've suited me way better.
Sheesh, just standing here silently
is such a bore.
I wonder what this lever does...
Ah... No, you can't be pulling that...
Gimme a break! Ugh...
I did it again!
Ah! So it was you
who was behind all of this!
They've found us! Run away!
Hey! Don't let them escape!
They're the saboteurs!
Stop!
Leave this to me.
Hurry up to Marquis!
Okay. Thank you, Editor-in-Chief!
Shinobu, I missed you so much.
It's me, Benio!
Don't you remember?
I'm your betrothed!
Betrothed?
Found her!
Outrageous!
How dare she come!
I can't believe it!
Wait a minute!
She's a friend of mine,
so please don't try to restrain her.
Please follow me.
Okay...
So my husband was your...
When he saw me, he said "Malinka."
That sounds like something
Sasha would say.
Excuse me for laughing.
Malinka is the Russian word
for wild raspberry flowers.
But it also has the nuance
of "cute petite girl."
Cute little girl?
Yes. In Russia,
young men say it to approach girls.
That was probably why Sasha said it.
Well then, shall I show you the proof?
The proof?
Yes. Here it is.
The man on these photos
is not your betrothed,
but none other
than my husband Sasha Mikhailov.
I hope you'll understand.
I was wrong...
The marquis is not my Shinobu after all...
Shinobu... My Shinobu...
did die on that battlefield!
Shinobu!
When Larisa saw Shinobu, who looked exactly like her late husband, lying injured in the Siberian snow,
she took advantage of his amnesia
and started referring to him as her husband.
Shinobu!
Storms come with flowers, and when the storm finally subsides, the malinka flower will surely bloom.
For everyone in Taisho romance,
a day will come when they will finally smile.
Someday flowers will bloom for them.
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Your High Collar Lady will stay forever and ever with you, in your heart.
Our world is but a
fleeting dream of the wise.
So let us live a dream
in the Milky Way for a single night.
It's the thing that ties us together,
beyond the sky...
The End
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Thank you for sticking
with us and with Benio
through all these years and editors!
-The ex-Sorcery Party.
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing & translation checking
Special thanks
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo
Golden time Anime (vk)