Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
A new era begins. Our High Collar Lady
is determined to fight for freedom,
and while on a mission to subvert
this old mansion's way of life,
she encountered firm defense, and a resolute enemy
commander who kept giving her test after test.
Naturally, this drove Benio up the wall after
Shinobu's kindness granted Benio her first palpitation.
But then, the formidable enemy
irked her where she least expected.
Refusing to put up with it any longer,
she now faces him in a life-or-death situation,
using her tomboyish two-handed fencing!
Episode 10
Gulp Down the Medicine of Love
Oh my! He doesn't appear to be in a good spot.
How did this little girl do it?
She eluded my attack.
However, I have a real spear here against
her three-pronged stick. I simply can't lose!
I won't go on easy her for being a woman.
I'll skewer her all the same!
If a thrust lands... I might actually die.
Benio...
They're done.
W-What was that?
Well, I'll be...
Lord!
Hang in there!
Just 10 more centimeters
and my life would have been no more...
It hurts!
You monster!
Can't you be a little more gentle, huh?
I can't apply the patches
because you move too much.
Just stay still for a second.
I'm good!
No, you're not.
It's nice to take care of you once in a while!
Oh, for goodness' sake...
Getting defeated by the young girl like that...
Although, her swordsmanship
kind of reminded me of something...
Huh? What is it?
That goes back a long, long time ago.
Shinobu's father, Soichirou, was still a child.
Well done! You're strong, Soichirou!
And thirty years after that,
he abandoned Shinobu and went abroad.
Only to never come back...
That look on Benio...
It's the same as Soichirou's.
Oh...
That girl's really something!
Dear...!
Ah, quiet! Get out!
Jeez, I want to be left alone!
Heh, you're flustered.
Outta my way, go-go-go-go-go!
Hey-hey, make way, make way!
Don't blame me if you get hurt!
Hey, Ranmaru!
Come here, Ranmaru!
What happened?
Ushi!
That guy really is a weirdo.
I know, right? He always goes crazy
if the neighboring girl's involved.
Yo, Nanny, big news, big news, big news!
Oh, Ushi, you look enthusiastic.
Did you find a 200 yen coin?
Even better! You think I'd be this
happy from just finding some coins?
Let's see...
One, two, three!
Ushi!
Did anything happen to Benio?
Oh, Ranmaru! Perceptive as ever!
What happened to Lady Benio?
Nanny, you need to prepare a grand meal!
Eek!
Hey, Ushi, tell me the good news!
After many things happened,
the Boss will soon come back home!
Really?! I didn't expect it!
I know, right!
She hit that stubborn geezer with her stick
and she floored him! You should've seen it!
Whoa! That's amazing!
Hooray, Benio!
Calm down, you two!
That means Lady Benio
will surely be booted from there.
Of course, to cap it all!
Did someone call me?
In any case, we need to
give her a warm welcome soon.
Show her how happy we are to have her back!
That's true! Bring out the red rice
to celebrate this occasion, Nanny.
How foolish of her to break such
a great engagement. What a waste!
I'm so frustrated!
Oh, it's you, Benio.
Um... I need to tell you something.
I see... What is it?
So... How is the Count doing now?
Oh, so that's what this is about?
Yes!
I'm really sorry for acting recklessly!
It's not that big of a deal. He's been
tempering himself ever since he was young.
So please, don't worry about it.
But...
Rather than that, Benio,
what is it you have there?
Well, after I did such a thing to the Count...
My, Benio, don't be so worried.
If anything, he was greatly pleased by that.
Huh? Greatly pleased?
Yes, that's right!
You're kidding me...
He likes strong-arm tactics.
Oh?
I hear that's way better
for him than simple medicine.
Huh?
True, indeed.
However, due to his stubbornness, he'll never openly admit it.
Benio, you're part of
our family. Don't forget that, okay?
Now then...
Let's go back to your room.
W-What? What's wrong with my heart?
Something's been wrong
with it as of late, hasn't it?
Or so I thought...
It's you again, missy. What an eyesore.
My heartbeat's completely different now!
I'll be going, Benio.
S-Sure.
Boss Benio's Greeting Party
Excuse me, Lady Benio.
Will I have to fight her, too?
Is this for the next schedule?
It's not that.
There's a guest here to see you.
Huh? To see me?
Yes.
I wonder who it could be...
Come on...
Hey, hey! It's me!
You two never change, sheesh.
But you don't have to worry anymore.
I won't return to this house ever again, after all!
Oh, so it was you, Ushigorou.
Aye. It's me.
So what are you waiting for?
If you need something, come inside and find me.
These two damn dogs won't let me in!
I-I understand, I said too much.
Tenmaru, Chimaru,
this man is my dear henchman.
Haven't you met him before?
Jeez, how'd you ever
manage to tame them, Boss?
I didn't do anything.
They just gradually warmed up to me.
Well then, let's hurry you home before
you win over any more animals in this house.
Because I came to pick you up!
Oh...
Come on, hop in.
You must know Nanny made grilled chicken, and even
Ranmaru put his heart into making roasted potatoes!
I'm not coming home, though.
But you hit that old man on the head!
It seems that made him like me more.
I can't believe it...
But they still won't kick me out.
Then, even that stubborn
geezer got won over by the Boss...
At this rate, they'll all become her henchmen.
Like hell! This isn't real!
I'm the only henchman she'll ever need!
Then, let's go home, Boss!
I'm sorry, but my mission isn't complete yet.
What mission?
Leveling this mansion's way of life.
That's one hell of an idea! I'll also join!
I'll always be...
by your side...
Sorry, sorry.
Alright, scratch that.
So, are you sure won't come home?
Y-Yes...
Grilled chicken and many
delicious things are waiting for you!
I'm weak to food, I know...
I want to eat them!
Now you're talking!
But I'll have to abstain for now.
Gah!
Ushigorou, you go eat the chicken
meatballs and potatoes in my stead.
So you're saying that
I'll have to meet these dudes again?
Yes.
Shinobu, oh you...
Is she really the only
woman appealing to you?
What a shame.
Well, I suppose you
could always have an affair.
Insulting me right to my face...!
Is this what they call "greatly pleased," huh?!
Grandfather...
You see, men from
the Meiji era were admirable.
Very, very admirable.
Keeping multiple mistresses in his
house only made that man more adorned.
Should I add some milk?
What are you doing...?! You monster!
Oh, my bad!
I apologize on behalf of all Japanese women!
What did you say?
You...
Grandfather, times have changed.
Benio, you can leave.
How long have I been living here?
I thought I'd go away in
a snap, but it's taking so long...
Father, are you okay?
Nanny...
When it rains for long,
you always have a headache.
Take care, okay?
Ranmaru, what are you doing?
Benio!
You can't get married
to another man! Come back!
I, too, want to come back home.
What was that?
What happened? It's pretty noisy.
Lady Benio, sorry for the loud noise.
Ah, don't mind me. Did anything happen?
Yes...
Because of this rain,
the Count's neuralgia is worsening,
and it doesn't look like
it's going to get better any time soon.
Didn't you call the doctor?
Of course! I tried,
but unfortunately, he's away.
Neuralgia, huh...
My nanny went through it, too.
That's a tough condition.
If you'll excuse me.
Ah, wait.
Huh? What is it?
Do you have any geraniums?
Huh?
The Chinese medicine ones?
Yes, after that...
swertias, chameleon plants,
plantagos, aractylodes, ginseng,
red spider lilies, et cetera.
Then, could you find
them and bring them to me?
Understood.
Way to go!
Time to make my medicine!
H-Here it is!
Hanamura's special medicine!
Oh? It's so strong that it made those dogs
run away with their tails between their legs.
Whatever, it's not like I'll drink it myself.
Ugh!
Count.
W-What do you want?
I said, nobody's allowed to come in here.
It's medicine for your neuralgia.
I don't need it!
Just seeing your face is painful enough.
Go away, go away.
But it works wonders for my nanny.
Just give it a try.
Huh? W-What is that?
It's a Chinese herbal medicine.
I don't need such unscientific things!
My wife only buys
reliable medicines from Germany!
This works better on Japanese people.
Drink it and see.
W-What is this stench?
It makes me dizzy, I don't need it.
What now? Getting cold feet already?
Wh-Who's getting cold feet here?!
If you're a real man as you say,
then this medicine is nothing special, right?
G-Give it to me!
I... drank it all.
As expected!
Shut up! What's this lizard-like thing?
It's a charred newt.
It's very effective!
A-A newt...
A newt?!
Oh, Count, you're already asleep.
Oh, you're visiting him, too?
Yes.
Then I'll look after him for a while.
You can go rest, Lady Benio.
Don't worry, I'll do it by myself.
You can go to sleep.
Oh no, I could do it myself...
No, I'll do it!
Are you awake, Count?
You were sitting here all night long?
How are you feeling now?
It looks like it got better.
As I thought! Amazing!
Count...
H-How shameful!
The daughter of a
shogunal vassal healed me!
You see, Count...
It may be true, but it's from way before
the Meiji Restoration, and it's the Taishō Era now...
I know that much myself,
but I still despise vassals as a whole!
Oh?
Moreover, my wife...
Huh? She did what?
Before marrying me,
she was in love with a vassal.
Who should be my grandfather, right?
Correct.
And even after she married me,
she still won't forget him no matter what.
Count...
I was aware that I could never be
quite as handsome, so I tried to bear with it.
But she'd always keep watching wistfully into
the distance with that dreamy look in her eyes.
They say your first love
stays with you for the rest of your life.
Oh my, Dear!
Eek!
Hearing that from you...
Y-You!
Y-You heard that?
My, how shameful...
Did you really always think I was like that?
N-No, it's not...
Even after we had a son and
I was faithful to you for so many years...
How shameful. Shameful!
My love for that man is but a
beautiful memory of the bygone times.
However, I know I can't spend
my whole life living in the past.
Ever since the day we became united,
I've been living for you only.
Th-Then, you...
But you just kept focusing on
your work and treating me as a bother,
even though I...
love you so much...
Dear, what do you think about me?
Sh-Shut up!
I'll go to sleep!
You're doing it again...
He's always loved her...
That's why he hates vassals so much.
I had a bad impression of him,
but he's really a good person.
If only I could find
someone who loved me that way...
It'd be lovely. Lovely!
Huh? Shinobu?
Unthinkable!
This guy would leave out the "love" in
marrying someone and wouldn't make much of it!
So give him to me!
Whaddya want?
I won't give you anything!
Give him to me!
Wait!
A lady's heart changes like wind in a storm,
and there's nothing wrong with a High Collar Lady pursuing true love in the Taishō Era.
But where is her bluebird?
To officialize his engagement with this lassie,
Shinobu organizes an outdoor party.
But hold on. Our High Collar Lady doesn't know
any high-class manners, and many troubles await!
On top of it, all of a sudden,
a seductive maiden appeared.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Welcome to the Party of Grief"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies