Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The Ijuuins, while broke, live without a worry in the world and squander all their money.
Taking the burden all upon herself,
Benio has been looking for a job.
While her motives are commendable,
everything our High Collar Lady does
turns into a spectacular train wreck.
Despite being open to all sorts of occupations,
in the end she was left empty-handed.
All of a sudden, a shop caught her attention and she decided to become a High Collar Geisha herself.
Meanwhile, in the snow-clad Siberia,
Marquis Sasha Mikhailov and his wife Larisa are hiding from the Red Army amidst the heat of the Russian Revolution.
Coincidentally, this marquis happens to be
the spitting image of Shinobu.
Who am I really?
Dear...
What are you talking about, Sasha?
Larisa...
Darling...
Look, this was our honeymoon in Paris.
You are Marquis Sasha Mikhailov.
Tokyo
House of Flowers
Y-You'd like to become a geisha, Lady Benio?!
I'm begging you, Kichiji.
B-Boss, are you serious about this?
I need to get a job, whatever it takes.
But why a geisha of all things?
Well, if I became a geisha
I could record my own album,
or even try my luck as a model or a dancer too!
And I could take breaks whenever I want!
Dreamlike, isn't it?
She has such a carefree attitude...
So, can you grant my wish?
Please.
You sure are clueless, Boss.
Life as a geisha ain't all roses, you know?
Besides, even if they printed your posters,
I'm dead sure nobody would dare
to buy a single copy!
Besides, to be a geisha,
you need to be feminine in the first place!
Hop-hop! I got carried away!
My intrusive thoughts prevailed!
Please, Kichiji.
But, Lady Benio, you must understand that being a geisha is nowhere as easy as it seems. And besides...
Why not, Kichiji?
Madam...
It sounds like a pretty good offer.
Since this young lady is so enthusiastic about it.
What's more, she's from a good family,
so she's surely versed in traditional arts,
such as flower arrangement
and tea ceremonies.
We can send her to the parlor at once
with an easy heart.
We're chronically short-staffed, anyhow.
See?
And here's another carefree one.
It's all settled, then!
Episode 34
Good Evening
from Geisha Benichiyo
Wonderful! I've always wanted
to try on a black kimono like this one!
It looks great on you, Young Lady!
Really? Does it suit me?
Of course it does,
no two ways about it!
As the saying goes,
fine feathers make fine birds— Oops.
Ushi...!
Hop-hop! I got carried away!
Once again, my intrusive thoughts prevailed!
That seemed intentional to me!
Well then, Young Lady, why don't you dance a little
to show us all your elegance and charm?
Yes. Give me just a moment.
Ahoy, join me, ya slackers!
Oh? Was doing a loach-catching dance a bad idea?
Slam!
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Th-Then, what about singing?
That's where I shine!
I'm pretty confident.
What a blatant lie.
Well then...
A single steam whistle goes off in Shinbashi!
I've never heard someone this tone deaf in my entire life!
My train has already...
Kichiji, please give me a tranquilizer.
Here.
What should we do, Madam?
I guess we couldn't refuse her now
even if we wanted to.
Look at her, she's brimming with joy...
In that case, we could make her start
with just serving alcohol.
See you later.
We're off!
Try not to embarrass yourself, okay?
Not embarrass herself?
That'll be tough. Alright...
Benio...
This is bad! This is so bad!
U-Ushi, did something happen to Benio?
Sh-She's become a geisha! A geisha!
Huh?! That's why I wanted
to keep an eye on her...
Exactly! You gotta do something about this!
Outta my way!
Outta my way, everyone! Here I come!
Watch out, watch out, everyone!
Here I come!
Wow, what a beautiful geisha!
Man, that's one fine woman!
Whoa, you're right!
Yamato
Restaurant
Wow, how elegant...
Ouch, that hurt!
Why would anyone put a pillar in a place like this?
Take this and this and this and this!
I have no words...
Good evening.
Oh, Kichiji? I couldn't wait any longer.
Hey there, beauties!
Come closer, come closer.
Oh? So this is what a parlor looks like...
Drinking alcohol here
will be the easiest job ever!
Perfect!
Keep in mind that you'll only be
pouring it, Lady Benio.
Sure, sure.
Now then, here you go.
Hey, you go ahead too, child.
Huh? Y-Yes...
Ah, here you go.
Oh? You look like you're new here.
Yes, she is our new apprentice.
I see, I see! So what's your name, child?
I am Benichiyo, Sir.
Such a cute name, don't you think?
Unlike your face.
I'll eat you alive!
Sister, may we have a word?
You shouldn't take everything
our customers say personally.
Understood?
If there's a customer you can't stomach,
just imagine a stack of bills in his place.
Ah, I see now.
So the customer becomes a cashtomer?
I apologize for the earlier
inconvenience, Mr. Cash.
I'll pour some more for you, Mr. Cash.
It's urgent, Ma'am,
which parlor is my boss in?
She's not here.
She's with Kichiji at a restaurant called Yamato.
Huh?
Oh? My, what a beautiful child!
You don't work here, do you?
Where are you from?
Uhm... from over there.
Huh?
Wouldn't you please accept me?
Hey, Benichiyo, come pour me some more.
Sure!
Hey, Benichiyo, someone's calling you!
You are Benichiyo!
Huh?! Right, I forgot.
Here you go.
I'm sorry, I have just been hired here.
Hmm, so you're a new one?
Good to know.
Benichiyo, come back here, won't you?
Yes, I'm coming.
Well, you seem to be doing mighty well.
This is my true strength.
So here you go now.
Here you go!
Hey! Come here as well.
Sure!
A military uniform...
Stop boasting that!
Hey, something wrong?
Oh? N-No, it's nothing.
I'll pour it now.
Oh my, ever since Shinobu went missing,
I've become so intolerant of soldiers,
I'm now allergic to military uniforms.
Hey! Why do you keep on dawdling?!
Pour me one already!
Y-Yes...
Screw it!
Benichiyo!
Ah... Oh no! Sorry!
My hand moved on its own!
P-Please hold tight, Mister!
What are you doing?!
Can't you see?
A relaxing massage...
Ow, I don't think this is relaxing at all!
Benichiyo!
I got carried away...
What a terrifying geisha!
That was the final straw, you heard me?!
Spring is the time of flowers
come and see them at Mount Higashi
Oh, she never disappoints...
I wonder how long it will take me to reach her level.
On second thought,
you're actually pretty cute.
What are you doing?!
Wanna spend the night with me, Benichiyo?
So?
What do you think you're doing, you pig?!
Benichiyo!
The hell are you doing, you wench?!
How dare a geisha disobey a customer?
Geisha or not, I still have my limits!
How insolent of you!
Come at me!
Come on, bring it on!
You'll pay for this!
Whoa, things really heated up.
Keep it up! Can it get any crazier?
Benio...
Where could that parlor be?
Whoa!
Over there, Ranmaru!
That's gotta be it!
Were we too late
to prevent her drunken frenzy?
Had enough already?
Benio!
Eat this!
Get this!
Impertinent girl!
And here I thought I could've danced in her stead to help her...
Ah, Ushi...
Alright! It's showtime!
Hurry up, Madam!
What? Benichiyo flew off the handle?
There's no way a little alcohol
has such an effect on her...
One more toast.
Do you even realize what you've done, Benichiyo?!
I've had enough, I'm leaving!
I don't know how to apologize, Sir...
I'll never come again!
Benichiyo!
I'm sorry, Madam.
I... I absolutely can't stand men
who behave like that, no matter how hard I try!
I'm such an awful geisha!
I'm sorry, Madam!
C-Come on, there's no need
to be crying that much.
Besides, everyone makes mistakes
when they're inexperienced.
Madam...
EMPTY!
You've guzzled everything yourself!
Good morning, Lady Benio.
Good morning.
Um, where am I, Kichiji?
I hope you had a good rest.
I dreamed about a big commotion last night.
No, it wasn't a dream.
And here I was already relieved
it was a dream, damn it!
Madam has fired you.
With officers making up most of our clientele,
this is not the right place for someone who hates them.
That aside, you drank over three liters.
No wonder you were in a drunken frenzy.
Kichiji,
I'm sorry for putting you through all this trouble...
Don't mention it.
I knew from the very beginning
that you weren't a good fit for this role.
Moreover, could you imagine how sad Shinobu would have been if he had known you'd become a geisha?
Shinobu...
Now cheer up,
I'm going to introduce you
to a job that suits you just right.
Huh?
You heard me right.
A small publishing company asked me
to find a new employee for their ranks.
However, their editor-in-chief
is an awful misogynist.
I'm not sure whether you'll land this job...
Don't worry, I'll try my luck.
I'll do my best!
Try not to embarrass yourself this time, okay?
Thanks for everything you've done.
Good luck now.
Keep your head up.
This is what Shinobu would've wanted.
For him, I will.
It seems that the Red Army is already near.
We have to leave immediately, darling.
I'm home...
Benio, you made us worry so much
by sleeping out without warning us.
Right. I'm sorry.
So, where did you spend the night?
Well, as a geisha—
Ah, I let it slip...
Excuse me? You spent time with a geisha?
W-Well... Y-Yes. Yes.
It's good to refresh
and have fun once in a while.
Right. Nothing wrong
with hanging out with a geisha.
If anything, I'm glad to know that we've saved enough to afford such a luxury!
While we're at it, I should call the antique dealer
and buy a couple of new swords. Not a bad idea, huh?
Y-Yes... You're free to do
whatever suits you the most.
Hm?
I wanted to fix our situation,
but as a result I just ended up
encouraging the count's reckless spending...
What should I do, Shinobu?
Benio?
Countess?
I understand everything.
Huh?
You lied to us, didn't you?
You didn't actually spend time with a geisha.
In reality, you were trying
to become a geisha, weren't you?
N-No, you see...
To think that we're putting you
through all of this...
Countess!
Thank you, Benio.
Shinobu left behind such a treasure of a wife...
You're such a good wife...
Countess...
Now, let's go tell Count the truth
to deter him from his impulses.
No, Countess.
The count's reckless spending is his own way
to cope with the loss of his grandson.
So please, let him squander as much as he wants,
no matter what it puts me through!
Benio...
Okay, let us go now.
Oh, Benio. On second thought,
I'm not calling that antique dealer.
Huh?!
Well, you see, for some reason
I suddenly grew to detest swords.
I won't be buying any for some time.
Oh? Count, your newspaper is upside down.
Huh? Oh?
N-No, I just wanted to read it
like this, for a change.
Even if she's not related to them by blood,
Benio will overcome any hardships
for the sake of this elderly couple.
This is because our High Collar Lady made up her mind to do her best to replace Shinobu for them.
What awaits her in this harsh world?
Next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady
After being fired, our High Collar Ex-Geisha
is now looking for a new job,
specifically, at the place Kichiji suggested to her.
The editor-in-chief she told her about is none other than Aoe Tousei, a known misogynist,
and, given the upcoming interview,
it will definitely not be a walk in the park!
Our Hot-Blooded Lady will be put to the test!
What kind of troubles will she cause this time?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Beautiful Lies.
Don't miss it!
Episode 35
Beautiful Lies
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon