Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The time has come for our
Romantic Era High Collar Lady to leave the nest,
as her fate takes a new, unexpected turn.
She now has to move in with the fiancé someone else picked for her to learn proper etiquette.
Nobody can stop her any longer.
What's worse, Benio is greeted by a
mysterious armored warrior on her first visit.
If this is just a dream, it's definitely a bad one!
What do you want?
Hey, you!
Are you the shogunal vassal's daughter?!
W-What's this tone...
Don't stall! Answer at once!
Oh, I got it.
What did you get?
You're preparing for a festival?
Or maybe an advertisement for a new doll?
Y-Y-You insolent fool!
Does this spear look decorative to you?!
That looked painful...
You're the shogunal vassal's daughter, aren't you?
You're an enemy of the emperor!
An enemy?
Are we going back to the days
of the Meiji Restoration now?
This feels pretty anachronistic.
Being a woman won't save you.
I'll pass the judgment on you
myself to rectify the mistake!
You butcher!
Episode 7
Count, Forgive Me!
Hey, calm down. Come on, you two!
Please, relax! I'm a good guy, why can't you see?
Help me!
They wanna kill me!
Huh? Is this Boss calling out for help?
There's no time to wait!
Go-go-go-go!
Make way, make way!
Cut it out!
I told you to calm down, you damn...!
Don't you dare run away!
I'll skewer you!
Stop running away!
Are you kidding me?
What else am I supposed to do?
I got you!
Wait!
Oh, Darling...
I'm not sure if I trust this strict count.
Benio is now being taught to be ladylike,
but I wouldn't expect her to be very dedicated.
Yahoo!
Hop!
Here we go!
Wait!
What's wrong with this house?
Sure, my goal for coming here was
to raise hell and get promptly kicked out...
But the tables have turned!
Take this!
Wait...
That warrior doll wouldn't
stand a chance if I had a sword! If only...
Do they have a sword somewhere?
Sword, sword...
Ah! There's one!
I'll compensate for its size
with my two-handed fencing.
Stay still!
It's stuck!
En garde!
If I were in that armor's place...
Say your prayers!
That's it! I'm done for!
Boss!
Milord!
Did someone say "Milord" right now?
Yeah, now that you mention it...
Um... could they be referring
to this mansion's owner?
Boss, I wouldn't think so.
Nowadays, only princes,
counts and barons get called that way.
But I don't suppose this is the case.
It's likely that there could be a count.
Really?
In that case, could it be...
As mad as it sounds,
this stuffed samurai doll is...
Yes,
he is Count Ijuuin.
And I am Shinobu's grandmother.
I'm pleased to meet you, Benio.
So, you're saying...
that this guy is a count...?
Ah... M-Milord, hang on. I'm so sorry.
Oh...
T-That girl is out of her
mind, treating me like that!
To be fair, it was your own doing.
What in the world were you
trying to do, dressed like that?
Enough! Just shut up!
In any case, I'll never allow a marriage
with the daughter of a shogunal vassal!
Understood?!
So irritating!
I apologize. I had no clue that he's a count...
I'm sorry, too.
He's a genuinely good man,
but he's a little headstrong.
"A little headstrong" is
quite the understatement.
Anyways, you didn't get injured, right?
Hey-hey-hey, that's enough!
Shut up and listen, won't you?!
I don't care if he's a prince or a count,
he was still trying to murder one of his guests!
Oh, it was a misundersta—
Remember this!
If anything ever happens to Boss Benio...
I'll show you what
this goldfish tattoo truly means!
So crude!
W-Whadja say?!
What on earth are you saying to her?
You're just an oaf!
Ouch!
Moreover, why are you making such
a racket with your rickshaw over here?!
Get out of our sight right now!
Crud, I'm beaten...
Thanks for coming here, Benio.
Y-Yeah...
It's not going well.
You truly resemble your grandfather, Benio!
Your thick eyebrows, your sharp lip line,
and your masculine features, too.
Masculine features?
This stings!
At last, my long-time love...
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually turn into one again...
...will be finally fulfilled, thanks to you.
My happiness...
My first love...
Shinobu...
Will the day we marry ever come?
Impossible!
He'll marry me!
Phew...
Help!
No! Ah! Not like that!
Help me, please!
Boss! Boss!
Boss, I'm afraid of dogs!
Calm down, please!
Ushigorou isn't a bad person.
Is it so hard to understand?!
Good boys, you can listen to me.
Just like how you're
protecting the people who live here,
Ushigorou is trying his best to protect me.
It looks like they've got it.
Thank you.
Goodness! They've never
been affectionate to strangers!
Impertinent girl!
Truly, our world works in mysterious ways.
Oh?
Young Master!
Something incredible just happened.
Unbelievably, Benio easily
tamed Tenmaru and Chimaru!
Just what I'd expect from Benio.
Benio, welcome!
I knew you'd sense it in her, too.
Seems like dogs are way more
accommodating than people here, am I right?
Right... There, there.
Hey! Tenmaru, Chimaru,
look after Boss Benio while I'm not here!
I got it, I'll go away at once. Don't worry!
Boss, take care!
Benio, who is that man?
Oh, Ushigorou? He's my hen-
Ah! No way!
What did you say?
Sorry. He's my—
He's Lady Benio's devoted manservant.
Really? I'm sure I heard him say "Boss."
Well, to make it short...
In Benio's family, they use that word
instead of the usual "Sir," grandmother.
Oh, I see.
You're finally here.
H-Hello.
Honestly, knowing you,
I didn't expect your arrival.
On top of it...
This get-up!
There he goes again with the snickering.
Also, I bet you've already
caused some mischief.
What a pity that I wasn't there to watch it all.
What a pity, I'm not an Asakusa
spectacle for your amusement! Get it?
Oh?
I'm pleased to see that you two are
already playing pranks on each other!
Wait, it's not what you think!
Come on, it wasn't that embarrassing.
Shinobu, you didn't have to say that.
Yes, Grandmother.
Oh? That guy is such a grandmother's boy...
It must be because she brought him up.
They say older people
often spoil their children.
Seems like that's just the case with him!
Benio, Ms. Kisaragi is going
to assist you all the way through.
Leave her to me, ma'am.
Since the Count is from Kagoshima,
we follow those traditions.
I know that it's difficult,
but please get used to them.
I'll teach her with
great attention until the wedding day!
Blood-curdling!
Shinobu, please show Lady Benio her room.
Sure.
Um...
So your grandfather is from Kagoshima?
Yeah, you've already met him, right?
Yes, that old-fashioned dotard.
Deep down, he's not a bad person.
He's just a little stubborn
and often gets carried away.
He's completely unhinged!
He was this close to outright
spearing me back there!
No, about that...
He just wanted to intimidate you a little.
Why does he resent me?
He doesn't seem to like
that your ancestors were shogunal vassals.
During the Meiji Restoration,
Satsuma fought them to the bitter end,
even though they were both Japanese...
That happened moons ago!
It's inappropriate to fuss over it now!
Please calm down, I apologize.
I admit that even I
didn't behave properly at all, still...
I can picture this!
Hey you, just stop laughing!
My apologies.
S-So, to sum it up, after your grandmother
bade farewell to my grandfather,
she met and married your grandfather, Ijuuin,
who was a samurai from Satsuma?
That's right. After that...
Since they had a son, and so did your grandparents, their promise was passed down to their grandchildren.
So we're the chosen ones...
More or less,
but let's go easy about it for now.
Where's Benio?
Ushi...
Hey, Ushi!
Where's Benio?
Don't you understand?
She's now on the Ijuuin family's bucket.
Hey, don't jump to conclusions yet!
They're still not officially married yet!
Well, kind of.
Ushi, why are you so battered?
Two enormous lupine dogs attacked me.
Huh? What about Benio?
She didn't get injured, right?
It ended in a blink of an eye.
So, Benio...
No, the dogs.
The dogs?
That's right. Even though
they shredded my clothes,
the moment they saw the Boss,
they became docile!
At this rate, even the Ijuuins could
become as affectionate to her very soon.
No, no, that can't be!
Benio went there to
try and break her betrothal!
Well, I'm doubtful about the viability of this plan.
Destiny could already be written.
Well, it's here.
It's beautiful...
This is just like a foreign princess's room.
And he's like a prince...
Hey, what's that I'm thinking, all of a sudden?
There's also a great panorama from here.
I'm sure you'll like it.
You must be tired, so I'll take my leave.
It truly is a marvelous room.
I hate both Shinobu and this house, though!
I only like my new room!
Nice, nice!
Lady Benio.
Erm... Dinner is ready.
Please dress up.
Huh?
Do I need to get changed just to eat?
These are our rules,
so follow them and dress up!
S-Stop it!
Huh? What?
Stop, let me go!
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go!
Hurry up and get dressed!
I don't... want to... Just... let me... go!
It was tough, but we made it with style.
It was just because you forced me!
At any rate, I'm starving now.
I'd love a good dinner.
Alright, I'll eat all of it and lick the leftovers!
W-Western style? What the...
I don't know these manners!
I don't know these manners...
Wherever our High Collar Lady goes,
it turns into a symphony of laughter and romance.
But don't give up.
Destiny has many things in store!
Our High Collar Lady,
not knowing Western manners,
is catapulted into a clanking table.
Despite being on the verge of tears, the kind
Shinobu gives her a glimpse of a sweet dream,
incessantly disrupted by her table mates!
What will Benio do?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"I Won't Weep 'til I Win"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies
Ziusudra
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies
Ziusudra
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies
Ziusudra