Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Upon returning to Flowering Tokyo,
Benio found the Ijuuin household to be grief-stricken.
So she resolved all the more
to stay with the Ijuuin family for life.
The news left Ranmaru utterly crestfallen.
Meanwhile, Ushigorou was forced to recount Shinobu's last moments
to his grandparents, unbeknownst to Benio.
Benio did what she does best, holding back
her tears and devoting herself fully to work.
Today she came to Yasukuni Shrine
to interview the families of the fallen soldiers,
but, to her amazement, she also saw Count and Countess, who came in secret.
There, she realizes that while they know about Shinobu's passing, they feign ignorance.
Both petals and tears are falling.
The Spring haze covers Yasukuni Shrine.
I gotta work. I gotta do my best!
Ah, an incident!
Excuse me!
I absolutely need to pass through here!
What? Why is there a woman?
Don't get in our way!
Get out of here!
This is no place for a woman!
Smell ya later!
How naive, Akechi!
This is not enough to discourage Benio!
Whoops, my bad!
Episode 41
The Man Who Got Off the Airship
I'm first!
Mmh, I see, I see. What else?
Oh come on....
How embarrassing!
How dare a woman humiliate us?!
Yeah, it's unbelievable!
Of all the people that can come to a man's workplace,
a woman is definitely not one of them!
Well said!
What the...?!
If you guys got something to say,
don't do it behind my back!
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves?
Mind you, the Imperial University
now allows female students to attend classes.
In an era when 170,000 women nationwide are building a career,
it's regrettable that the journalists,
who are supposed to be forward-thinking,
are so old-fashioned.
N-No, actually, we...
If you're embarrassed, act like real men
and try not to get outpaced by women and children.
Wow, she sure has some guts.
I wonder where this journalist lady works.
Oh, if it isn't Benio!
It's me.
Ah, Tamaki!
Long time no see!
How are you? I heard that Compunny recently hired a female reporter,
but I had no idea it was you!
I never thought I'd meet you here.
Likewise, I thought
you went to a women's college!
Oh, you're working for Papernews? Impressive.
Not really.
Hey, how about we celebrate our reunion?
Sure! Let's have a toast!
There's so much I want to talk about!
Cafe
Spring
Hey, Tamaki!
Ah! Good afternoon.
Hey!
Do you know them, Tamaki?
They're all rising authors.
You got anything interesting?
Dear me, that's supposed to be my line.
She looks so fresh.
Is she what they call a "new woman?"
What am I, even, compared to her?
That's amazing, Tamaki!
What is?
You're still just as popular with boys.
Oh, but aren't you yourself?
I heard that your handsome Editor-in-Chief
is second only to Valentino.
Oh no, he's not in the slightest interested in that.
For your information,
he's a committed misogynist!
Besides, I...
You still can't let go of Shinobu?
Yes...
In any case, I can't help but wonder why you're surrounded by so many handsome men at all times.
I wonder if all handsome men
have weird preferences.
Hm?
Despite being this beautiful,
I've never had any luck when it comes to love!
I guess it's true that good-looking people
are not meant for each other.
So you’re not above
a drunken frenzy yourself, huh?
Life is brief
fall in love, maidens
Before the crimson bloom
fades from your lips
Before the tides of passion
cool within you,
"Fall in love, maidens?"
This song is no longer about me.
For there is no such thing
as tomorrow...
Life is brief...
Fall in love,
Hey, Tamaki, it seems you've drunk a bit too much.
maidens...
Are you okay?
Don't worry!
Hey, imagine what a scoop we could have
if a UFO suddenly showed up here!
The jaws of all those
male journalists would drop!
But UFOs aren't the hot topic yet!
What's wrong, Benio?
Ah... Th-There it is!
It's a flying saucer!
Seems like we both
had one too much tonight.
So it seems.
We're both seeing unlikely things.
Okay then, let's take a deep breath
to clear our minds.
It's still there!
Oh, screw it!
I'll make it come down now!
Whoa!
I refuse to be in this
burlesque anime any longer!
How can there be
UFOs in the Taishō era?!
Hey, take a good look, Tamaki.
That's clearly a cigar-shaped UFO.
That can't be real!
If this is a joke, it's simply not funny at all!
If anything, even airplanes
still need two wings to fly.
Unless it's spirits playing tricks on us?
That'd be scary!
What's wrong?
Th-There's someone inside.
Huh?!
Could it be an alien?
Take a look yourself, over there.
An alien...?
Shinobu...
Shinobu is on it...
What are you talking about?!
Get yourself together!
There's no way it could be Shinobu!
But it's the truth!
So, what you're saying
is that Shinobu is an alien?
That's just what I saw!
I see.
But this surely has to be a hallucination.
Let's try this, then.
We'll turn around at three.
Got it!
One, two, and...
three!
It disappeared!
We two definitely need some rest!
But don't you worry. A good night's sleep
should get us back on our feet.
Let's go to sleep!
Zzz
zzz
Excuse me, ladies!
You're not supposed to sleep in the streets!
CLUNK
A new day in the Ijuuin mansion
starts with a hangover.
Explain yourself if you please!
Ugh, I'm gonna die!
My head hurts so bad!
As much as our family has been reduced to poverty,
your behaviour is disgraceful!
After last night,
I made it home somehow...
I wonder if Tamaki
also managed to return safely.
Now then, where had I seen this thing before?
A rugby ball...
An aerial bomb...
A spaceship...
The aliens are attacking!
Eek!
Lady Benio, your contrived excuses
for not getting up are unseemly!
Now, get up at once!
No, you don't get it!
I saw a UFO with my own eyes!
Huh?
And even an alien...
Why did that alien
look just like Shinobu?
I don't know what to think of it.
No newspapers mention anything of the sort.
I guess that was really just a hallucination
from drinking too much.
Or maybe I've been so busy working these days
that I had almost forgotten about him.
That must be why he appeared
before me as a ghost.
I'm sorry, Shinobu.
I've learned my lesson.
There's no way I'll ever forget you.
It's just that I was so busy
with work and I got overwhelmed...
Compunny
What? A flying saucer?
Yeah, but not a normal one:
it was rugby ball-shaped.
And it was floating softly, just like this.
Until it disappeared with a bang!
Uh?
To sober up you should drink tomato juice,
eat a persimmon, and take a bath.
Just as I thought.
What are you doing here just blanking?!
Go pick up the manuscript
instead of slacking off!
Okay!
Edogawabata
What, a flying saucer?
Yes. Um, Edogawabata-sensei,
do you believe such things exist?
Your tea.
Certainly, and the same goes for aliens!
I knew! Ah, so I wasn't imagining things.
Good to know! This means that what I saw last night
was no dream or hallucination.
Oh, but how do you know that, Sensei?
Don't you understand, Akechi?
"The Cripple with Twenty Faces"
is just Edogawabata Sanpo's invention!
Huh?
Take a guess, what do you think I'm hiding?
Of course it's the fact that I'm an alien
from outer space myself!
Come now, Earth Defense Squad!
Yeah!
H-Huh? Leaving already?
We were just getting to the good part!
Nah, I'm not interested!
Maybe it was just a dream after all.
There are no aliens.
Oh?
How did you learn about our plan?
Actually, we are all the descendants
of a faraway planet from beyond the stardust,
the world of hermaphrodites—Transylvania!
We came to Planet Earth
to recruit beautiful girls and boys.
You look down in the dumps.
How about a trip, dear?
Would you like to enter a time warp with me?
Get a grip!
Wanna get bitten?
Ah! She was always
the most terrifying alien among us!
Somebody give me a break! At this rate,
it won't be long before I completely snap!
Aren't you still hung over?
Come to think of it, maybe I am...
I'm ba—
You're late!
I swear!
How long could it take to fetch a manuscript?!
I'm sorry.
You've been looking gloomy all day.
How about I take you to a journalist party?
You've never been to one, right?
Yeah...
Journalist club,
welcome!
Impressive!
The tobacco smoke is so dense I can't see through!
Look over there,
it could help your clouded mind.
Wow! Well said!
Amazing! I'm in heaven!
Look at that,
seems like you're finally feeling better.
I figured that’d do the trick,
given your borderline obsession with food.
He saw right through me...
That stung.
I'll go say hello to my fellow editor-in-chiefs.
Aoe is such a nice guy after all.
Well then, I shall let myself be spoiled!
Let's see, what should I try first?
Oh, guess I'll try this.
Urgh!
Mh? I grabbed it first!
The enemy is not giving in either!
Think I'll lose, you dimwit?!
Think I'll lose... To you...?!
It's you!
The impudent woman reporter from yesterday!
Ah! The rude male reporter from yesterday!
Hmph! You gluttonous woman!
First a scoop and now a chicken thigh!
For how long are you planning on crying over spilled milk?!
The only one crying is you, wench!
What? What's going on?
There's the impudent
female reporter I told you about!
Oh? She does look mighty impudent indeed.
I'd sure like to see the editor-in-chief
who was so desperate to end up hiring her!
What now? Not only they slander me,
but Editor-in-Chief as well!
Even though it was me who persuaded Editor-in-Chief to hire me, a woman.
Fine, you wanna fight?
Huh? Wh-What's going on?
I've been in a bad mood
ever since this morning anyway.
She wants to fight.
Sounds interesting.
I'm her editor-in-chief.
Huh?!
Who of you here wanted to see me?
A-Aoe...
Ah, so it was you?
Editor-in-Chief!
If you’ve got a bone to pick with my reporter,
you’ll be dealing with me.
It doesn't matter
whether you're a man or a woman,
as long as you are good at it,
you'll land this job.
Any problem with that?
Oh, uhm... No, nothing in particular... Right?
Yeah, yeah...
I get what you’re driving at now.
Well then, if you'll excuse us.
Who'd think she was the reporter
working for Aoe...
She's way out of his league.
Just what happened
to the legendary misogynist?
Editor-in-Chief...
Hm?
I'm speechless... It means the world to me
that you'd stand up for me!
No, I said nothing but the truth.
It's undeniable that you're very valuable.
Ah... What's this palpitation in my chest?
After all, you're the only woman who doesn't give me hives.
Gotta value that.
Hey, Benio,
your editor-in-chief is a dreamboat!
Please introduce him to me!
Alright.
Editor-in-Chief! Huh?
He was right here just a moment ago...
Editor-in-chief?
Editor-in-chief!
Huh? Why are you hiding here,
Editor-in-Chief?
Didn't I cure your allergy to women?
No-no-no.
I might have a fit again
if I talk to someone that beautiful.
Hmph! Now I understand!
He can stand me because I'm not pretty!
Tamaki, you must remember, right?
Huh? A UFO?
What are you saying
all of a sudden? How ridiculous!
Eh?!
So you completely forgot about it?
Truth be told…
I don't remember anything
about last night anymore.
Tell me, Benio!
Did I perhaps do something terrible and forget it?
You went crazy!
If Tamaki doesn't remember it either,
then perhaps it was just a dream after all?
Or maybe the alcohol ultimately took its toll
and I ended up getting poisoned...
Ah, I'm scared!
Should I go to the hospital?
Hey! It happened, people!
The first such event in the history of Japan.
It's an airship.
An airship landed in Tokyo!
An airship... Is that the balloon
that flies with hydrogen gas?
Yes. A little more advanced,
but that's the gist of it.
So, did anyone come on it?
Of course! On board were...
exiled aristocrats from Russia.
Moreover, it's a couple: a man and a woman!
Oh? From Russia?
Alright, let's go take a look.
It's right there.
Man, look at that crowd!
What's there?
Lemme see!
It came from the sky!
That's... The cigar UFO from yesterday...!
What do you know—the UFO that Benio saw last night was actually this airship.
But what about the alien
who was Shinobu's spitting image?
Her colleagues told her
about two exiled aristocrats being in there.
Could the man be the one
she saw on the UFO last night?
Next episode preview
Before she knows it,
Benio rushes to the exiled aristocrat,
thinking it's Shinobu who somehow survived.
However, he coldly turns her down,
saying he is Marquis Mikhailov.
Benio's heart sinks to her stomach.
After much agonizing deliberation,
she makes up her mind
and finally goes there to meet him tête-à-tête.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Oh, Taishō Romance!
Don't miss it!
Final Episode 42
Oh, Taishō Romance
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika