Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
To err is human,
but if you break a precious heirloom plate, of all things, you get the death penalty!
Seeing how the elderly Count has completely lost it,
Benio takes responsibility by smashing the rest of the plates.
For the stubborn Count, this is like pouring fuel on the fire.
So he decides that Benio must die too, now or never.
Even Shinobu, her last hope, stands idly by,
paralyzed by fear and too dumbfounded to act.
Unable to back down, in her heart of hearts the High Collar Lady curses the indifferent lieutenant.
Episode 16
Farewell, Failed Bride
Fine! Ready yourself!
Ma'am!
Benio!
Ah, stop!
W-What was that?
Count, give me a minute.
She wants to get away after all she's done?
No need to worry, Tenmaru, Chimaru.
Benio must have a plan.
What is that?!
B-Benio!
Apologies for the wait, Count.
There, go ahead and swing.
Good. I see you've prepared yourself well.
Begone, then!
H-He'll cut Benio down!
P-prepare yourself for your fate!
Father, Nanny, please forgive me for going first.
M-Madam, we need to stop him right now!
No.
Are you going to let him kill Lady Benio, then?
Do you think he'd really do it?
He is just waiting for someone to stop him.
I-I'll kill her!
Y-You won't be able to stop me,
so don't even try!
Alright, I think he's learned his lesson.
Now is the time to help a friend in need.
Go, Tenmaru, Chimaru!
Ugh, now these stupid dogs!
Don't try and stop me!
I'll split you open too!
In truth, he is relieved to be interrupted.
Grandfather, that's enough.
Huh? Shinobu?
This is none of your business!
There's no need to be so stubborn.
This duel was won in a single stroke.
Huh?!
And the one who lost this standoff
is you.
My precious heirloom plates
from Lord Shimazu...
Well played on your part, Benio.
Hey! Why did you just stand
idly by and not intervene sooner?!
I was actually scared to death there!
But you just kept watching and didn't lift a finger!
Since everyone here would rather see me dead,
I'll just take my leave!
R-Really?!
B-Benio...
I've had enough of this household. As for you...
If I'm gone, that just means you can marry someone you actually love, doesn't it?!
Benio!
You're mistaken.
Please hear me out.
Don't stop her, Shinobu!
Farewell, Lieutenant!
Ah... Wait, Benio!
Benio...
Ah! Here they come!
Right, let's get going, Ushigorou.
As you wish!
There, hop on.
Benio, wait just a minute!
Don't try stop me.
You won't be able to, even if...
I won't.
You forgot this, Benio.
Ah... My mourning dress?
That's right.
From now on, you belong to the Ijuuin family.
Should something tragic happen to
Shinobu, you'll have to wear this.
Benio...
B-Benio!
Boss?
B-Benio?
Grandmother... No, Countess Ijuuin,
I'd like to inform you of my grievances.
After all, it's because you, the Countess Ijuuin...
No, you weren't yet a Countess back then, but
long ago you were in love with my grandfather.
It's because of your naive hope of making good on that love one day
that I was made to go through this ordeal.
My father made me, who didn't know anything, bring this mourning dress
as a symbol of my vow to never remarry!
So I... I... had to spend endless nights thinking about this hopeless future that awaits me.
Please, don't try to vainly impose your own love upon your grandchildren...
Don't let it happen ever again!
Have you ever thought how much it hurts an innocent girl like me who just wants to live her life,
Countess Ijuuin?
Benio, please stop calling me Countess Ijuuin, just Grandmother is fine.
Don't say anything!
Goodbye, Countess!
Benio!
Thanks for waiting. Let's go now.
Anytime!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, you're the only ones who are sad to see me leave.
In this house, the animals are more genuine than the people, huh?
Yeah, that's it.
Tenmaru, Chimaru, goodbye.
No, you can't follow me.
You can't come.
That's an order, got it?
Here we go!
Go-go-go-go-go!
Goodbye, Tenmaru, Chimaru!
Shinobu... Aren't you going to stop me?
Please understand, Tenmaru, Chimaru.
I'm sure that everything will resolve itself, eventually.
Hyono! Hyono!
Hyono District
Boss, it's such a lovely day!
We gotta raise a toast!
Why? Why didn't Shinobu do anything?
Hey! Don't let Benio drink any alcohol!
She's an angry drunk!
But it really is a day to remember!
Then let's celebrate it with some anmitsu.
Huh? Anmitsu?!
Gee, Ranmaru, how girly can you really be?
Ah, you're mistaken. I may have the body of a boy, but I have the soul of a true Japanese lady:
poised and elegant, like a pink carnation.
Tsk. You're just not right in the head.
And I'm a woman, both in body and soul.
We summoned her!
Famous bean soup
Renowned onigiri
Tsk. No matter how much of this jelly I eat, I'm not feeling any better.
Oh?
Boss, something wrong with your stomach?
No, not at all.
I got it! You won't be able to cheer up
until you down it with booze, ain't that it, Boss?
Ow-ow!
Ushi, won't you please let that Pandora's box remain shut?
But he's right - relying on anmitsu to cheer me up
at a time like this is just wishful thinking.
I know, right?
I said cut it out!
Sister! They serve great anmitsu here.
Hurry up, sister!
Oh...
Oh crap. This is "oh crap" big time!
U-Ushi...
Oh, the tea stalk is floating upright. A good omen!
Here, now.
Praise be the Lord.
Ma'am, what good things
are going to happen today?
Congratulations, Miss Kichiji
of the House of Flowers.
Why are you congratulating me?
It's finally your time to shine.
I surrender Young Master Ijuuin to you.
Excuse me now.
Ah! Lady Benio!
H-Huh?
Ushi, pay our bill, will you?
Benio!
Could you please tell me
what on Earth happened?
Get this, their engagement
came apart at the seams!
What did you say?
Ma'am, I left our payment here!
Thank you very much!
Excuse me, may I use your telephone?
Sure.
Excuse me.
In 1906, the number of telephone service subscribers exceeded 180,000
and only kept growing from that point on.
Hello, may I please speak to Count Ijuuin?
In the aftermath of the Great Kanto Earthquake, sales exceeded 870,000 units in 1925.
Hello, this is the Ijuuin family...
Oh, it's you?
Master Ijuuin, is it true that your engagement to Benio has been broken off?
How did you know that?
By chance. I ran into Benio.
But are you sure
you should let go of a lady such as her?
Benio seems to have a certain misconception on your account.
Well, that explains everything!
Lady Benio nearly burst into tears when she saw me and said she concedes you to me.
A nobleman and an ignoble geisha like myself?
I know better than anyone
that such a union is unrealistic at best.
But no matter the reason, how can you make such a well-meaning lady cry?
I can't explain it now,
but I'm sure, before long,
you'll understand it yourself.
Hold on!
Y-Y-You did what?!
Yes, I'm free again. Rejoice!
But the tea stalk was upright... Upright...
Hey, bring me some tea!
Tea!
Hey! I told you to bring me some tea!
What's wrong with you?
And all those long faces?
If you got something to say, I'm all ears!
There was never any doubt
that we'd kick her out!
If anything, Benio was never
a good fit for our family!
And she destroyed all of my precious plates!
You three! If you have anything to say, go ahead!
K-Kisaragi, if anyone understands
me here, it would be you.
Right? That girl couldn't be reasoned with
and only ever kept giving you trouble, right?
Yes, you are correct.
O-ho! So I thought. Don't be shy and say aloud everything you've held back so far.
Okay. In all the years that I've been working for this household, never have I met anyone quite like her.
Well said!
So, what did she do?
She was the first ever person who didn't give in to your obstinacy.
I've followed you through a lot of difficulties myself,
so I already know we'll never meet anyone else like that.
Yes, that's true.
With Benio's arrival, I felt that things
would never be the same again.
I've been the one who changed the young master's diapers throughout his babyhood.
So I entertained the thought that Benio and the young master would have a child at some point,
and at that point in the future, good health permitting,
I would still be working for you and singing lullabies to that child.
I've spent many happy moments fantasizing about it.
If Benio had a child,
they'd be our great-grandchild, Dear!
Great-grandchild, eh?
But now that child is destined not to be.
Yes, this is also his fault.
S-Silence! Stop talking like I killed that goddamned child myself!
Shinobu!
Y-Yes?
Get moving!
What the hell are you waiting for?
I-Isn't Benio your fiancée?
Hurry up and bring her back!
L-Lord!
This means...
I knew you'd say it.
But you don't often let yourself get swayed by others,
so I've been waiting for you to realize you miss her presence, and admit it by saying those very words.
I'll take my leave.
Giddy-up!
I'm so relieved to see that you've changed as well. It's because of Benio, isn't it?
The Meiji Era is long over.
Oh, really?
Refill!
Please consider stopping,
it was your fifth one!
Why not, Nanny?
Your grilled chicken is one of the reasons I couldn't wait to return!
Please don't make it sound like it's something I should be proud of! Oh dear me...
What is your father going to say?
Getting kicked out before
even tying the knot...
I feel so bad for your mother...
Oh well, I can't say I didn't have a feeling something like this would happen.
What's with you? After all that time I spent away, at least pretend you missed me.
I bet she wants to discuss everything that happened while I was away.
Ah...
Shinobu...
We will never meet again...
You see, I happen to be in love with the young master.
No, I don't care about that womanizer anymore!
Ah! Could it be that Shinobu came for me?
I'm home.
What a bummer, it's just Dad.
What? Benio came home?
Yes, that's what happened.
Benio.
Oh! Welcome home, father!
Oh? I think you've gained some weight
since the last time I saw you!
Oh? You think so?
I slimmed down!
F-Father...
Benio, follow me.
Is it true that you got kicked out?
Ah! Not at all, it's just a misunderstanding, father.
What? So you didn't get kicked out?
I see! That's a relief!
Right. You can relax. I wasn't kicked out; I left of my own accord.
Oh, I see, I see.
Wh-What?!
How is that any different, you halfwit?
B-But, you don't know the whole story!
Living there was like living in a haunted house!
What are you saying? The Count's family lives there, so it can't be haunted!
Quit saying nonsense!
Oh no, Mr. Hanamura, the Count by all means is a crazy geezer.
A-Are you that infamous lady who's crazy about men?
Oh no, it's just me!
Ra-Ranmaru, is that you?
Yes. It's been a while, Mr. Hanamura.
What's that disgracefully effeminate look doing on a proud son of Japan?
Oh? So you're saying I look lovely?
Hey-hey-hey... Back off! You nauseate me!
I'll have nightmares tonight.
Well, how else could I stay by Benio's side?
By her side?!
Yes, we even slept in the same room.
I was so happy...
Wh-What's this now?
Benio!!! What is this disgraceful behavior?!
Y-You misunderstand, Father!
What did I misunderstand?
Misunderstandings, misunderstandings...
Here we go, I stacked these!
What did you say?!
Geez, Father, you still don't understand?
I understand enough.
Benio.
Do you know why I gave you this dagger?
Even after finally parting ways with the stubborn Count,
life is still unbearable—was leaving worth it after all?
Outside and even inside her own home,
Benio is surrounded by obstinate geezers.
Although Benio left Ijuuin's mansion to go back home,
her stubborn old-fashioned father can't accept it.
With no other choice, she runs away to wander the four corners of the world.
Little does she know that alcohol is a bad partner to vent your endless frustrations with.
In a drunken frenzy, the flower blooms in disarray.
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady: "Petals of a Wandering Flower."
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Chika
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Chika
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Chika
JmePenseBon