Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Make way, you there,
here comes Benio!
She comes to confront the despised Lieutenant Colonel Innen.
Meanwhile, the Lt Col himself only has Buddha to rely on
as he holds onto that bathroom stall door for dear life.
How can this weakling be in the military?!
Instead, without realizing it, Benio meets
the division commander and explains the situation to him.
Being the man with a big heart he is,
Lieutenant General Okouchi
is saddened to inform them that once an order is enacted, there's no taking it back.
When it's finally time to say goodbye,
their hearts become one for the first time.
Benio swore to herself that,
once Shinobu comes back alive and well,
she will be his wife for good.
But until then,
alas, the cruel destiny
decided to split their paths.
Oh, right. I have to learn to behave
like a proper woman before Shinobu returns.
Oh, pardon me.
I didn't realise I was in your way.
Go ahead.
Oh, thank you.
Yahoo!
Huh?
Wait! I need to behave myself from now on.
!oohaY
Oh, my apologies!
Wasn't this wrong as well?
Episode 26
Behave Like a Woman and Quit Drinking!
This mansion feels empty without Young Master, don't you agree?
You're right...
What's worse, there's something wrong with Benio...
I don't know why,
but she's been acting eerily.
Oh, she's just like me!
Shut up!
Ouch...
I wonder if she ate something weird.
No, that is just how a woman
in love for the first time acts.
I want a passionate romance!
I'll go men-hunting now.
Ow, ow!
T-Tea... c-calms your mind...
A-And is a true... cure-all...
Ugh, I can't take it anymore!
Ow! That hurt...
An impatient apprentice
never becomes a master.
A flower is able to project its own arranger's heart in its purest form.
So, Lady Benio, follow your heart.
Oh, okay, I'll do just that.
Finished. Not too shabby if I do say so myself.
When will you stop making fools of other people?
Enough!
What if I do it like this?
Why is it so hard...
to be feminine?
Nevertheless, I'll do my best!
When Shinobu returns,
I have to be a changed woman.
Still,
I wish I told him how I feel, after all.
I just couldn't bring myself to say anything.
One way or another,
I have to confess...
Done and dusted.
Tell me, Boss, where are we goin'?
C'mon, at least say something!
Boss!
Oh? Boss! Boss!
Special edition!
Special edition, everyone!
Oh? How unusual.
Special edition!
May I take a look?
Sure! Only five sen!
Have some shame!
I'm suffering here, you know.
And yet you're out here,
trying to profit from a serious matter!
Rude! So rude!
I get it! I get it, alright?
Here.
The Imperial Army goes to Siberia to help the Czechoslovak Legion!
After the 5th Division, the 13th Kokura Division is to follow.
Boss! The 13th Kokura Division—
isn't it Shinobu's?
Departure on August 13th
August 13th...
They've boarded the ship already...
Siberia...
Shinobu went to Siberia...
Hail Mary, full of grace, the Lord is with you
In August 1918,
troops were dispatched from all over the world, including Japan,
to help their ex-allies
in the revolutionary civil war in Russia.
That would mark the beginning of a protracted war of intervention that would last four years.
Benio.
take care of Grandfather and Grandmother while I'm away.
Not only them, but also Tenmaru and Chimaru.
They wouldn't accept food from anyone else.
Oh, poor me... What should I do?
Shinobu...
It's my fault that they sent you to Kyushu.
And now they're sending you
to the Siberian battlefields too.
Siberia is a cold place...
Full of dangerous animals like wolves.
Will you be fine?
Won't you get hurt?
Oh, I'm worried...
I'm so worried!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen
definitely knew all about this.
He knew that the Kokura division
would go to Siberia next,
so he purposely transferred Shinobu...
Ah, what a gutless excuse for a man!
Right, this isn't the time to weep!
Oh, are you going out, Lady Benio?
Please be safe!
He sent my Shinobu to that place!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen,
we'll talk face to face now!
Imperial Army First Division
Excuse me!
Hey! What do you want?!
Hey!
D-Don't try to stop her!
I want to have a talk with the Division Commander!
So sorry, but we don't have the authority
to address him directly...
No excuses! Get me to him!
Yes, ma'am!
Hello? Hello!
What? Hanamura Benio?
Tell her I'm away. Got it?
Uh-huh.
Don't you dare pretend you're not here!
No, no, I didn't mean to do that...
Uh, coffee or cocoa, which one do you prefer?
Uh-huh?
I'll go with cocoa...
Never mind! I don't want anything.
You're not going to buy me off with food and drinks!
Let me meet Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen!
Let me meet him!
Let me meet him! Let me meet him!
Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen's not here, uh-uh...
Then make him come here!
Well, I can't do that either, uh-uh.
How come?
He has been transferred to Manchuria, uh-uh.
To Manchuria?
Yes.
Why was he transferred?
Well, you see, uh, on top of the Ijuuin case, you know, there were many rumors about him, uh-uh.
So this is why he's there?
Uh-huh, yeah.
I've had enough of your uh-huh-huhing!
Is this really the only thing the Imperial Army is good for?
Uh-huh-uh? Oh-huh-ho!
W-W-What?
Speak clearly!
However... uh... even if I do something... well, uh...
Too wishy-washy!
You see, uh, if anything happens to Shinobu,
I, uh, well...!
Uh, but like, you, uh...
Slimy
Uh-uh! Well!
Quit mimicking me!
But, uh...
Uh-huhing and oh-hoing is my shtick!
Uh-oh! I've unconsciously started to do the same!
Uh-uh, well...
Can't you stop?
Sir!
However... well, uh...
Aye-aye-aye! Uh-uh-uh! Aye-aye-aye!
You can't talk entirely in that!
Uh-huh... Oh-ho! Uh-uh... Aye-aye!
Uh-uh... Aye-aye-aye!
Uh-uh!
Huh?!
Lieutenant General!
I bit my tongue.
Heh! I won!
It's no fun, though.
I still need someone to vent my anger on.
Eat it!
I surrender, alright?
So anticlimactic...
Think you can have fun while I don't?
Eek!
Whoa!
Wh-Why did you do this?
Ah, you're barbaric!
What have I done to deserve this hate?
Monster! Demon!
You think I hate you?
You're right!
I despise everything alcohol-related!
Take a look: this is the face you have.
Why so rude? You know how much
of a narcissist I am!
Well, what can I do?
Blame alcohol, not me!
Hey, Boss! I got myself some good one!
Wanna have a toast?
How does that sound?
Don't try to make me relapse!
Guess she doesn't need to be drunk to be violent.
I have to do something about this...
I just can't sit still right now.
Young Lady.
Young Lady!
You could make a tea vow or a salt vow.
Uh? A tea or salt vow?
Yes.
What are those?
Well, you make a wish to the gods
and in exchange,
you sacrifice your strongest food habit.
Stop consuming that thing completely.
When you were still a baby yourself,
you got a serious case of measles.
So, since your mother truly loved tea,
she swore to the gods that she would abstain from drinking it
and asked them to help you recover.
So it's a tea vow because you can't drink tea?
Yes. Back in the day, people used do to this for their loved ones,
metaphorically sacrificing for them.
Oh! I get it!
Huh? A headstand?
No, not that.
Abstinence
Not headstand, but abstain.
I'll quit drinking. Once and forever.
God, Buddha, I beg you.
Abstinence
Please protect Shinobu.
In exchange for your kindness, I will try to abstain from drinking alcohol with all my heart!
Shinobu... this is all I can do for you...
Banzai!
To our brave heroes, banzai!
Hey, listen, Benio!
Benio...
Huh?
Forgive me, Shinobu...
Benio, there's a huge lantern procession outside! Wanna see it?
They're wishing our army success in Russia!
What? Lantern procession?
I'm not interested in that stuff.
Huh? Now that's rare...
What happened to her?
Even if she didn't know what was going on,
she would always go and steal someone's lantern.
Banzai! Dunno what this is for,
but all the best to everyone!
Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai!
But now she's like this...
Come on, wake up! You're going to miss the lantern procession!
Buzz off!
Go away! I told you I don't care!
Whoa!
You're strange!
Uhm...
Hang in there!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Lady Benio, the Count wants to see you.
It's Benio.
Did you want to see me?
Oh, good thing you've come.
Here's to our army's ultimate victory.
I thought you'd wanna join too.
Now, hold this.
It's sweet potato shochu sent from Count's homeland - Kagoshima.
Here you are.
If you drink, you do it with this kind of cup.
Today is a special day, isn't it?
Help yourself, now.
Uh, a-actually..
You don't like it?
Ain't no way you'll refuse a drink.
I know you too well. Now, bottoms up.
We're drinking to Shinobu's safety.
At least take a sip if you don't want all of it.
O-Oh, but...
So you're saying you don't want to drink to Shinobu's safety?
No, I would never!
It's unthinkable.
Why are you vacillating and not drinking, then?
The tea vow and the salt vow come from the innermost part of your soul. It's a sacred promise to yourself.
So if you chatter about it to other people,
it's not going to work.
I-I'm sorry, I just can't allow myself to drink it.
Hey! Does this sake taste worse to you somehow
if it's for Shinobu's safety?!
Oh my, don't take it personally
over a mere cup of alcohol.
I'll excuse myself now.
Wait, Benio. Since you came,
you could at least eat some sushi with us.
It's delicious sushi.
Now we're talking!
Help yourself.
Wow, it looks amazing!
Thanks for the meal!
It reeks of alcohol so much!
As it should be. It is sake sushi, a specialty from Kagoshima.
It's made with sake instead of vinegar.
People who can't hold their liquor
get drunk with it.
In Kagoshima, we always make those
for celebrations and festivals.
It has propitious effects!
Come on now, eat some.
I-I just can't.
I'll excuse myself.
What about some cake, then?
What? There's always time for cake!
Here you are.
Bon appetit!
Even this smells of sake, somehow.
This is savarin—there is always plenty of rum in it.
Rum? I-I can't eat this.
Then, what about some bonbons?
Wow, amazing!
These are whiskey bonbons.
Whiskey?
I just can't have good things!
G-Goodbye.
What's with her?
It's not like Benio to pass up treats...
Let's hope no natural disasters happen.
Abstinence
Soldiers this, soldiers that...
Stop boasting it!
Get this!
That's right.
If only I didn't get drunk that day...
I've loved you...
...all this time.
Don't worry about that.
I've chosen to spend my life with you,
so I'm willing to face with you
any curveballs fate throws your way.
Oh no. I'm such an idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
I've made an irreparable mistake!
Excuse me.
Huh?
You're crying?
Who cares!
Boss, you've got a letter.
I don't want to read that!
Don't bother me while I'm mourning!
But it's from Second Lieutenant, you know.
I don't care if it's Shinobu or anyone else,
just let me grieve in peace...
Huh?
From Shinobu?
Aye. 'Tis right.
She was crying until a few moments ago,
but now she's smiling broadly!
What will Benio find written
in this sudden Pandora's letter?
Her heart is racing like crazy,
but what awaits her?
Happy news or a sad notice?
We can't wait for that seal to be broken!
Next episode preview
Benio opens her first letter from Shinobu,
filled with emotions sent from a far-off land.
Ah, how sweet, yet heartbreaking.
Meanwhile, Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen
keeps on plotting against Shinobu,
fixing him up with some of the most unruly soldiers out there.
Nothing wrong with accepting a fight from another man,
but this is a real battlefield now, in the hostile Siberia.
Next time on "Here Comes the High Collar Lady":
Red Sunset in Siberia.
Don't miss it!
Episode 27
Red Sunset in Siberia
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
JmePenseBon