Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
After a night of excessive drinking and brawling,
our High Collar Lady is exhausted,
So she nodded off, snoozing peacefully
on Shinobu's back.
A gentle breeze of romance
blows between the two betrothed,
and even the stubborn Count, who previously opposed it, is finally placated.
But don't get relaxed just yet!
For through a quirk of fate,
the bill for the last night's rampage is sent to an unexpected villain, who doesn't take it lightly.
What kind of devilish form
will his revenge against Shinobu assume?
Shinobu ❤ Benio
That'd be a shame, though...
Agreed. I'd like to write my own name here.
Good grief...
No matter how you look at it,
we're way more charming
than Lady Benio, aren't we?
That's right! People's destinies are a sad thing...
We still gotta look out for our chance!
What's this? We've known each other
for all our lives, so there's no way she ends up with him!
Like this...
Ranmaru ❤ Benio
Fixed it!
What are you so worried about,
O willow by the river...
Oh?
Well, it's not like I don't get
Ranmaru's feelings...
But if someone from the mansion sees it,
they'll make a fuss.
Let's retcon it like this, just in case.
Ushigorou ❤ Benio
But that could get Boss in trouble...
Well, let's change it
to something more harmless.
Ushigorou ❤ Kisaragi
We'd sure be a quarrelsome couple
if that happened!
Ushigorou ❤ Kisaragi
Oh my!
Oh, how did it come to this?
But I'd feel bad if I destroyed that man's cherished dream.
Let's pretend it's not here.
Episode 20
Who Are the Two Under the Love Umbrella?
How shameful, getting all these love letters...
Oh, more love letters for Shinobu?
That's right. They keep on coming every day.
Have you ever seen a playboy like him?
Benio, wouldn't it be best for you to simply give up on someone as incorrigible as him?
So, does he also read them every day
and answer each one?
He doesn't even look at them
and tosses them straight into a bin.
Then how is it any different
from not receiving them at all?
How forgiving can Benio really be?
What's worse, she's defending Shinobu now?
I gotta watch out!
May I?
Hey, Ranmaru. I mean, Ranko.
Your mail.
Here.
Throw them away for me.
As you wish.
Ah, hold on a second.
There, throw the rest.
May I help you with anything else?
Nope.
Yes, fine by me.
Then, tomorrow at three, at our usual place.
"Tomorrow at three, at our usual place..."
This is bad!
Not too shabby, considering it's mine.
B-B-Benio! It's awful!
Ah! Oh no!
It was my masterpiece!
I can arrange all the flowers you want later,
there's something more important right now!
Shinobu just called one of the love letter senders
and appointed a date!
Oh? But didn't you say
he doesn't read any of his love letters?
He made an exception for this one!
We gotta act!
And who was the sender?
I didn't catch that.
I only play detectives sometimes...
Then it might just be a completely harmless letter,
where the sender is a man.
No!
It was definitely a woman,
I have a hunch.
A woman's intuition never errs.
I'm sure. I must be right!
A woman's intuition, huh?
One way or another, tomorrow at three,
he is seeing this sender at their usual place.
He even said "at their usual place," you hear?
But if you keep fretting over every little thing like that,
there'll be no end to it!
Maybe. But I've already made up my mind to protect you in everything, so just leave this to me!
R-Ranmaru...
Jeez, I can't tell if he's
a girl or a boy myself sometimes.
Now, then. Let's try again from scratch.
Tomorrow at three, at our usual place...
Shinobu... You're meeting a man, right?
That's right. It's got to be a man.
Even though you keep receiving tons of letters from women...
Lady Benio, you've got a call.
Oh? For me? Who is it?
You'll understand once you answer it.
Ah, really?
Who could it be? Probably Nanny.
But it might as well be Tamaki.
Hello? Hanamura Benio is here.
Hello, this is the head teacher
at the Atonashi School for Girls.
What now?
It's just you, teach?
Well, sorry I'm "just a teacher!"
No, I didn't mean it like that...
Hanamura, your recent absence from school is worrying. Are you feeling unwell by any chance?
N-No, it's just that more and more matters
keep besieging me lately.
In that case I think it'd be better for you
to also start tending to your attendance.
Frankly speaking,
with grades that are as abysmal as yours,
if this attendance trend continues, I cannot exclude the worst by the end of this academic year.
What do you mean by "the worst?"
You'll fail the class!!
U-U-U-Understood!
I'll be there on the dot from tomorrow onwards!
Dear me...
I got behind on so much homework...
Benio? Still not coming to bed?
You have to be ready by three tomorrow, remember?
I'm not worried about Shinobu's affairs.
But this homework, I can't leave undone.
Should I help you out?
English, Math, History, Religion, Science and Writing, which one can you do?
Have a good night!
Pathetic.
And... Hm... Maybe this?
And this? Good. Next.
What's this?
Okay.
Finished!
I've done all of my homework in one night!
I feel so good!
Are you sure you'll make it by three?
Still worried about that?
It's all fine!
Ah! I'll be late if I don't hurry.
Good morning.
Hey.
Kisaragi, I'll skip the breakfast today,
I need to hurry to school.
But I've done all of the homework! Look!
You do know it's Sunday, don't you?
If the other party is meeting him there at three,
Shinobu will probably leave around two.
I suppose.
Then I need you to follow Shinobu closely.
Don'tcha think it'd be better if I grabbed him by the lapels, and asked directly,
"Who're ya meeting at three?!"
Until he just blurts it out? Ugh...
You've no notion of delicacy.
Hm? Lotion?
Nah, all those fancy oils are for women.
Don't worry, it's all for Benio's sake.
Or are you saying that you don't care
about Benio's well-being?
Hell no! Say it again, I dare you!
If there's ever someone who hurts Boss,
I, Ushigorou, will see to it personally
that he gets his just deserts!
You're gonna strangle me! Let go!
Ah, my bad...
Then do you realize that we need to ascertain Shinobu's true persona now for Benio's sake?
Really? Alright, gotcha.
If so, you stay here until it's two,
then you shadow Shinobu wherever he goes, got it?
If it's for Boss, I'ma do everything!
Don'tcha doubt me!
Good.
Been a while since I last went shopping!
At times like this, going out to relax is what the doctor ordered.
I might go to Minatoya in Gofukubashi.
In 1913, the artist Takehisa Yumeji opens his print shop Minatoya in Gofukubashi,
which was wildly popular among young women.
I might be able to see
Takehisa Yumeji's newest work.
Just you watch.
I'll catch that Second Lieutenant by the tail.
Ah, Boss...
Won't you take me to Gofukubashi?
Aye-aye.
I meant to say...
Tough luck! I can't...
Let's go, Ushigorou.
You know, actually, I, uhm...
Why the holdup?
No, right... Thing is...
Lady Benio, I'm not sure if I should say it... Ahem.
Oh? If there's some reason for it, just say it.
Nuffin' serious, really!
Then start moving already!
Aye-aye.
Here we go...
Ushigorou, can't you speed up a bit?
Sure, sure, sure!
What's wrong?
Did you suddenly turn into an Edoite?
Aye-aye.
Dammit, it's all or nothing now!
He's finally going out.
Ushi!
Where did he go now?
Hey.
Are you looking for someone?
R-Right, d-did you see Ushi?
Ah, if you need Ushigorou,
he left with Benio a little while ago.
That dumbass.
Well then, I'll be going too.
Ah... I'll go with you!
Ranko. Ranko!
Oh, come on...
Thank you, Ushigorou.
I'll come back on my own later, so you're free for today.
Alright.
By the way, what time is it?
Hm, should be about three, I think.
Weirdo.
Shinobu and Kichiji...
At three, he's meeting someone...
There's no way...
Shinobu is cheating on me!
Even though I trusted him...
I trusted him!
This is wrong.
Why am I acting so timidly and hiding here?
That's right, I should step out boldly
and tell them what I think!
But what should I say when I confront them?
"So... Hello there!"
Or maybe, "I'm lucky to be able
to see you two together today."
Ugh, no, it has the same ring to it as a wedding ceremony speech.
How about...
Do you prefer Paris or London?
"The Moon Cried" or "The Cuckoo?"
Football or soccer?
Oh, suit yourself then!
No, this won't work.
Or maybe...
Maybe get straight to the point?
Hey!
Never mind
Never mind, never mind.
Never mind...
Never mind
Never mind, never mind, never mind!
Panicking
Ah, I... I-I can't stop anymore!
Ah, make it stop!
Ugh! I can't stop!
Never mind
I can't stop! I can't stop!
Panicking
Whoa!
Hey, stop it, stop!
Whoa, stop, stop, stop! Stop!!
Young Master...
Yeah?
Did something happen
between you and Lt Col Innen?
Lieutenant Colonel​?
When he invited me
to the tatami room the other day...
Does Second Lieutenant Ijuuin
come here often?
Yes, he is our regular customer.
Huh. Don't you know that he has a fiancée?
Ah, is that so?
Moreover, she is the daughter of Major Hanamura.
Lieutenant Colonel​ said that?
I see.
So something did happen, after all?
Well, yes. But it's not that big of a deal.
Please watch yourself.
The Lt Col I know doesn't forget grudges easily.
And he wields an enormous influence
at the Ministry of War.
If he takes it so far
as to do something irreversible...
It won't happen.
I'll be fine.
Even someone like
Lieutenant Colonel​ can't be sour
over a trifle like that forever, I think.
I appreciate your concern, though.
Young Master!
What could they be talking about?
I can't hear.
If something were to happen
to Young Master, I...
Please accept my apology.
I said something improper.
Kichiji...
Thank you.
So those two...
Really do have an affair!
Young Master!
Kichiji, let's not make a scene
and just go separate ways.
It is customary among men to say that to geishas.
But I'd have preferred it
if you simply commanded me to die now.
Kichiji, please forgive me.
I now have a fiancée that's been imposed on me.
She's pug-nosed and too ugly to look at,
but I have to endure this for my grandmother.
Ah... Young Master...
Kichiji...
Stop it!
Stop!
Go away!
You hear? Stop! Hands off! Ugh...
Stop...
Oh, that was just a dream?
I guess I'm so concerned about those two,
I even see them in my dreams.
But why am I concerned that much about it?
That's right, if it's my dream, I can direct it wherever I want. So let's have sweet dreams instead.
Good, good! Ranmaru, set the mood!
Please forgive me.
I now have a fiancée that's been imposed on me.
She's pug-nosed...
Cut! Cut, cut!
I really don't like that one line.
Change the script!
Start!
Please forgive me.
I have a wonderful fiancée that I love deeply.
She's pretty, she's smart,
wholesome all around.
I don't deserve a mademoiselle such as her.
Young Master...
I don't want to see you ever again.
Let's forget everything that happened
up to now and cut all ties.
I see. If she is as wonderful as you make her out to be,
then I clearly can't hold a candle to her.
I shall gracefully step aside.
Oh... So you do understand?
Yes. But in return...
In return?
Please let me see how splendid she really is
with my own eyes.
Fine. I can do that.
Benio!
Aye-aye!
Somebody called me?
Didja call for me?
Enough!
Why is it me who has
to play the bumpkin every time?
No matter how you look at it, they're two beautiful people, who'd make a perfect couple.
She's a way better fit for him in every way!
The one snuggled up under the Love Umbrella with Shinobu, who is it going to be at the end of the day?
Which one of them will get the last laugh?
Nothing is lost yet if High Collar Lady doesn't leave this matter to chance like she did in her dream.
In the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Asleep or awake, Benio can't drive Shinobu and Kichiji out of her mind,
to the point where her appetite is long gone.
Does she only has herself to blame for being too trusting, or her adulterous husband too?
At the end of a long string of worries,
Benio finally makes up her mind.
Next time in Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Life is Short, Yet Riddled with Worries. Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika