Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Even though Benio was set on trying to learn the ways of femininity while Shinobu is away from home,
all of a sudden, he's deployed to Siberia.
Assuming that this was yet another scheme of Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen,
she once again headed
to the 1st Division headquarters.
However, she was surprised to discover that Innen had also been transferred to Manchuria.
With nothing else she could do, she decided to pray for Shinobu's safety
by promising not to touch any more alcohol.
Abstinence
But for some strange reason, the Count and Countess
were in the mood to do nothing but drink that day.
So abstaining proved very depressing,
but then she received
her first letter from Shinobu.
What could be waiting inside?
Shinobu!
Oh no! T-That's too much!
Oh?
Oh my!
You've suddenly grown so handsome, Ushigorou!
Feelings sure work in mysterious ways!
Yours is a special case, Boss.
Hey, hey! A letter from Young Master arrived!
My, how wonderful!
So, what did he write?
I-I don't know...
Ah, I'm so curious!
I know, right? I can't be thinking about work at such a time!
It's...
over.
Hey, Boss! Aren't you gonna read it?
A letter from Shinobu... A letter from Shinobu!
A letter from Shinobu!
Yahoo!
Shinobu!
Episode 27
Red Sunset in Siberia
Benio...
Benio!
You got a letter from Shinobu?
Yes.
W-What did he write?!
Alas, I haven't read it yet.
Hurry up, let me see it!
Dear...
Hm, what is it?
He sent that letter to Benio, not to you.
Please be patient.
Aye, aye.
She's right.
Even I'm waiting patiently.
Why didn't he send me one?
I apologize. I'll let you know as soon as I read it.
This letter is for my eyes only!
Lady Benio! Lady Benio.
Is that the letter you've received
from Young Master?
I can't do it while that monstrosity is staring at me.
I'm not in the mood anymore!
Uh-oh! Oh...
Does she think me too ugly an audience?
I wonder what he wrote to me... Ah, my heart is racing!
C-Count!
Benio!
Whisper it just to me!
O-Okay...
C'mon, open it up already!
R-Right...
Maybe later!
H-Hey! I should be the first one to know!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
S-Someone help me!
Futon Room
This looks like a good spot.
I knew you would come here!
I'm so tired of this!
Well now, hurry up and read it to me!
Sorry!
Wait! B-Benio!
I should be the first to know!
A-An earthquake?
Wham!
Where are you, Lady Benio?
Come on, Lady Benio,
show me the letter!
I've had enough!
I guess I have to do it outside...
Oh!
Lady Benio!
Read the letter to us!
Did he write anything to us?
Lady Benio!
Anything about me?
What about me?
Or about us?
What's the deal with everyone?
This letter is for me!
Gimme a man!
Show it!
We want to read it!
I just need a quiet place,
or else I'll never read it!
Oh, I forgot about one place that could work!
Too late.
Sh-Shinobu...
Benio.
I've chosen to spend my life with you.
So I'm willing to face with you
any curveballs fate throws your way.
Shinobu... Don't joke like that!
I've loved you ever since we first met.
Shinobu...
You haven't left my mind
ever since you told me those words.
Ah! My letter!
Ah! Stop!
I said stop!
Here I come!
There!
Wait!
Wait, you two!
Tenmaru! Chimaru! Give it back!
Hey! Hey, wait!
Come on! Tenmaru!
Tenmaru, you bad dog! Stop!
Chimaru!
Wait! That is mine!
Give it back!
I said stop!
Just stop running!
Give it back! Please!
I get it!
It's because the letter smells of Shinobu.
You are his dogs...
Just smelling Shinobu
is enough for you, isn't it?
Benio!
You got the letter?
Come on, what's in there?
Let me see, let me see!
No chance!
Whoa!
Slam!
This is the only place where I can be alone.
Shinobu...
Rustle
The scent of the Russian wind...
Russian wind?
I only know the fragrances of the farm.
Wham!
Why?
It hurts...
My dear Benio, are you doing well?
Shinobu...
I've been sent here all of a sudden,
that must've spooked everyone a great deal, hasn't it?
But I am doing fine here,
so don't you worry.
It's been two weeks since I've arrived to Siberia.
Siberia
Our unit is far away from the actual battlefield, so it's pretty quiet.
As I'm writing this letter, when I look out of the window to collect my thoughts,
there are wide plains for as far as the eye can see.
Right now I'm only in a small section of Europe,
but it's more than enough to sense the immensity of Siberia.
I'd love to show you this breathtaking scenery.
I can clearly picture you running around these fields, cheerful as usual.
Hooray!
Wink!
Gagman
Oh, there's one more thing that might interest you, my dear heavy drinker.
Here they have a very strong spirit called Vodka.
Vodka
Good enough.
I bet you're drooling.
Oh my! How could he tell?
It's taking her quite a long time.
Yeah... I wonder if she's eaten something bad.
What a lovely flower.
This flower grows in the wasteland.
The locals call it Malinka.
In Siberia's short summers, these flowers bloom and cover entire fields.
I picked one because it reminded me of you.
Malinka... raspberry flowers...
From the wastelands of Siberia,
I hope that you, just like this flower,
can spend your days carefree.
P.S. This war is silly and
it has nothing to with Japan,
so I might end up coming back home earlier.
P.P.S. That day, I'll bring many bottles of vodka for us to drink.
Look forward to it, okay?
Sincerely yours.
Thanks!
What a relief...
it's such a relief to hear that he's safe!
His unit is not on the front line!
Yay! Banzai!
Oh, gimme a break!
I can't take it anymore!
Banzai, yay!
Thank god! Thank god!
Shinobu is safe!
Lovely, lovely! Hooray!
And also...
Vodka...
Abstinence
Get a grip, Benio!
You swore that you'd abstain!
Yes? It's open.
Lady Benio, Count and Countess
can't wait anymore.
Huh? Oh, I see. I'll be there in a minute.
Benio! What in the world did Shinobu write to us?
Right, he said that his unit is not in a dangerous place,
so we don't have to worry.
Hooray! That's such good news!
Right, that's good. That's the most important thing.
But tell me, what did he write about me?
And about me?
Huh? Oh no... He only wrote about me here -
there's not even a word about anyone else.
Which means...
I'm all Shinobu can think of!
Hey! What's so funny in it?
My bad...
I want to hear what he wrote about me.
No, what about me? Hurry up, Benio!
Okay, here goes...
Oh my, what should I do?
He wrote nothing.
Somehow, this has only become
more troublesome.
Come on! Stop dawdling and read it!
Okay!
"Is grandfather as grumpy as usual?"
What?!
Oh my!
"Grandfather may seem grumpy,
but in reality he just needs company at all times, so please be kind to him."
Oh, I see. So he said that about me...
Nailed it!
U-Um, anything about me?
Yes, yes.
"Grandmother has frail health and often falls ill,
so I trust you to look after her in my place."
Oh, my, I'm moved!
U-Um, what about me?
Why'd he ever write about you?
So, anything?
Ah, sure, sure.
Right here...
"Ms. Kisaragi is the backbone of the Ijuuin family:
without her, nothing would work the way it does,
thus I hope that she lives long and serves the Ijuuin family for years to come."
Young Master, I promise that... I promise that...
I'll serve you until the day I die.
Hey, hey!
What about us?
"Ranmaru," err, I mean, "Ranko and Ushigorou
are your right-hand and left-hand men and I hope they continue to to boost our family's morale."
I won't let you down, Shinobu.
I, the goldfish-tattooed Ushigorou,
swear on my life that I won't let you down!
Oh?
Even Tenmaru and Chimaru are eager to know what he wrote.
Sure, sure.
"Please tell Tenmaru and Chimaru to keep being good dogs and to protect the Ijuuin family."
Oh well...
It's harder to fool animals than people.
It's finally time to write my response to Shinobu.
Let's see...
"I'm currently abstaining from alcohol,
so, instead of vodka,
bring some raspberry jam, okay?"
Whoops!
Why do I always end up talking about food?
This won't do.
Back to the beginning!
What could I write?
Let's try it this way...
"To the honorable Ijuuin Shinobu..."
No, this is way too formal.
"With respect, to Mr. Shinobu."
No, that sets the wrong mood...
"My beloved Shinobu..."
Oh? Oh, oh!
To think that I originally came here to make a mess of this place...
And what it came to...
There, go ahead and swing it, please.
A-Accept your fate!
This duel ends in...
Benio's victory.
Whoa!
I-I'm spinning round!
Wham!
Shut up! Let go of me! Hey!
Ow...
I know that your marriage with Young Master
will be the one that stands the test of time.
Miss Kichiji...
I've finally realized that Shinobu is a good person!
Banzai! Banzai!
W-What's with that disgraceful look!
And I love my dear Kisaragi too!
Huh?
Anyway, I ended up dozing off.
Here's the drool stain proving it.
Benio never changes, doesn't she?
This is the first time I get to laugh so heartily ever since I left Tokyo.
That's my High Collar Lady.
Heh. A letter from his girlfriend. My, oh my.
Our lieutenant's actin' too affected, am I right?
I gotta be honest,
I just can't stand him and his blond hair!
Ain't it ridiculous that he's our officer even though he's got no real experience in the battlefield?
Damn if our unit is led by someone like him.
We'll be doomed when push comes to shove.
It's not a surprise,
we're all outcast rogues ourselves, after all.
Hey, chill out, Onijima, are you really gonna drink this early in the morning?
Sure I am.
Anyway, how about getting him into some trouble?
We'll poke fun at that pretentious officer.
Sounds like fun.
Hello, this is Garrison Commander Sasaki.
Oh, it's you, Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen?
When did they send you to Manchuria?
Huh, is it Second Lieutenant Ijuuin's fault?
Yes, here's here.
You don't need to worry,
I've set him up with the worst rogues out there.
He'll have a hard time controlling them.
It won't be long before something happens to him.
Everyone, fall in line!
Fall in line!
I told you to line up.
Didn't you hear me?
Bud, did you hear anything just now?
Nah, nothing.
Maybe it was just a mosquito buzzing.
Understood. If you don't want to listen to me, I'll force you.
That's funny.
You have some nerve speaking like that.
I have to, since it's the only
language you understand.
Wow, you're made of stronger stuff than I thought.
I expected a Tokyoite,
wet behind the ears.
Bring it on!
Take this!
Don't think that I'll back down after this scratch!
Show him, Onijima!
Let's help Onijima!
Let's go get him!
There's a fight!
What?
In Ijuuin's squad?
It's always those thugs!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
I say, what the hell is going on here?!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin, step forward.
Yessir.
You five stay back.
What are you even doing, you bastard!
Smack
What do you think you came here for?
Corporal punishments were an everyday occurrence
in the Imperial Army.
However, it was very rare for officers to be punished before their subordinates.
If that ever happened, his authority would undoubtedly be eroded,
like what Shinobu is facing right now.
Tell me why, won't you?!
Aren't you embarrassed to stand before soldiers who've fought in battle?!
Tsk, they spotted us so soon.
Way to spoil the fun.
Go ahead and say it, Second Lieutenant.
After all...
I'm no stranger to the brig.
Second Lieutenant! Who started this brawl?
That's...
Don't worry, you can say who.
You're not gonna tell me?!
If Shinobu reports his subordinates' lack of discipline, he'll escape harm and Onijima will be punished.
What choice will our blond Second Lieutenant make?
Either of them probably
would've caused Benio to cry.
While Shinobu is away,
Benio is still set on her goal:
To become as feminine as possible.
But it's not an easy path.
Perfecting skills like making tea and arranging flowers may be out of her reach.
Upon realizing that, the Count decides to take her to a ball.
However, this will also end in chaos!
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"A Battle for Men, A Battle for Women."
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan