Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
It's the Taishou Era, an era of Romanticism.
And that quiet girl is none other than Hanamura Benio,
a seventeen-year-old High Collar Lady.
But a single bamboo sword is all she needs
to transform into a full-blown tomboy!
People are sometimes brought together in strange and interesting ways...
And that was the case for Benio,
as fate had her run into a
princely Second Lieutenant.
She challenged him,
wanting to test his reflexes,
only to discover that she had been betrothed to him by her father.
Wh-What did you say?!
En garde! Ten points!
Twinkle twinkle little star,
how I wonder...
what you are...
Oh, you're finally awake, Young Lady.
I-I can't stand it!
Who was it that said a warrior should always be vigilant?
Ugh... I've never lost to anyone before!
Just thinking about it gets me all fired up!
Howdy, I'm Boozy the Kid.
Don't mind me, I'm just passing by.
She heated up nicely!
Who the hell are you?
Can't you see I've got a lot on my mind?!
And that guy's going to be my fiancé?
F-Fiancé? My future husband?
Episode 2
Eloping
Father!
I don't think it's funny
when you joke around like this,
so stop messing around with me!
No, this is definitely not a joke.
Ijuuin Shinobu is your
husband-to-be, and that's final.
Yikes!
Wait, now is not the time to faint.
F-Father, this is so out of the blue...
Why on earth are you doing this?
You see...
For ages, the Hanamura dynasty was a vassal family in service of the Tokugawa Shogunate,
while the Ijuuin dynasty was always a noble family.
A long time ago, your grandfather and Ijuuin's grandmother, who met each other by chance,
fell in love with each other.
But then, on the night before the Meiji Restoration began,
they were forced to break off their relationship due to the end of the Shogunate.
However, before they parted ways,
they swore that someday,
once the world became a better place,
that their two families would become one.
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually become one again...
However, despite that, their descendants were male,
so they decided to wait until
their grandchildren were born.
So, in other words, I'm the chosen one.
Anyway, this was a promise that long predated your births.
Y-You've got to be kidding me!
There's no way I'm going to do this!
Don't I get a say in this?
That promise has long since expired,
the deal is off!
A-And with a guy like him, of all people.
You have to accept that this is an
everlasting promise between the families.
And to break a promise
is to discard your humanity.
We are both bound by this military oath:
"Warriors! Let faithfulness be your creed!"
But that guy isn't a warrior. He's a coward
who hits people when they're not looking.
Those military oaths also say this:
"First and foremost,
etiquette shall be followed."
Doesn't it?
Benio! Don't object to your father's words!
We'll be holding an informal wedding in the near future.
Going to Ijuuin's house will help you learn some manners.
Understood?!
F-Father!
Nanny, is the bath ready?
Th-There's no way...
No matter how you look at it,
this is too much.
Darling,
I'm glad this happened.
I've always treated Benio like a child...
But if I hadn't done something, she would've gotten more and more tomboyish.
Also, her fiancé is from a good,
noble family, so she'll learn a lot...
...even though it might be difficult at the beginning.
"That is the question."
"To be or not to be,
that is the question,"
remember that one well!
Phew...
That was a line from a work by William Shakespeare,
a famous English playwright.
Hanamura Benio, interpret this!
Interpret this line: "To be or not to be,
that is the question!"
Sure!
It means the author is asking himself whether something is there or not.
What?
Where are you at, Benio?! Read this!
Cheatsheet - English
It means that suffering in life is better than dying,
that is his dilemma.
She's just reading right off the cheatsheet!
Uh, should I keep reading?
Oh jeez...
Shut up! Get out of this class!
...Or not.
Saved by the bell!
Thank God, Benio!
I lost again...
Hey, Benio, is something wrong?
I thought English was your strong suit!
You've been in a daze all morning long.
Right?
Well, to tell the truth...
I've been betrothed to
someone I don't even know.
Huh?! Betrothed?!
You, of all people, Benio?!
Is he handsome?
Is he tall?
Is he a real man?
A man?
A man...
To think that you, the dunce, would be the first to get engaged!
Benio, you sly dog, you!
People sure have strange tastes...
No kidding!
Gimme your man...
Shut up!
I don't care if he's handsome,
I don't want to get married yet!
I-I have interests,
hopes and dreams too, you know?!
I-It's easy for you guys to say that...
Oh, she started crying.
Benio is right.
She shouldn't be forced to marry a stranger.
Tamaki...
Hang in there, Benio.
You are well within your rights to reject this old-fashioned marriage custom.
Tamaki, you're the only one who understands me!
Thank you, I'll do my best!
Still, Benio,
if you're too picky, you might end up alone.
Yeah, sometimes even I worry about that.
Living your whole life alone is tough.
Well, cheer up a bit.
Ah, that's right, didn't you say that this man is a noble?
That's right.
You're from a noble family too, aren't you?
Yes. Life in a noble family is hard, though.
Hard? How so?
For example, "Omawari," "Akaka,"
"Iriiri,"
"Okabe," "Misomiso," "Tsukutsuku," "Harihari," "Surusuru."
Do you understand any of that?
To make it short,
"Omawari" stands for vegetables.
"Akaka" are azuki beans.
What?
"Iriiri" are soybeans.
"Okabe" means tofu.
Moreover, "Misomiso" is miso dressing.
"Harihari" stands for dried melon.
"Tsukutsuku."
"Surusuru."
Understand, Benio?
All of these are words nobles use.
They don't speak Japanese?
I wouldn't go that far,
but it is a rather different world.
A world without Japanese...
No way, I'd hate a place like that!
What should I do, Tamaki?!
Welcome home, Young Master.
I'm back.
Okay, I hear you, Tenmaru.
Oh, Chimaru, good dog.
Have you been good?
Mrs. Kisaragi, is Grandmother here?
Yes, she is currently on the terrace in the garden.
I see.
All right, Tenmaru, Chimaru, we'll play later.
Oh, it's you, Shinobu.
I'm back home, Grandmother.
Welcome back.
I'm sure you're tired.
Grandmother, I got to meet
Lady Hanamura yesterday.
Oh! Tell me, Shinobu, how did it go?
What kind of lady was she?
She seemed to be full of spirit,
I would say it went well.
Oh, so you would be willing to marry that girl?
I'd do anything to make you happy, Grandmother.
Really?
The rapid flow of water
may get split in two by a stepping stone,
but it will eventually become one again...
Today, you, as my grandson, have granted one of my lifetime wishes.
I can't thank you enough, Shinobu.
Sorry for bothering you, Young Master.
This is today's share of letters for you.
All of them are from women.
I see.
Young Master, I hear your engagement came through,
so why don't you try to discourage them?
I know, I know.
Can you blame them, though?
Our Young Master is so handsome!
I might send him a love letter, too!
Hm?
Greetings, Shinobu!
Hey, Tamaki.
May I come inside?
Of course.
I was on my way back from piano class,
so I thought I'd drop by.
Really? I'd love to hear you play sometime.
Oh.
You always get so many love letters...
But it pales in comparison
to the number you must receive.
My, always the charmer!
A friend of mine got betrothed today.
And on top of that, her fiancé is a noble.
Oh, so he's like me.
I hope I'll get lucky, too.
Oh, but shouldn't it be easy for you,
with all the proposals you get every day?
It can't be...
Tamaki is too different from my fiancée.
She couldn't possibly be friends with her...
Hey, Shinobu,
is something on your mind?
Oh, nothing important.
Flower Garden
These safflowers are a rare sight.
I think they'd suit her.
Huh?
Can you send some flowers to this address?
Sure thing! Sending a gift to your girlfriend, eh?
The nerve...!
Thank you very much.
Sorry for the wait.
It's none of my business,
but your reputation is sure to be damaged
if you keep acting so carelessly!
Tamaki!
He's never acknowledged my feelings at all,
even back when we were kids.
My goodness, is it cold for spring.
Young Lady, dinner is ready.
It's your favorite, chicken dumplings!
I don't want any.
Hm?
Oh!
Even her favorites won't get her
to open the door.
So it's a hunger strike?
She must be really serious then.
That's right.
But she'll eventually get sick
if she keeps on going like that.
Maybe we shouldn't be so hasty, then.
Girls who are betrothed usually go through some self-reflection.
Regardless of the circumstances...
This book is so funny!
Here Comes the High Collar Lady
King, King, Ki—
It's not funny anymore.
No matter what I do, I still can't cheer up.
I don't even feel like practicing fencing.
Oh, I thought it was quiet. It's snowing...
Ranmaru?!
B-Benio!
Why are you standing
out here in the snow like a fool?
You're gonna catch a cold!
Hurry up, come in.
I guess I can't help it, then.
Come on, get near the fire.
How long were you standing outside like that?
Benio, it's awful!
You being betrothed... betrothed like that!
Ranmaru...
It's terrible!
I've always,
always liked you, ever since I was a child.
W-What are you saying?
It's the truth!
But my social status is lower than yours, and I'm a year younger than you.
That's why I've never told you.
There's nothing I can do,
I can't go against my father's decision.
But, according to what he said,
that second lieutenant seems to be a good man.
But to make such a decision, all of a sudden, when there was so much I wanted to do...
I can't be happy about it.
Benio!
Let's run away together!
R-Ranmaru, what are you saying?!
I'd give up everything to be with you!
I'd even give up kabuki!
A-Am I not good enough for you?
Ranmaru...
I-It's not like that.
I do like you,
but in a more brotherly way.
So it's okay, then?
Ranmaru!
Let's meet tonight, I'll be waiting!
He stood in the snow
all this time to tell me that?
But...
What is this warm feeling?
Why is this all happening so suddenly?
Well, Ranmaru is cute,
so I can't just ignore him.
But to run away with him?
That's a bit much.
Something drastic like eloping
doesn't sound like the smart thing to do.
Shakespeare said:
"Is it better to suffer in life than to die?
That is the question."
Shut up!
Young Lady?
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin sent some flowers.
Oh, I see.
Huh?
These are safflowers, right?
He even attached a card.
Let's see.
"It's not a color
I'm very fond of..."
It's not a color I'm very fond of, but, for some reason,
I picked out these safflowers for you.
"It's not a color I'm very fond of,"
so, what he's saying is...
Even if he doesn't have deep feelings about me,
he still decided to send these safflowers with some kind of intention, I guess...
Safflowers, typically used as a dye...
Ouch!
Flowers meant for dyeing?
So he wanted to dye my nose red?!
Now I'm mad!
Why, that no-good—
I didn't think he'd be this mean!
I never liked him, but now I'm completely done with him!
Now I'm running away, no matter what!
You think I'd marry him?!
No one dares make fun of me!
Let's go, Ranmaru.
Benio...!
This is goodbye! To my dad, my home, my friends,
and to my fiancé! From now on,
I'll be going down my own path!
And so, walking at a fast pace alongside Ranmaru,
High Collar Benio is determined to start anew.
Where will escaping from her forceful engagement
and living the "High Collar" way take them?
High Collar Benio is running away with Ranmaru,
but following the path of true love
might lead to unexpected encounters.
Like Ushigorou from the Kurumahiki Clan,
willing to become a girl's escort.
But it turns into a cheerful
and a drunken singalong,
Until she meets her blond
Second Lieutenant fiancé once again.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"A Romantic Hangover"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it gets so hard to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
when he goes away, I want him to turn around,
to give me a loving glance one more time
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Editing
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing, TLC
darkcart
ImAWasteOfHair
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo