Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Sorrow lurks deep within
a maiden's innocent heart.
Shocked after learning
the man she gazes upon
is none other than
her friend's fiancé.
Overwhelmed by an internal conflict
of friendship and love, Tamaki ran away.
On the other hand, we have
another story of one-sided love:
Even though he had
been looking for Benio,
he didn't make it in time, as our dear High Collar Lady already had a hand in yet another scuffle!
Where do you think you're going, after causing all this mess?
Never come back!
Boss!
Boss, are you alright?
Huh? Ranmaru,
what are you doing?
What am I doing?
I was looking for you!
Oh, was that it?
Boss, who's the one
who threw you out?!
I'm gonna have a
few words with 'em!
W-Wait! Ushigorou, it was my
fault to begin with, so it's fine.
Hey, Lieutenant!
Wherever you go, something bad happens!
First the bar and now this!
Ushi!
What's your relation to the boss?
Please, let's not cause any more trouble.
Can you do that for me?
Benio!
We should hurry home.
Benio, how about I buy you some coffee
or an ice cream in that dairy bar?
Ice cream...
I'm truly helpless when
it comes to food...
Come on, let's go.
B-Benio!
Episode 5:
Godspeed, Bride in Training!
Dairy Bar
Now, what's so funny to you?
Sorry, I was thinking about what happened
today and that exchange with your friends...
Hey, you...
Do you have any
notion of anger at all?
Not only did I ruin the opera,
but I also embarrassed you, didn't I?
Is that bad?
Why should I be angry?
Huh? My...
Had I been with any other girl,
I wouldn't have had so much fun at the opera.
I'm dead serious!
I didn't mean to make you have fun!
After all, doesn't it revolt you that you'll have
to marry me just because your parents said so?
And Tamaki is a
dear friend of mine...
I'd much rather you reciprocate
her feelings instead!
On top of that,
I'm crass and pigheaded!
Moreover, Tamaki is
such a refined beauty,
anyone in their right mind
would pick her over me.
Well, I've never met a girl
who's as self-aware as you.
I was just trying to be modest!
Wait, I didn't mean
to make fun of you.
Then why do you
want to marry me?
Your ice cream is melting.
I just can't help it
when food is involved.
Hey, could we at least get
in and have some coffee?
Nope! Not possible.
The boss's orders are sacred.
There's no way I'd ever breach them.
Anyways...
What could they be talking about?
Benio...
What are they talking
about so cheerfully?
Coffee... Coffee...
Hot as the depths of hell,
black as the darkest night,
and bitter as this love of mine.
Oh, sweet coffee...
Benio, look straight at me.
I want you to take a
good look at my face.
Surely, a pretty,
perfectly chiseled face...
Encircled with that bright hair
that's unique among Japanese people...
The faint color of his cheeks...
Furthermore, those expressive, yet mysterious hazel eyes...
Those mysterious hazel
and vaguely bluish eyes...
You see, while my father is Japanese,
my mother is German.
My mother...
She's probably
somewhere in Germany.
She, too, is a daughter
from a noble family.
They feel in love when
my father was studying there.
However, my mother's family would
never have allowed her to marry a foreigner.
And thus, she left my father with me,
a newborn baby,
to marry a man
from another family.
Since I resembled my mother a lot,
it became painful for him to even look at me.
So he left me in Japan and moved to
another country, where he eventually died.
Ever since I was abandoned,
I was taken care of by my grandmother.
Even now,
I can't forget those days.
Shinobu! Look, that's a steam train!
Wow!
Amazing!
That rising smoke!
Grandmother!
If I ride on that train for long enough,
I'll get to where Mother and Father are, right?
Hey, Grandmother!
If I keep trying,
I'm sure I'll meet them!
Second Lieutenant...
To think that I could
feel so sorry for him...
Is it awakening my
maternal instinct?
Because of this...
as I grew up,
over and over again,
my grandmother dwelt
on her doomed romance.
And so, ever since I was a child, I grew up
thinking I could make her love bear fruit.
What?!
So you'd settle for a loveless marriage just to please your grandmother?
If the love comes after,
I certainly wouldn't mind.
Jeez!
There's no way a couple can
start getting along so suddenly!
I'm against such selfish
views on marriage!
At any rate, I don't want
the engagement to be called off.
Huh?!
This has been my grandmother's
purpose in life for all these years.
T-This guy has a severe
grandmother complex!
A real granny lover!
Don't you feel anything about this?
Doubts? Worries?
Not really.
Huh?!
Whaaaat...?!
Oh Lord, have mercy on this young and
handsome man and his twisted ways.
It's not normal!
Not normal at all!
And to have a granny complex,
of all things...
Benio!
I bid you good day!
It's like he would be fine
with marrying anyone.
Yes, if she were from
the Hanamura family,
he would marry even
that giddy bimbo!
You called?
Shut up!
Oh, I could've sworn
she said my name...
To say that to a modern lady,
does he have no shame?!
Benio!
Boss!
You got in another fight?!
Tell me who it was! Where are they?!
A fight?
Is this the best your powers of
imagination could come up with?
Huh?
Aren't people aware that girls
have their worries too?!
Bonk
Wait, Benio!
I don't understand
what's happening at all!
Boss!
Boss, wait, please!
Why do you care?
I'm just a girl that does
nothing but fight, aren't I?
It's not like that!
You got it all wrong, Boss!
You've got this all wrong, Boss!
Hey, hear me out, will ya?
Just stop following me!
It's not about that anyways...
I have a message from Nanny.
Nanny?
She said there was no homework for today,
so you needn't worry.
Huh? I see...
Hanamura!
Thanks to Ushi, I know there wasn't any homework today.
Hanamura, one minute.
Miss, there shouldn't be
homework for today, right?
Homework has nothing to do
with what I want to tell you.
Huh?
I wonder what it's about, then.
Is it true that you've been
betrothed to Second Lieutenant Ijuuin?
Y-Yeah...
Wow! So that was true!
My!
How could someone like you, of all people,
marry into the noblest of all noble families?
Cooking, sewing, and etiquette.
You're rock-bottom in all of them!
All of them?! In other words, all ones?
No way... Getting to know
the truth hurts so much!
Are my grades really that poor?
Poor? You're the worst student
who has ever stepped in this school!
Top, good, average, poor.
You're bottom in all of them!
Come now,
it's not worth crying over.
A complete failure!
Fourth-rate
Has she lost her mind?
Wh-What should I do? Maybe it was
the shock of hearing she's rock-bottom...
How are you feeling? I'm Benio...
Rock-bottom.
Yes, that's right!
Best news I've had in ages.
Tamaki...
Tamaki!
Wait, Tamaki!
Benio...
I can't bear to look at you.
The fact that you're
marrying Shinobu...
I have something to
tell you about that.
I...
I've always loved Shinobu,
and to make it worse,
you're my rival, of all people...
J-Just wait!
I'm not marrying him!
Huh?
Aren't you going to his house
to learn marriage manners, though?
That's true.
Then it's already settled, isn't it?
Well, I wouldn't say that...
Hey, hear me out!
I will, so be straightforward.
You got it.
In short, you already know how worthless I am as a
lady of the house—in cleaning, washing, cooking...
Yeah, so?
So...
As my training is undergoing,
what'll happen once they figure it out?
As much as Shinobu's grandmother
wants him to get married,
I don't think she'd want him to get married to a good-for-nothing like me, don't you think?
Then, do you think
it'll be alright?
Wow, Benio, you're so clever!
This is why you're
my best friend!
I love you!
Benio, you're incredible!
I see...
Will it really be alright, though?
Well, just look at me.
I had the worst grades in etiquette,
cooking and sewing.
Anyone would be a better wife
for that granny's boy than me!
It's going to be fun!
When I'm done with this vase,
we'll decorate upstairs too.
Yes, ma'am.
I want this house to be
full of beautiful flowers.
Yes, ma'am.
The sky is also clear...
It's such a beautiful day.
I trust you'll handle today's task with the utmost care. Make sure there are no mistakes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'll be going, Grandmother.
Do your best.
Take care, Young Master.
Oh, what beautiful flowers.
Shinobu, do you understand
what they are for?
Today is the day Benio will be stepping
inside this house for the first time.
After waiting for all these years,
my wish of a lifetime is about to
be granted through my grandson.
So these flowers are for Benio?
Yes.
I just want the whole house
to look like it's in bloom.
I wonder if that high collar girl can
even appreciate all those flowers...
Even her neighbor Ranmaru
is more feminine than her.
Then, I will see you later.
Benio...
Where did Ushi go,
at such a crucial time?
He doesn't
understand how I feel...
I am Rickshaw Ushigorou!
Tokyo's most...
Ah, this world is so dull lately...
Hey, you, Lady!
Fancy a ride?
It's cheap.
Absolutely not!
Well then.
Suit yourself, uggo.
Well then!
A little drink couldn't hurt.
Let's go.
If you drink, don't pull,
if you pull, don't drink!!
-City Police
I am here today to pick up Lady Hanamura
and deliver her to her new home for training.
That is most considerate of you.
Thank you for your trouble.
It's all pitch-black...
All, all, pitch black!
Hey, join so we can sing
this together out loud!
Yah, let's do this.
It's all pitch-black, yeah!
It's pitch-black!
Across Mount Hakone...
In the past, people used
to travel on backs or in a bier...
Nowadays, as in a dream,
trains take people wherever they want to go!
All the smoke makes
the tunnel pitch-black!
It's all pitch-black!
Benio...
Is Lady Benio still getting
her things in order?
Can you check in on her?
Yes, I will go and see to her.
Benio!
Young Lady!
Here I am!
Did you call for me?
Chin-less Nanny.
Y-Young Lady...
Th-That's Lady Benio?!
Benio...!
What's wrong, Daddy?
Daddy?
Young Lady,
wh-what are you wearing?!
What's the big fuss? I decided to get all dressed up for the big day is all.
This is bad news...
It appears that Benio devised
an effective deterrent tactic!
What is awaiting her?
Stormy winds, or heavy rain?
The die of fate has been cast.
The high collar betrothal
breaking mission has begun.
Benio is acting in a
most unladylike manner,
in order to avoid her marriage
to Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
However, oh my, oh my,
something unexpected
is waiting for her...
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"A Fleeting Wedding March"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
amicus
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
Ziusudra
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
amicus
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
Ziusudra
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
amicus
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
Ziusudra