Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Is he a Hikaru Genji or just a Narihira?
The super handsome second lieutenant receives mountains of love letters every day.
But among them, there is one from a woman
whom Shinobu is dating regularly, in secret.
Wishing for nothing more than to protect our High Collar Lady,
these two conspire to tail Shinobu.
But because their mission is to be kept secret from Benio, Ushigorou fails his assignment,
and so she stumbles across
Shinobu's date herself, in all her glory.
Was she a fool for being so trusting?
Or is the deceiving side in the wrong?
Our High Collar Lady can't sleep.
When will the truth come to light?
This affliction goes way deeper than I thought.
I have to do something about it...
It's a bummer that we have to wake up before everyone else.
It's tough, isn't it?
That's true.
But I'm sure it's for a reason
that they say "the early bird gets the worm."
Ah!
Huh?
What could it be?
It must be Ranko exercising.
You're right.
Let's ask her to train us too!
Ranko!
Could you teach us to...
Huh?!
P-Pardon the intrusion.
We thought it was Ranko...
It's okay.
So, wanna try it?
N-Not a chance!
We're good!
Excuse us!
Nothing like a good workout
to wash your worries away.
Episode 21
Life is Short, Yet Riddled with Worries
It looks delicious.
Benio will surely like it.
Wh-What is this?
You see, Benio has been working out since early morning, so she'll definitely be very hungry.
Ah, is that so?
Good morning.
Good morning!
This is looking to be another
especially pleasant morning.
I can already feel
the heavy stomach and the heartburn...
Lady Benio, you aren't eating?
Take it away.
I don't feel like it.
Oh...
But breakfast is important for your health.
It's okay.
W-What's wrong, Benio?
Usually, you'd down three bowls of rice first thing in the morning.
Did you perchance eat something bad
while scavenging?
Ugh... Hate to break it to you,
but even I have periods when I'm simply not hungry.
Ugh, I'm so mad!
She seems to be in a rather ill humor.
I can't believe my eyes.
Hm! This might just be an omen of an incoming cataclysm!
I sure hope it's not an earthquake, though.
Cut it out!
How can you joke so casually
about Benio's condition?!
You should all be seriously worried for her instead!
I sure wonder what actually happened to her.
For all he's worth, I'm not supposed
to give a diddly damn about him...
Benio!
Benio.
Here comes the reason I lost my appetite.
What's the matter?
You do know going to school without eating is unhealthy, right?
Won't you at least drink some milk for me?
Boom!
L-L-Leave me alone please!
I can't keep my cool
when I see you!
Leave me alone!
I don't wanna see you!
Benio?
Benio...
Shinobu?
Did something happen?
I seem to have fallen into her disfavor.
It really hurts my pride.
I've never met a girl so cold to me.
And even though I've always been serious about my feelings, we didn't grow any closer.
It's already been a while
since I first met her.
But no matter what I do,
that bird keeps flying further away.
Ushigorou, it's finally time to go to school again.
At your service!
Benio!
Are you sure you should leave without eating?
It's all good.
Boss! You've done your homework, haven't you?
Even if I didn't, that doesn't matter right now.
Just leaving this place for a while
would be good enough.
Once I meet up with all of my classmates again,
I'll cheer up in no time!
Alright, let's go.
Aye!
She seems to be in very bad shape.
I'm worried... What should I do?
Benio!
Benio, I'm going out too,
so let's ride together 'till the gate.
Hell no!
Ushigorou.
Yes?
Can't you go any faster?
I'm telling you to speed up.
Didn't you hear me?
J-Just sayin', they call me Supersonic Ushigorou,
so try not to fly away!
Benio!
Ushigorou! Faster! Don't slack off!
Sure...
So she is avoiding me. But why?
Shinobu, wait!
Shinobu...
Why didn't you ride along Benio?
That was my intention,
but with the power of loathing, she broke away.
Why aren't you following after her, then?
If I did that, I'd only end up
hurting her even more instead.
Don't lie!
If it was me, I'd put my life on the line,
and follow the person I love to the end of the earth.
I'm sure that Benio
was hoping that you'd chase her.
No way...
If you can't understand such a simple thing,
you don't deserve your playboy title.
Deep down, Benio...
She thinks about nothing but you.
That's why...
That's why she's pushing you away
with her words!
If you can't understand even such a simple thing, hands off Benio!
Ranmaru!
Idiot... Idiot...
Ushigorou, you idiot!
Didja say somethin' to me, Boss?
Why did you actually go faster
when I told you to?
Eck! I don't understand!
Oh, my bad, my bad.
But I always follow your orders, so...
And that's why you're an idiot!
Why... Why would I not want
to ride side by side with Shinobu?
Why'd you command me to speed up, then?
I mean... Why would you necessarily run faster
just 'cause someone tells you to?
Boss!
Didja want me to go faster, after all?
Or did that mean I should slow down? Tell me!
You can't even understand that?
Aye! It ain't make no sense to me.
You thickheaded henchman.
Hyaah!
Ouch!
That's my answer...
Now I get it!
You have that thing for Shinobu!
Oh no, how could I?
Hanamura!
Why, it's you, teach!
Teacher, good morning.
Oh, right, long time no see.
Now that I think of it,
we've not seen you in a long while indeed.
Maybe that's why I feel
like I've missed y'all so much!
Teacher!
Hanamura says she missed me?
This can't be a good omen. Ah...
Righteous path towards wifehood
I hope nothing bad happens today...
Good morning, everyone!
My!
Benio!
It's been ages!
Ah, you must be so busy you have no time at all to go to school these days!
Yeah... I've got a lot on my plate...
But now that I'm finally here,
let's celebrate it with some anmitsu!
Oh, so sorry, but I'll have to go
straight home after school.
Oh, why so?
Ah? Oh...
Osono needs to prepare for her official wedding.
Oh?
But it's not just me. Kanoko too.
Otei too.
Then there are also Shizuko and Matsuya.
In other words, we can't spare any time for anmitsu right now.
Sorry!
Osono, when will they hold the ceremony?
Uh-huh, before asking others,
why don't you let us know about your own one?
Hey, listen, who do you think
is gonna get married first?
Hm. Probably Shizuko?
Wouldn't it be Kanoko?
But don't forget Matsuya!
No, it's obviously Shizuko!
Wow-wow
Chitter-chatter
Kyaa Kyaa Kyaa!
Matsuya for sure!
Not a chance!
Dear me...
After not coming to school for just a short while,
n-now I feel like I've been left behind!
Left out
How miserable...
It's time for all of us to decide our path.
We'll graduate soon, after all.
Tamaki...
What's with that long face?
Aren't you getting married to Ijuuin yourself?
Ah! Speaking of which...
Doesn't it mean that Benio's marriage talks were the first to be concluded?
You're right! It was her!
Look at you!
Silence!
Wifehood
Now then, one more thing I'd like to talk about
before checking your homework today.
Since many of you are brides-to-be by now,
I'd like to give you some advice
regarding your choice of the woman's path.
May I, Teacher?
What is it, Kobayashi?
Ma'am! While your academic advice
on our womanly duties could indeed prove invaluable,
wouldn't it be more beneficial for us
to listen to the first-hand account of the married life,
grounded in one's actual experience of it?
Oh, I'm all for it!
Agreed!
Let's do it!
Silence!
If you want a firsthand account,
grounded in experience...
y-you're out of luck!
I devoted my life to teaching,
so even in my age, being unmarried,
I'm not in the position to advise you on the matter!
Are we clear?!
T-Teacher, you shouldn't take this personally.
That's right.
In fact, I wasn't asking you, seeing as we have an engaged bride in this very class,
who already lives at her husband-to-be's house
and is an unrivaled expert in the matter!
B-But I'm not...
R-Right, I see.
Well, then...
Yes! We'd all like to hear Benio
recount her firsthand experience vividly to us.
Benio, tell us more!
Tell us!
Hanamura, please let everyone make use
of your valuable experience.
O-Okay...
Uhm... I... I...
How do you address your future husband?
Have you held hands yet?
Have you kissed yet?
Mwah, mwah!
I... I...
Alright. Why won't the ever-vigorous Miss Hanamura
tell us about how her life is these days?
You have my permission.
No, it's an order!
I... I really have...
Relax and speak already.
Say it!
Tell us all about it!
Hurry up, Benio!
Benio, tell us.
Tamaki? Why are you interested in it too?
Well, I believe, I have every right to know that.
You understand why, don't you?
Good, go on now.
Fine.
Everyone, I'll be perfectly honest with you.
Hurry up!
Actually, in regards
to the personal experience I could share,
I have nothing...
I have nothing!
Benio...
Tailoring Club
Huh? Shinobu is seeing a geisha?
I can't believe it...
N-Not Shinobu...
But it's true...
On the Sumida River of spring’s freshness
No, this can't be right. Shinobu loves you.
But I even spotted them going out together.
She writes him letters too. It's the truth!
Boatmen come and go with the tides
Would I be crying this much if it was a lie?
Tell me, Benio,
you still love Shinobu, don't you?
Yes...
Drops from their oars scatter like blossoms
Not a chance! I'll never like him!
Liar. Look at this liar.
Why'd you be so upset if you hated him?
Y-You're wrong!
Those tears and the stubborn denial
give you away at once.
What should one make of this scene?
My best friend sees through me,
as is to be expected.
In any case, the one Shinobu loves is that geisha.
You loved him too, didn't you?
So, aren't you shocked?
Oh, speaking of that...
I've already let go of him.
Tamaki...
I didn't want to live in doubt forever.
After graduation, I wanna try working.
Living on my own, as a new woman.
And then, find myself a new love.
Short is the life...
Fall in love, maidens...
Tamaki is bouncy as usual.
She's moved on without a second thought.
Benio, we might end up
walking different paths after this,
but may we both find the way to happiness
with our own efforts.
Yeah. I will.
I'll forget that I've ever met
that dumbass lieutenant!
There we go again...
There must be something
you got wrong about that geisha.
Because I know what kind of person Shinobu is.
She really does know Shinobu better than I do in every regard!
I'm so miserable...
Ushigorou, stop!
Stop!
Let's go the opposite way.
Huh? Aren't you goin' home now?
No questions. Just do it.
Aight!
Whoa, whoa!
The road to the Ijuuin mansion is to the left,
but she went to the right, which is very suspicious.
As a teacher, I cannot let this slide.
Wait! Wait, rickshaw. I need a ride.
Alright.
Hurry up now!
Chase after that rickshaw!
Chase?
That is not a very nice thing to do...
Stop objecting!
Hurry up!
Aye, aye...
Hurry!
Make haste!
Aye, aye...
Can't you run any more energetically?
Do your trademark "here I go" or something?!
Miss, if you keep complaining while sitting up there, dangling your legs, nobody is going to serve you.
If you're in that much of a hurry,
why don't you do it yourself?
You lowlife, you dare patronize a woman?
Let's switch then!
Bonk
Here I go!
If I run you over, you're dead!
Make way!
Geez, what was that?
I wonder.
Wild rickshaw, maybe?
Turn right on the next intersection.
We're going to Yanagibashi.
Yanagibashi?
Ooh, wanna get even with those Violet Band dudes, Boss?
No, I don't!
Where the hell are we goin', then?
To a geisha house, of course.
N-No way! Fooling with geishas
ain't somethin' a woman should do!
What's it to you,
who doesn't see me as a woman anyway?
Right, but well...
Ushi!
Aight!
Oh! Found them!
Out of my way!
House of Flowers
Well, I'll be going now.
Gotcha, Boss! Take your time!
V-Visiting a geisha?!
Unbelievable...
I must be hallucinating...
A geisha...
May I come in?
The battle is about to begin...
Y-Yes!
Good evening.
Oh?
Lady Benio...
With how progressive our High Collar Lady is,
can fooling around with geishas as a girl
be considered a mere vagary,
or is she going too far after all?
Face to face, the two are as different as day and night.
The knives are out in the red light district tonight,
as the two women clash in a decisive battle.
High Collar Lady decides that tonight is the night
to clarify her relationship with Shinobu,
so she asks Kichiji to marry Shinobu herself.
This turns into a heated woman-to-woman battle
where love is at stake.
But what do you know - Kichiji stuns Benio
with her astonishing life story.
See in the next episode of Here comes the High Collar Lady:
"Falling Flowers, Blooming Flowers and Flowers of Love."
Episode 22
Falling Flowers, Blooming Flowers and Flowers of Love
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan