Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Benio was excited to become more feminine to at least do something while Shinobu is away,
and so, she went to her first ever ball.
Meanwhile, Shinobu, once again fell prey
to Lt Col Innen's plotting, as after covering up for his unit, he was sent to the front lines along with them.
But even women can make war at home:
Benio found out that the ball is actually full of jealous and resentful people.
On top of this,
she unknowingly broke her oath of abstinence by drinking apparent juice.
Will this enrage the gods?
Before long, Shinobu ended up
wandering the wasteland.
Just when he thought he was saved by the man-to-man bond he had formed with Sergeant Onijima,
they both ran into even more trouble,
finding themselves surrounded
by Russian troops!
You are in Siberia, the enemy's land!
Episode 29
In the Thick of the Siberian Battle
Shit, we've been surrounded.
Ura!
This is bad timing.
Hey, over there!
Let's slip through there!
Alright! They won't get us
that easily, Chief! Let's go!
Crap! Another ambush! Whoa!
Onijima, let's hide in those woods!
Alright! Go!
Can't go through there.
Is this how it ends for us?
Dammit...
So this is Shinobu's fiancee?
It's what I've been told.
My, how peculiar!
Very peculiar indeed!
What's so peculiar about me? Humph!
I'm surprised that somebody like her managed to hit it off with Young Master.
Oh, I'm so jealous!
I must assume that he took a liking for girls with the proportions of a telephone pole.
My, how distasteful!
A telephone pole?
How lame!
Where have you seen a telephone pole with limbs?!
You there, bring me more juice!
What's more, I heard that this girl
associates with Yakuza members.
My, how scary!
I am sure that Young Master simply proposed to her on a whim, amused by this eccentric side of her.
Did you really think that Shinobu would seriously date someone like you?
Well said.
Shinobu is known to have a fondness for jokes.
He just plans to keep you around as a quirky pet.
I'm sure, at home she is just a fancy lap partner,
like a Persian cat of sorts.
Ladies,
the common folk does things that nobles like us could never think of.
Plebs like them yearn for things such as societal status and wealth,
which happen to be the birthright of us nobles.
What are those hags talking about?
Do they really think I got engaged with Shinobu out of greed?
I've had enough of this!
I have something I need to tell you all!
Second Lieutenant proposed to Benio unilaterally and then also forcibly took her to his family's mansion!
Then he did take her in as his new quirky pet.
So it seems!
W-What did you say?!
Stop it, Ranmaru!
"Ranmaru..."
She said "Ranmaru," didn't she?
Come to think of it, you look exactly like Fujieda Ranmaru, the dancer!
You're absolutely right!
Ah, I know who she is!
She resembles Fujieda Ranmaru so much that they've hired her as a maid who poses as Ranmaru.
I guess that makes two peculiar pets
in Lord Shinobu's custody!
I can't stand this any longer!
Calm down. Let's sit down over there, okay?
Keep yourself together. Do it for Shinobu.
Juice!
They're approaching, Commander.
We have no other choice:
Let's break through the middle.
Onijima, sweep through the enemy's center!
Roger that! Second Lieutenant, see to it that we're not crushed in between!
Onijima, are you okay?
I wouldn't be worthy of my name if I croaked for this scratch.
Alright, let's get out of here.
Ready?
Now!
Onijima, duck for cover!
Hey, let's hide behind those rocks.
Good idea.
They won't attack us right away.
Are they gonna take us prisoner?
Benio,
I promise I'll come home safe and sound.
Please wait for me.
Another one!
Pardon?
Oh wow, she perfectly suits
my ideal type of woman!
Hey, mommy.
What is it, child?
Well, you see, actually...
I'd love to dance with this li'l lady!
Ugh...
So? Can I? Please, mommy!
Oh, my, you're such a hopeless child.
Huh? What's with this guy?
He sure strikes me as the definition of a manchild.
I really, really wanna dance with her!
Can I? Pretty please?
Sheesh, what am I going to do with you?
Just make sure
to keep your distance with her, okay?
You never know what could happen to you!
Ugh... One, two, three, four, five!
Young Lady!
Eek! W-Well, for your information, I actually have two left feet!
Oh, dear! You can't be bad at dancing if you've come all the way to a ball for nobles such as this one.
So, how would you like to dance?
Maybe one of those Bon festival dances?
Huh?
Heh!
Oh, don't sweat it, I'll take the lead.
Uh, I-I don't think we should do this...
He'll pay for this!
You scoundrel!
What's this?!
Mommy!
Tsk! What are you trying to do
to my grandchild's bride?
Hey!
G-Grandfather!
My baby!
Please, let's talk! Let me speak!
Silence! You've got some nerve, making a move on another's bride!
You're a blob of disgrace!
Grandfather!
Y-You're wrong, he just wanted to dance with me for a spell!
What? Spell?
They dance to cast spells nowadays?
I-I-I have to run...
No, "spell" meaning "a while."
How pathetic!
So you're saying that modern Japanese boys even dance with the likes of women?!
You'd never think this conservative old man is actually Shinobu's grandfather!
Ah... If only Shinobu was also here, at this ball...
Benio.
Shinobu!
Commander!
Let's move on, quick!
Jump!
Onijima, are you alright?
Those tenacious bastards.
Second Lieutenant, I want you
to have these as a charm.
Don't say nonsense. You keep it.
I'm begging you! I want you to survive.
Our platoon needs you.
You have to survive, even if everyone else dies.
Do it for all of us!
Please.
Thank you, Onijima.
I appreciate it, but you can keep the dice.
Commander! Are you refusing my charm?
I don't need it.
I have another charm here with me that's just as good.
It's this one.
Ah, a letter from your fiancée?
I won't die as long as I have this with me.
It all suddenly settled down.
It's the calm before the storm.
I'll attack with all my might the next time they come.
When that happens,
I need you to run away alone.
I guess I have no other choice.
Second Lieutenant, rest here for a while.
I'll be the decoy.
Too bad, I've got used to this
during my military academy days.
Heaven's sake, what's with that moron?
Is he gonna keep dancing by himself?
Ah, that man is called the conductor.
Really? Then I'll take it that he's part of the band.
Ah, may I? You, the conductor.
Huh?
Could you move?
You're in front of the band and I can't see them play.
W-What are you saying?
I'm the conductor, you know.
You're in my way, move!
You uneducated boor!
Let me see the band!
This geezer here is out of this mind.
I've had enough of him.
You oaf! Who in their right mind would show their butt to the audience?
Just get out of my way!
AAAAH!
Now, turn around once and for all.
Come on, come on!
Turn!
No one ever treated me this way...
How embarrassing...
Humiliating... Woesome...
Oh, my... Grandfather is hopeless...
Now then, may I have your hand, milady?
I can't believe it! What is Benio thinking, dancing with a man like that?
I know it's only for a dance,
but I can't just stand still.
Now, put your left foot forward.
Like this?
Oww!
Why did you stomp my foot?!
No, not like that.
My, you're so inexperienced, milady.
Look...
Put your feet here and your hands here.
Good, now swirl.
Should I do it like this?
Ah, that didn't seem right.
That is pretty unusual for a mistake.
Let's just try again.
Here - slow, slow, quick, quick, and swirl!
She must be doing this on purpose.
Pull if you're pushed, push if you're pulled!
It seems like Benio
is doing judo more than anything else!
Voila!
Ah, I didn't mean to do this!
I-I can't take any more of this violent dance!
Huh? Oh, my!
Milady, won't you dance with me?
O-Oh, we can't do that.
You see, I'm just a maid.
Love is never bound by societal status!
Now, milady!
Whoa, what a beautiful prey!
Listen, I'm sorry to break it to you,
but I'm actually a guy!
Someone so beautiful
being a man is a blasphemy!
It's but a trifle.
Love knows no gender bounds!
Tee-hee
W-What's going on?
Oh, baby, take a look at my jewel!
U-Unfazed!
Now, let's pick the forbidden fruit together
and indulge in sodomic love!
N-No! Ah! Help! Help, Benio!
Now I've had enough!
Forgive me, Shinobu, but I'm not cut out to be a traditional woman!
Hold it, you!
Can't you see that he's crying?
Our love is none of your business,
you telephone pole!
Huh?
A drowning man will clutch at a straw!
F-First that geezer made a fool of me
and now I have to endure this humiliation!
Ugh! I've just moved from the opera house to this place, but enough is enough!
I can't take it anymore!
How are you, Akechi?
Huh?
U-Uh, what do you need that for?
Take this!
Ugh! How can you do this to a countess?!
You'd better get ready!
What's all this commotion for?
Get back here!
Ah! So many men! I'm so happy!
Please stop, everyone!
Please respect this ball's customs!
Uhm, Missus, you got some
change of clothes for me?
E-Eep!
How disgusting, how perverse, how dirty!
G-Go away! Away!
Sorry for troubling you this much.
Disgusting...
Way to go!
Kyaa
Whoosh
Clank
Isn't it strange?
Why did everything end in a brawl again even though I haven't drunk any alcohol?
Would you like more champagne?
This isn't juice?!
No, it's liquor.
Huh?! So the juice was a spirit all along?
Yes.
Whoa! This is bad! I ended up breaking my oath of abstinence!
Shinobu!
Will anything bad... happen to him?
Ura!
They're here.
So long, Onijima.
Benio, look at me now!
How miserable, this means that I endured
this abstinence for nothing!
Then forget it!
I'll show you my true drunken power!
Here I go! Eclair charge!
Here I go! Charge!
Second Lieutenant! Commander! Dammit!
Commander!
Commander, where are you?!
Please answer me!
Second Lieutenant Ijuuin!
It may have been a punishment for the oath being broken, but the battlefield is still a notoriously merciless place.
Onijima is desperately crying out to Shinobu,
but only the howling wolves are answering.
Did Shinobu die the warrior's death?
Where will our wandering warrior be?
In the next episode
It's been a while since the Ijuuins last received a letter from Shinobu
and they can't help but think
about him all day long.
Meanwhile, the front line commanders, abandoned by the headquarters, are receiving no food nor supplies,
thus the soldiers, having no other means to survive, are forced to fend for themselves.
There, they suddenly meet a battalion of Cossacks!
In the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Shinobu's Final Battle in Scattered Petals.
Episode 30
Shinobu's Final Battle in Scattered Petals
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing & translation checking
Editing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo
Chika