Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Through some unfortunate twist of fate, Benio's parents chose this man as her groom,
whom she'd never have considered as her husband.
One day, however, she is suddenly attacked
by a bunch of vindictive hoodlums.
But she is saved by a prominent woman,
who has an unrequited love for Shinobu.
She is understandably shocked
to discover Shinobu's playboy habits;
this is the final straw.
Benio resolves to leave of her own accord,
but a nostalgic letter from Nanny
stops her in her tracks.
Now then, what will our strong-willed
high collar lady do next?
There. Remember to treat everything with care.
We'll carry them to a sunlit spot on the second floor's balcony.
Where should I place this?
Ah, you can leave it there.
Are you airing out these old things, Countess?
Yes.
This mansion is rather old,
so we have a lot of them.
Sounds like a big deal.
Then, I'll try to help too!
Let's see...
A-Ah! Don't touch it!
Huh?
No need to push yourself.
Just leave it be.
Humph...
Phew
It feels like you don't trust me...
Episode 15
So Long, Old Relics
Oh, it's you, Benio!
Why the long face?
They're airing out old things, but I can't join them.
Oh, but aren't you glad that you can slack off?
True, but I'd like some company.
Then how about airing out
some of your own belongings?
I don't think I have anything dusty enough to need airing.
Oh wait, there is one thing!
It represents the vow that a wife makes to never marry again.
Should something tragic happen to Shinobu,
you'll have to wear this.
You're so old fashioned, Father...
Why should a wife sacrifice herself after her husband, unless she loves him that much?
My, a dagger too?
If Shinobu falls in battle,
I'll need to take my own life with this?
Shinobu, how do you feel about me?
Our moments together should give you the answer.
Our moments together...
A single leaf falling out of season...
I told you to go away! Go... Ah!
Come on, let's flee, quick!
What's going on?
Why is my heart pounding?
You see, I happen to be
in love with Young Master Ijuuin.
It couldn't have been my Shinobu...
Benio, did you meet her?
Live your life in the white dress...
My love has finally come true!
I beg you not to come home,
no matter what happens.
Benio, did you meet her?
Don't ever come back...
In the white dress...
My love...
Stop it! Stop!
Why should I ever die for someone who clearly doesn't love me?!
I hate this!
I hate this so much! No!
No!
Oh, Lady Benio, why...
Stop it! Stop it, I said!
H-Help me!
Ah! No, you're mistaken!
Help... Help... Help me!
Wait! Wait, I said!
Wait! There's been a misunderstanding!
Wait!
Calm down, you!
How do you imagine I'd calm down?!
Help me!
Just wait, Mrs. Kisaragi!
Mrs. Kisaragi!
Mrs. Kisaragi, hang in there!
Please, hang in there, Mrs. Kisaragi!
Oh, how silly of me!
Oh-oh-oh! Boss!
You took matters into your own hands and finally did away with the old hag? Gotta celebrate that!
What is this nonsense you're saying?
Ushigorou, hurry up and lend me a hand!
Yessir!
Just a moment... Here.
Heh... You even know how to resuscitate!
Boss, you truly are something else!
What else did you expect from someone initiated into the ancient art of two-handed fencing?
Ah, wait, Mrs. Kisaragi!
Indeed, this sword from the Komatsu forge was a bargain; it's sharpened excellently.
We were both so young
during the Battle of Toba-Fushimi.
The Shogun's forces united to oppose us...
N-No, that's too much.
Oh my!
Mrs. Kisaragi, hang in there.
Hang in there, you hear?
Oh, what should I do?
Count, let's call a doctor.
We can't handle this ourselves.
Well, call him if you want.
Ushigorou, call Dr. Yamada.
Sure!
Hey, wait!
Not Yamada!
Huh? Why's that?
He lives where the sun rises.
In other words, to the northeast from us.
And northeast is today's inauspicious direction.
If the doctor comes from an unfavorable direction
those he's supposed to save would be doomed.
What is this superstitious hooey?
It's not superstition, it's divine will!
No, nothing divine about it-just a superstition.
Enough!
Silence! I'm speaking from my own experience!
It was the 3rd of January of 1868.
We were assembling
for the Battle of Toba-Fushimi.
I was leading the Satsuma-Hayato Regiment to battle.
His Majesty appointed us to protect the area near Fushimi.
That was when I spotted the enemy ahead,
in an inauspicious direction.
Instead of attacking frontally,
I opted out for a more auspicious direction,
so I sprang into action.
To avoid the inauspicious direction, we turned directly to the sun and went on a massive detour...
hitting the enemy where they least expected!
Attack!
Don't stop! Shoot!
Die!
Thus we routed those shogunal dogs
without losing a single man!
All because we avoided attacking from an inauspicious direction!
That was just a coincidence!
For how long are you gonna cling to those outdated views?
You anachronistic geezer!
What's this "anachronistic" hooey?
It means that your head is stuck in the last century!
Why, you...
Shut up, you manlady!
What a dimwit!
W-What?
You obstinate hoyden!
Die!
Come at me, you stubborn geezer!
Good grief, where the hell did Kisaragi go when we're all so busy?
Ah, dear.
Hey, where's Kisaragi?
We're so busy and she's nowhere to be seen!
I wonder where she could have gone?
This isn't like her.
Right. Well, take care now.
Thank you very much.
You're finally awake?
You're a bit overworked, but if you rest for a couple of days, you'll be okay.
But didn't Dr. Yamada come from northeast?
Yes. I absolutely insisted on him coming!
From the northeast?!
Yes.
It's to ensure that those
he's supposed to save would be doomed.
Just kidding!
Turns out you're quite
old-fashioned too, Mrs. Kisaragi.
Yes. Like it or not, I guess I am.
No, don't get up yet.
But... For me to slack off on a day like this...
Don't worry, both the count and countess have granted you leave today to rest.
Aww...
Doc, thank ya and all that!
Oh? Is that Dr. Yamada?
Who the hell called for that doctor?
I spent so long warning about folk coming from inauspicious directions!
Who was it? Who called him?!
How should I put it...
Whatever. Even if you don't tell me, I know who it was.
There is but one person in this mansion who would dare disobey my orders!
Why did you call that doctor?
Sir, we needed one, so I called him.
So you think you can just
ignore me and get away with it?
Where's Kisaragi?
She's resting.
What? Who released her from duty?!
I did.
Y-You what?!
I am currently the bride to be,
so I also exercise authority
over the servants of your house.
Got a problem with that?!
My loss...
This is a commemorative statuette,
gifted to the count by Emperor Meiji himself.
It's an item with a long history.
Ah! Be careful!
Yes, ma'am.
What in the world could be inside?
Do they really treasure
such a simple plate that much?
Even my cat's bowl is prettier than this...
Ah! Wait...
No!
The plate!
Drat, I broke it!
Sorry!
Hey, what's the matter?
Why's everyone suddenly so serious?
Calm down! It's not like I
broke Humpty Dumpty or something!
With a bit of glue, I'll put it back together again.
Like so!
So, are we making progress?
L-Lord.
Now, where could my plates be?
Oh, there they are!
This color, this gloss! As expected of Imari ware
manufactured under Lord Shimazu.
Lord!
W-Who did this?!
Who broke it?!
I'm sorry, I d-did...
Ah... I mean, it slipped...
T-Th-Th... D-D-D...
You'll pay for your error!
By death!
By death?
L-Lady Benio!
Dear, please wait!
No! You keep it shut!
Ready yourself!
Stop running!
You bitch!
Wait!
Jeez, I had no idea he would follow his old ways to such disastrous lengths!
Benio! Benio!
Wait! Wait!
Count, that's enough!
To pass capital punishment over just a single broken plate...
A plate versus a human life,
which one is more important?
A plate!
My bad...
That plate is no ordinary plate!
Lord Shimazu of the Satsuma domain
personally bestowed them upon me.
You could say it's our family's heirloom!
Be it one plate broken or all ten of them,
my reputation as a samurai is tarnished forever!
Dear!
Shut up!
I'll exact the punishment!
My honor as a samurai is on the line!
Dear...
please try to contain your rage.
No amount of restraint will bring back my plate!
I suppose not, but still...
In any case, wouldn't it be inauspicious to kill her over a dish—like in that ghost folktale?
That's right! I'd totally return from the grave to haunt you as a ghost!
I'd like a man, maybe ten, or maybe just one...
Worry not, young maid,
for you won't die alone!
W-What do you mean by that?
After executing you, I'll then slice open my guts to clear my honor!
Get out the way, Benio!
Get away, you hear?!
What's wrong, Tenmaru, Chimaru?
Did something happen here?
Ah, Sublieutenant, just in time!
Ushigorou, what is it?
W-We're in big trouble!
Boss and Ranmaru--
Err, Ranko, are...
Tenmaru, Chimaru, show me the way!
Dang it all! If anything bad happens to Boss at all,
I'll set this whole place alight!
Why, you...
Get out the way!
Are you deaf?!
Can't you hear me?
Get lost. Now!
B-Benio!
Benio...
Wh-What have you done, Benio?!
It's better this way.
Wh-Why did you break the plates?! My plates!
I ask that you execute me as well.
If you take one person's life for a plate,
the breaking of the remaining nine
means you'd have to take nine other lives.
So, I take the responsibility for those nine lives.
Come on, finish me off however you like!
Benio...
Prepare yourself!
I can't take it anymore!
Wait, Ushigorou.
Huh?
We must not interfere.
But... But Boss is gonna die!
Benio will carve her own destiny.
Damn it!
Hey, old hag!
How dare you barge into a woman's room uninvited, you creep?!
D-Don't be stupid!
This is not the time to laze off!
B-But the lord permitted me to take the day off...
I guess ignorance really is bliss,
if you still don't know anything!
Mind you, Boss has taken all the responsibility on herself to allow you to rest!
Huh?
And now Boss is about to be executed for that!
Wh-What?!
Alright, I hope you've said your prayers.
As per your wish, my katana is going to taste your blood.
B-Benio...
I-I'm coming!
From now on, you belong to the Ijuuin family.
So take good care of yourself.
Father...
Forgive me for going before you.
Is Shinobu just going to watch me get killed?
He's too scared to oppose his grandfather!
Idiot! Spineless worm!
I hate you!
I hate...
The old count hailing from Satsuma-Hayato
is beside himself and can't wait any longer.
Facing him is Hanamura Benio,
currently 17 years of age,
silently cursing the cowardly Shinobu, who is watching on helplessly as she is about to be executed.
Shinobu, the only person she can count on, is just standing there, dumbfounded.
So, our High Collar Lady has made up her mind.
Oh, how pitiful it is that the flower's life is so short, at the age of 17, Benio is about to meet her end.
Was her fleeting acquaintance with Shinobu just an illusion or evanescent dream?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady, "Farewell, Failed Bride".
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Anonymous
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Anonymous
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Anonymous
CeleryMan