Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Things in life never seem to go the way you like.
Even in an all-important romantic elopement,
you could stumble upon a shady man
and even the fiancé you were running away from.
Everything resulted in a general bar brawl,
but Benio managed to run away
hand in hand with Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
At this point, how will
Benio's high collar life continue
as she's ushered full-speed to school?
Here I go! Make way, make way!!
What's wrong with that guy?
Here we are!
Boss, we arrived.
Come on, stretch your hand.
Come on!
Boss, what are you doing?
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Haven't we sworn an oath?
Go on.
Boss, you forgot your bag!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Have a nice day!
Boss!
Whoops, excuse me, sorry...
Please, wait!
Boss, you forgot your bag!
Ushigorou?
You can go now.
Don't be ridiculous, you're my Boss,
I'll be your shadow, through fire and water...
A ma-ma-ma-
A man...
Episode 4:
A messy Asakusa Opera
Teacher, hang in there...
I came hurtling like an ox, my bad...
Ushigorou, this is an all-girls school
and men are barred from entry.
Barred?
So you're telling me
no man ever stepped foot in here.
Yes, that's right!
And yet, half the world is made of men...
What a waste...
Just get out of here!
Hurry up!
Okay, call me if you need any help,
I'll be around here!
Phew, that was close.
What happened now?
What do you mean?
There was a man here a little while ago, I am sure.
A man...
A man?
I need a man...
Shut up!
T-Teacher, isn't it time
to start the lessons? Isn't it?
What's with the sudden excitement?
You're being odd today, Hanamura.
Well, I'm a student too, after all.
Sometimes even I feel like learning.
Righteous path towards wifehood
Stand up!
Bow!
Sit down!
Oh, Lord...
Ushigorou isn't a bad guy, deep down.
But then again, he's one extra worry.
Well then, show me your homework.
I-I forgot again!
I was about to run away from home,
so I didn't think I would come to school ever again...
What in the world? You forgot it again?
Uh, yeah, but...
What the hell do people like you
plan to do with their life?
It's not about my plans, uhm...
A lot of things happened in the meantime and...
Stop lying, I know you did it in bad faith!
This is the final straw,
I'll inform your father!
Hey, hey, whatcha doin' to my Boss?
You old hag, threatening my Boss like that!
Stop it, Ushigorou, stop it!
Don't you dare laying a finger on my Boss!
Stop it!
This is your boss's order!
Cut it out!
Hmph!
I'll let you go this time,
but if you fool around with the Boss,
I won't let it slide!
Sorry for the trouble.
He's finally gone.
I even had to make use
of my Boss authority make him stop...
Look, that guy's still there.
That's crazy, could Hanamura be a Yakuza?
What should I do,
this is just more stress adding up...
Hanamura, people like you...
My apologies!
Huh, an elopement?
Ranmaru is your pretty neighbor, isn't he?
Hey, hey, you're a femme fatale!
Stop, you don't know the whole story...
Is the guy your parents chose so awful
he made you run away?
It's not that...
There's something about him you dislike, right?
Falling in love
before getting married to him.
That's what I'd wish for.
I understand how you feel.
Oh, what happened?
You don't look too happy.
You're not like this usually.
Am I not?
It is kind of evident.
So, what bothers you?
Now it's your turn to talk!
But...
Please,
even though we're classmates, you seem to belong
to the world of grown-ups much more than I do.
Tell me about yourself, please!
Okay, then.
To tell the truth,
there is someone I like.
He's a childhood friend.
I've been fond of him since we were kids
and I thought I'd be able to marry him one day.
But he's never showed me any fondness.
Not being loved by who you love,
being loved by who you don't love,
everything always seems to go astray.
Moreover,
it seems like he's already set for marriage.
It's just heart-wrenching, isn't it?
But Tamaki, aren't you dating boys all the time?
Yeah.
I've been looking for someone better,
that's why I've been doing it.
But it's no use.
I just can't give up on him!
How will his fiancée look like?
What do you think?
Who knows.
Only if she's smarter,
prettier and better than me personality-wise,
I'll be able to let him go.
Don't you think so, Benio?
Yeah, I do.
But if that's not true, I won't back down.
Not at all.
Yes, that's the right thing to do,
never giving up!
You have to snatch him away from that girl!
I'll be cheering for your victory!
Thank you.
I have to meet that girl, no matter what.
I'm sure that she pales
in comparison of you, Tamaki.
I hope so...
But I wonder, what kind of boy
makes you fall head over heels?
I want to see him!
Wanna come with me then?
I'm going to watch the Asakusa Opera.
with him today.
Really? Won't I be like a tagalong?
Don't worry, you're welcome.
If it's you, I don't mind.
I wonder what kind of fellow he is,
to not be attracted to a wonderful girl as Tamaki.
Things are about to get wild!
What will happen when these three people
understand what's going on?
In Japan, opera started to become well-known
during the turn of century,
and since Asakusa is a hub for this art form,
it started to be called "Asakusa Opera."
In particular, the Boccaccio Opera
was centered around crossdressing girl parts
and was sparking in popularity.
There are so many people!
It's the Opera Craze,
it's been going strong lately.
Hey, tell me, Tamaki! Where's your beloved?
Oh, right...
Oh, there he is!
W-Where, where?
So, where is he?
Look, he's there!
That guy?
Yeah, it's him.
Hey... Huh? You..
Oh, do you know each other?
It can't be...
Benio, are you Shinobu's betrothed?
But if that's not true, I won't back down!
Yes, that's the right thing to do, you mustn't give up!
Heck!
S-So t-this sublieutenant
is the guy Tamaki is in love with?
It has to be a joke!
You're telling me that...
Of all people, Shinobu's betrothed
is Benio, a misfit!
No way!
My delicate heart
can't possibly withstand,
such a shock!
Tamaki!
Wait, please wait!
Tamaki, what are you doing?
Running away won't solve anything!
This is no good...
So you and Tamaki are actually friends.
Anyways, it's so strange,
acting like that all of a sudden...
It's my fault...
Oh,
don't fret about it,
she is the whimsical type.
She wanted to watch this opera at all costs,
Opera Boccaccio
so she invited me today.
How about we watch it together
to not waste the tickets?
Wait, so I am just the backup plan?
Come on!
Ah!
Nanny.
Nanny!
Oh, Ranmaru,
are you feeling better now?
Not really, but I'm worried about Benio.
Is she here?
She should be back from school by now,
but she is still not home.
The young lady is always a bundle of trouble!
Worry after worry, I'm going to thin down...
Really?
I wouldn't have guessed...
Oh!
It's you, Ushigorou. Where is Young Lady?
What? She's still not here?
That's strange...
You don't know?
I thought that,
as her bodyguard, you'd be informed.
I'm glad to hear that,
anyways, I'll go look for her now!
Wait, Ushi, I'll go too!!
Ranmaru, aren't you still ill...
It doesn't matter, I have a bad feeling
that something could happen to Benio...
I have a bad feeling about her every day!
How did it come to this...
My friendship is in jeopardy...
Tamaki, I'm so sorry!
What should I do?
By the way, this guy is acting
so flippant right now,
as if nothing happened
between me and Tamaki...
Uhm,
did you really not notice it at all?
...About Tamaki.
You see, Tamaki...
Caramel sweet rolls right here!
To tell the truth, she...
Oh, do you want some anpans?
Anpans?
This is not the right time to talk about food!
What about lemonade or dried squid?
What are you picking?
Let's see... I'll go with a sweet roll,
lemonade and dried squid!
And a candy, too!
Sure, here you are!
Welp, I missed my chance.
I just can't help it when food gets involved.
Here I go!
Let's go-go-go!
Ushi, stop here.
Yessir!
That high school skirt
is the same as Benio's one.
Good eye, as a Kabuki dancer,
clothes are your turf.
Hey, wait a minute, schoolgirl!
May I ask you one thing?
Oh,
you're Benio's henchman, we saw at school.
And you must be Ranmaru, right?
Oh!
You are well informed!
Then let's make this short,
do you have any idea
about where Boss might be?
If it's about Benio...
Please tell us if you know it.
She's at Asakusa Opera...
Something's off.
She didn't seem alright,
from her expression.
Come on, let's hurry up!
Here I go!
After something like this,
Tamaki might cut ties with me,
I need to do something...
Love is full of kindness
A flower in the meadows
Tamaki loves Shinobu,
Not even under summer sun
and I am Shinobu's fiancée,
but I don't feel anything for him.
Letting itself wilt
Well, it shouldn't be a hard fix!
Permeated with warm thoughts
Hey! Shinobu!
Uh?
What's the matter?
Rushing through my chest
I have a proposal...
A proposal? What is it?
Let's cancel this nonsense!
Not ever transfixed in doubt
Our wedding and stuff.
Huh!?
Louder!
Not even as winter comes
In my young heart,
What kind of pathology is that?
Can you ever do anything but laugh?!
You are the only one
Damn you, you're always laughing at me!
More, more!
Play louder!
Tamaki loves you, like, for real.
She loves you!
Uh?
Did you say something?
It's Tamaki!!
I barely hear you!
You want to eat tamarind?
Tamaki is...
head over heels
in love with you!
Oh God,
everyone heard it...
Gulps.
I swear, the audience these days...
Love is full of kindness
A flower in the meadows
Not even under summer sun
Letting itself wilt
Permeated with warm thoughts
Getting to know that Tamaki likes me
all of a sudden...
Rushing through my chest
What? Could you raise your voice a bit?
Not ever transfixed in doubt
It is such a sudden news...
Not even as winter comes
Don't you feel bad, though?
Huh?
Don't you feel bad, though!?
In my young heart,
W-Well...
Tamaki has always loved you,
then wouldn't it be better if she was the one marrying you?
You are the only one
There's no way I could do it!
God, why are you so pigheaded?
Hey, it's getting interesting over there!
I should be the one saying this to you!
W-What did you say?
Now is not the time for negotiations!
I mustn't give up.
I'll get attention back through my skills...
Love is full of kindness
Oh, so you're saying that you don't care about
my friendship with Tamaki?
A flower in the meadows
No, I'm not saying that...
Then what are you saying? Tell me!
Not even under summer sun
You're right, nicely said, go you!
Oh my,
Letting itself wilt
aren't those my favorite sweet rolls?
No, you thief!
Permeated with warm th-
I'm gonna kill them! Kill them all!
Be over with this cursed audience!
Hey, please, calm down, Primadonna!
Kill you! Kill you!
Take this!
Here Comes the High Collar Lady Complete Edition
UFO!
Causing all the fuss and sneaking away?
Never come back!!
Weee!
Here I go!
Go-go-go-go!
Boss!
Benio...
Please, hang in there, Boss!
Sweet rolls... Sweet rolls...
Why is Benio a bundle of trouble
wherever she goes?
What is going to happen tomorrow?
Tamaki's one-sided love
and getting to know Shinobu's story
will lead to a lot of sad moments.
Benio, upon realizing it,
decided to quit the high collar way.
And now she's determined to make the marriage fall apart
by looking as disagreeable as possible.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Godspeed, Bride in Training! Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Ziusudra
Perevodildo