Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Wherever our High Collar Lady goes,
trouble is sure to follow.
Even after hearing
Shinobu's tearful story,
the fact she learned of his grandmother
complex only made her decision firmer.
Moreover, in order to support
Tamaki's one-sided love,
Benio decided to make a mockery of her
lessons in manners to break off her marriage.
Who will the goddess
of fortune smile upon?
Episode 6
A Fleeting Wedding March
Howdy there!
Are you Shinobu's nanny?
Benio's the name.
What in the world...
Oh? You look white as a sheet.
What's wrong?
Hey, what's wrong?
Young Lady,
what are you wearing?
What's the big fuss?
I decided to get all dressed
up for the big day is all.
W-We, as nobles, are taught to
maintain composure at all times...
Oh, that so?
Benio, we need to talk.
Please follow me.
Sure!
What could it be, Daddy?
Mrs. Kisaragi,
we humbly beg you to forgive us!
It must have been
tough to raise her.
Indeed.
You say somethin'?
Here we go! Go, go, go, go, go!
Get outta my way!
Hey, who d'ya think you are?!
You can't just stop in the middle of the road!
Oh, well, if it's a bother,
feel free to go around.
Wh-What was that?!
Hey! Do you know
who you're talkin' to?!
Listen up! I may not look like much, but I'm Boss Benio's top henchman, the one and only Ushigorou!
I am in service of Lady Benio,
the future young lady of the house.
Lady Benio? The young lady
of the house? You don't mean—
You're from the Ijuuin family?!
No way!
Yes way, I assure you.
They're tryin' to take the boss away!
Benio.
Oh come on, Father,
no need to be so formal.
This...
is the only promise that I had made
to your mother before she passed away.
Mother?
That's right.
A white mourning dress...
Indeed. It symbolizes a woman's
vow to never re-marry.
But why are you showing me
this all of a sudden, Father?
Your mother didn't
need to wear this dress,
but you're going to marry a soldier—
if something tragic happens,
you'll have to do it.
Never get married again...
Am I supposed to follow that?
Isn't it obvious?
Unless you object to it?
But...
Hey!
Don't tell me you'd start a new life
with another man if Shinobu died!
Father, I'm not even married and
you're already acting like I'm a widow.
You see, you'll soon become a member of
the Ijuuin family, so you will seldom visit here.
Father, you see...
About Shinobu...
W-Wait!
Benio, take care of yourself.
But, Father...
Tsk! Ugh...
You're bad luck!
Have a little of this, some of this,
and a little of this too!
Wh-Why are you throwing salt?!
This is a luxurious foreign car!
Well, what do you expect?!
You're trying to kidnap the boss!
Kidnap? How dare you!
What are you blabbering about?!
Yeah, you heard me!
You wanna piece of me?!
If you've got a problem,
Ushigoro will take you on any time!
Salty...
What d'ya expect?! You think you
could go up against the boss?
You'd better remember that taste!
Givin' up already?
Exhaust gas... I didn't predict this!
Getting married off like this was never in my plans...
Yet everyone begs me to do it...
Benio...
Oh, Ranmaru, what are you doing there?
Benio, so, after all...
After all, you're getting married, right?
Ranmaru...
It's unfair! It's so unfair!
C-Come on, dummy!
I won't let myself get married that easily!
I'll be back home in no time!
Really, Benio?
I can guarantee you they'll kick me out right away.
Thank God, Benio!
I-I... I...
Boss! Boss!
Huh? Ushigorou?
What happened all of a sudden?
Boss...
Oh, come on, Ushi!
Boss, what's that look for...
Starting a call girl biz?
Call girl biz?!
Excuse me!?
Watch your mouth.
Benio...
Ranmaru, you don't need to worry that much.
It's just apprenticeship.
After being evicted, I'll go home very soon.
Really?
Thank God!
Hey, Benio,
if everything goes well, after being back home,
you could be my wife.
What, Ranmaru?
Ah... ouch, ow-ow-ow...
Until then, I'll learn to cook
your favorite grilled chicken,
and all kind of dishes.
I'll train to become a top-notch chef!
Man, this conversation's going all over the place.
So,
would you become my wife?
I... don't know how to answer.
Young Lady!
W-What is it, Nanny?
It's about time to head out.
Are you ready to go?
Yes. I am, Nanny.
I have to go. See you, Ranmaru.
Wait!
Benio!
Somehow, it looks like she'll be gone forever...
Aaah! It's so depressing!
Tsk!
Man, you sure are annoying.
At this rate, if Benio doesn't come back...
No, no, no!
What should I do?
Ushi, I have to do something!
Hey, don't touch me!
It feels awful!
Anchin missed Princess Kiyo...
she went crazy.
Yaoya Oshichi was lovesick, too...
As was Onatsu Kyouran...
I feel all of you.
There he goes again,
confusing reality and fiction with one another!
Take good care, Benio.
Father...
Please, don't be so sad...
I'll be kicked out in no time, after all!
Benio...
Nanny, look after Father, okay?
Young Lady, take care of yourself!
Boss, see you!
Benio!
Good morning, madam.
Oh, it's you, Tamaki, welcome.
Today is a beautiful day, aren't you going outside?
Yes,
I was walking past here, so I thought of stopping by.
Such wonderful flowers!
They smell so nicely...
Is there any special occasion, madam?
Indeed, Shinobu's fiancée is coming over.
So, it's Benio...?!
Uh, I mean, is it Lady Hanamura Benio?
Yes.
Ah, that's right,
she's your classmate, isn't she?
Yes.
Then, I can imagine you know her rather well.
Certainly, we're close friends, after all.
Then, could you tell
me how the young lady is like?
Well, let's see...
I don't know what it is going to take,
but I'll act as rude as humanly possible!
She's very kind, also...
Boss Benio's ride
Boss!
Hey, Boss,
wait for me, Boss!
Hey, hey, here we go!
Let's go!
...and her acquaintances are wonderful people too...
Who's pulling that rickshaw over there?
That's my henchman.
Henchman?
Any complaints?
What's with this girl?
Why is she, of all people, the chosen one to marry the poor Young Master...
Judging from this shocked expression...
I already have a 1-point lead!
No, I won't give in.
Until marriage, I'll do what it takes for her to be taught properly.
Benio, do your best.
I'll be cheering for you
in your engagement-breaking mission!
We're still far from
the Ijuuins' residence, aren't we?
No, we're already inside the mansion.
But isn't this just a forest?
No, this is part of the estate, too.
Look, the mansion is over there.
A castle?!
No way! I had no idea they were this rich...
Benio...
Please do your best, for my sake, too.
Hey, make way!
Go-go-go-go! Boss!
Huh?
He's Benio's faithful henchman...
He could be a decisive hand on this game.
Oh, excuse me!
Boss!
No, I can't stand mutts at all!
Calm down, please...
Look at my face, I'm not suspicious at all!
Ushigorou!
If your face is not suspicious,
then I don't know whose is!
Hey, Tamaki!
Enough laughing, I may be in danger!
Is that so...?
The Ijuuins' guard dogs are
very faithful, they bite all strangers without hesitation.
Oh, then, I'm Boss Benio's
most faithful guard, aren't I?!
So, let's negotiate, shall we?
What I'm trying to say is,
we're like the same pack of dogs, right?
Please do something about it, Tamaki!
Oh?
It's the first time
that I've seen Ushigorou so frightened.
It's kind of cute, isn't it?
Well, shall I escort you to the mansion?
L-Lady Benio?
Young Lady, you may come in.
Whaddya think of the young lad...
I needa young lad!
Keep cool, we're on the same side!
Tamaki, please do something, I...
Tenmaru, Chimaru.
This man might look threatening,
but he's far from that.
It's just a wrong impression!
Was that a compliment or an insult?
Ushigorou, these dogs are actually very smart.
They'd be eager to hear you introduce yourself.
Huh? Introducing myself?
Oh! Sure, just leave it to me!
Hear me out, hear me out.
I'll make it short.
Just like the great Musashi, I was born
in Hanakawado, on the district of Asakusa.
I took an oath of serving Boss Benio...
I'm the one and only Ushigorou...
D-Don't misjudge me! Don't...
Take it easy, take it easy...
Help me!
Mr. Shinobu is still
busy and hasn't come back yet,
so please wait here for a while.
Whoa, how splendid!
Clean as a new pin!
This is incredible!
Maybe I went a little overboard with this style.
Well, who cares.
My goal is to act unsavory,
and get properly kicked out.
No need to hold back.
Hm?
Oh, a cigar!
I'd love a box like this.
What are you doing?
Oh, you must be my stand-in.
Huh?
I work here as a chef assistant!
But it's almost time for my
wedding soon, so I'll have to resign.
Hey, you...
If you're my stand-in, why are you here?
The kitchen is right in this direction!
So you're saying that you think that
I look like a chef assistant, don't you?
Yeah, so what?
Yahoo! I made it!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Hey, what the hell are you doing!?
You sicken me!
What a strange act...
Hey you, get a grip!
Yeah, I sure will!
Thanks to this misunderstanding, I now feel fully confident!
It's so flat...
I lost my confidence already!
Well, there sure is nobody dwelling there.
I guess this is what
kept company to Shinobu as a kid.
Is she Young Master's future wife?
She doesn't have the look of the position!
I feel bad for him!
This is such an old mansion...
W-What's this strange sound?
It's... getting closer!
Sure, the mansion may be old,
but it's not haunted, or is it?
It must be a joke!
What?
It's just another set of armor.
Anyways, it's good craftsmanship.
En garde!
Ouch!
Oh?
"Made in Japan" armors can speak, too?
It's amazing!
Oh, it moves its eyes, too!
Alright, let's see if it's ticklish.
Hey, come on...
Stop! It tickles.
Oh! It's like the thing's alive.
I wonder if it's part of the service.
Stop, enough games!
Halt now!
There's someone in there!
I need to teach you a lesson. Get ready!
Our High Collar Lady is about to get
acquainted with a rusty lance...
What kind of foe wields it?
An armored warrior appears before Benio,
but the man under the helmet
is none other than Count Ijuuin.
In other words, an intrepid Samurai of Satsuma!
He dislikes Benio from the get-go.
As a problem can hide another, the High Collar-style
engagement-breaking mission takes on water!
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Count, Forgive Me"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it gets so hard to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
when he goes away, I want him to turn around,
to give me a loving glance one more time
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Editing
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing, TLC
MartyMcflies
TougeWolf
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo