Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Our blooming apprentice bride
had to face a fully armored warrior who attacked her out of the blue,
as she doesn't know how to tame anyone but dogs.
Alone and without support,
a beautiful and luxurious room can't comfort her.
Now she's in dire straits because
she doesn't know Western manners at all!
What will you do?
What will you do, High Collar Lady?
Episode 8
I Won't Weep 'til I Win!
Young Lady!
Lunch is ready!
Ah, right... I forgot.
Silly me. I need to remind myself
that she's not in this house anymore.
Making food for Benio
even when she's with the Ijuuins...
How thoughtful of her.
Oh, Benio, my beloved...
Nanny, aren't there one too many plates?
Ah, yes, I don't know what's gotten into me.
It hurts to see them,
so please put them away.
No, it's a kagezen for Lady Benio.
A kagezen, huh?
"Kagezen" is a term used to define
a meal made for an absent person.
Maybe I'm drinking a bit too much.
That's right.
Since I made her favorite grilled chicken...
Ma'am, the Young Lady is now with the Ijuuins,
and I'm certain that she'll be
eating lots and lots of delicious food.
May she be well.
What should I do? I don't know...
I don't know any Western manners!
Don't worry. Go ahead, Lady Benio.
Easier said than done.
This evening, our cook
truly did his best to impress you.
Go ahead, eat as much as you desire.
Well, I'm hungry, so...
But even if I wanted to...
How am I supposed to use
this small blade and this rake?
Well, as long as it's just soup,
I should be fine. Ah, this ladle should do.
Shinobu.
Shinobu, dear.
What is it, Grandmother?
Now that your fiancée is finally here,
we should choose the day in
which we'll announce your engagement.
Y-Yeah, t-that's right.
Bingo!
Nobody will notice me
since they're too busy chattering.
Now's my chance!
Delicious!
Nice!
Very good!
Huh?
Uh-oh...
That didn't go well.
The dish wasn't that special, right, Benio?
Is there an issue, Ma'am?
What...?!
Oh no, my ladle-
Oh, I'm so careless!
Excuse me.
W-Wait!
C-Crap...
My only means of eating!
That waiter better remember this.
Disrespecting food is terrifying!
Oh, is something the matter?
Was the food not good?
N-No, it's not that!
As expected of a vassal's daughter.
You barbarians don't know Western manners!
Come on, it's not nice to make fun of her!
Shinobu.
Benio.
Just watch me.
Okay.
Let's see... The mini-sword on my right hand
and the mini-rake on my left one...
I got it!
This looks tasty...
What sort of hellish sound is that?
Ah, right...!
Excuse me.
Oh, whoops!
So this is how you do it...
Well then, let's toast—the Western way!
She's completely clueless...
Oh? What did I do wrong...?
This is such a hilarious show!
A woman who doesn't know Western manners at all
should not be allowed to step into this house!
She'd better go home right away!
Well said.
Kisaragi!
Check me out! I won!
I'm already leading by one point!
I'm so angry!
I can't stand that old geezer!
What's that? Am I bad just because
I don't know Western manners?
That idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
In the end, I didn't manage to
eat anything and my stomach is still empty!
I'm such a fool...
Why'd I ever come here?
If only I were home right now...
Here you go, help yourself.
Bon appetit!
Grilled chicken... Benio's favorite...
I still need to accept that the
Young Lady's not here anymore...
Oh? So this is the Boss's favorite dish...
Yum! This rocks!
Benio... What are you doing now?
Right... Worry after worry,
I'm going to lose weight.
For real?
Me too!
I spent the day crying and worrying for her.
Hey, Nanny, what kind of things do
they teach at marriage apprenticeship?
Let's see,
in such a renowned noble family...
Cleaning,
sewing,
cooking, and all sorts of female duties.
They'll educate her in all aspects.
Will the Boss manage to learn all of that?
That's out of the question.
I know, right?
I can't bear it... thinking about
Benio getting scolded is painful.
Ushi!
You're eating without a care in the world!
You dummy!
N-Nanny, where is
the Ijuuin mansion located at?
It should be there.
Boss! I, the goldfish-tattooed Ushigorou,
will come to rescue you tomorrow morning!
M-Me too! Hang in there, Benio!
I'm starving...
This is stupid, I'm going home.
Who'd ever want to stay in such a place?
Who is it?
It's me!
Good evening, Benio.
Shinobu...
I brought some food.
You must be hungry, right?
Here you are.
I'll place it here.
U-Um, Shinobu...
I'll be heading home!
Where did that come from?
U-Um...
Because I've decided so!
I can't keep on going like this.
I had planned to make a mess
of your house and get kicked out...
You probably despise me now.
Interesting. So what's next?
It's not looking like I can do it!
S-So...
So you're turning tail
and retreating? It's not like you.
But I don't think I'll ever get used to this
atmosphere, and I don't know any manners.
Shinobu...
Benio, you see...
What is it?
I think that...
you could bring
some fresh air in this family.
Fresh air?
Correct.
Some fresh air in this old house.
Remember what I told you.
Neither my grandmother nor my father could
marry the person they loved of their own free will.
If there's anyone who could rid this
old house of its dull customs, it's you, Benio.
But, Shinobu...
In any case, giving in for
so little is not very high collar-like.
Ah, and also,
since it'll probably
take you a while to sleep...
I brought you some of my books.
Read it if you'd like to.
Well, it's already late,
so hurry up and go to bed.
Shinobu, I...
Good night.
At any rate, it's finally time to eat!
Delicious!
It looks like I got won over again.
As Shinobu says, giving up
this easily would be frustrating.
What kind of books does he read?
K-Kant?
Hegel? Schopenhauer? Dialectics?
I don't understand a thing!
What's this?
"I think, therefore I am."
What the hell is this?
Ah, I'm getting sleepy.
Asking me to mess up his own house...?
What a weirdo.
Wake up! Wake up!
What-what-what?
W-W-W-W-Wha...?!
Is there a fire?
It's time to wake up.
Wake up?
But it's only four.
Indeed.
It's the habit in our residence.
Why do I need to wake up this early?
I'm neither a postman nor a natto salesman.
From today on,
you'll be learning wifely duties.
In order to become a nobleman's wife,
you'll need to get acquainted
to all the household duties—
from top to bottom!
Now hurry up and get ready!
Let's start by cleaning the main hall.
Oh?
These two girls will be helping me, right?
That's right.
Oh, so you're kind sometimes, too.
I don't know much,
so excuse me in advance.
Go! Don't hold back!
Yes, ma'am!
What are you doing?
Your assistance ends here!
Yes.
Ah...
Darn, I should've
expected something like this.
I don't care if you're a Yakuza wannabe
or whatever. You're firmly in my grip now!
Be it doing the laundry or cooking,
I, Fujieda Ranmaru, can handle any wifely duty!
Forward! Let us aid Benio in this time of need!
Help is on the way!
Get outta my way! Go-go-go-go-go!
Hey, Ushi, why'd you stop?
Ask those dudes!
Now start cleaning!
Eat this!
I don't mean to brag,
but cleaning's always been my weak point.
Benio!
Ugh, I lost my lead.
A-And now, cooking!
Do I have to peel them all?
Of course.
Ugh, she really hates me.
Ushi, don't you
understand what we came here for?
I-If you want to complain, do it to these dogs!
Phew. I'm done.
It's peeled!
Let's see.
A-Are these supposed to be potatoes?
Sure! Any complaints?
Be patient, be patient...
Shall I wash these dishes next, Kisaragi?
I can't let her make any more disasters!
Stop!
Oh? Already?
Enough with the kitchen. Go sew now!
I'm even worse at that!
First of all, sew a yukata.
If it's just a yukata, it's all a-ok!
Here, I'm done.
S-Should this be a yukata?
Keep calm, keep calm...
Oh, this is bad.
I forgot the iron on the cloth!
Oh no!
I completely ruined this black dress.
Whose is this?
M-i-n-e!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
It's my fault I lost three points!
Now you see why
I failed all of my domestic classes.
Oh, I should head to school now.
Kisaragi, can I have my breakfast?
This way, please.
I-In the kitchen?
Women and children eat here
according to the traditions of Satsuma.
Ack!
I can't stand this awful misogyny!
One-point lead!
I'm late!
Have a nice day.
Two-point lead.
If I arrive late,
I'll get kicked out to the hallway again!
Ushigorou! Ushigorou!
Boss!
Benio!
Why are you so slow?
I-I didn't know what to do with those dogs!
Oh, you two,
did you want to protect me?
Ah, Benio, school's
more important than that!
Ah, that's right.
Get out of my way! Let's go-go-go-go-go!
It's no good... the bell has rung.
Hey, stop, stop!
This is enough.
I'll be late if I enter normally.
Alright, understood.
Then, I'll see you later, Ushigorou!
Take care, Boss!
Come on, hurry up!
I got it!
Hop!
I saw that...
Our High Collar Lady is on her path to
becoming a good wife in her own tomboyish style.
But the road ahead is still truly, truly long for her.
Our apprentice, Benio, is getting scolded
repeatedly—just as she's about to lose it,
Shinobu once again sends
her heart fluttering with his kindness.
My, how embarrassing! But it feels good.
Unexpectedly, her sworn enemy loses
patience for her over a slip of the tongue.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"The First Palpitation"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it gets so hard to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
when he goes away, I want him to turn around,
to give me a loving glance one more time
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Editing
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing, TLC
MartyMcflies
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo