Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Ranmaru, as indistinguishable from a woman as a butterfly is from a flower,
arrived to help Benio, but unknowingly only caused her more trouble.
However, if someone exposes his disguise,
they would both be in dire straits;
so as they observe Shinobu giggling ominously, they can't help wondering if their game is up.
Following the law of "the older, the wiser,"
the Count promptly sees through Ranmaru's cover,
turning things from bad to worse.
That's when Benio seizes the moment to cut the Gordian Knot and forcefully dispel all doubts.
You're going to enter the bath with Lady Benio and rub her back.
And here we are, with troubles piling up one after another!
Episode 13
Love is a Sailboat of Reflection
Ah... That was an awfully close call, Ranmaru.
But aren't you at least glad that they didn't blow my cover?
You're right. That's what happens
when you rush things.
Excuse me, Lady Benio.
You see, the Count asks if you would like to join him for tea.
Alright, I'll be there in a minute.
Let's go,
Ranko.
Sure, Lady Benio.
Then, I'll have my leave now.
Good night, Benio.
Good night.
Oh, Ranmaru, do you have a room now?
Yes. We've got a room just for us, three maids.
Huh? Three of you?
Then, you need to be extra careful with them.
Don't worry, don't worry,
All that's left now is to go to sleep as usual.
I suppose. Today went smoothly.
See you!
As usual, with his habitual...
lily loincloth?!
I need to stop him!
Ranmaru!
Ah, I let it slip.
Ranko! Ranko!
Ranko!
What's the matter, Lady Benio?
Fancy.
Lady Benio, do you need help with something?
Ah, no, it's nothing important.
Then, let us take care
of our new friend Ranko.
T-Thank you.
What was she so panicked about?
Can you make me some grilled chicken?
Come back here. High beds aren't suited for people who turn in their sleep.
I wonder if Ranmaru tosses while sleeping.
J-Just as I thought!
Hey, Ranmaru, wake up!
Wh-What is it, Benio?
Quiet!
Young Master...
Come to my room.
Uh, why?
Do you really think they won't notice that?
G-G-Gotcha.
Hurry up.
We'll move your things tomorrow morning.
Getting to sleep in the same room as Benio...
I'm such a happy man!
You need to get down from the clouds.
It's going to be my territory here,
and your territory there.
Got it? If you breach this border,
I won't let it slide!
S-Sure thing.
Well, goodnight, Benio.
Goodnight.
Mh, it's so bright...
Come back here.
Benio, are you awake yet?
Benio!
Benio...
Huh?
Oh, so you were here, Lady Benio.
Hey, good morning!
Ranko, why are you giving me that kind of look?
Benio used to be such a late riser...
I can't believe this is happening.
Lady Benio, what is it you're doing here?
What am I doing?
What does it look like? I'm sweeping.
Masters should delegate this kind of work to their subordinates!
Why do you think you have maids in this house?
I still need to have some general idea of what our numerous servants' work is like.
Wait, Lady Benio!
Hey, who gave that order?
It was Kisaragi.
I'll remember it, you old hag!
It's not like she makes me do this out of spite,
that woman is just devoted to her duties.
No, I'll give her a piece of my mind!
Oh, come on, why be so vindictive?
What are you saying?
Wasn't making a mess of this place
your original goal here?
Good morning!
Good morning, everyone.
Well done.
Who arranged this flower?
Who was it?
Uhm, I...
No. It doesn't resemble your style.
So as I was saying, I ordered Ranko to do it.
Did you arrange all the vases here?
Yes.
You've done an excellent job.
Well, that sounds about right. Ahem...
However, you did something unnecessary!
If you keep doing it for Lady Benio,
she'll never learn herself!
From tomorrow morning on, refrain from unnecessary actions! Is that clear?
I asked Ranko for it, so I'm to blame!
No, it's my fault for answering it.
Both of you must abide
by your own roles. Is that clear?
Mrs. Kisaragi!
There's a loose thread on your dress.
There, I cut it.
Sorry for the holdup.
Thank you.
Wha-What is that?!
I've been so careless!
How disgraceful of me!
Today, you'll learn how to compose haiku.
By mixing simple and transient,
with enough practice, you can even reach the zen.
This is the essence of haiku.
Here is a poem by Matsuo Basho.
"Frogs jump;
water splashes;
old pond."
This is one of his best known haikus.
Fly, my pretty.
... for this reason ...
Gross!
Oh my!
Ranko...
I just wrote one too.
"Old pond;
old hag jumps;
splashes all over;
fourth line."
Even with my enormous experience
of posing as a woman,
the way women's clothing is
still doesn't rock my boat.
Luckily, there's no one around,
so here's my chance!
Ah... This must be men's heaven.
Oh no! Mrs. Kisaragi, you look ghastly!
Don't you need some rest?
She... She's taking a—
Here's a special massage just for such cases.
R-Run away!
I-I swear I just saw that Ranko
relieving herself like a man.
It can't be real! It's too disgusting.
I need to collect myself.
Ever since Lady Benio came here, I've been feeling more and more worn out.
Oh, my roses, always a welcome sight.
You've bloomed wonderfully
with the proper upkeep.
No, th-that's where...
Lord, stay away!
Huh? Why should I stay away?
Sh-She just...
Relieved herself here! No!
Hm? You've been acting weird recently.
Go see a doctor if that helps!
No, I assure you, you needn't
concern yourself with that.
Such a fine smell!
This is hopeless...
Ranmaru, can't you be a little more careful?
I just answered nature's call.
What happened, Boss?
One way or another, you need to follow at least some basic etiquette.
Benio, can you hear what you're saying?
The reason we all came here
was to break your engagement as soon as possible, remember?
Right, right. Isn't that right, Boss?
Well, yes...
If so, let's not hold back and raise all hell
to get the boot in the shortest term.
Hell yeah! Truth be told, I've been itching for action like mad, Boss!
There, see? What better time will we have to put our plan into action?
I guess you can't avoid the unavoidable.
Right! The best way to go about the farewell show
is doing it with one big flashy bang!
I suppose. If it came to this,
we might as well go medieval.
Attaboy! Let's put our backs into it and level this place in record time!
Exactly! I'm so glad I can count on you, Ushi!
I'm your Huckleberry!
Shinobu... So this is goodbye.
Hm? That sound...
Boss Hanamura Benio's Dwelling
Alright! I'm done.
Looks good to me.
Oh my! Ushigorou!
What did you come up with this time?
What's it look like? It's a signboard.
A signboard, cantcha see?
W-What's the meaning of this...
With this, the whole world will know
where to find Boss!
It ain't the only one!
Now, lemme show you. Here!
This is for her personal chambers.
Boss Hanamura Benio's Bedroom
And this is for the lavatory.
Boss Hanamura Benio's Toilet
You unruly brute...
C'mon! Just kidding, just kidding!
I say, you know a thing or two about style, Mrs. Kisaragi! I really like it!
Silence!
Leave immediately!
Oh no, you're so scary!
You bastard! Making a fool of me!
I'll chop your head off!
Oh no! Time to skedaddle!
Wait!
I'll get you!
Hey, you shouldn't be swinging that!
You coward!
Help!
Boss was right, messing with that grandma is always a load of fun!
Scoundrel...
Stop right there!
I said stop!
I ain't stopping! Here we go!
Stop!
You villain! Stop!
Stop, you skunk!
Like hell!
I ain't losing to you!
Huh?!
How'd it come to this?
Oh my.
Kisaragi, what in the world happened?
Your eyes are bloodshot,
what is the matter?
No, it's just that...
Oh my! What do you need that for?
No... No reason.
Don't you think you need some rest, Kisaragi?
N-Not really...
Adjusting to all the changes in our way of life caused
by Benio's arrival was probably exhausting for you.
N-No, something this trifling wouldn't bother me.
We're making steady progress in Lady Benio's education.
Good. That is most relieving to hear.
How strange. That must be Tenmaru and Chimaru barking, and it comes from inside the house.
What was that? Did something
just sweep through the corridor?
Uhm...
My eyesight is rather poor these days,
what did it look like?
Right... That was... Well...
It's the dogs!
Young Mistress hitched the dogs
to the rickshaw!
Kisaragi! Hang on! Kisaragi! Somebody!
I see, I see.
The brain appears strained.
Actually, I see considerable overall exhaustion.
She needs to rest for the time being.
Oh my...
Mrs. Kisaragi...
Will she really make it out okay?
I'm so worried!
Thanks.
Well, take care now.
Thank you very much!
We did it!
We finished that hag off!
I can already hear them
sending you home, Benio!
Home?
Right... I'll have to return.
Go home...
If I return home,
I'll have to live without seeing Shinobu.
that'll cut all ties between Shinobu and me.
We'll become strangers.
I'm going to miss him...
Nonsense! Why am I having such thoughts now?
I never intended to stay here in the first place.
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me that Benio...
Eek! Who's there?!
No! No! You can't come in!
Ms. Kisaragi, it's me.
My, Young Master.
I apologize.
Mrs. Kisaragi, I heard you collapsed.
It's nothing you should
concern yourself with, really.
I should be ashamed to be seen in such shape.
You shouldn't overwork yourself,
my irreplaceable Nanny.
Please take better care of yourself.
Young Master, I don't deserve such words...
You need to take breaks sometimes, Nanny.
Nanny?
So what Mrs. Kisaragi is to Shinobu
is about the same as what my Nanny is to me?
Perhaps we overdid it a little?
Your tea.
Thanks.
Here you are.
Ranmaru, your pads moved to your back
and are now vertical.
Be-Be-Be-Be-Be-Be!
Huh?! What did you say, Ranmaru?
Did someone see through your disguise?
I-I'm dead sure!
He just called me Ranmaru!
Oh no! Called it!
But why didn't he tell everyone yet?
He knew all along that I let you, a boy, stay so close to me,
that we sleep and wake up
in the same room every night.
He also knows full well that Ranmaru loves me,
which means my fidelity might be at risk every second.
And yet he was never worried about it...
I guess...
He couldn't care less about me, after all.
He loves me,
he loves me not;
he loves me,
he loves me!
He loves me not...
Flowers are scattering
and delusions are intensifying.
Love is a sailboat of reflection.
Shinobu!
Invincible in battle, High Collar Lady
just proved powerless against love ruminations.
Unable to understand Shinobu's feelings,
our restless High Collar Lady
stumbles across a trio of thugs.
But in the heat of the moment,
none of them realizes that she is unmatched in battle.
She's always quick to draw her weapon
and show off that tomboyish two-handed fencing.
All of a sudden, geisha Kichiji,
who's in love with Shinobu, appears.
Next time on "Here Comes the High Collar Lady":
Two Bewildered Flowers.
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CrashOveride
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CrashOveride