Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Ranmaru and Ushigorou raced against time
to stop Benio from yet another drunken frenzy,
but, as expected, she's a lost cause
when she has to deal with angry soldiers
and their efforts go up in flames!
The ever so sagacious countess, sensing that Benio tried to become a geisha for the whole family's sake,
cried heartfelt tears of gratitude.
The count, after eavesdropping by chance,
said that he doesn't like collecting swords anymore: what a beautiful lie!
Now that you're the closest
you've ever been with your family,
what job are you planning to go for next,
High Collar Lady?
Episode 35
Beautiful Lies
With all the maids and servants laid off,
my work has doubled.
But I'll do whatever it takes
for the Master's family...
Here we are...
Whew, I'm beat...
Hm?
Oh?
My!
Lady Benio is working for two,
tending to both schoolwork and housework.
The least I can do is lend her a hand.
Finally finished.
Oh? I wonder who did it for me?
Was it the countess?
Or was it Ms. Kisaragi?
Hey, Ushigorou. Stop for a moment.
Roger!
Didja forget something, Boss?
I'm sorry, could you raise the tent?
What? The tent, ya said?
Close it from the front as well.
Gotcha. Like this, Boss?
If you peep, I'll give you no quarter, Ushigorou.
R-Roger.
Boss! We'll be late if we dawdle about here.
Hm... Surely she ain't sleeping, is she?
Okay, you can raise the front now!
Aye-aye!
And up...
What do you think? It suits me, doesn't it, Ushigorou?
Huh?! Are ya gonna skip school again?
I don't have the time
to twiddle my thumbs at school.
I need to work.
Let's go job hunting.
Oh no... 'Tis not the life
a high-school girl ought to be living...
Oh woe is me!
Oh my, Ushigorou is in tears.
Did I make you cry?
Th-This ain't no joke! I feel so bad
for what ya gotta go through!
Don't worry about it. To tell you the truth,
I've never been good at studying in the first place.
Still, you can't let the Ijuuins know
that I'm not going to school.
I know, I know, Boss!
It should be around here...
Ah! This must be the place!
Compunny
Huh? Which way does this door actually open?!
Doesn't work if I push it, doesn't work if I pull it!
Come on!
And it's open!
Um, excuse me?
Um...
What do you want?
You see, I got your door off the hinges.
What? You tried to open it by pulling?
This door slides open.
See?
What a bizarre publishing house...
In any case, what are you here for?
If it's for the bar bill,
you've caught me at a bad time.
Come another time.
Ah, I'm not a bill collector.
You see, Ms. Kichiji—
No... Kichiji from the House of Flowers Restaurant
said you were looking for a reporter...
What?
Didn't you hear me?
Sheesh. So young and yet
already hearing impaired?
You see! I'm here for a job!
What? You're looking for a job?
You, a woman?
Huh?
I refuse!
I told her to only send men our way.
None of the jobs we offer are open to women!
How rude!
Women are just as capable
as men for this work!
What's more, my late mother
was a journalist!
Oh? Was that mother of yours
anything like to you?
N-No... If anything,
I resemble my father way more.
Figures.
Either way, I'm a male chauvinist
through and through.
There's no way I'll ever hire a woman.
Begone!
What the hell?! You can't just
look down on women like that!
I'm too busy to be babysitting you.
I have work to do.
Oh? I see.
Long story short,
you're scared witless, aren't you?
If a woman managed to do her job just fine,
it would undermine the authority
of the men here, am I right?
Wh-What was that?!
You heard me right!
Editing office of Compunny here. Yes, it's me.
What? Housewives in Ushigome?
They're besieging a rice dealer?
Hey, wake up, people!
Listen up, woman.
Huh?
For a trial, you go cover what's happening.
An impeccable article will land you this job.
What?! Really?
Now we're talking!
I'll cover everything!
Bye! See you later!
Are you sure, editor-in-chief?
Sending her out to cover a civil unrest incident?
Yeah, even a man wouldn't be safe
in such a situation.
She'll just come back in tears.
Whatever, let her go.
She wouldn't have given up otherwise.
Give us our rice!
We have no food!
Due to a recession, rice prices started to skyrocket around August 1918.
What was widespread dissatisfaction
turned into revolts, with over 700,000 people protesting nationwide.
So this is what besieging is...
We want our rice! Give us the rice!
Excuse me...
What is it? I'm busy right now!
Moreover, it's dangerous to loiter around here!
There!
Get this!
Where's our rice, huh?!
How did it come to this?
How could it not come to this?!
With the war being so costly, the country is now in recession
and people are struggling to make ends meet...
On top of it, when we talk to rice dealers,
they just hold onto their rice and hike the prices up.
All of this despite having storehouses full of rice!
They're heartless monsters.
Uh-huh. "Hike prices up..."
Tomorrow, I won't have enough rice
to feed my children!
This is just not fair!
Man up! Let's smash that storehouse to pieces!
I'd do it right away,
but at the same time, take a look at that.
There's no way that door will ever budge!
Ugh... If they don't hurry, the police will come!
How weak...
Missus, help me push that cart.
Quick! Now place that log on it!
Tie it firmly to the cart!
Don't waste any time!
L-Like this?
We did as you said, Young Lady.
By the way, just who are you?
I don't recall ever seeing you around here.
I'm a magazine reporter
who came to cover this protest.
What?
What was that?!
So you're just inciting us
to spice up your article?
Exactly, we ain't falling for your tricks!
What are you saying?!
You have no more than a couple of minutes to break in before the flatfoots arrive!
And then you won't see any rice at all!
Or perhaps you're fine
with your kids starving?
So, what are you going to do?!
Answer, everyone!
Are we doing this or not?
Can you guys call yourselves real men?
Let's do it!
Hey, we're doing it!
Let's go!
We can do it!
Okay, ready?
Yeah!
Let's join our forces to smash through the gate!
Alright! We'll follow your orders!
Get ready to charge!
There!
Charge!
Go!
We're in!
Yes! Our rice!
Quick! Grab as much as you can!
Hey! It's the cops! Run!
Run! Run away! Flee!
Quick, everyone! Run away!
Give us rice!
Ah! Missus!
Run away, Missus!
Thank you!
Hey, you!
Resisting an officer, you punk?
Huh? You think we'll let you run away?!
Catch her!
Hey you, come down immediately!
Don't you dare put up a fight!
There!
Yes, Compunny Editorial Office here.
Huh? One of our employees?
What? She assisted the rioters
and got arrested?!
Hello?
This lady here said
she works for your magazine,
however, she doesn't have any papers on her.
I suspected she's just pretending to be a reporter.
In that case, she'll be prosecuted—
No, she's not pretending!
Ueno Police Station
They released her!
Thank you, Young Lady!
Well done.
You're our new hero!
Thanks to you, my children
were able to eat their fill of rice, Young Lady.
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
Company motto:
Bow to the strong
Punish the weak
Compunny
I'm sorry. I was supposed to just observe,
but I just couldn't help it...
People are struggling, but all rice dealers
can think about is making money.
So you decided to break into the storehouse with them?
Y-Yes, I suppose...
Is it really that funny to you?!
From what I can see, you're the hot-blooded kind who easily gets carried away.
Well, I can't really deny that...
Journalists can never
lose their cool and objectivity.
With this attitude, you'll never be one.
Fine by me! I guess I'm just
a scatterbrain then! Goodbye!
H-Hey!
Why am I like this?
I embarrassed myself and also Kichiji, who introduced me.
What should I do?
We'll all be in dire straits if I can't find a job...
Hey, woman!
I told you to wait...
You sure are hot-blooded.
Then let me be hot-blooded in peace!
And a blunderer, too.
Sorry I ever bothered you in the first place!
Sheesh, I can't believe you're a woman.
Did you chase me
just to add insult to injury?
That's not it.
I'm willing to bet on your knack
for taking everything to heart.
You might very well grow into a reporter
like we've never seen before.
Do you think you'd be able to forget
that you're a woman while at work?
Yes...
If you work for me, I won't treat you
as a woman either. Is that fine by you?
Then you're hired. My name is Aoe Tousei.
I'm counting on you to do a good job.
I will!
Eh? What was that?
Sorry, I didn't mean to...
See you at the office tomorrow!
I'm so happy. I'm so happy!
I think I've finally found my own path!
Watch me, Shinobu.
I'm gonna do it!
And then, someday,
you'll surely come back to me!
Hello? Ijuuins' Mansion here.
This is Benio's homeroom teacher
at Atonashi School for Girls.
Huh? I-I mean, did something
happen to Lady Benio?
Yes. Lately, she's been absent almost daily.
At this rate, she may have trouble graduating.
Huh?!
But she heads out every morning saying she’s off to school… Did she skip today as well?
Yes. She was absent.
S-So she doesn't hand in her homework either?
No, Ushigorou always delivers her homework.
That's all we ever hear from her.
Ah...
I'm well aware of Benio's
extremely difficult situation,
but her graduation from school
is only six months away.
It's my duty to let you know.
Thank you for your time.
Kisaragi, is something wrong?
Ah, Madam... It's about Benio.
Oh? What's wrong with Benio?
She doesn't show up at school at all.
Huh? Why would she do that?!
Madam, it must be because
Lady Benio is too busy working.
Oh my...
So Benio is working?
Didn't she try to become
a geisha the other day?
She was so mortified,
she couldn’t help but try to cover it up...
Yes. That's the kind of person Lady Benio is.
Please forgive me, Benio.
This needs to stop today.
Let's ask Benio to quit working.
No use. Lady Benio only ever
follows the call of her own heart.
Huh?
Lady Benio has done more
for the Ijuuin family than anyone else.
That is to say, for Young Master.
It’s all for Shinobu...
Yes. And I’m sure he would’ve been just as proud
of the path Lady Benio is walking now.
Very well.
We'll keep pretending
that Benio attends school diligently
and that we do not know anything at all.
Yes, ma'am. It's a necessary lie.
Ushigorou, stop!
Raise the tent.
Aye-aye.
Ushigorou.
Huh?
Nobody must know that I have a job now.
Yeah, I remember.
I'll pretend
I'm diligently attending classes.
Right...
The Count and Countess
don't need any extra worries. Got it?
Aye-aye, Boss.
Rest assured, I gotcha.
I'm home!
Oh, welcome back.
Welcome back, Lady Benio.
You see, I played tennis
with my classmates after school.
This is why I'm a bit late.
If so, why don't you take a bath at once
and follow it up with an abundant dinner?
S-Sure.
Whatever I get to eat...
Ushigorou.
Huh?
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Shine her shoes.
Lady Benio is going to use them
again tomorrow, right?
No, uh, that's not... That's...
I know everything, Ushigorou.
And Countess too.
Wh-Wha—?! So we've been exposed?!
Yes. But let's not tell Lady Benio
that we know the truth.
R-Right...
Graduation is just around the corner
and school life has become merrier
than ever these days.
My, I'm delighted to hear that.
I can't handle watching her family
pretend to believe her lies!
It is often said that people live to find truth.
In this house, though,
a lie is always followed by even more lies.
But in all fairness, if they're meant to soothe others,
than what are they if not beautiful lies?
The question now is,
when will the truth come to light?
Next episode preview
Having to deal with a painful reality
and harsh family finances,
Benio is now a full-fledged member of society.
After writing her first article,
she gets carried away on the streetcar
after she notices the spitting image of Shinobu,
leaving her all-important manuscript behind.
So, what will you do next, High Collar Lady?
Next on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
First Salary with Blood, Sweat and Tears.
Don't miss it!
Episode 36
First Salary with Blood, Sweat and Tears
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC, Timing & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika