Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
After dueling, Benio used her tomboyish two-handed fencing and beat the boastful Count with ease.
These two began to celebrate,
concluding that it'd spell Benio's imminent return.
But hold your horses!
For the Count saw his long-gone son's
look in Benio's eyes, and was charmed by it.
In addition, Benio's special herbal medicine
helped the Count open his heart up to the Countess.
All of a sudden, the flame of the
elderly couple's love is rekindled.
Conversely, Benio's own betrothed doesn't seem
to mind the arranged marriage forced upon them.
You call yourself a man after that? Unforgivable!
Episode 11
Welcome to the Party of Grief
Thank you so much for today's training.
You're welcome. Make sure they perfect
that technique for next month's rehearsal.
Certainly.
Then, I'm off.
Thank you again.
Oh, it's Fujieda Ranmaru,
the young kabuki dancer!
Wow! He's fabulous!
And a young teacher, too!
Wait!
Ranmaru!
Please, wait!
Don't run away!
Wait!
Young Teacher!
Wait, wait!
We love you!
Oh, poor me.
I can't even leave after class in peace anymore.
Oh, gosh...
Why do all girls have to be like that?
No matter what they do,
I would never love a girl other than Benio.
I don't want them. No sir.
A man!
A delicious man!
Gimme a break!
Oh?
It's Ushi!
Ushi, you're a sight for sore eyes!
Ah! Ranmaru?!
I've missed you!
G-Get a grip, dammit! You're embarrassing me.
Besides, how did you
miss me if we meet everyday?
I still missed you!
Keep it to yourself.
I'm not into that kind of stuff.
W-What does that mean, Ushi?
Nah, nothin' special.
Hey, Ushi, how's Benio?
Well, you see...
Believe it or not, our manly Boss
has become unrecognizable.
She looks completely emaciated and broken.
Benio... Moving to an unfamiliar mansion
belonging to nobility was too much for you, after all.
We need to do something about it...
Ushi, please go see her at the mansion for me.
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'd gladly go there, but I don't have
to bring her to school since it's Sunday.
So you're refusing me this little favor?
Very well. It's not the end of the world.
I have my methods, too!
W-What methods?
Molester here! A molester!
I'm being molested!
He's molesting me—
I get it, I get it!
I'll go, now calm down!
And this is why you're the best!
Tsk. Geez...
What are they getting ready for?
An open-air party.
Huh? An open-air party?
You have nothing to worry about.
It's a closed door party.
Only my close friends are invited.
B-But...
They were all awfully
excited to meet my fiancée.
Ah... H-Hey, I object!
Even if I'm your fiancée, um...
Hold on!
I've still not agreed to this marriage.
No need to be so stiff about it, Benio.
D-Don't you just laugh my opinion off like that!
Why is he always so self-centered?
Jeez...
I'm so mad!
Oops, I'm sorry...
Eh?
It appears the Boss is heated today.
Ranmaru's feminine intuition was right.
Whoops!
He's a guy, but whatever. I need to inform him.
You're Ushigorou, right?
I'm in a rush, so I'll see ya later.
No, I won't tolerate it any longer.
Hey, aren't you being too rude?
Certainly, because you're
encroaching on my profession!
Whatcha sayin'?! Whaddya mean by that?
Ushigorou, please stop carrying
Lady Benio to school on your rickshaw!
H-Huh? Are you out of your tiny mind?!
She's a very important lady for this family.
Therefore, it's plainly obvious
that I escort her with the Ijuuins' car!
You bastard!
Think you can boss me around, huh?
If you don't agree soon, I'll have to!
What's the difference between
agreeing quickly and slowly, you idiot?!
Then you've agreed!
Shut up! You're just trying to sow discord
between me and the Boss, but I ain't falling for it!
I'm in a rush now, but I'll be sure to
come set things straight with you later! See ya!
That damn punk...
They should be here soon.
Oh? Well, here they are.
Whassup!
Yo!
Hey, Ijuuin, where's your fiancée?
Benio's her name, right? C'mon, introduce us!
Where's your beautiful Mädchen?
Is she the one?
"Beautiful?"
I didn't know you were into these things.
Lolita complex, right?
Yeah. Lolita complex it is!
I see, I see.
Exactly. Lolita complex,
and borderline boys' love on top of it.
B-Boys?
For boys! For boys!
What did you say?!
Apologies! I only meant to praise you.
Benio, this is Takayashiki, a buddy of mine.
He's sharp-tongued, but he's really a nice guy.
That was sharp, indeed!
Nice to meet you!
And here, it's the same Boozy Kid!
An outdoor party?
Yeah, so it seems.
In that case, lots of people are there, right?
Probably. I hope the Boss
won't feel too awkward there.
She's not so good with social skills.
If it's a party, there'll also be alcohol, right?
Could be.
Oh, shit!
The Boss has a really bad
inclination for drunken violence!
That's bad! We gotta do something!
Ranmaru, can you think of something?
Leave it to me. I have a wonderful idea!
It'll work out for sure!
I don't know why,
but I just can't stop worrying.
Cheers!
This is Takayashiki Kaname—he wants to be a poet.
Nice to meet you!
His pen name is Lionmaru.
Lion?
I-I feel like no further explanation is needed.
Good morning, everybody.
Thank you for inviting me, Shinobu.
Oh, it's the beautiful Tamaki!
Our angel!
Goddess!
Hello, everybody.
Benio, come with me for a second.
T-Tamaki!
What's with that request?
Benio, what happened
to your breaking mission?
The fight is on and
the enemy won't yield an inch...
It's a tough one.
Oh... Really?
Yeah...
But I'm still trying my best.
I'm counting on you.
Oh, ho... this conversation between classmates sure is getting lively.
Right... Benio was telling me about all
the gossips permeating the Count's mansion.
Hey, hey, you two.
Girls shouldn't abandon the party like that.
Shall we play a game?
T-Tamaki, I wrote a poem for you...
Really?
Be sure to let me read it later.
Later, huh...?
Sidelined twice, huh?
Unrequited love is the truest one.
I'll write an even better poem.
Thank you for coming today.
I hope you enjoy your time here.
Certainly.
Shinobu...
Shinobu, wait!
Shinobu!
Tamaki?
So... there's something I want to tell you.
How much longer
will you keep detaining Benio?
I know everything.
You're Benio's betrothed simply because your grandmother said so, not because you love her.
But Benio's not the right person for you.
Shinobu... There must be someone who's better
suited for you, both in their mind and descent.
So don't you feel bad for Benio going through all
the difficulties of learning to live in a noble house?
Someone's gossiping about me.
A noble house, you say?
Yes!
Right, that reminds me...
You descend...
from a noble family, too.
Yes, and?
Tamaki, you need to understand.
The fact that we were born into noble families...
The privilege of high descent—
we owe it all to chance.
And we have to live our lives brandishing it.
All I ever wanted was to escape this bizarre world.
But... ever since I met Benio,
I realized that this boundary
could be crossed, after all.
And that's what I intend to do.
She's a girl who, having seen a dream once,
can easily make that dream a reality.
In that sense, I just keep seeing dreams,
but do nothing about them.
Of course, at first, I only wanted
to do it for my grandmother.
But things have changed.
Benio has this mysterious charm...
that I've never felt in any other girl.
Shinobu—deep down, you've
always wanted someone like Benio.
Shinobu...!
There's no place for me in his heart.
I understand you now.
Tamaki...
You're a fantastic girl too,
so you'll definitely find a fantastic partner...
Please, stop.
I... have given up.
However...
Benio is my best friend.
Tamaki...
If you ever make her sad, I...
I won't forgive you!
What a bother. Where did those two go?
Oh, Shinobu!
He's never done anything like that to me!
Is she better than me?
What could those two be talking about?
Tamaki is so beautiful...
She's better suited for Shinobu than I am.
What is it?
Let's go see, Tamaki.
Right...
H-Hey, hey... Whaddya want?
What did I do?
Dammit. What's wrong with you two? Stop it!
Ijuuin!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, cut it down!
Sit down!
What's the matter with them?
No idea. By now, these dogs
should know Takayashiki rather well.
Hey, Ijuuin, do something!
I've come to this house countless times,
but I don't remember ever being barked at!
Is that so?
Benio...
Benio, you don't believe my best friend's story?
I believe the unadulterated
instinct of these two better.
They must be sensing something
abnormal about Takayashiki today.
But I can't think of anything.
I still believe these dogs.
Tenmaru, Chimaru...
Bark!
You two! Hush!
Hush!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, after him!
Hush! Hush! I'm telling you to hush!
H-Help me!
Benio, please!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, hush!
What's this?
They'd rather listen to Benio than to me...
That was close.
Hey, Takayashiki,
there's something on your back.
I-Is that so?
A wasp!
Everyone, hide!
Oh no!
I haven't taken a bath in ten days,
I'll be doomed if I get stung!
Phew! It left.
Their stings would hurt like hell.
You're such good dogs! So you weren't
barking at Takayashiki, but at the wasp?
Man, they're so smart.
Better than the military ones!
Yeah, amazing!
No, I'm shocked for an entirely different reason.
I raised Tenmaru and Chimaru
myself ever since they were puppies,
but even then, they'd
rather listen to Benio than to me.
Man, I thought it would end badly
for a second there.
Did you say you haven't bathed in ten days?
You're gross. At least take a shower.
Certainly! If you say so, Tamaki...
Yahoo!
Dear, I'd say Benio is doing remarkably well.
She must have some guts
to have tamed the dogs.
But I won't let myself be tamed!
Well, of course!
Here I go!
Man. Really, Benio never ceases to amaze me.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I spoiled the party with my sloppiness.
Oh my! You look brand new!
That's true.
Then, shall we drink?
Alright, let's do just that!
Cheers once again!
Yeah!
I am... deeply sorry, but I'll be leaving now.
Oh, Tamaki, why?
I'm not feeling too well.
I see. It's a pity.
Then, I'll tell our chauffeur to take you home.
Yes, thank you.
Okay. Th-Then, I'll escort you.
Please, Tamaki, may I have the honor?
I shouldn't see why not.
Oh! Riding with the beautiful Tamaki...
Shall we go?
Yes.
I need a ride. Tamaki needs to be
escorted home. Can you do that for me?
Yessir!
Well then, please get in.
Oh...
Ushigorou!
A rickshaw is such a fancy vehicle!
I suppose. That looks way more fun.
You can't be serious!
Ushigorou, may we?
Sure! Hop in, hop in.
I'm always happy to help
the Boss's friends! Jump right in!
Excuse me.
Ushigorou!
Yes?
In this male-dominated world, shouldn't we abide
by our spheres of influence above anything else?
Lady Benio...
Right, yeah. Understood, Boss.
Dear customers, unfortunately,
driving you is not in my competence.
You may use the car over there.
Aw, but I really wanted to ride it once...
Well, Mr. Chauffeur, they're all yours now.
R-Right, thank you so much!
Thank you, Lady Benio!
After the dogs, she won the chauffeur over!
Just an overbearing upstart.
Why won't you admit
that you've grown fond of her?
T-The hell are you saying?
Lady Benio.
Isn't Sunday my day off on the schedule?
I need you for a little different matter.
Right now?
Yes, right now and not a minute later.
What is it?
Right, you see...
We've just gotten this new maid who
insisted on becoming your personal servant.
A new maid?
Yes.
Come in!
Come closer.
From today onwards,
Lady Benio is your Master.
Greet her.
My name is Ranko.
Delighted to meet you, Master.
Ra-Ra-Ra-Ra...
Ranmaru, is that you?
An unexpected meeting
at an unexpected place.
The desire to help by any means necessary
drove the tormented Ranmaru to this.
So with her full feminine dedication—
I mean... Should I say masculine resolve?
Anyway, how will things play out for Ranko?
The desire of the tormented beauty Ranmaru,
who's now a maid in disguise,
to help Benio by any means necessary
is now becoming an inconvenience for others.
Still, he must do whatever
it takes to not reveal his true sex.
As usual, thanks to his keen look, the Count immediately starts questioning Ranmaru's true identity.
Well, this spells major trouble for him.
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Dance, Tormented Beauty"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
MartyMcflies