Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Slam!
The wandering dejected flower
blooms wildly in her drunken frenzy.
In his search for her, Shinobu checks out every public disturbance in the city.
Meanwhile, Ushigorou hurries to the Count for reinforcements,
only for him to cause even more trouble!
Are you alright, Lieutenant Colonel​?
That geezer is out of his mind!
When Shinobu finally arrives,
his jubilation is short-lived,
as the opponent happens to be none other than Shinobu's direct superior, now deeply aggrieved.
This might just be the beginning
of an endless tragedy.
Episode 19
Fleeting Happiness
Wait a second!
Uhm... Uhm, you haven't paid your bill yet.
Hey, pay her.
Sure, but...
Just shut up and pay!
Right...
So how much is it?
3 yen 50 sen, sir.
There!
Much obliged!
Oh? Running with your tail between your legs?
What?
Here, don't forget your things!
Don't you treat a soldier's soul like that!
You call that a soul?
Gimme that, Ranko.
Only a katana is fit to contain the warrior's soul!
Take a look!
My precious saber!
If that tin scrap is what our soldiers consider their soul,
the future isn't looking bright for the Japanese Army,
imbecile!
I tried to act respectfully,
on account of your age...
Asking for more?
Ah! You forgot something else.
Another piece of your soul.
Catch this!
Ouch!
You brat...
What's wrong, Lt. Col?
Benio!
You'll regret making fun of the army!
Weirdo!
Tsk! Hey, we're out of here.
That wasn't half-bad.
Alright, let's go home too.
This is a triumphant return!
Hip hip, hooray!
Geez, Count, you truly are something else!
Then, I guess we should be on our way.
Yes.
Ah, whoops. Oh, eh?
What's happening to me?
What's wrong?
Now that the fight's over,
it seems the alcohol has kicked in.
How embarrassing.
One, two, and three!
T-The Earth is spinning too fast!
Bam!
How about we return like this?
I'm shocked!
N-No way!
Don't you see how embarrassing this is?
It's just a husband carrying his wife on his back.
What's so embarrassing about it?
Wife?! Wife... He said wife...
Wife?! Wife! Wife?
Never! Never! Put me down! Down!
Ahem!
Put me down! Put me down! Down!
I think it's only fair that a husband should pay her bill.
Huh?
Won't you look for a moment
at what she's done!
Five chairs, three desks, decanters,
glasses and plates,
for a total of... A total of...
Never! Never! Let go of me!
I apologise, we'll compensate you for everything.
Just let go of me!
She ain't getting no compensation!
Why should we pay her for any of that?!
You'll hurt yourself if you keep struggling like that.
Let go of me! Put me down!
Ah! Shut up! Shut it, you all!
Ah!
Ugh...
Are you alright, Benio?
And one pillar too.
Puff
A messenger came from the mountain village...
He came from the mountain village riding a horse...
To tell everyone that the cherries had blossomed...
The double cherry blossoms on the Kurama Mountain...
The Count's looking pretty merry.
What is that chant, though?
The Kurama Tengu Noh song.
Hey, why are you so gloomy then, Ranbuddy?
Take a guess...
It feels like this exact same thing
already happened once a long time ago...
Being carried on someone's broad and steady back...
Was that... my father?
No...
No, not him.
It wasn't my father.
Was it... Was it someone I don't know?
I was fated to be carried on someone's strong back...
It was decided from the very beginning.
But who...
Who was supposed to be that man?
I slept so well!
Whoa!
Dazzling!
Good morning.
Oh, good m-
Are you awake already, Lady Benio?
What's that supposed to mean?
How in the world did I return here?
You're welcome to live here again
from today onwards.
I see...
Ah! Ow...
Ow-ow-ow...
What's this? Did I hit my head?
No way! Where did this giant bump come from?
And when did I get it?
Huh? Can't you remember?
Oh, Sh-Shinobu!
Morning. Feeling better already?
What happened yesterday was so like you!
By the way, when did I get this bump?
You really can't recall?
I came back home, I quarreled with my father,
then me, Ushigorou and Ranmaru went to get just a bit of alcohol...
Just a bit of alcohol?
That's as far as I can remember.
But everything after that...
has slipped my memory entirely!
What's so funny?
Are you that fond of laughing at others' worries?
Right. I'm s-sorry,
but this is also so much like you!
How about here?
It hurts! Be gentler!
Didn't I say you would sprain your back again if you pushed yourself so hard at this age?
What's so funny?
If only you saw my heroism last night!
I knocked out every soldier, one after another,
so it's no wonder they took flight in the end.
Hey! Where are you going?
Are you listening to what I'm saying at all?
Huh?
Forget it. Just come here and look at this.
There'd better be a good reason
why you stopped massaging me.
Look, isn't it a sight for sore eyes, dear?
Right, Tenmaru and Chimaru look really healthy.
Not the dogs!
B-But...
Benio is finally back to how she was before.
Right. This is also only thanks to my heroic fighting against eight enemies at once last night!
Is blowing hot air about your bravery
the only thing you can think of?
Those two are making the new flowers
bloom in this old mansion.
If they have children at some point,
those will be our great-grandchildren.
I know that! You all think of me as boorish,
but even I can appreciate such simple beauty.
Not my fault I'm bad at expressing emotions!
Of course, I wish nothing but happiness
for those two, as much as everyone else.
Still... If I was that drunk,
how on earth did I make it back here?
Ah!
Did I come here on Ushigorou's rickshaw?
Probably... Maybe.
Ah! That's not it.
I'm dead sure someone carried me on his back.
Who was it?
Let's see...
I think...
Ah! I've remembered!
So who carried you on his back?
I know! That all happened in my dream only.
In reality, I got home on my own.
My love that I thought lost will finally bear fruit two generations later, in our grandson Shinobu.
Shinobu...
Benio...
You'll be happy together.
Whatever hurdles you may face in life,
you'll overcome them with ease.
You know, that got me so worked up! And...
Alright. This is the perfect time
to tell her my feelings.
Here, I think it suits you.
Benio.
Huh?
Why the serious tone?
There's something...
I've always wanted to tell you.
You see, I...
Hey, Shinobu!
Look there!
What a rare sight!
The cockroaches are flying in a flock!
Whoa! They're a single line now!
Oh? It's V-shaped now!
So? Isn't that peculiar?
Oh, by the way, what did you want to tell me?
Oh no, is something wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
Hey, talk to me.
No, I'm fine.
It can wait for a better day.
But...
The mood needs to be just right
for that kind of conversation.
Also, I need to leave soon.
See you in the evening, Benio.
A-Ah... Sh-Shinobu!
What a weirdo.
He could've just said it then and there.
Really, that guy doesn't know what he wants himself.
Oh God! R-Ranmaru!
Hey, what are you doing out here?
What does it look like?
I'm working out.
Huh? But are you sure it's safe
for your delicate fingers?
Don't worry, Benio.
I'll be the one protecting you,
without relying on that lieutenant!
I just don't get it.
Something must've happened last night, after all.
Good morning, Lady Benio!
Oh, morning!
Hey, what do you think this voice is?
Sounds like Ranko.
Uh! Oh shoot!
What could she be doing?
Let's go see!
Sure.
H-Hold on!
N-No! You can't go.
H-How come?
Ah, well, you see...
She's there, and...
Ranko is one of us, so it's fine, right?
Right?
Sounds about right. Right?
Beg your pardon!
I've done what I could...
What's up, girls?
Weren't you making strange sounds here just now?
Ah. I was just exercising, you see.
Exercising?
Yes, doing calisthenics.
Oh, so it was calisthenics?
Wonderful!
I also want to be as fit and pretty as Ranko!
Take me with you tomorrow, will you?
And me! Please!
Won't you, Ranko?
Teach us how to do it!
Teach us, please!
Oh, you girls...
Fine, then.
Yay! Perfect!
Well, shall we go now?
Thank God!
He was this close to getting exposed.
Then, I'll be on my way, Benio.
Come home safe!
Come home safe, Young Master.
See you.
So, Boss, we should also get going
in a couple of minutes.
Huh? Where to?
No way you really are that forgetful!
Are you trying to skip school?
C'mon, get on.
Boss Benio's ride
You're still a school student, remember?
Ah! You're right...
There's been so much stuff happening lately,
that I've forgotten completely about school!
Does that mean you've not done
a smidgen of homework either?
Naturally!
Then, I guess, maybe you should play hooky just today, after all?
Deal!
This is the first smart thing you've said
ever since I met you!
Like boss, like underling, they say!
In that case, I'll just go to town
to attend to some business.
Here we go!
Well then, don't miss me, Boss!
Good luck with your business!
Ijuuin... Oh, so it's here?
That's one luxurious manor.
Means I'll have no problem collecting the dues!
Wh-What's that?!
I-I'm a decent woman,
you've no reason to suspect me!
S-Somebody help me!
Rickshaw, help me!
Oh? Aren't you last night's proprietress?
Yes I am, and I'm here to bill Mr. Second Lieutenant
for yesterday's damages!
Tough luck, then.
You! Please do something about these dogs.
I'm begging you!
No can do.
These two are my eternal nemeses.
Proprietress, I don't mean to be rude, but if you value your life, you'd better give up and turn back now.
Did they want to threaten me?
Well, you've only got one life,
so don't waste it!
Wait, you!
Are you kidding me?
I need to do this to make ends meet!
Fine, then!
If I can't get it here, I'll get it elsewhere!
Excuse me...
You cannot come through.
No, I just wanted to ask for a favor.
Hey, what does that civilian want?
Well, you see, I'd like you
to give this to Second Lieutenant Ijuuin.
It's open, come in.
Officer on guard duty here!
At ease. What is it?
We just had a civilian,
who asked us to deliver this to you.
Oh, really? She came all the way here!
Okay, I got it. Please tell the giver
that I'll be sure to pay it in full.
Yessir. That's all.
This one is done.
Officer on duty here!
I need a favor from you.
These documents on the desk,
could you deliver them to
Lt. Col Innen at headquarters?
Yessir! Understood!
I shall now go deliver this
to Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen!
If you'll excuse me!
Yeah, thanks.
Attention!
Salute!
Main Administrative Office
So infuriating...
That hoyden is Hanamura's daughter...
Ugh! Just thinking about her irritates me!
Do you need me for something, Lieutenant Colonel​?
Uh? N-No, it's nothing.
Sir.
I see.
Hey, Major Hanamura.
Correspondence for you from Second Lieutenant
Ijuuin of 1st Battalion, 3rd Company!
What? From Second Lieutenant Ijuuin?
Yessir, he asked me to give you this.
Thank you. Dismissed.
That Ijuuin again...
He, who ignores our regulations against long hair in broad daylight...
And he's not even a pure Japanese.
I can't stand the fact that someone like him
is a part of the sacred Imperial Army.
I need to give him tit for tat,
one way or another.
Wh-What?!
A compensation for five stools, three desks,
decanters, glasses and plates?
What's this scrap?
An invoice from last night's tavern?
Ugh! That Ijuuin again...
Did he forward it to me,
implying I should pay for that too?!
That was the last straw!
This is just unacceptable!
Scary, scary! That was the line one ought not to cross with Lieutenant Colonel Innen!
Oh, the intervention in Russia?
Yes. We might need to dispatch some of our troops
to Siberia alongside Americans.
Would be a good show of force.
The year is 1918 and Japan is about to dispatch
an expeditionary corps to Siberia.
Intervention in Russia, huh?
This could prove expedient.
There. Aren't they pretty,
my lieutenant?
The gentle breeze of love
suddenly turns into a violent typhoon.
Will it be enough to blow High Collar Lady's happiness completely away?
Was this happiness just a fleeting dream?
You're in danger!
You're in danger, High Collar Lady!
Our High Collar Lady now trusts Shinobu, not caring about his mountain of love letters,
and she decides to go shopping in Gofukubashi.
However, to her horror, she stumbles
across Shinobu, who's on a date
with none other than the beautiful geisha Kichiji.
What are you gonna do now?
What are you gonna do, High Collar Lady?
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Who Are Those Two Under
the Love Umbrella?"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
JmePenseBon