Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The dawn had broken, but the specter of Shinobu and the geisha Kichiji keeps weighing on Benio's mind.
So upset she is, she's even lost her appetite.
She doesn't even listen to Shinobu's explanations,
since she no longer believes him.
For a change of pace,
she even goes to school after a long break.
But what do you know!
All her friends are already engaged,
so Benio feels like she's the black sheep of the family.
And then her best and only friend Tamaki
also says she trusts Shinobu no matter what?
Benio realizes that she won't find respite
in talking to others.
Something snaps inside her
and she changes her usual route.
New destination: Yanagibashi.
New contender: Kichiji of the House of Flowers.
Let the strongest win and keep her love!
Lady Hanamura?
Yes. Just call me Benio.
Are you by yourself?
Naturally.
My... What could you possibly want
at our establishment?
Oh, isn't that obvious?
I had some time to kill today,
and money to splash.
You shouldn't have come.
This is not a place for a respectable lady.
Sorry. I just wanted to see what it's like.
Oh...
You're one strange lady.
Sis.
Ah, you can come in.
Welcome.
Good evening...
Please enjoy your stay.
Oh, wait!
How old are you?
I am nine years old.
Oh, so you're in elementary school?
Y-Yes...
And what are you doing here?
I'm learning how to dance,
training to sing and play the lute.
My dream is to be a jikata!
Oh... And what is a "jikata"?
When other geishas are singing or dancing,
jikata is someone providing the accompaniment
by playing lute or drums.
Wow, sounds like a lot of fun!
You must be the master's daughter!
No, they bought me.
They bought you, as... A human being?
Yes, but I am happy now.
Happy to have been bought?
Episode 22
Falling Flowers, Blooming Flowers,
and Flowers of Love
Havin' fun, huh?
Hey, hearing about this trafficking
is already strange enough,
but how can you also say
that you're happy with it?
R-Right...
Sis, may I talk about it?
Yes, you can tell her everything
from start to finish.
Okay.
I was born in an impoverished village in Touhoku,
where families are forever poor, because the snow and the cold make the crops fail year after year.
Thus, girls who are lucky enough
to be born at least somewhat pretty,
are sold to geisha houses
to escape from this misery.
Listen, child, if you go to Tokyo, you'll be eating cooked rice three times a day and you'll finally be happy.
So try to stay strong, alright?
Stay strong...
Now, it's time.
Da...
Da!
Such transactions were rather commonplace
in rural Touhoku until the mid-1930s.
The smoldering injustice of this social landscape
would eventually boil over into an attempted young officers' coup in 1936 and ensuing civil violence.
But, but...
Are you really happy to be here?
Yes.
I can eat white rice everyday, after all.
In the countryside, we only had it for New Year or during festivals.
Wow...
But you still think about your
mom and dad, don't you?
I feel like I said something I shouldn't have.
Not at all.
You see, they never teach us a thing
about what geisha life is like at school.
Of course they don't!
Really, that was a complete shock,
seeing such a little girl here.
Young geisha apprentices are called "shitajikko."
I was also one,
as I have been here since I was ten.
Oh...
Sir, your soup is getting cold.
What happened to Benio, huh?
Well, sir, she headed out to school this morning
and hasn't returned as of yet.
Surely they aren't making her
stand out in the corridor all night?
I am sure she will be brought home soon,
so stop worrying and eat.
Seeing her weird face
always gives me appetite.
Where might she be?
What's wrong, Shinobu?
I'll go look for her.
Sure, don't take too long.
You got any ideas, Ranmaru?
Benio is too whimsical for anyone
to predict her actions.
Even the best diviner out there
would be in dire straits.
Well said. Which means, I guess we have no choice but to ask at Hanamura house for the time being.
Oh, Second Lieutenant Ijuuin?
What? Benio is?
No, we've not seen her here.
Sorry, I have no idea where she might be either.
By the way, there's one thing I'd like you to explain to me,
which might be linked to the events of tonight.
Would you mind coming over now?
Lieutenant, do you know this geisha Kichiji
of the House of Flowers?
Huh?
Kichiji of the House of Flowers?
I'll take your suddenly pale face as a yes.
Y-Yes, I do happen to know her.
But may I ask why you bring this up now?
The truth is... Benio was convinced that this geisha
is your lover, which worried her to no end.
Lieutenant!
You're a grown man and I'm not in a position to judge you for visiting the red-light district once or twice.
However, if another woman is driving a wedge between you and Benio, I, as her father, must take action!
So, let's get straight to the point -
what's your relationship with that geisha?
A-Actually...
Shinobu, don't you try to talk your way out of this!
Ranmaru!
H-Hey, you...
That's it, Lieutenant -
you tell us the truth about Kichiji here and now!
Why would you suspect me of that?
I've definitely heard Benio
mumble "Kichiji" in her sleep.
Huh?
Is that true, Ranmaru?
Lord Hanamura, I wouldn't ever
lie to you on such a matter!
These last few days,
Benio's been utterly dejected!
I can't just stand silent anymore!
Look, even Tenmaru and Chimaru
agree with me!
Now, Shinobu, explain yourself
once and for all tonight.
Just what is geisha Kichiji to you?
Explain yourself!
I'm waiting,
Lieutenant!
I want you to marry Shinobu, Miss Kichiji.
What did you say?
I want you to go live with the Ijuuins.
I'm doing this because I wish
to ensure Benio's happiness.
Tell us about your relationship with Kichiji,
in all its detail!
Very well.
I'll tell you everything.
So you were involved with her?!
Lady Benio, do you actually mean
what you just said?
Well, I, uhm...
Will assist you in any way I can.
I see.
Give me just a moment.
Whew, I finally brought myself to say it.
I can now say goodbye to the Ijuuins forever!
It's all finally over!
I'm quite hungry, actually!
After all...
Really, being a gourmet
sounds a lot like my thing.
Sorry not sorry.
Well then, may I tell you about my relationship with Shinobu,
leaving nothing out?
Yes!
I've been waiting for this moment,
so I've braced myself and I'm fully ready.
Please take a look at this, Lady Benio.
Who is he?
You see...
He is my late husband.
Well, though I call him my "husband," we were never officially married.
We only exchanged the vows
to never love anyone else.
This man hails from the same village as me.
Terasako Station
My fate is not unlike that of most geishas -
I come from a poor village, so I was sold away.
He, on the other hand,
came from a wealthy family in the same village,
thus, he went to the military academy
right after the middle school.
Several years later—when I was already
a geisha apprentice—surprisingly, I met him again.
From then on,
we, childhood friends, fell ever deeper in love with each passing day.
It just so happened that he was friends with Young Master Ijuuin,
who had always proved himself
a kind and well-disposed man.
But then, in the Siege of Qingdao
during The Great War...
Map of the Siege of Qingdao
(September-November 1914)
Charge!
When I found out that he had honorably died in battle, I lost my will to live.
Qingdao is ours!
By chance, the one who found and rescued me
was none other than Young Master.
Since then, he's been helping me in any way he can,
he was always there when I needed support.
He said that he simply couldn't let
his late friend's love die.
And this is how Shinobu and I
have become what we are now.
Wow, Shinobu did all of that?
I guess he's not as bad as I thought he is.
Lady Benio, may I assure you that Young Master
is a truly caring and chivalrous man.
'Course you say so!
But I'm not buying it.
This is an improper thing to say,
but I was also attracted to that side of him once.
There we go!
But in the end, I am nothing more than a lowly geisha,
one who is never going be with a nobleman.
However, if I know that you're going to be the one with the Young Master, I should be glad to give up on him.
I sincerely believe that your marriage
will be the one that stands the test of time.
Miss Kichiji...
You're the first ever person
to make me feel so special.
Lady Benio...
I see, I see. It's a huge relief to know that you've lived up to my expectations. I mean it!
Lord Hanamura!
It's a good thing we've determined Shinobu's character,
but we still, by all means, must find Benio!
Oh, you're right.
Unlike you, my daughter is a lost cause.
Let's split up and look for her.
She sure puts you through a lot of trouble...
Now then, where could she be...
Oh, I know!
I'm counting on you two.
Find her scent!
You're our only hope
at this point, Tenmaru, Chimaru.
'Preciate it, bud!
See you again!
Rub a dub dub-Ah!
Ushi!
Really, that's just you, guys?
You scared the shit outta me, y'know!
Why on Earth are you loafing
around here yourself, Ushi?
What can I do?
Boss is still in there, y'know.
Huh? Really, Ushi?
Rickshaw Man, Lady Benio is calling for you!
Now, to celebrate our acquaintance
with Lady Benio, let's have a good time!
Alright!
Now I, a professional jester, am going to initiate the lady into the art of performing this traditional song!
There we go.
Let's begin!
Looks like fun!
Don't be shy!
I think I can do this.
Like this!
Like that!
And then this way!
I don't understand a thing.
But I can do at least this much!
Like this! Ah...
Ah, and then this way!
Huh? Oh, what do we have here?
What's this?
A round of applause!
Caught ya! I said I caught ya!
I've finally made sure that Shinobu is a good person! Banzai!
Coming!
Hey, where's Kichiji?
I called for Kichiji, not you!
Unfortunately, Sister Kichiji
is in that tatami room.
Then bring her here! Tell her that Lieutenant Colonel​ Innen of 1st Division is here.
You see, that room rented her for the rest of the night,
so I simply can't do that.
Damn it all... They're so noisy...
She's in the room that's making that racket?
Yes.
And who is her guest?
That would be some schoolgirl, sir.
Schoolgirl?!
Ugh...
I've had enough of schoolgirls
getting under my skin lately.
Oh no, did you not like our drinks, dear guest?
Ugh, shut up!
I'll get Kichiji here whatever it takes!
Ah... I'm afraid that's impossible, Master.
You can't go there.
No! It's an affront to the officer of the Imperial Army.
She'd rather entertain a schoolgirl than me?!
P-Please, hold on a second!
You shouldn't do that...
Out of my way!
This Kichiji...
W-What the...
Where did these dogs come from?
They're the dogs of Count Ijuuin.
Ijuuin?
Ugh, that bastard again!
Don't touch me!
Somebody! Get these dogs off me, somebody!
I'm scared of dogs!
Ah! Help me!
Shoo! Shoo!
You! Don't just watch, stop them!
Ah! Help me!
Somebody!
Can somebody deal with them?
I'll remember this, Ijuuin!
You can't get away with it! I'll remember this!
Damn mongrels!
Ah! Shoo! Shoo!
That was too much... They stripped us
of everything but the clothes on our back.
That girl Kichiji already said
that we didn't have to pay...
Why the hell didja insist, Boss?
Geisha services ought to be duly rewarded...
Tsk. Now I need to find a way
to redeem my rickshaw tomorrow...
But I finally found out
what kind of guy Shinobu is!
Yay! Yay! Banzai!
Ahahahah!
Our High Collar Lady is as jubilant as can be,
but she can't even fathom the horrors
Lt Col Innen is preparing for her behind the scenes...
Thus, the bill for tonight's celebration
just keeps growing,
just as the hangover only hits in the morning.
Benio is on cloud nine after clarifying Shinobu's relationship with Kichiji
and, overflowing with joy,
she invites her classmates over.
But fate is a fabric woven by the devil himself,
as Lt Col Innen finally puts into motion
the revenge he's been plotting all this time.
Shinobu's life is at stake!
See in the next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady: "Heaven Yesterday, Hell Today."
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
CeleryMan