Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
After coming all the way to Manchuria,
Benio learned about Shinobu's last moments from Onijima,
which proved to be too heartbreaking for her.
Having lost her will to live, Benio attempted suicide in the most High Collar ways possible.
That is, until she realized that even if Shinobu is gone,
her love for him is everlasting
and thus she returned to the flowering Tokyo,
biding farewell to Manchuria, with her only souvenirs being memories of her beloved Shinobu.
Episode 40
Shinobu Lives on in my Heart
Good old Tokyo! Buses scurrying, streetcars clunking, street lights, and the willows of Ginza.
Haven't you forgotten
one important thing, Boss?
Huh? Oh, right, how could I forget about it!
The good old chicken skewer!
Right, right...
I'm telling ya, no place quite like Tokyo!
Moreover, the Lady
is looking gorgeous today!
Oh? Are you perhaps talkin' 'bout me?
No! It was 'bout me!
Of all places, this is the one I missed most!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, how have you been?
You guys looked after the house
while I was away, right?
Huh? What's wrong?
Whoa! Wh-What is that?
S-Smoke! T-To the sky.
To the sky smoke!
Boss, when you panic,
you start omitting verbs.
Idiot! It's not the time to act like a teacher!
P-Pump! Water! Bucket!
Ushigorou, hurry up!
Come on! Quicker! Go quicker!
C'mon, push it harder! Alright!
Phew...
One-two, there!
Achoo!
Wh-Who in their right mind poured water on me?!
Oh, was it you, Benio?
So you've returned?
Oh my, Count?
How was your trip?
I won't tell them that in reality
I went looking for Shinobu.
Huh? Ah, right, not bad...
I covered plenty of topics.
Rather, won't you tell me
what on Earth were you doing, Count?
Huh? Oh, you mean this?
M-Mackerel?
Kisaragi said she wanted to eat it,
so I decided to treat us some delicacy today.
Wow...
How painful... A respectable Count
is forced to stoop so low.
Now I see...
All our servants are gone.
This mansion used to be gorgeous
when Shinobu was still around...
I have to carry on!
Even if Shinobu is no longer around,
I still gotta do my best for all the others in here!
Count, please let me take care of it.
I should be able to do something this simple.
Oh? A-Alright.
Just leave it to me, I'm sure I'll manage.
It's just some mackerel, after all!
Now then...
I'll flip it like this— Whoops!
Oh my, I dropped one...
Wow!
It got beheaded!
Are you managing, Benio?
Yeah. More or less.
O-Oops, I burned it...
Oh, I see, I see!
What a disaster!
I had no idea mackerel
could be this hard and bitter!
Me neither.
I'm home, Mother.
Benio...
Benio!
Oh, Ranmaru!
I see. So by going to Manchuria you were able
to confirm Second Lieutenant Ijuuin's death...
Then, isn't your marriage arrangement is void?
Benio, when you were about to depart
for the Ijuuins' mansion,
I gave you your mother's white dress,
which was her memento.
It was the symbol of your lifelong devotion
to your first and only husband.
Yes, I remember that.
However...
Excuse me.
What I wanted to say is, for better or worse,
we still haven't held a formal wedding.
That's right. You can now go marry
a wonderful man of your own choice.
No, I'm staying with his family
for the rest of my life.
B-Benio...
Boss?
A-Are you sure about it, Benio?
Yes, Father.
If I leave now, I dread to think what’ll happen to the Count and Countess who are so hopelessly infantile.
Of course, I don't mean to sound boastful,
like I'm the backbone of the Ijuuin family or something.
However, I want to help in any way I can by comforting them for the rest of my life.
But Benio...
No, I've made up my mind.
I guess I should give up
on the hope of ever getting you back...
Well, we're here, Boss.
Good job. Good night.
Right. Good night to you.
Ushigorou. Ushigorou!
Here! Here!
Whoa, everyone's here.
Do y'all need something from me?
Ushigorou, did you manage to learn anything about Young Master's fate?
Come on, Ushigorou.
Just tell us the truth!
Benio ordered you
not to say anything, didn't she?
Y-Yes...
Forget it.
Just tell us everything you know
Whatever the truth may be, we promise
not to let on around Benio that we know anything.
A-Alright...
S-Second Lieutenant...
Second Lieutenant...
died heroically on the battlefield.
So it's true...
H-Hey...
My sincere apologies...
You don't have to apologise,
it's not your fault.
Never again will I be able to see
Benio's and Shinobu's silhouettes side by side...
Don't ever say that! That's just too depressing to hear...
Look at yourself! We promised we wouldn't cry!
Take a look at yourself—
aren’t you the one bawling your eyes out?
Sh-Shut up!
I-I'm just... s-sweating from my eyes!
My eyes...
My eyes can't stop sweating either!
Come in.
Oh, do you need something, Count?
Yes. I was just thinking, why don't you return to the Hanamura house, Benio?
Huh? Why should I?
Well, while there's no doubt that Shinobu is alive and will return one day,
we don't know when that'll happen.
If you're worrying about marriage preparations, you'll resume them once Shinobu returns.
I refuse.
Huh?
I've grown to truly love this mansion
from the bottom of my heart.
I'm willing to pay rent too
as long as you let me stay.
S-So this means you're not planning
on returning home?
Yes.
Aren't you glad, my dear?
Y-Yes!
Shinobu, I'll never leave your grandfather and grandmother, no matter what happens.
Remember: bow to the strong!
Remember: bow to the strong.
Remember: scorn the weak.
Good morning.
Hey, welcome back.
Editor-in-Chief, the miraculous
healer of hives is back.
Huh? Healer?
Ever since you hugged him back then,
Editor-in-Chief no longer has an allergy to women.
Good morning, Editor-in-Chief.
Welcome back.
Editor-in-chief...
Oh crud, she's crying now.
F-First, present me your report.
I'm sorry..
I've been holding back tears for a while, but when I saw your face, I just couldn't endure anymore.
Hmm... So I gather your journey ended in vain.
Such was the account from the actual witness,
so there's no reason for me not to believe him.
And what about that Colonel Innen?
I've embraced my true nature!
I am now The Cripple with Twenty Faces!
But even if I managed to take vengeance,
that wouldn't bring Shinobu back.
The entity we call reality...
is always crueler than what we'd like.
Maybe you'd be happier if you didn't know.
Editor-in-Chief…
Well, in any case, our company missed a valuable opportunity to get rid of a female employee.
Therefore, I have no choice
but to work you to the very bone!
Editor-in-Chief!
Understood?!
Yes!
Also, for your own good,
you should forget him as soon as you can.
No, I won't.
Alright, I've got just the thing for you!
First, focus on reporting Tokyo City
Automobile Company hiring female conductors!
When you're done, cover the rumors
about the Crown Prince's engagement. Is that clear?
I expect scoops that'll make other companies
eat their hearts out!
Understood!
So, Editor-in-Chief,
how would you rate Benio's work?
Her lack of experience is still evident.
Coverage notes
-Hanamura Benio
Refreshments coming!
Great! How attentive of y—
Whoa! Oopsies...
That was your tea...
Appreciate it.
Sheesh...
Oh poor me.
Editor-in-Chief, give me something to cover!
Enough for today.
Why not?! I'm itching for action!
Please, sir. I'll cover anything,
even the on-site situation of transvestites in Japan!
Alright! I heard you.
Go cover this upcoming fashion show!
Okay!
What a strange feeling.
I think that deep down I'm glad her fiance is dead.
What I want to say is,
I'm relieved I didn't lose her after that trip.
"Following the Great War, the Meiji-era classic bustle style has been since completely revolutionized,
as we moved the garçonne look,
well-known to Charleston's aficionados.
Hairstyles also went
from the classic low pompadour to the bob.
The skirts that used to end at 10cm above the floor
now reveal the knees.
The garçonne look symbolizes
the right of women to work alongside men."
That should do it.
"However, in the shadow
of the city center's flourishing development,
there are slum streets
crowded with unemployed people.
Meanwhile, poor family are selling off girls to spinning mills and geisha houses due to the recession.
Reacting to these gloomy social conditions,
impressionable young people
embraced decadence,
causing the boom
of a new literary movement.
Subaru and Shirakaba, the twin beacons of romance,
inspire the youth of the Taisho era.
April
Benio! Benio! Wait!
What is it, Ranmaru?
W-What a terrible nightmare! That was frightening!
Besides, that's not unlikely.
Whenever I see Benio these days, she's as unwomanly as can be: she's become a full-blown workaholic!
She always had that tendency,
but when I asked her out on a date recently...
I stopped living to love. From now onward,
I'll proudly live to work as a modern woman.
I'm afraid to say it, but perhaps the nightmare I had could potentially become reality.
Ah! No, please, no!
That would be too unbearable!
Today, I'm asking her out for sure!
Oh, Ranmaru! Long time no see!
Benio!
She's coming down!
Oh, sorry! We'll talk later!
I need to work! I don't wanna be late!
Wh-What should I do?
Ushi, Benio is going to lose the remains
of her femininity at this rate.
I don't mind.
But that's just you!
That's right! I never thought of Boss
as a woman in the first place!
How could she even hear me?
It's a mystery.
Have a safe trip.
Will you look after the house?
Of course.
Sir, Missus, please avail yourself to my services. It'd be a honour.
No, you don't need to worry.
Today, we'd like to go somewhere
without any escort.
A-Alright...
Huh? I wonder where those two are goin' all alone.
Could it be a date?
Editor-in-Chief, any assignments lined up for me today by any chance?
The assignment I have
may be a little too painful for you.
Editor-in-Chief!
Are you still refusing to treat me
like a full-fledged adult?
I'll go anywhere in the world if I need to.
No need for unnecessary pity!
Alright. Your assignment takes place at Yasukuni Shrine, in Kudan ward.
Yasukuni Shrine?
The Spring festival for the fallen is coming up,
with bereaved families coming to Yasukuni
from all over the country.
I want you to cover the event.
Okay, I'll do it.
Shinobu...
I can't be giving in
to my personal feelings now!
Work comes first! So top priority—
gotta get an interview in. Now, who should it be...
Remember, my dear.
Benio still has no clue
that we've been informed of Shinobu's passing.
She must not find out
that we've been to here today.
Sure, sure. I know that.
We can't let our sadness
show through when we are with Benio.
Right. That includes crying at home.
Exactly.
Isn't that the reason we came here for?
Shinobu... How could you part from this world before any of us?
I just can't bring myself to accept it, Shinobu.
Why are there terrible things
like war in this world of ours?
Our poor High Collar Lady can’t afford to cry at the sight of the grieving Ijuuins.
Her Second Lieutenant lives,
but now in her heart only.
Next episode preview
Making her way through male journalists,
our High Collar Lady makes a scoop coverage.
After stumbling across Tamaki,
they have a toast to their eternal friendship.
Wait, am I dreaming or it's an UFO?
On an airship there's the spitting image of Shinobu.
This could be the night in which dreams become reality.
Who is the man that's about to come out of it?
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
The Man Who Got Off the Airship.
Episode 41
The Man Who Got Off the Airship
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Timing & translation checking
Special thanks
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Perevodildo
Golden time Anime (vk)