Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
It's pitch-black!
Yeah! It's pitch-black!
Once more!
It's pitch-black!
Can't hear!
In the past, people used to travel
on backs or in a bier.
Let me go!
Nowadays, as in a dream,
trains take people wherever they want to go!
All the smoke makes the tunnel...
pitch-black!
Episode 1
Benio's Sweet Seventeen
It's the seventh year of the Taishou Era,
Wherein people's hearts are spellbound
by the Romanticism in vogue.
Those were the heydays of Taishou Democracy.
Hanamura
That hurts!
Hey Benio,
you're cruel, hitting me this hard...
Why, of course Ranmaru,
you are a boy. Get ready!
W-W-Wait, for God's sake, Benio!
There's no waiting in a duel!
You sadist!
If you can still run like that,
at least give me some sport!
Stop, stop, I give up!
Giving up so soon?
You weakling...
Ranmaru, once more!
That will do!
Benio, put a damper on that!
But we have only started training...
Ranmaru is on his way to become a Kabuki dancer,
overdoing fencing practice is not necessary.
That's right, Mister.
Shut that mouth!
Father, you already know that, just like me, Ranmaru lost his mother at a young age.
It made him such a scaredy cat.
Thus, to fill that motherless void,
I am determined to carve a man out of him!
Uhm, Benio, isn't it about time
you head to girls' school?
Yeah, you should hurry up.
I can't go!
Phew, that was close.
Teacher, thank you so much for the lesson.
En garde!
How often do I have to tell to lock eyes on the foe?
Mister!
It's no bed of roses, isn't it?
No bed of roses?
No, far from that.
Benio is amazing.
Yaoya Oshichiya, Agemaki Tayuu...
Among Kabuki women,
many are wonderful.
But among them, none ever, ever compare
to how divine Benio is.
I mean, why would I practice
every early morning, otherwise?
What are you trying to say?
No! Nothing...
I've got to keep a closer eye on those two.
Our Late Sister Akizuki Sumire
But now that I think about it, she's 17 now, too.
And I have to admit that without a mother in our home
she's become quite of a hoyden.
What should I do about it?
I'm off!
The cherries are in full bloom!
The swaying heat haze
and the water of Koishikawa...
Half boots on my feet,
maroon trousers
and the fluttering ribbon on my head...
This is the life of a teenage student.
It's really my Sweet Seventeen.
Good things will be bound to happen!
Go away! Away!
Damn, it hurts...
What's up with this guy?
Oh, sorry for that.
Shall I lend you a hand?
No thank you,
I don't need any of that!
Not for this much.
Smmmmack!
Oh...
What's with you?
Don't you know that making fun of ladies
is against the etiquette?
It's because of people like you
that Japanese women can't climb in status! Farewell!
What's up with that high collar student?
Oh well, oh well.
Oh well, oh well,
High collar girl's thick head is like a shellfish baking in its midst...
Atonashi Girls' School
My, Benio.
What happened to your feet?
Nothing.
Hey hey, wanna know the latest?
Yesterday I went to Asakusa's Rossi opera!
It was incredible!
Love is like a sweet flower in a field
Whoa, I wish I had been there too!
I'm jealous!
So what was the plot about?
Hey, hey, teach us opera lyrics!
Students!
It's been a while since the bell rang,
how long would you all chat!?
These youngsters are sure reactive...
Stand up!
Bow!
Righteous path towards wifehood
Everyone, today I am going to teach you
how to sew a lined kimono.
But before that, I will check the yukata
I gave you as an assignment last week.
Drat it!
Heh, to the hell with it,
I'll dish out the same excuse than last week!
What in the world?
You didn't do it?!
It completely slipped my mind!
Completely slipped, you say,
Hanamura Benio?
So it "slipped your mind" again, just as last week,
and the week before, and the one before that!
You have been forgetting it all along!
Isn't it so!?
Here you are!
watch those buckets out!
Everyone, such a shameless attitude,
keeps you from shining as the proud, envied and educated mothers
of Japan!
Teacher, I forgot about my homework as well!
Kitakoji Tamaki?
Be quiet, everyone! Is that so? With Hanamura, I expect little,
But from a honor student like you...
That's right, I forgot.
Additionally, teacher -
if we are to become women by ourselves,
Gentleman's pick should be ours, too.
Besides, to quote Hiratsuka Raichou...
In the beginning, women truly were genuine,
and shone like the Sun...
Righteous path towards wifehood
We, as women, shall not be "chosen" by men,
but the ones who choose men.
That's right, the choice is ours and no one else's.
Benio ❤️ Kazuo
Not a word more!
Keep your diabolical propaganda out of here!
Righteous path towards wifehood
Tamaki?
Isn't that teacher so dull?
All she says is that we should become "the mothers of Japan",
Half seriously...
On my part, I flatly refuse arranged marriage with a man
I have not set my sight on.
You sure speak in a fancy way, silk-stocking girl!
My, nobles are regular people too, after all.
Tamaki! So it was a complete lie
given your amazing homework!
All that for me?
That teacher is so cantankerous.
Tamaki is such a strong-willed girl...
And on top of that, she's also kind,
beautiful and wise...
I just can't help but admire her!
And I also refuse to wed
through to parental accord.
Right? Then let's promise we'll choose by ourselves!
I promise.
Flatly refusing arranged marriages,
looking for a blossoming romance
that will shine for the rest of their lives.
This and that, all comprises the character
of those new Taishou Era "High Collar Girls."
What are you two making a racket about?!
So harsh...
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Hey, Tamaki, how about
an anmitsu bowl?
Sorry I can't, I have a date today!
Take care!
She's the same age as us,
but while we go eat fruit jelly, she goes on dates!
Recently, I saw her in Ginza
with a university student!
And he seemed like the artist kind!
So bold! Especially when people still believe that boys and girls should be kept apart after 7!
Lovely, lovely! Lovely, lovely!
I'm sure of it,
soon I'll be in love just like Tamaki!
What's with her?
Lovely, lovely!
What's with those looks?
It goes without saying.
Those are looks of disdain.
Haven't you noticed the wide gap
between you and Tamaki?
What are you trying to say?
What gap?
Oh God, the cluelessness!
About the relief of her chest!
Itsy-bitsy
Who cares about that!
It's but a minute detail!
My ideals are shapely!
Yes, it's all about my ideals!
The fruit jelly went to her brain!
Must be it.
What's that?
My ideals... are... ideals...
Well, for instance...
What's wrong?
I think I'm tired after all.
I'll be going home.
She indeed wasn't very cheery today.
Maybe we shouldn't have compared her to Tamaki...
Well, it's a fact that she's flat...
Uhm... Here you are again!
I forgot this.
How dare they mock me?
Ever since I met that guy, it has gone downhill.
Sho-Sho-Shojo-ji Gardens...
And what the heck are you?
A Known-Not Fellow.
You not know?
I'm running into
nothing but oddballs today.
- It hurts!
- That'll teach you to be such a tomboy!
I feel so sorry towards your late mother.
I'm at loss of words!
She says that all the time!
The creepy old no-chin hag.
Hey, lady!
I even told her it was an important day...
Ranmaru? Ranmaru!
So pretty!
Even a boy like Ranmaru can look so sexy...
I must be unattractive, after all.
The housekeeper's complaint,
My friends making fun of me... Is it my fault for being like this?
Oh! Benio!
Are you busy practicing?
No, don't worry!
Well, that's it for today!
Teacher, we're halfway through.
That's enough for me,
I have to play with Benio!
It seems like our young teacher
is sweet on his neighbor.
Also, what's so good about that girl?
I really wonder...
Glare
Run!
A kite? Isn't that too boyish?
Kites are cool, but isn't that a boyish play?
So what, aren't you one too?
It's so up in the sky!
So high!
Benio's really innocent... She hasn't changed in the slightest after all these years.
Got it...
What a bad place to land it on, Benio...
Stop or you'll break the thread!
We're in trouble...
Alright, in that case...
Well then, since nobody's around...
Let's see...
Stop it,
Benio!
Stop it, stop it!
It's all good! Nobody's going to come here!
It's dangerous!
Don't worry, don't worry!
Let's do this!
A bit more...
Get down!
Once more!
Leaves are falling, but it's not Autumn yet...
That sneering guy from then!
Hey, here we meet again!
You'd better not stop down there!
As you'd better not climb up there!
Shut up!!
Ouch!
I told you to go away!
Oh no!
Oh my!
Don't look at me!
Benio's gonna die!!!
I take that High Collar people
are the climber type?
That's none of your business!
Why does something weird happen when I meet you?
Want a cheap laugh?
Laugh, then!
Ranmaru, let's go home!
Hanamura
Oh, Sublieutenant Ijuuin!
I've been waiting.
Good morning, Mr. Hanamura!
It's my pleasure to meet you.
Why is that guy here?
I didn't know he was dad's guest...
I assume Benio showed you the way here.
She's truly a daughter worthy of a Major as you.
She resembles her regretted mother,
I find her to be amazingly beautiful.
That's exactly my impression.
Oh...!
Actually, that one is our neighbor, Mr. Ranmaru.
Then you're saying... This is a boy?
And the other one...
That chucklehead sublieutenant...
Young lady!
That's edible seaweed!
Those are not the tea leaves,
they're over there!
Here you are!
Well, look at that,
I am going by the etiquette after all.
Sublieutenant, you can go ahead.
Sure. Thank you.
How come! Did you really serve them
those mugwort rice sweets, miss?
Yes, so what?
Those are a week old already!
They're probably all moldy!
Oh, excuse me!
Get a grip, please cut the jokes down
just for today! And be a little more cautious too!
Why should I, Father?
Huh, in reality...
Well, you'll find out soon enough.
Oh, while you're at it,
could you show him the garden?
That's fishy...
I bet Father's hiding something...
Huh?
What is that? I came looking, but he's not here...
How rude.
Where has he gone?
Oh, there he is!
He's sleeping in such a peaceful way, I see...
Well then...
Let's go...
Don't get too fired up,
it would be my turn to laugh at him.
En garde!
Catching people off guard is cowardly!
A true warrior must always be watchful,
even while asleep!
You'd better remember this!
You're just talking without thinking.
Stand up!
Stand up, I told you!
Well then, let's rumble!
So bothersome...
Really! I'm through with your teasing! Here I go!
You...
This sound...
Isn't this...
I got this!
No! Stop, stop, stop that!
Don't you know
that Sublieutenant Ijuuin is to be your fiancé!?
He's the guy you're going to wed!
Yes! Marry!
The hell are you saying?
En garde! Ten points!
Are you kidding me?
Him taking ten points off me is too much...
This can't be real!
It's like a nightmare!
And so, our High Collar Lady discovered
she was engaged to Ensign Ijuuin.
What sort of man is that blonde sublieutenant?
Thus, a romance in the Taishou Era began...
The lieutenant's engagement to Benio
was agreed upon three generations ago.
In an age bound by convention,
Would she have her way
or one laid out for her by her parents?
At a time where life
was too short for love...
And let's not forget Ranmaru...
What will be High Collar Benio's next move?
Next time on "Here Comes the Smart Alec":
Elopement. Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
trumann
Ziusudra
Perevodildo