Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
It's the season of falling leaves—Autumn.
The ever-so-melancholic autumn has come...
and the Ijuuins have been thunderstruck by Shinobu's passing.
The last glimmer of hope has died out
and now, wherever you look,
it's just tears, tears and more tears.
Rain is falling everywhere,
be it on Benio's hair or in her heart.
Even after a downpour of sorrow,
she had to face a group of obnoxious soldiers.
Despite being imprisoned,
she swore not to tell on the Count,
but Shinobu's funeral will be held tomorrow.
How will she manage
to free herself from this predicament?
Episode 32
I'll Cut my Black Hair
to Consecrate It to You
I wonder how long Tenmaru and Chimaru will keep howling there.
Could they be waiting for someone?
Let's see...
Uhm, excuse me, my good man...?
What is it?
Well, you see...
I'm here for the young lady
in your custody—around 17...
Do you know her?
Well, yeah, sort of...
I see.
What's up with that girl?
She just won't talk, no matter what I say.
She won't tell us her name nor address.
Even the police inspector is at a loss.
If she's your acquaintance,
come in and rid us of her!
R-Roger!
Good!
B-Boss!
Why won't you tell them your name?
I can't afford to stain the Ijuuins' reputation.
You do remember that tomorrow
is Shinobu's funeral, right?
Boss, what's your plan?
Ushigorou, isn't there a way to get me out of here
without getting the Count involved?
Huh?! Don't tell me you're planning a jailbreak!
And that's why I need you to think of a better way.
A-Alright.
See you.
I have to get out of here, one way or another.
Shinobu, protect me.
Huh? Benio did?
It's your duty to protect her.
I'm counting on you, okay?
R-Right... But what am I to do?
Police
Inspector
Okay, hurry up now, Ranmaru.
Police
Inspector
Okay...
Police
Inspector
I-I'm not good at dealing with the police, though...
Nobody is!
So? How's it looking inside?
Kabuki and art
Seems like I can pull this off.
Hold it! What are you doing here?!
Eek!
No, uh, you see, we're here to meet someone!
Excuse me.
Come in.
Oh? Did you come here alone?
Yes.
Good grief, that girl is such a thorn in my side.
I plan to keep her here for a day or two to make her reflect on her behavior,
I can't let her out now.
Perhaps, there is some other way?
First of all, tell me her full name.
I cannot do that.
Who do you think you are?!
Don't you look down on the police!
Let's hear your name first.
Your name!
So?
If you don't know it yet,
then I'll enlighten you!
M-My surname is Fujieda.
My name is Ranmaru.
Ranmaru? Wh-Which means...
Now, where was it... Oh!
I see now! So it's true.
Young Kabuki actor Fujieda Ranmaru!
I'm pleased to make your acquaintance.
You see, my wife is a fan of yours.
No, I mean...
I am one myself!
Right? You know what I mean, right?
Whatever! Anything for Benio!
Well, I'll take custody of her from here on.
I'm the happiest man alive!
I just bribed him!
Ranmaru!
Benio!
You vanished all of a sudden, I was so worried.
I... I...
You don't have to say anything, Benio.
I understand better than anyone else
what you're trying to say.
Ranmaru...
Benio?
Countess...
Oh, no need to get up.
You really shouldn't have gone for a walk during the downpour.
I'm sorry. I made all of you worry
out of selfishness.
But you seem better than I had expected,
and that's all that matters.
Countess, are the people
outside of the window guests?
Yes, they're our relatives.
Are they here for tomorrow's funeral?
No.
That's not the only reason they've come so far.
We also need to decide what to do with Shinobu's belongings.
What do you mean?!
We've just received news of his death and yet...
How can they be that heartless?!
What are you planning to do, Count?
Surely, you don't mean to make Shinobu's betrothed inherit all of it, do you?
We won't stand for it, you hear?
Exactly! There's no way
our share of inheritance amoun—
Won't you shut up?!
All you ever think about is money!
There's no need for you to make your schemes.
Benio is going back to the Hanamura estate.
And beyond that, the Ijuuin family
has no property to share!
What?!
That's right.
Up until now, we've been able to maintain a semblance of order by making Shinobu our heir apparent.
Countess...
Do you understand now?
This is why you should return home.
You'll have no future living in our impoverished and grief-stricken house.
Countess!
For the better part of my life, I've dreamt of the day
you and Shinobu would finally be one.
But you're still so young.
You should live and enjoy
your life from now on.
Countess...
I'll always be by your side, Countess!
Thank you.
But only the elderly should have to bear the burden of grieving the dead for the rest of their lives.
⬅️ Ijuuins'
Mansion
Lady Benio, I brought your mourning garb.
May you please don it.
Lady Benio?
I'll be wearing something else.
This white mourning garb.
It's my mother's dress.
A symbol of undying love for one's husband.
Lady Benio! Wh-What are you doing?!
Eh... L-L-Lady Benio!
Shinobu...
I let you die before I could ever tell you all about my feelings.
And this is why...
This is why...
Mourning
Can you believe it?
They have no other property!
So all they have is this mansion?
Oh!
Ah!
Shinobu...
This is my bridal gown.
The oath of my everlasting love for you.
Humph. How impertinent.
What's the meaning of this?
Shinobu, I'll be by your side
from now on and forever.
I'll look after Grandfather, Grandmother,
Tenmaru and Chimaru in your stead.
Benio...
Benio.
Wh-What's the matter with them?
They won't accept food
from anyone this morning.
Hey, Tenmaru!
Let's chase after them!
Sure thing!
Sister Kichiji!
You're praying out here, ma'am?
Yes. I'm doing it here, where nobody can see me.
There's no reason to keep it a secret!
Let's go now! I'll show you the way.
He's right.
I'm sure Shinobu would've wanted you to
attend his funeral instead of those greedy relatives.
Come inside, please.
But I'm not worthy of it...
There's no need to be hesitant!
Come now!
Dogs can tell a kindred spirit
better than humans do.
It'd be better if you just left.
This here is no place for a woman like you.
Shut up!
You don't have a say in any of this!
He's right!
We want this lady
to offer incense to Shinobu.
I am well aware that a woman like me should not have come here.
But I'd be happy if I could at least say my goodbyes to Young Master...
Let her in.
Huh?
What?
Lady Benio...
Don't you see that she's a geisha?!
It's beyond foolish to let her barge in
on a formal ceremony!
Kichiji might be a geisha,
but she is way more welcome here
than any of you.
Thank you, Kichiji.
I can't even begin to imagine how happy Shinobu would've been.
Please, come this way.
Thank you, ma'am.
How displeasing to let a lowly geisha
invade our space.
How can she be so audacious?!
Well said. How dare she barge in like that!
Not to mention that "bride" of his.
What in the world did she mean
by donning that white mourning garb?
She cut her hair too.
Benio, why did you cut your hair?
Yeah. On top of that,
what's with that white mourning garment?
Count, please let me stay here
as Shinobu's wife for the rest of my life.
Benio?
You're still such a young maiden.
Even if you two were engaged, you never officially got married.
You should keep on living as a free woman.
Right? No need to hurry,
give it a second thought,
Benio.
Count, Countess,
I stopped being part of the Hanamura family
the moment I set foot in your house.
I humbly ask you to accept me
as your granddaughter in Shinobu's stead!
Benio?
No can do!
You're out of your mind!
Does this mean that she'd
inherit this mansion?
This house alone will fetch a fortune.
No way we let her snatch it from under our noses!
We'll never approve of that!
Yeah! You can't decide on such an important matter arbitrarily!
Exactly!
Right!
Would you really hand the estate over
to a perfect stranger?
How brazen of her
to keep the fortune all for herself!
Shut up!
I've heard everything! All you ever talk about
is inheritance, fortune and whatnot!
Ushigorou...
You guys have no notion
of kinship or anything!
Did a single one of you
ever cry for Shinobu at all?!
You didn't, did you?!
I still can't believe Shinobu died.
That's right! There's no evidence!
Dear relatives,
until it's established for certain
that Shinobu passed away, I'm going to...
manage this house myself!
Does this sound reasonable to you?
Wh-What...?
I got carried away and I really said it.
Still...
It's true that we have no way of knowing
what really happened to Shinobu.
But I want to believe that he's still alive.
Right now, I just want to cling on to that one-in-a-million hope.
It's all I can do to cope with this pain.
Benio has even gone as far
as to wear that gown for him...
No way! No way, Benio! You have to...
Y-You have to take that off!
You'll chain yourself
to Shinobu for the rest of your life!
Take it off already, Benio!
Calm down!
Calm down, Ranmaru!
I'm sorry.
Ranmaru, before I knew it, you've grown
so much taller and stronger than me...
Ranmaru, you need...
You need to go home.
You can't stay here any longer.
But why, Benio? Am I a nuisance?
Have I done something wrong?
It's not that.
But you can't stay here for the rest
of your life just to follow me.
You should return home, focus on training
and become a respected actor.
Wasn't that what you dreamt of?
I can't.
I can't do that, Benio.
I must stay here,
to be by your side and help you out!
You can't!
When I say it, I mean it, Ranmaru!
I can't stand blockheads like you!
Fine.
I'm leaving.
But remember, Benio, whenever you find yourself in trouble, I'll be here for you.
Whenever you need someone,
I'll be here for you.
Whenever you need me,
no matter how much time passes, I'll always...
come to your aid.
Thank you...
I love you.
I love you. Love you!
Ranmaru!
Now I'm all alone, huh...
Shinobu...
Shinobu!
So you're taking it hard too, Benio...
Not at all! I'm completely fine!
Look at me, I'm brimming with life!
See?
And most importantly,
the future of this house is in my hands!
Oh, I gotta run!
There's so much to do!
Right, there's no time to wallow.
C'mon! Get yourself together, Benio!
What kind of High Collar Lady
would I be otherwise?!
High Collar Lady:
An appellation as bright as the sun.
Having tucked the grief away deep in her heart,
our High Collar Lady has forbidden herself to cry.
By hiding her tears and cutting her hair,
she's made another big step towards adulthood.
Next episode of Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Benio might have accepted to run the mansion in Shinobu's stead,
but the Count—the head of the family—
doesn't know the first thing about managing finances.
To make ends meet, Benio has to go to work.
Her first occupation: rickshaw!
But then again, she's our High Collar Lady,
so all sorts of absurdities may be awaiting her.
Next on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Heading Straight for Tomorrow.
Don't miss it!
Episode 33
Heading Straight for Tomorrow
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika
Encoding & QC
Translation
Timing, TLC & Typesetting
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
Chika