Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
And have you seen it?
Those two shockingly beautiful eyes
Overflowing with startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishō Era charming lady
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Hi, Hi, Hi,
Hi, Hi, Hi, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Though they've been born and raised in different families,
the spiritually rich Shinobu threw a lavish garden party to show off his garish tomboy fiancée.
Her best friend Tamaki, who was among guests,
bursts into tears as she hears that the marriage break plan isn't necessarily developing to their advantage.
On the other hand, the staunch Ushigorou
reports seeing Boss embarrassed and oppressed, making Ranmaru feel uneasy.
In reality, however,
through a series of unforeseen happenings,
things were going great for Benio,
as she kept winning people over one after another.
That was when she got gobsmacked by the sudden, flashy appearance of her fan club.
Now then, what kind of conclusion
is this escapade going to arrive to?
How are you finding her, Lady Benio?
Follow me.
Lady Benio, what are you doing?
Uhm, well... You said that Ranko
is going to serve me, right?
So, I thought I should start
by showing her my room.
Let's go.
That girl is too flashy for my taste.
Ah, wait a second.
I am Ranko, nice to meet you.
Ciao!
Episode 12
Dance! Tormented beauty?!
Hey, don't rush me like that!
I wanna take my time!
I've always wanted to visit a noble's mansion!
How can you act like nothing happened?!
Ranmaru, you need to stop it.
Benio, what do you think? It suits me, right?
Look, I even put pads on my breasts.
Y-You idiot! How can you
keep being so nonchalant?
Even disguising as a maid...
Do you have any idea of what'll happen if that geezer unmasks you?
Oh! What a wonderful room!
It's just like a princess's.
Looks so cosy to live in.
No wonder you don't wanna go home.
Listen to me for once!
Really, what is your plan here, Ranmaru?
Aren't you going too far?
I know you're prettier than most girls, but still...
That's why I changed my coiffure to this.
I've discovered that western hairstyles suit me well.
In 1915,  curling iron
becomes widely used for styling people's hair.
This was, in other words,
the pioneer of permanents.
Ranmaru!
I mean, I have to do this,
or else I won't be able...
to be with you.
Wh-What?! Then, do you mean to stay in here as a maid for the rest of your life?
Sure! Leave all the women's work to me!
Y-You can't be serious!
No can do! Go home now!
Just pack and go.
But, Benio...
No means no!
But, but, but, but...
I was worried about you...
Benio, you...
After you didn't come back immediately,
even though you said you would,
living with that handsome Shinobu
that I can't hold a candle to...
I started to worry that you'd fall for him.
I could no longer stand
living my days and nights in this...
This heartbreaking agony.
Gimme!
Nay!
Just give it to me!
I said no!
Come on!
It flew away!
And then...
You looked so troubled at today's banquet.
Ushi told me.
I could no longer watch idly,
so I made a beeline for here.
You did all that... for me?
Yes, that's right.
Ranmaru...
Yes!
Here, stop crying now.
Ah, you hopeless child...
Once you start crying,
you won't stop for hours.
Benio!
Have you ever met Shinobu before?
Right, I did.
Remember that time we flew the kite?
He even mistook me for you!
Ah! And after that too.
There, at the pub, when you went haywire.
Ah, you're right... It's no good.
Benio,
is something wrong?
If he finds out,
we might as well return home together.
Que sera, sera!
Ranmaru!
Hey.
Excuse me.
Ah, you, wait a second.
A-ah-hey, h-hold it.
Shinobu! Weather sure is so nice today...
Well, the weather today
was no complaining material...
Uhm, this here is my new maid,
name's Ranko.
Ranko, huh?
Then, welcome.
Everyone's waiting for you
downstairs. That's all.
Thank God!
He didn't seem to notice.
Ugh, but that trademark laugh
doesn't bode well.
Could he have noticed?
I don't think so...
If he had, he'd have said something.
That means you can still return without blowing your cover.
Please, let me stay with you!
We can't do that.
Can you even imagine
what'll happen if the Count notices?
What was that?
Excellent!
S-Stop.
Why can't I praise him?
You need to mind your place here!
If he loses his nerve, he'll cut you in half with one fell swoop just like that bamboo!
No way!
You think so because you don't know him!
I really, really don't want to get skewered again.
That's a problem for the future me.
If anything, you came here with
the mission of breaking off the engagement.
If they unmask me, that'll just make it easier for us to pack up and leave.
And they can kiss our butts goodbye!
Yes, I suppose.
If anything, I've mastered a lot of women's roles in my early days of training to be an actor.
Leave all the misleading
to my impeccable acting!
Boss, it's as Ranmaru says.
If we three join our strengths,
we can make a mess of this house in no time!
You get it? And even if they find out,
we'll just take our leave then and there.
Now, what'll likely happen instead, is you'd be begging Count for forgiveness when he finds out.
You're worrying too much about him.
Huh, where are you going?
For a moment...
Ladies
Gentlemen
This way.
Benio! Help me!
Benio! Help me!!
I-I-I got it, I got it, I got it.
You want me to go the other way, right?
You saw right through me, heh.
Gentlemen
Oh, I see. And what happened next?
If it isn't Takayashiki returning to the party!
Yeah. I saw Tamaki all the way home,
but she still was noticeably
deeply dispirited by something.
Oh well, let's drink.
Thanks.
Huh? Hey, Shinobu, where's Benio,
the star of the party?
Should be back soon. A new maid came,
so she's showing her around.
Count, that training must've been exhausting.
Would you perhaps like a shower?
Who's that?
I am Ranko, the newest addition to your maids, sir.
You're the one who clapped earlier, right?
Y-Yes.
It was so outstandingly spectacular, I couldn't help but lose my bearings in the most inappropriate manner.
Good, good.
Unlike most of your peers these days,
you've demonstrated
an admirable respect for martial arts.
Yikes, that look...
D-Did he find out?
She's pretty.
Pretty lady, pretty lady!
Was it Ranko?
From today onward, you're my personal aide.
Only cater to my orders and needs. Is that clear?
Dear!
You'll have to forgive her fit of impropriety.
Ranko is Benio's personal maid.
Too early to relax just yet!
This way!
Hold it!
Your name's Ranko, isn't it?
Y-Yes.
So you serve Benio now?
Oh geez, I don't like where this is going.
Where do you come from?
Who's your guarantor?
Dear!
You really don't need to interrogate her like that.
No, I do!
You've never dealt with common folk so you don't know,
but the make-believe fraudsters are aplenty these days!
I know full well
about those make-believe fraudsters.
They get hired in rich families and
use their assumed personalities to rob said families blind, never to be seen again.
Yes, precisely.
Count, Ranm-
Uh, erm, I mean, Ranko
would never be implicated in such things.
And her guarantor is...
Ushigorou from Kurumahiki Clan!
...And that too.
But anyway, our two families have always been close,
so your suspicions are groundless.
Nice one!
I'm a dude disguising as a girl.
Who'd ever call me suspicious?
In that case, was she sent here by your parents?
Yes! That's right!
So, what can our new friend do?
Yessir. As a woman, I know more or less about every part of the housework,
but cooking is definitely my forte.
And what's your special dish?
Let's see...
Your special dish, say it!
Dear! Enough of this farce!
Shut up!
If Benio's family deemed her worthy of being sent here, she has to be a very capable individual!
Your special dish, what is it?!
Uhm... I know, it's the boiled potatoes!
B-Boiled potatoes?
I can feel it.
Aren't you just saying that
to mock my Satsuma origins,
and my samurai prowess?!
Is potato a forbidden product in your family?!
Insolent brat, you just can't stop
talking back, can you?!
En garde!
Count! Ranko knows nothing
about you and your origins!
That's right, lower that katana.
My sixth sense just can't
stop detecting something fishy about her.
It was thanks to my unfaltering sixth sense that I
weathered and survived the Meiji Restoration.
You may have fooled others,
but I can see right through you.
I can feel it. I definitely feel it.
There has to be some other thing that you excel at.
Don't you dare hiding it!
What he means is...
Are you familiar with any of the traditional arts?
Y-Yes, I know a bit of traditional dance.
That's possible.
So what is your school?
Well, uhm...
Fujieda school.
Oh! Fujieda school, huh.
Yes. As a matter of fact, I'm the head.
What? You're the head?!
No, I meant to say the head himself
appointed me an accredited master.
A master at that age?
Y-Yes, she's been practicing since she was this small, you see.
Well, let's go now.
Hold it!
A dancing master is just what we need,
as today is the day we're holding a banquet.
Your dance will entertain our guests.
A dance would prove invaluable
to adorn the celebration!
You're asking for too much!
To be honest, she was only
promised an accreditation.
You may find yourself severely unimpressed by it...
No need for modesty. Wife, make arrangements for the costumes and stage to be prepared.
Dear, I also think we're asking for too much.
No, since we're holding an introduction party for Benio today,
it befits us to provide an elegant display to everything she brought with her.
Do it!
Y-Yes.
We're done for!
Nice, nice!
Hm. That was not half-bad.
It's only natural!
The performer is the founder of the Fujieda School
young kabuki actor Fujieda Ranmaru!
This had suddenly took a turn for worse!
Wh-What? So she's the head herself?
Benio, would you care to explain...
Y-Yes! W-Well, you see...
Fujieda Ranmaru... Isn't that a male name?
Explain yourself, or else...
Crap! This is turning into a disaster!
I have to do something...
O-ho! Hold up!
That's right! I can just play along!
Count, please forgive me.
Her being the dance school master Fujieda Ranmaru was a fabrication all along!
What?
This girl was so lucky as to have a face that resembles Fujieda Ranmaru's,
on top of that,
she was born with a gift for dancing too.
And even her name is Ranko!
Taking after Fujieda Ranmaru
is a nasty habit she just can't give up!
They're like two peas in a pod, though.
Allow me to dispel your doubts
here and now, gentlemen.
You idiot!
Still clinging to that bad habit of yours?!
Idiot!
You like to feel yourself Fujieda Ranmaru so much,
you'd even deceive others for that!
Idiot!
Idiot-idiot-idiot! Idiot!
Idiot, idiot-idiot!
Enough, Benio!
Idiot!
Ah... Okay.
The Count had decided to overlook your slip-up today, if you promise to reform.
But if he catches you returning to your old ways ever again, you're getting a taste of his katana,
so better watch out.
Understood.
It looks to me like her determination is firm.
Ranko, you can start with your duties!
Okay...
It worked!
And that's how a certain day of a certain month of 1918 was concluded.
Good job, Benio!
Lady Benio, the bathroom
is prepared for your use.
Ah, I see.
And you, Ranko!
Yes?
You're going to enter the bath with Lady Benio and rub her back.
Wh-What?
Huh? Was that a joke, Mrs. Kisaragi?
It is the custom for high-ranking
ladies of noble families
to leave the matters of bathing and such to their court ladies.
Come on, Ranko.
Get naked and bathe with her!
Oh jeez...
Now then, Lady Benio.
Start undoing your clothing. Hurry up!
What's there to be so embarrassed about?
All our maids are females too, after all.
Now...
Ah... B-But not all of them!
Ranko is actually a ma—
Benio!
"A ma?"
What's "a ma?"
No, I mean, you're a ma-ature person,
so we find it embarrassing to undress before you.
Right, Ranko?
Uh, huh?
Ah, right! That's exactly the reason...
I see.
I'll come see you two later then.
Benio!
Ranmaru!
Tee-hee-hee.
She may insist all she wants,
but we won't bathe together.
How about you sneak out and hide somewhere?
Yeah. It's not like your skin and bones
interest me anyway.
How do you know it's skin and bones
if you haven't seen it?!
She's always so rough with others.
I knew something like this would happen!
Go back in!
Ranko!
Don't you neglect your duties!
Get back in!!
You slacker!
You pervert!
I-I lost my cool for a moment.
I think I let him see my shapes.
It seems she finally accepted it.
I had nowhere to go!
Out of the frying pan into the fire,
a boy and a girl are forced
to bathe together.
Even in the warm waters of our springs...
Will the flowers bloom or not?!
Benio can't help but worry
that Ranmaru's true cross-dressing identity
might be unveiled.
However, Ranmaru and Ushigorou
live without a care in the world.
Naturally, chaos and commotion ensue.
Boss Hanamura Benio's Dwelling
The ruthless drilling instructor
is finally knocked down.
Ah, but even so,
Shinobu uncovers Ranmaru's disguise.
Next time on "Here Comes the High Collar Lady":
Love is a Sailboat of Reflection.
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that phase
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with the people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart;
I want him to turn around before he leaves
to give me that loving glance once again
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have these unrequited feelings
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady who's a little pretentious
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
WOWmd
Encoding & QC
Translation
TLC & Timing
Special Thanks
Editing
Anonymous
alucardnoyuuutsu
Perevodildo
Golden Time Anime (VK)
WOWmd