Hermit Village
The Skaro Hunting Society
(Tetris no Miko, Nanto)
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translation
TLC
Editor
Episode 5
Venus
Ah... My heart tingles!
I wish I could become that shell.
If I could, I would be a big clam.
Venus's shell, Venus's shell,
shell, shell, shell, shell...
Oh dear. I've gotten itchy.
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
Eh?
Venus, you say? You mean that naked woman standing in the shell?
Friend, you sure have good taste.
If you go down this way,
you should encounter her before long.
But I don't think your legs'll take you there.
You should take a taxi.
Where to, Sir?
Take me to where the shellfish live.
Right away.
200 yen already?
It's the shell!
Hi.
Oh, welcome. Would you like
a little something to warm you up?
I can make a discount just for you, hun.
Oh dear, he's gone.
Thank you very much
for visiting our store.
Would you like to buy a gift,
build up your wealth, or go on a love hunt?
Pardon me.
Perhaps, if you were to place it
on your lady's finger, like so?
Her heart would melt for you for sure.
Not buying?!
The Venus?
Yonder, inside a comfortable shell...
ON DUTY
Oh, what's up?
I may be a shell of a man,
but I'm a shell of a good admiral!
Long ago, I was on the Battleship Yamato
and oh, how we drank!
Weird, this one won't open.
Oh, dear, aren't you Alain Delon?
I'm sorry, I just can't! My grandfather died from eating bad abalone, you see.
Oh, how cruel.
So this is the sad fate of an Abalone.
My unrequited love...
Shall I give up on it?
Salty!
Ooh, this is incredible!
Venus!
I... I have endured quite a struggle
to f-finally find you.
I love you! I love you
from the bottom of my heart!
I love you.
Y-You're the only one
I will ever love in this world! It's true!
My head was filled only with you.
That's how I found you! I love you. I love you!
Will you please answer my love?
You have no idea how much
I have struggled to find you.
Shit... You don't understand me, do you?
Look, me—a man.
A man?
Yeah. Woman.
Woman?
Yeah. Wait...
I don't suppose you understand.
That word refers to the body, and...
Oh, you're here again?
Eat this.
Thank you.
She'd probably understand
at once from eating this.
No!
No...
It's beautiful...
You're gorgeous!
One serving of takoyaki coming up!
And in the red corner, we have Black Tiger,
weighing in at a whopping 620 pounds!
Oh, no! Oh, no, oh, no! Oh, no, oh, no!
Oh, no!
Hey! Follow me for a bit!
B-But I'm kinda b-busy here...
And in the black corner, we have a human playboy!
Weighing in at 120 pounds!
3... 2... 1...
0!
Oh! I-It's a gold coin torpedo!
All right...
Giving a gold coin to a cat! What a shock!
[Japanese idiom]
Let's go to the Earth's surface
and live happily together.
I am happy.
I'm very happy.
Yes...
She became Venus the mummy!