Hermit Village
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translator
Editor
Episode 2
Wind Chimes
Sure is hot today...
You really don't feel like doing much
of anything when it's this hot.
Ah, all because of the heat...
Ah, I even brought out
the shogi board, but then again—
there's no one to play with 'cause of the heat!
Or maybe there is someone?
How about that?
There we go!
Hello.
Wanna play a match?
Oh, that is a bold move right there.
Maybe go here next?
That's a decent trade.
I see, then how about this?
Here, this is my response.
I see...
Here. Like this, see?
Then how about this?
Well, that's some impressive moves!
There!
Caught you!
King
I give up!
Ah, he's damn strong.
Too strong for me.
Maybe there's someone a tad weaker around?
Ah... Someone weaker...
Hey, you!
Wh-What was that? What happened?
Someone is...
What?
So creepy!
Oh? A mosquito?
No, rather, a midge.
Whoa! A beauty!
Well, I'll be...
You're a pretty thing, you know that?
Oh! You're devilishly alluring!
You're so naughty...
Oh no, it's just that you...
This is irresistible...
O-Ow! Ow-ow!
Ow! Help me! I ended up
letting her suck my blood out!
This love was devilish indeed!
What a useless man...
Ah, sure is hot today...
Why is it so hot?
Oh geez... The wind is so unkind to us today.
So hot...
It's unbearable...
I'm drenched in sweat.
I can't stand it.
We've gotta do something...
That's right, let's go to the Wind Hermit.
I beg your pardon, Wind Hermit?
Please, Wind Hermit...
Come on, wake up, please.
Wake up!
Quick...
Here, tickle-tickle.
P-Please, I can't eat more... Just one more...
Come on, wake up!
Please...
Wh-Wh-What's going on? What?
Hey, the heat is unbearable today.
Please blow a little wind for us, won't you?
Ah, sure. No problem.
Here I go, then.
How about it?
Ah, that's better...
Feels so good!
Then I'm happy too.
Hey, husband!
What's that you're doing, at your age?
Well, you see, wife, I was actually just...
Spare me your excuses!
Why don't you cool down
your head a bit instead?
Like, for example, with this!
H-Hey!
No, I mean...
Your hair is blowing such a cold wind!
Hey! My head feels weird
when you blow it at me... Hey!
Come, come...
Come on, don't you like it?
Here you go.
I only came here to quickly wet my throat,
but when the sake is good, it's real good.
Hey, Missy, I'll have one more.
Maybe...
One turns into two.
Two turn into four...
No, four turn into eight.
Eight turn into sixteen,
but I'll have just one more.
Just one more.
Yes, one more!
M-More...
Oh, gosh?
So he's finally turned into a tiger?
[tora = tiger (primary meaning) / drunkard (colloquial meaning)]
Can you even get home when you're so drunk?
It's fine, I'll get home, all right.
Your house is that way.
Take care!
That hit home...
Have you been drinking again?
Oh?
Been drinking again?
Been drinking again?!
I'm seeing things...
Been drinking again?
Why should I be scared of my own wife?
I'm not scared!
I'm scared...
Mom...
forgive me...
Don't think I will, after all...