Hermit Village
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translator
Editor
Episode 3
Charleston
Is that...?
Having all that fun to himself!
What a stingy grandpa.
Elder, I want to join as well.
Join whom?
The women, of course!
Aren't you having a lot of fun together in there?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I saw it, Elder.
Saw what?
Oh?
No women in here...
They weren't real.
Let me just show you.
You stay still in there.
Oh?
Ah, pardon me.
You there, watching this—
you shall suffer the same fate!
Nothing personal.
And then we do this...
How about this?
You're coming with me.
Your intentions are impure.
I apologize.
I wasn't watching where I was going...
You still can't get over
your impure wishes, can you?
Maybe you're in need of asceticism?
Do you think so?
Maybe I just don't have the right makings?
You're not making it easy for me...
You'll need to feed on air.
Oh, I see...
The universe is infinite.
Right, right, eat up.
Wow... This air is tastier
than anything I've ever tried!
Are you feeding on air again?
That's right...
But are you sure you can survive
on nothing but that, husband?
Of course, my love!
Goodness, you're so light!
Because I want to be fluffy for you!
Isn't he taking the whole
lightness idea too far?
Think I'll quit feeding on air.
And you, what practice are you doing?
Well, you see...
Really now, that didn't sound one bit good.
My! Saying things like that in my face!
I'll make you regret this!
Ah!
What a pathetic sound.
Ouch!
I feel you, kid.
Losing to a woman is painful.
So frustrating...
All right, how about I avenge you? Ready?
Fine by me.
Can you see her?
Is it ready yet?
Yes, yes, I've got the water temperature just right for you.
Hey, now.
Wh-What is it?
Whisper-whisper...
I'll take care of her body.
Your work here is done, go home now.
Sorry, could you wash my back?
Sure, sure.
I'm getting tired of this kimono.
Why don't I give it you?
My... I don't deserve to wear
something so gorgeous...
So, do you think it suits me?
Yes, it looks great on you.
How did I end up like this?
Welcome back.
How did it go, Elder?
You're Elder, aren't you?
So did you avenge me?
I fell flat.