Hermit Village
The Skaro Hunting Society
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translator
TLC
Editor
Episode 4
The Merry Spirits
Here they come!
Hey, they're here!
Coming this way!
I'm feeling great today!
That's right.
I wonder what they want.
Good day!
Great! We have visitors!
Here they come!
They're here!
How lascivious!
This is where the spirits rest, you know!
What do you think you're doing?!
How lascivious!
What a romantic night...
Sheesh, what are you thinking of?
Oh, my...
Don't forget this.
That's better.
It's so hot...
Oh?
Ow-ow-ow!
Now just a minute!
Just what do you think you're doing,
always following and pestering those two!
Now! You're coming with me, you jester!
Okay...
Husband!
I won't do anything bad...
Didn't you hear me?!
Then... how about I tell you this?
Attention!
Hey, let's run for it!
Grave of the Cutlery Maker
Cutlery Maker
Help me out, man!
You see, this and that happened, and then...!
Cutlery Maker
How about this? Seen this?
Oops.
No! Help!
No!
My, this is lovely!
Will you dance with me?
Huh? Where's the music?
You losers!
They're at it, aren't they?
Hey there, lovebirds.
Don't go defiling this graveyard.
Are you deaf or what?
Hey, hey there! Keep at it!
Stay here. Just a bit longer!
Wanna fight for it?
Yeah, I'm gonna fight you!
Hey, babe, let me see your face a bit closer.
Sure.
Here you go.
That's not right.
I want your body, too.
Sure.
Stop messing with me!
The real you, not a copy, get ready for bed!
Hurry up with it!
You little... Now you've done it!
Go to hell!
My! How vexing.
How dare he kick me like that?
No, no, no, help, help, help, help me!
Now, do you understand?
I apologize.
Well done, well done.
Um, but the hermit is asleep again!
My...
Hey...
Can we now...?
Just once more.
I love you.
What is that?
I apologize for disturbing you all.