Hermit Village
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translator
Editor
Episode 1
Stamina Ampoule
Whew! What a dazzling beauty!
Simply stunning!
What's this?
I can't see a thing...
That's right...
I have to go get my glasses.
Huh? She's gone.
My, oh my.
Ah...
Ciao! Ciao, babe!
Oh, my...
Hey, hello there.
Hello.
Hello!
You're quite the man.
You're getting prettier every time I look at you!
Oh...
What a charmer you are.
Tsk! Did someone beat me to the punch already?
Hey...
I can be that handsome too,
I feel like it!
Go!
Ladies don't even look at me.
I'm home!
Blazes, husband! Where have you been?
T-Taking a walk.
With other women?!
Ah, no...
Every night, every night, you've been giving me
the one and the same excuse—in your age!
Even at home, my man's pride is under attack!
Hey, friend. You, in glasses.
I've got just what you need.
Just call this number
and they'll let you right in.
It's the true paradise on Earth!
This looks interesting...
I'll do it at once with this public phone...
Hello?
Sir, we need to check if you're not with the police.
You're good, go ahead.
Ooh! Wonderful.
Meat and drinks all around.
Not bad, I'd say...
Hey, won't you drink with me, dear sir?
Oh! Benten, my goddess!
Is this sake too sweet for you?
You've such a wonderful chin,
it's driving me crazy.
Oh, my...
I guess it really is hopeless for me...
Hey, lady... Lady!
Ah, that was invigorating.
Now I'll have something nice
to bring with me to the underworld...
The life of a flower...
sure is short.
Elder, I beg you.
I know, I know.
It's this that you want.
Eternal Youth
Thank you...
And Asian ginseng—100 grams...
And after that...
The juice of half-a-dozen taro stems, right...
In you go.
And um... Now, steadily, calmly.
Squeeze it for several seconds...
Ground cherry to taste?
Chinese medicine miracle cure
Eternal Youth
Just half of it will grant you
infinite vitality.
My word, this is totally unbearable.
All that's left now is to wait for this old hag to croak, and find a better wife for myself.
Let's start with an experiment...
Now, another experiment.
Don't get in the way of others exploding!
This means I am immortal now.
That's the Hermit Village style heart-strengthening technique.
I'm looking forward to what happens next.
Huh? How did this happen?
Look, daughter—he's even unafraid of me!
Go deal with him, the sexy way!
All right.
Hey... Husband! Wake up!
There's something strange with me.
I drank that black juice you left.
What? Juice?
From the ampoule, right?
Did you drink it too?
Ah, I can't go on anymore...
Look, Husband, since you've fixed the roof,
fix the room too, okay?
Our kitchen pump is broken too.
And help me in the garden too.
Oh, right, the room was full of paper scraps.
Someone will need to feed the chickens too.
Then there's also the bathtub next to it.
It's overflowing now because of all this rain.
Really, I have so many errands
to keep me busy all day long!