Hermit Village
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Translator
Editor
Episode 7
Fairy Tale
Um... Mesmerizing.
What is the tea?
Without tea, it's unteanable.
When tea is bitter, it's regretteable.
When you put tea and tea together,
it's a disastear!
Ah... What a pleasant sound.
So good...
This is irresistible!
Whoa! The ladies love him!
I'm jealous!
Sound is the key to a woman's heart.
Sound?
The sounds of instruments.
Music, get it?
Please, music.
So soothing...
Heavenly!
Okay, even I can conquer her with this!
She's so beautiful I'm always
too shy to approach her.
Okay, let's play music right away.
Now grow up and become a saxophone.
That!
Bend a little and become a saxophone.
What a weird rain.
Hey, I'll be taking them all!
Thief!
Say what you will, the violin is the finest setter of moods.
Hm? Where might I have seen this before?
Ah, still not it.
Ah, then let's move on straight to the stereo.
All of these are just various junk.
It's a music box.
I'll just have to rely on her maternal instinct.
Everyone has a mate.
Only I'm alone!
Hey, what's wrong?
Why don't you stop crying
and tell me the reason?
Everyone has a mate.
Only I'm alone.
Now that you put it this way, I understand.
Okay, leave it to me.
Let's all create an orchestra.
Orchestra?
Right!
Hey, become a stick!
I'm a conductor.
Now, let's gather the others.
Those two are going at it!
Huh?
My heart can't resist you...
Found them!
That chest reminds me of drums!
Huh? Thought I was kissing a woman...
Hey, is everyone ready?
Now gather in front
of the Stuck-up Hermit's house!  Got it?
Chief, don't we need drums?
How about you take care of that yourself?
Please, big stones, small stones,
become a drum kit.
No, that won't do. It had uranium inside.
I need a thud be a "thud," not an atomic blast!
This is ideal!
Mr. Moon!
Out of the question. Forget it!
Become a small drum.
Become a big drum.
Become a drumstick and a cymbal!
Here, sorry for the delay.
No good, it's just laughing!
No!
Huh...
Pretty good...
Hey, everyone, let's try our best one more time.
She's not impressed at all.
Maybe it's just not to her taste?
That's it, you've got me serious.
I can't stand it anymore!
Ugh! So annoying!
If you lose your cool,
you're out for the count.
Women love the stoic and unperturbed type.
Like this—knock, knock.
Try it.
Okay.
Oh, not there! That sound
is my weakness, it makes me numb.
Oh? Then how about this one?
What have you been loitering outside my house for all this while?
Come on in, don't you see it's not locked?
Sound-sound-sound.
You're a worthless man, after all...