It's neither round nor square.
Let alone obscurities like a rhombus!
As strong as an elephant
and shining like a rabbit's eyes!
It's neither red nor blue.
Let alone obscurities like ultramarine!
The Shape of Happiness
[The whole episode is a massive parody of Dragon Quest 2 (1987)]
Dark Demon King Tempest Chapter
Sheesh, they're so noisy.
How am I supposed to sleep like this?
That's a huge monster-oh!
Nice! Been a while
since our last big catch.
Shumomomo!
Kachink
Momomo!
I'm gonna borrow this.
Momo's home!
Amazing, Omae!
H-He's strong...
I need them...
The United Army is weak and needs people like them who can go into battle on short notice...
Here, thanks a lot!
Say, don't you wanna keep it?
I do!
Then it's yours. However...
Hey!
Look what I got!
Wow! Nice!
I wasn't done talking!
If you want this sword, then come along with me.
Mama told me not to follow
any old men I don't know!
What about an old women?
No, not that!
Why are you talking to yourself?
No, I was just saying
I want you to join our United Army.
Is your United Army delicious?
Yeah! In our army,
you always get to eat your fill!
Wow, maybe we should try?
But it's not just all fun and games, is it?
You're sharp, girl!
But it's not a big deal, really.
You'd just need to beat
the Dark Demon King once, that's all.
Who's the Dark Demon King?
What?
You don't know about the Dark Demon King?!
We don't.
And no one watching this OVA knows, either.
Wouldn't this be a good time
to do some exposition?
Yes. Let's do it, then.
Our planet is slowly falling under the control
of an evil super-psychic, the Dark Demon King.
REENACTMENT
Our forces are putting up a valiant fight,
but it hasn't been easy.
Archive footage
But as long as our allied forces have the Statue of Mokemoke,
the Demon King's army
can't launch a full-scale attack!
What's the Statue of Mokemoke?
You don't know
about the Statue of Mokemoke?!
Then there's no choice.
Part 2 of the exposition!
More archive footage
The Statue of Mokemoke
is the last advantage our forces have.
The Demon King is deathly afraid of this statue.
This is because the statue has the power
to revive the God of Destruction.
The God of Destruction
is a demon of terrifying power.
The legends say he can plunge the whole world
into a sea of fire in one day!
If that's the case, wouldn't it be easier
to just revive that God of Destruction right away and defeat the Demon King?
It's not that simple!
You see, the God of Destruction
wipes out friend and foe alike!
If we use the Statue of Mokemoke,
we all fuckin' die!
Wow!
Who came here to watch two men undress?!
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Next morning
at the United Army's
National Pension
Good morning!
Da-oh!
What, you're still sleeping?
Should we let them sleep?
We can help ourselves to some cola.
The United Army sure is nice, letting us use this pension-oh!
But as long as we have that Statue of Mokemoke on our side,
the Demon King can't make a move, right?
Then I guess we're safe.
But he's the Demon King,
so you never know
what he might try to get the statue.
Carelessness is the enemy.
You're annoying me so early in the morning!
That dog is really creeping me out.
Is that really a dog?
I'm no dog, no ma'am!
I'm Papo, a police officer
from the United Police Department!
We have an emergency.
Did something happen?
The thing is, the Statue of Mokemoke...
Ah! The Demon King's minions might be eavesdropping.
Come closer, won't you?
Is it really such a big deal?
Thing is...
What's your problem?!
Ah! Omae is still half-asleep!
Do you really find it that fun to bully me?
By no means!
So, what did you have to say about
the Statue of Mokemoke?
Yes, I was getting to that.
It's always been stored at this secret location,
but now it's gone!
Huh?!
If you apply a force strong enough to it,
the God of Destruction might be resurrected.
Sorry.
Where's the Mokemoke now?
Right now, the Mokemoke...
is in Aria's hand.
So that's the Statue of Mokemoke?
It's just an empty cola bottle!
That's exactly how it is, my friends!
Nobody would think to look
for the Statue of Mokemoke
in the pension refrigerator, would they?
You think so?!
The God of Destruction is being reborn!
No way! He really is being reborn!
If we all died, this anime would be canceled too!
Man, I slept so well!
It was a little loud, though...
What's this? A morning marathon?
Alright then, I ain't gonna lose!
No! The God of Destruction has resurrected!
Eh?! I just woke up and it's time to die already?!
Let's go! Let's go!
H-He's tiny...
Statue.
That's...
The God of Destruction?
Are you sure he's the same one from the legend?
Hataboda Castle
United Forces Headquarters
Professor, were you able to figure out anything?
Hm. It seems the God of Destruction
was resurrected as a baby.
But why?
Surely, there must be
some intricate logic to this.
[yayakoshi = complex/confusing; yayako = baby]
Ugh... No.
I mean...
I'm just a retired crepe wholesaler.
I don't understand the complicated stuff.
That makes sense.
But hey, if the world isn't gonna be destroyed,
shouldn't we be celebrating?
But the Dark Demon King
isn't afraid of the United Army,
he's afraid of the resurrection
of the God of Destruction.
If he learns that it's just this helpless baby...
They'll launch an all-out attack!
Guys, we absolutely must keep this a secret.
If we manage to hide the truth,
they'll probably be too afraid to attack...
The demon army went all-out!
We're surrounded!
So the Demon King
finally lost his patience?
Ah! That's...!
That's the Dark Demon King!
That's the Dark Demon King?
Victory is already assured!
Either stick to your guns and be wiped out,
or hand over the Statue
of Mokemoke and surrender!
Even if we gave him the Statue of Mokemoke,
he'd probably execute all of us anyway!
So we're out of options?
Leave this to me.
Ah! Your Majesty,
they've raised the flag!
Oh-ho! Are they surrendering?
Yellow Handkerchief of Happiness
[koufuku (幸福) = happiness (alternative reading "shiawase"); koufuku (降伏) = surrender (usually signaled with a white flag);
Yellow Handkerchief of Happiness (Shiawase no kiiroi hankachi) is a classic 1977 film,
centered around yellow handkerchiefs fluttering on a line as we see here]
Yellow Handkerchief of Happiness
A yellow handkerchief of happiness...
It looks like my stopgap "Yellow handkerchief of happiness" attack was a success.
Too cheesy!
Looks like there's no choice...
I'm going in!
Ah, hey!
You cannot-oh!
Let's go!
Not in your ripped suit!
Oh...
Don't go!
No matter how good you guys are, you're up against the Demon King's Large Tank Unit!
There's no time to argue!
Let's go, Omae!
Okay!
Go, Retiree!
Yeah!
Ah, you're going to fight with us, Retiree?
Naturally!
I wonder if they know this anecdote?
Take two M72A2 bazookas...
Easy to break.
Take three M72A2 bazookas...
So?
Look, Kintaro.
What the hell are you yapping about?!
I see. I think I have a rough idea
of what you mean...
Enough!
Attack!
Some hotheads showed up!
Blow them to kingdom come, men!
I guess we can't win the normal way against tanks, huh.
I thought so too.
This is no time to be yapping!
All right, then! If it's come to this,
I'll attack with my Fluttering Water Fleas!
Take this!
Nice!
Hey, aren't biological weapons kind of a no-no?
Men! Don't flinch, crush them!
What's wrong, Retiree?
Speak to me!
Charades
Dog! Dog!
What? Wrong?
Charades
N-Not a cat either...
And probably not Bulgarian
Madara wolf either...
Charades
Ah! I know!
The Demon King! Yes, yes.
Charades
Putting that aside...
Six? What, wrong?
Ah, a hand! Hand!
Yes, what is it this time? Huh?
Something's hanging from your hand...
Uh? No, not that...
Under the hand... U-Under the hand... Hand...
I get it! Minions!
Yes, I see!
The Demon King's minions!
So, what should we do
with the Demon King's minions?
M-Mountain!
What? Smaller?
Hill!
Not that... Not that either?
Not hill... What could it be?
Doesn't he mean a "mound?"
Yay!
So, is it "jump over the mound?"
Not that. Before the mound...
Mound front?
To catch!
Ah, that's right!
So what's the message?
Catch the Demon King's minions!
You fell for it!
What unbelievable cowards!
Hey, Demon King, if you want the hostages back,
then pull your tanks back immediately.
Or else, your minions...
I'm not sure who's the villain here anymore.
Your Majesty, what are we going to do about their threats?!
Blow them up, and the hostages too.
What? So cruel!
'Course it is! We gotta uphold our reputation as villains!
Demons
Long story short, die!
The plan failed!
Now it's over!
We won!
I wouldn't be so sure about that!
What?
[烈火亜舎 on Koitsu's back is a typical biker gang name,
烈火 in it is spelled "rekka"—the same as "tow truck"]
TICKET
Raging Fire Gang
The Tow Truck Squad is here!!
TICKET
Raging Fire Gang
Along with beautiful policewoman
Kuribayashi Kimie!
TICKET
Raging Fire Gang
It's Papo!
He and Beruno brought help!
Begin the battle!
What? What? What?
What are you doing?
Okay! Okay! Okay!
H-H-Hold it! What are you doing?
Can't you see?
We're towing all your tanks away!
This is a no-parking zone.
Any violators will be towed without exception.
You made that up just now!
Fines and transfer fees
add up to 100 trillion in gold!
ASTONISHED
We did it!
It was a success!
Next time, I'll definitely get my hands on the Statue of Mokemoke! Don't you forget!
Demon King...
Such a trite parting threat!
Oh, I see. He doesn't know yet that the Statue of Mokemoke has been revived already.
Oh? Come to think of it, the God of Destruction
is nowhere to be found.
Ah!
Commander! We found this letter in the castle.
I’ve heard a woman’s voice
is best suited for reading letters aloud.
You're probably just scared
of long lines and rare words.
"I'm about to board a train bound for the north country to set off on a journey by myself.
I want to have enough time
to ponder life...
When I finish this journey
and set foot in my homeland again,
I think you’ll see me as someone
a hundred times more mature than I am now.
Until then, please don't try to find me.
From the God of Destruction."
I see... it was foolish
to think he'd stay a child forever.
We didn't notice him growing up...
Come back as a wonderful grown-up man,
God of Destruction!
To the grave...
[hakai shin = God of Destruction; hakaishi = tombstone]
No, that's terrible!
If we don't find him and do something
soon, it'll become irreversible!
We'll depart at once!
Thus, Omae and his friends suddenly set out
on a six-day journey through the northern regions in pursuit of the God of Destruction!
The Shape of Happiness.
Dark Demon King Raging Waves Chapter
[Parody of Infant Island from the Godzilla universe:
島 (island) can be read as "tou" and tou usually means 塔 (tower)]
INFANT TOWER
There's a tower.
It's an Infant Tower.
INFANT TOWER
Things would be so much faster
if the God of Destruction was here...
Let's split up and investigate!
Oops!
Whoa-ah!
Y-You're stepping on your socks!
Put your shoes on, dammit!
Oh. I can walk now.
Let's all look for him.
God of Destruction!
God of Dewoun...
Please return the egg!
Oh?
Please, sir!
Please return the egg.
But you've already got it right there.
[kaesu (返す) = to return; kaesu (孵す) = to hatch / to incubate]
Please warm this egg
until the chick hatches.
Fine...
We'll be hiding inside this box now.
Could you please lock us inside?
Sure.
Huh? The egg is moving!
It's hatching!
Hi!
Fantastic!
Amazing!
Retiree!
What are you doing?!
Hey, mister!
A tip, please!
Huh?! You were doing this for money?
A tip! A tip!
You should give them their due.
What about looking for the God of Destruction and defeating the Dark Demon King?
Huh? Are you going to defeat
the Dark Demon King?
That's right-oh!
The thing is, the Dark Demon King extorts a ton of gold out of us every month,
and he says he'll knock down the tower if we don't pay!
Please! Defeat the Dark Demon King!
Is that so?
Don't worry.
We'll make sure to crush the Dark Demon King.
But before that, we have to find
the God of Destruction.
We understand.
If that's the case, you can borrow this.
This is Mosira,
the guardian deity of Infant Tower.
[Parody of Mothra, a butterfly-like monster
also from the Godzilla universe, a guardian of Infant Island]
Great! This Mosira will be a real godsend!
Well then, take care!
Okay, let's go now! Depart!
Weapons, everyone! Weapons!
Anyone need weapons?
Dad, nobody wants to buy any weapons!
Giovanni, we got a customer!
Weapons! Weapons!
Wow! It's fast!
Yes! Giddyup! Ah!
Stop! There's someone on the track! Brake!
Oh no, we ran someone over!
Are you okay?
No, we're not!
Sorry for running you over.
Who are you?
I'm Gorath, the forest fairy.
[Parody of 1962 film "Ominous Star Gorath":
yousei (妖星) = demonic star; yousei (妖精) = fairy]
And I'm his son Giovanni.
Ah!
Oh man! All my best goods are ruined!
Ah! That hat!
The God of Destruction had a hat like that.
Eh? Huh? You mean this?
Well, if you wanna know...
That's some trash I picked up on the roadside...
It's not a hat!
It's a full-fledged weapon!
If you've got your eye on this weapon,
you're a discerning buyer—I can tell, sir.
Weapon?
How is that a weapon?
Well, you see, all you need is some magic and...
He's joking! I just found it...
Glove!
See? No matter how hard you hit someone with it,
your hand doesn't hurt at all!
Really? But I was certain that was the hat the God of Destruction had.
Maybe it's best to buy it, just in case?
Yeah. It'd make a good argument
if we need to apologize to him.
Introducing the hobby sculpturing machine Modella
Please walk closer to the edge of the road.
Vroom...
Wow! The tip of his mouth
is spinning with incredible force!
If you got attacked with that,
you wouldn't stand a chance!
Don't just suddenly appear
to start putting together a garage kit!
OH NO!
The Dark Demon King appears!
Dark Demon King!
His costume is different from last time!
I'm a TPO adherent, you know.
[TPO = (appropriate to) time, place, occasion​]
But more importantly,
I have some good news for you all.
Huh? Did you manage to find
the God of Destruction?
Don't say it out loud!
I know the God of Destruction was resurrected
as a baby from the Statue of Mokemoke,
and is now missing,
having left to travel alone.
I already captured Papo and everyone else.
S-So it leaked?
Right now we're holding a massive search
for the God of Destruction.
If you keep wandering around here, that might be a problem, you know!
They haven't noticed
Retiree and Mosira yet.
'Sup!
Too loud, hello!
What are you doing?
Just wanted to ask you something.
Surely, you know where the God of Destruction is, right?
Now tell me!
Tell me where he is!
I don't know!
Do it, Modella!
Stop!
No, you stop!
Take one more step, and we'll crank up
the rotation speed even more.
Beruno’s soft skin would end up more scraped
and raw than the Hare of Inaba’s!
[According to the myth of the White Hare of Inaba,
a hare tricked sharks into being used as a land bridge, but provoked them,
so the last shark attacked him, ripping his fur from him]
Damn you!
Come on, just say it!
I really don't know!
Increase rotation speed!
Beruring is in danger.
Okay, let's step in!
Mumble-mumble.
What? You've got a good strategy for this?
Okay, let's hear it.
He put it right through my ears!
T-The hell is that thing?!
Now!
My ears!
Okay, use that!
No! Stay away! Don't come near!
Omae!
Stop!
Looks like I have to summon the last and strongest monster! Killing Kitora, come on!
Oopsie-Daisy.
Kitora is the most cruel
and ferocious monster in the universe!
Just try to imagine how terrifying he is!
Buzzing...
Ah! The Demon King is toast.
I feel like I know exactly
how terrifying he is now!
We won't be able to hit it
unless we attack from above-oh!
If only you were
already an imago, huh?
Things have taken a turn for the stupid, but hang in there!
Come on...
No luck...
No luck, huh?
Perhaps we can't win this one
unless the God
of Destruction appears!
Ah! Look over there!
What kind of thing is that?!
["Aen" is a calque of the word eien (永遠), meaning "eternal"—
typical for monster names in Ultraman]
Aen monster Shirako
appears
Ugh. Yet another eldritch horror.
Oh! Look at that!
It's standing up to Kitora!
This is our chance!
Let's get to a safe place!
SAFE    PLACE
Looks like everyone made it out alive.
Yeah, but what are we gonna do now?
For starters, how about
you put something on, Beruno?
Gorath, sell me some clothes.
Sure! Only one million gold!
Kidding! Kidding!
Dad! You've told enough lies already!
Listen up, everyone! That “magic glove” Dad sold you was just a hat I picked up somewhere!
It probably belongs
to the God of Destruction!
Giovanni! Shut up!
Is that so?
Yes, that's right! But that's because I was just about to tell you...
So you weren't going to?
Yes.
I get it now. So this was
the God of Destruction’s hat all along?
Huh? Come to think of it, weren't Shirako's
spine fins shaped like this too?
Huh? So, then...
That's the God of Destruction?
It's burning!
Really, that was just a stuffed animal?
He's the God of Destruction, all right!
Armage!
Badass!
He dealt with Kitora in one fell swoop!
Hey, God of Destruction!
You've become so handsome since we saw you last!
Grand! Splendid! Bravo!
So the Dark Demon King is still alive?!
Wasn't it obvious? I haven't even shown you my true form yet, so how could I die?
Your true form?
What is it?
Dark Demon King...
Jam Bear King!
[ankoku maou (暗黒魔王) = Dark Demon King;
anko kumaou (アンコ熊王) = Red Bean Jam Bear King]
We're going home.
Hey, wait a minute!
Now that you know my true identity,
I'll have to kill you all!
You told it to us yourself,
so whatcha yapping about?
Kill!
Demon King! That's not "kill" but "roll"!
[korosu = to kill; korogasu = to roll]
I know that!
Huh?
This one's ready!
Yes, now to cover you in jam...
[ohagi = rice ball coated with sweetened red beans]
My Rice Ball Attack is completed!
Th-This is so dumb!
Is there some meaning to this?!
In fact, inside this rice cake, he's growing up nicely, feeding on my sweet bean paste.
You think you're a dung beetle?!
Oh! He's already ready!
So what? He's the same as before!
What's wrong with you, Retiree?!
He's been baptized in the jam
and become my loyal servant!
Now he's gonna kill his ex-friends!
But then, why didn't you
baptize someone stronger?
Don't mind if I do!
Ah! No way!
I didn’t think he’d actually be able
to roll up the God of Destruction!
Don't underestimate my powers!
Just watch me cover him in jam now...
A lone
bear
Ain't got enough jam?
A lone
bear
Yeah.
A lone
bear
Wh-What now?!
The God of Destruction is growing again!
Probably because
of what the Dark Demon King did!
Don't tell me the baby finally grew up?!
Grown-ups are just destructive machines
with no emotions!
This planet is done for!
G-Good thing I hid a rocket
for this kind of occasion.
Other planets are calling for me already, so goodb—!
You bear bastard! You think you can do whatever you want and get away with it?!
Ah... he got him.
Armage!
We gotta stop the God of Destruction!
Stop! God of Destruction!
Omae!
Control your anger!
Oh! Look at that!
The Demon is...!
Nah, it's still the same.
Well, you can't really read his emotions
with a face like that.
The soul of the God of Destruction...
Soared up...
And so, that's how the Dark Demon King was destroyed,
and love and peace
were restored to this planet.
Come on, Retiree! That jam is dangerous!
You gotta wipe that stuff off!
I'd hurry up if I were you!
Arrogant fools!
I am the Dark Demon King!
Do you really think you can do
this to me and get away with it?!
What happened to your magic power?
Without any jam, I have none...
Then I guess you're gonna be a rug forever.
I'm not a rug!
But where did the God of Destruction go-oh?
Hm...
I bet he'd sealed himself in a Statue
of Mokemoke again on some other planet.
No way!
All that's left now is the Song of Light.
These days I think he was the main character of "Shiawase"
Rainbow crayon on a white planet
Busy
Ao-san, Kaneyan, Eikichi,
are you watching? It's me.
Badumtss
Fluffy marshmallows in the blue sky
I claim this cell for myself!
I claim this one 💞
This one's for me!
What kind of drawing can I draw?
I don't want this cell!
I'll draw it all with my dad
I... can't approve this work
Maybe paint it with a happy color?
Never...
Mom also spins around with us
Would never approve
The culprit
Tamakichi-san
Jellyfish eyes, giraffe tail, sumo wrestler's butt, alien earlobes
I'm just a producer.
A fish's back, a turtle's flaps,
a whale's whiskers, and grandpa's glasses!
Maid's sideburns
Am I pretty?
Mom said this shape is the shape of happiness
Naturally!
I have to do this much, but the pay is the same!
Mom said this shape is the shape of happiness
Give me some money!
Give me some money!!!!
I'm sorry
-Ishikawa
(the producer)
This is the end-oh!
That was a bit weird, teacher.
What are you saying?
See you again...?
Raw
Translation & typesetting
Editing
Inspiration
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkcart
wowmd
Kafka Tamura
Anonymous
Muzu's nudes
The Shape of Happiness Extra Edition
Packed with original comedy
and super sound composed by Kawai Kenji