It's neither round nor square.
Let alone obscurities like a rhombus!
As strong as an elephant
and shining like a rabbit's eyes!
It's neither red nor blue.
Let alone obscurities like ultramarine!
The Shape of Happiness
Wonder Oh
Protect the Ocean!
Dazzling sun, white clouds,
tanned lovers frolicking by the water and families.
ICE
Yes, that's the sea for you!
At times like this...
I wish you were by my side.
But why think about that now?
Ah, you're right.
This is no time to get sentimental!
Yes! Even this peaceful beach
isn't safe from Nibonibo's evil clutches!
I'm sure those conniving evildoers
will try to attack with some nasty tricks,
so I better be on patrol and keep my guard up-oh!
Patrol!
Wow! What depth of expression!
Ugly
No old-fashioned pranks!
So it's you—Nibonibo's agent!
Running away?
I don't think so!
Stop!
[The fish is a parody of Kingyo Chuuihou;
penguins are from Suntory ads; Beruno's dog-paddling]
He's fast!
What's this?!
ICE
SEA HUT SAHAHAHA
Welcome!
Ah! It's him...
So this is Nibonibo's undersea fortress?
What are you talking about?
As you can see,
we're just a sea hut.
ICE
Yes, a true sea hut!
[海の家 (umi no ie)—literally means "house of the sea,"
practically means "beach hut / beachside clubhouse"]
Let those on the beach
call themselves "beach huts!"
Huh?
We are a true sea hut!
What's with these guys?
Well, anyway, have a seat.
I'll observe the situation for a bit.
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
Noodles
Ramen
Wonton
Corn ramen
Wonton noodles
Tanmen
Miso ramen
Tantanmen
Meat noodles
Chicken noodles
What can I get you?
Now then...
Let me get the miso ramen!
Still, there probably aren't many customers eager to come to a literal sea hut like this, are there?
That's why we had our son bring customers over.
So you're telling me I've been played by this kid all along?
It's too late now.
Yes, too late now.
I've made your ramen already.
Okay, here you go.
It tastes awful!
Oh, you spilled it.
Oh man, you spilled the ramen.
But you'll still have to pay for it.
How much?
100 trillion drachmas.
You think I'll let you run this racket?!
Space Kick!
Someone who would do
such an evil thing must surely be
a Nibonibo agent,
plotting world domination!
No, no! We don't know anything about Nibonibo.
That's right, we don't know.
["Sea monkey" is the common name of brine shrimp, aka Artemia—its ability to produce dormant eggs that can be stored indefinitely and hatched on demand led to the creation of a toy—a small aquarium that you grow your own sea monkey in from the eggs included with the package]
We are
the sea monkeys!
Shh! You're in library!
Oh, really?
You're not gonna fool me by playing cute!
You don't look anything like you do on the package.
The real thing is like this—
limp little bugs.
But we're also sea monkeys!
Those are real sea monkeys too.
Wh-What?
But we are also real sea monkeys!
So what does it all mean?!
Whatever. We've already wasted enough screen time on you,
so now it's time to deal with you Nibonibo lackeys! Brace yourselves!
Just a moment!
Before you hit us,
there's something I want you to hear.
Wh-What is it?
A long, long time ago...
The land belonged to us.
Until one day...
Aliens called "Humans" arrived from another planet
and drove us out into the sea.
Humans think
the Earth only belongs to them,
but in reality, they are invaders here.
It's you guys who are the invaders!
S-Such a strong line...
Huh?
What happened?
Ah! Your son got snatched by a UFO!
Shinichi!
It's them-oh!
The guys operating that UFO
have got to be the minions of Nibonibo!
Shinichi!
It's gone!
It's fine!
Ah! You're...
[Junichi Yaoi (1935)—a producer, director, and researcher, who's been obsessed with UFOs and everything paranormal on Japanese TV for all his life]
Yaoi-chan!
Look, there's this top-secret agreement between the US government
and aliens that says they can't kill you,
even if they abduct you with a UFO.
I see. Then we don't have
to worry about Shinichi for now.
Thank goodness...
Ah, but there's a special case for animals:
they get eviscerated.
Which means...
It's not fine at all!
But fine for me!
Goodbye, humanity!
To greener pastures I go!
Don't cry for me, monkey!
Lucky! I caught two today! Two!
Ah! He's operating the UFO beyond the stage!
Of course! I am Nibonibo's Agent No.2,
UFO Catcherman!
["UFO Catcher" is a trademark name of crane claw arcades, launched by Sega in 1985;
"Catcherman" is a parody of the "Gatchaman" anime series]
I'm abducting everyone—
humans and animals alike!
Get on stage and face me like a man!
I'll give you a proper beating here—
fair and square!
You bonehead!
You people are merely
fancy stuffed animals in a glass case!
Just stop resisting
and let yourself get snatched! There!
Ah! It's coming!
Sh-Shit! Why are you so slippery?!
I slathered myself in sun oil.
Damn it!
Not bad, young lady.
But the longer you have to chase a girl, the sweeter the victory is when you finally get her!
I'll keep trying again and again
until I get you!
Oh? Huh?
Oh? 100 yen for three attempts?
Hey, buddy, why don't you
lend me 100 yen, huh?
Don't extort money from the audience!
If I get Beruno, you'll all be entered in a raffle for her used swimsuit!
100 yen! Yes, 100 yen!
This is your chance to win her swimsuit!
Beruno, look how much I've gathered!
Animals.
And now that we’re financially in the clear...
Ah! What are you doing?!
Let's see you try to apply sun oil now!
Our sea hut...
Oh, now I'm angry!
Change! Wonder...
Beruno has three ways
to transform into Wonder Oh.
First, when the audience unites
in showing her Wonder Sign.
Second, by getting caught
in a passing whirlpool.
And finally, by spinning herself at high speed.
Now back to the show...
Fiddlesticks! I can't spin fast enough
because of the water resistance!
All according to my cosmic UFO brain's plan!
Brace yourself!
The situation is desperate!
Oh is in trouble!
Wh-What's with this guy?
Now! Let's all help her with a Wonder Sign!
Come on! What's up with you guys?
But...
I already gave him 100 yen...
Hey, people! Oh is in crisis!
Show her Wonder Sign! Come on, more!
Yeah, go!
Good!
My only hope now is to get caught
in a passing whirlpool.
If you are bothered by hemorrhoids,
our store has all sorts of...
A store sign?
If you are bothered by hemorrhoids,
our store has all sorts of...
No, a physical phenomenon!
That's it, you're done now!
Nowhere to hide!
It's over!
Young Aurora Spin!
Oh? I won't let you escape!
Oh... Appears!
[Pose is parodying the signature "Sheeh!" (シェー) stance
of the character Iyami from anime and manga Osomatsu-kun]
Shit! My catcher has been smashed to pieces!
Catcherman! Your reign of terror ends here!
We'll see about that!
I still have an ace up my sleeve!
Ace up your sleeve?
This is my secret weapon—Dirty Leg Lock!
Caught you!
Disgusting! Let go!
Wonder Oh!
Now you're mine!
It's suffocating!
And even more so, nauseating!
Well, I'm enjoying it! Huh?
Oh no...
Say, how much do you weigh?
You've asked something
you should never ask a lady!
Kick!
Wonder...
Wow! At this rate,
I'll be seeing stars around me!
Shuwatch!
[Parody of Ultraman's catchphrase]
Thank you, Oh! Our Oh!
Now, let's congratulate her
with a Wonder Sign of victory!
Thank you, Oh!
Thanks to you, our son was saved.
I should be the one thanking you.
Ah, one more thing
before the episode ends.
It's not that I'm overweight—
this costume just soaked up seawater
and made me heavier.
Oh?
Huh? What with that reaction?
It's the truth-oh!
Oh?
It's true! It's true, you hear?
Our fighting Wonder Oh
is at that bashful, blossoming age.
Please look forward
to Wonder Oh's future conquests!
The Shape of Happiness.
I'll see you here again in a year.
That's a promise.
Yes, I believe you.
Bye, then.
Ah...
You good, bud?
Original Video Series
"Shape of Happiness"
Now on sale
You're the third person to fall down there.
I wanna see you.
We met!
Mom!
Original Video Series
"Shape of Happiness"
Now on sale
Wonder Oh
Uncover the Mystery
of the Construction Site!
Good evening.
Honda Beruno is here-oh.
I've been informed that this is the location
where Nibonibo's agent would appear tonight.
So let's hear from Omayama,
our informant.
Good evening, I am Omayama.
Are you sure Nibonibo's agent
will appear here tonight?
I'm sure.
Ah! What are you...
Now, please chant with me!
Ah... Ventura, Ventura...
[Supposed word for "spaceship" in Alien language,
according to a widespread conspiracy theory]
Who asked you to summon a UFO-oh?!
Ah, they're here...
Oh my God...
Look! They're watching us
from the shadow of that steel beam.
Oh no, I'm scared!
Look, I'm covered in goosebumps!
You think you're Gibo Aiko or something?!
Cut it out with the paranormal otaku nonsense!
[Gibo Aiko (1932) was a supposed psychic, prominent on Japanese TV in the 80s]
I'll go look inside.
Did you hear something weird down the corridor just now?
No, seriously...
Look at my goosebumps!
One, two...
Don't count them!
We'll just have to go down and see.
Pounding
Whoa! I got so excited,
I ended up with a vase!
[doki (ドキ) = heartbeat; doki (土器) = earthenware]
Are you stupid or something?!
Who goes there?!
[dareda (だれだ)]
Rotor!
Racecar!
Ma has a ham!
Toot!
Quit it with the unprompted
palindrome battle!
So as I was saying...
Who are you guys?
I am the champion of justice, Wonder Oh!
And who are you?
Me? I am the champion of workers!
Koizubayashi Obuyasu!
I work at the Nibonibo Building!
Huh? So you're Nibonibo's agent?
Then brace yourself!
Ah, w-wait a minute!
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm just a worker.
I was told to contact them if anyone suspicious showed up, so here I am—that's all!
Is that true?
It is true.
As proof that I'm just a worker,
I'll play my guitar for you.
Pretty convincing argument.
You think so-oh?
However, would a company such as Nibonibo Co dot comma Ltd dot do something so bad?
[He's reading out loud (株) the way it usually looks in writing;
(株) (kabu, literally "stocks") is short for Kabushiki Gaisha;
he says "Open parenthesis, kabu, close parenthesis"]
That's right!
And you're sure you aren't the bad guys?
Exactly!
Well, I'll still let them know, just in case.
Here they are—Nibonibo fighters!
Don!
[They are stacked in the shape of kanji 丼 (don)]
Wh-Who are these guys?
Didn't I tell you?
They're Nibonibo fighters!
They're part of an evil organization
plotting to conquer the world!
You were merely a puppet
in their schemes!
I-I had no idea...
Damn it!
These guys are the true enemy of the workers!
Fine then, now it's time for workers of the world
to unite and take over!
You know, the president of Nibonibo is actually on the top floor of this building right now.
President, four of our fighters
haven't returned.
Looks like the dog girl's
sniffing out our trail.
Just a little more time,
and our fortress will be finished.
You're dismissed.
Yes, ma'am!
I've blocked all the emergency doors.
I cut the elevator cables.
We have them trapped now.
It's our chance to crush
Nibonibo once and for all!
All right!
Let’s sing a song to set the mood!
One, two, three, four!
Spitting, spitting spitting spittoon!
It's them...
Wait, they haven't noticed me yet,
so I can win if I catch them off guard.
And then I'll have all the glory to myself!
I'll get rid of these three annoying bastards in one go!
Nibonibo's minion?
Eh? Uh... No! You're wrong!
No way that's me!
Who are you, then?
Uh, I am... well...
A crossing guard!
Come on, now. Hurry up and cross.
Stop!
Like hell we'll cross!
Is it broken?
No, wait...
Stop!
He's getting away!
No, wait.
Stop!
Anyone got a microscope?
No!
He's probably not coming back.
So he's been defeated too?
Then the next victim...
will be you!
Ah? How can you say that?
I hate it when people are mean to me!
Just a minute!
Let me go, president.
My!
Good luck! I know you can do it!
Wonder Oh, or Wonder Over—I don't care!
Whoever gets in the way of my plans is gonna get it!
Now, the final battle is upon us!
It's time to charge in!
Is everyone armed-oh?
Yeah!
What's that?
Pickaxe!
[Tsuruhashi = pickaxe; Furuhashi = most likely
a reference to Furuhashi Hironoshin]
This is a one-foot figure.
Please, be more serious, dear!
Are you guys stupid?!
Nibonibo's agent is already here!
I'm a tough female warrior, Aliazona!
[She is named after Aliahan, a location in the 1988 game Dragon Quest 3;
her outfit is a possible reference to the 1985 movie "Barbarian Queen";
also she uses "ora" which is masculine version of "I" in Japanese]
I can't stand people like you
who lead frivolous and foolish lives!
What are you talking about?!
Better that than being a meanie
who's always putting others down!
Shut up!
Change! Wonder...
Hey, dude.
Right! They didn't include
any stage play elements this time,
so I thought they'd forgotten about us!
All right, everyone!
Let's spin the Wonder Sign now!
Oh appears!
You're wide open!
That's a very sharp blade!
Hey, let me tell you something—
with that level of skill,
you can't hope to beat
the president of Nibonibo.
Hm. At least you'll have a good story to tell when you get to the underworld.
[meido no miyage (冥土のみやげ) = souvenir for hell;
meido no momiage (メイドのもみあげ) = maid's sideburns]
Here they are—maid's sideburns!
It didn't land well!
Actually, I'm the one who's gonna do the president of Nibonibo in.
Huh? What do you mean-oh?
When I was little, the Nibonibo fighters used to bully me out of my lunch money.
That was when I vowed revenge
for my lunch money.
I went undercover, dug into the president’s secrets, and finally found his weak spot.
And now I’m just waiting
for the perfect moment to strike.
So, what's his weakness?
Like I'd ever tell you!
Was worth a try.
Regardless—he's mine, you got it?
I'll kill anyone who gets in my way!
Mr. Sea Monkey, why are you here?
Oh-kun, please, we are the rulers of Nibonibo.
Yes. Ever-so-slightly whimsical rulers.
What happened the other day was merely a test
to see what you're capable of.
That's why that story felt so contrived.
Darling, let me do the talking.
Sorry.
That said, it’s true that the Earth
originally belonged to us.
And we intend to take it back.
As for you, Aliazona...
I suspected for some time that you might be a traitor, and now you've made it clear to me.
Aliazona... No, all of you, prepare to die!
Oh, I guess you cheated death tonight.
That's 'cause I'm the protagonist!
I'm not interested in small fry!
Hey! Sea Monkey bastards!
Brace yourselves!
Um... I'm supposed to be the protagonist...
You think you can beat us?
Oh? I wouldn't be so calm if I were you.
Because now I know—your weakness is this!
PICKLED ONION
Oh! I see!
If you give a monkey a pickled onion,
it will keep peeling it for eternity!
So you're gonna use that as your opening to defeat them?
I ended up getting reduced
to a commentator...
So, what are you waiting for? Pick it up!
You just can't help wanting to peel it, can you?
Okay, now's my chance!
I'll help too!
What exactly are you doing?
Sea otter. This is pickled onion.
Sea otter. Pickled onion.
[rakko (海獺) = sea otter; rakkyo (辣韮) = pickled Chinese onion​]
So?
That's the joke.
Y-You swine!
You're looking down on me?!
M-More importantly, Aliazona,
it seems that pickled onion
wasn't their weakness at all.
Precisely.
We fed you lies,
not our true weaknesses.
Only the rumors we deliberately leaked.
Shit for brains...
So you played me?
And now,
you guys can't hope to defeat us!
Die!
Watch out, these guys are hella dense!
Fine... Squid Ring of Anger!
Huh? It didn't work?!
You jerk...
Guys, run away!
Gimme a minute.
It's pretty addictive if you try.
Are you monkeys now?!
You bastard, I was just about
to finish peeling it!
Crabsticks! I was so engrossed in oraora-ing I ended up with "It's me, Santa!"
["ora, santa" is an iconic line from the 1961 TV drama "Santa Monogatari";
Santa there was the protagonist's name and had nothing to do with Santa Claus]
Are you really this stupid?!
Got you!
Oh!
Omayama really did it!
He defeated the father monkey!
I'm fine!
Don't you think he's too strong to be in a crappy manga like ours?
He's like an anime version of Jason!
[Jason Voorhees from Friday the 13th (1980)]
That's right.
Despite having such a dull face!
Why are the champions
of justice sulking?!
All right!
Beruno the protagonist will do her best!
If you think about it,
you and I are monkeys and dogs!
[ken'en (犬猿) = dogs and monkeys (idiomatic example
of a bad relationship)—akin to "cats and dogs" in English​]
We're proverbial rivals!
No we're not.
How is that?!
Because we...
Are actually frogs!
F-Frogs, you say?
So they were never monkeys, huh?
I see. No wonder he survived the pickaxe treatment.
What strange frogs.
No, wait a minute...
It's a bit embarrassing,
but this might just work.
Omayama!
Yes?
Look.
DIZZY
I got so dizzy
I ended up with an air conditioner!
[kurakura = dizzily; kuura (cooler) = air conditioner]
Good thinking!
Crank it up to full blast!
Okay!
Let's fight, frogs!
You're gonna get it!
And then you'll die!
So cold!
I see! Since frogs are cold-blooded, their movements slow down as the temperature drops.
As long as we don't lose speed,
we've got this!
Croak... Croak!
You did it, Oh!
You saved the Earth at the cost
of your virgin modesty, Oh!
With this, Nibonibo's ambitions
have been totally crushed!
Now peace has returned to Earth!
And you can go back to being
just a normal tomboyish high school girl, Oh!
So, for now, everyone,
keep your nose up, and goodbye!
Thank you very much for visiting
[Sakura Tamakichi is the author of the source manga]
the 3rd performance of Sakura Tamakichi's
Theater Company today.
With this, the arc of Wonder Oh
in "Shape of Happiness" is concluded.
Everyone, please make sure you don't forget anything, and be careful on your way home.
If you head to the lobby now,
you can buy Wonder Oh mittens and single pillows designed by Sakura Tamakichi,
as well as Catchman Dolls,
as well as sea monkey helmets like those they wore in the show, and other merchandise.
Wouldn't you like to commemorate
this excitement with another souvenir for the underworld?
In addition...
Hey, Miss Announcer,
which way's to the bathroom?
Don't interrupt!
Please note that the number of items is limited,
so please make your purchases soon.
Sakura Tamakichi's Theater Company's next performance will be a special:
"The Shape of Happiness:
Dark Demon King Arc."
Please drag your relatives and friends along and come see us again.
We at the theater company look forward to seeing your tears of happiness again!
And today...
Hey, sis, where are you staying?
Thank you very much for visiting today!
So, where are you staying, huh?
Raw
Translation & typesetting
Editing
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkcart
wowmd
Kafka Tamura
Anonymous
Next episode preview
We're finally reaching the show's climax
The Shape of Happiness 4
"Dark Demon King Tempest Chapter"
"Dark Demon King Raging Waves Chapter"
Look forward to it-oh!