It's neither round nor square.
[Referencing 34 negations of the Immeasurable Meanings Sutra]
Let alone obscurities like a rhombus!
As strong as an elephant
and shining like a rabbit's eyes!
It's neither red nor blue.
Let alone obscurities like ultramarine!
The Shape of Happiness
[Parody of Toho Scope company logo;
Tamakichi Sakura is the author of "Shiawase no Katachi" manga]
Killing Kitora Attacks
[Kagawa Ryo aka Tanaka Punch—
one of the original manga editors and VAs here;
the guy on the right is the self-insert of Tamakichi Sakura]
My, Kagawa-san, looks like we finally made it to Pluto.
Well, I didn't think we'd actually make it.
Let's begin by zooming in
on the surface of Pluto.
Ah! There's a city! It's a city!
There's something moving...
Ah! It's a goat!
It's the King of Goats!
Me, you see?
Ah? What's that?
Wh-What could it be?
Whatever it is, it'll cross Pluto's orbit soon.
Pluto's orbit
Ah, it jumped over!
That mannerism is incredible!
[jijou = deferring to another;
jiba = magnetic field (can be read as "Jijou")]
Did you mean to say "magnetism?"
Look, it's making a shape.
Wa-hoo-hoo!
Sure we won't get in trouble for this?
This is NASA, America's National Aeronautics and Space Administration.
[taihen = serious/important]
Poss! It's a thisaster!
What? The base?!
[teihen = bottom / base]
What's base * height / 2?
The area of a triangle!
What's the volume of a cuboid whose height is equal to the square of its width?
I don't know!
You're a spy!
How can you say that?! I took an oath!
That's what they all say!
What did they send you for?
Spit it out! Come on, spit it!
Still in the ring!
Are you drunk or somethin'?!
So, what's wrong, American?
Aren't you one yourself?
I mean, you're the poss.
What is it, Eight?
What? Eight?
I said it in English, "What is it, Eight?"
What is it, Eight?
Eh!? Are you going to call me Eight now?
Come to think of it, you're Omae, right?
Hey! How dare you doubt others now?!
Not my fault your name is "Omae!"
Oh, I see.
So my name was "You?"
This is no laughing matter!
So...
More importantly, what is it, Eight?
Well, poss, we got these photos
from our Pluto-scouting spacecraft.
Ah! What's this?
All right, hurry up and send this pic
to that place I told you about before!
And start taking countermeasures!
Yessir!
Why, this was a pretty silly photo indeed.
Now, this next photo
is from a viewer in America.
What on Earth is this?
I've told you about this before.
This happened during the Tenpo era, when there was a major crisis in the southern region of Pluto.
[Tenpō era = 1830 to 1844]
This is the spirit of a Plutonian
who died from abdominal hernia​ back then.
Told you—it was the spirit of an alien!
This is at the cutting edge of modern science!
And we did it! It happened in our domain!
[nasakenai = deplorable; nasa kenai = in the imperial lands of NASA]
Yep. We're NASA, after all.
When it comes to monsters from outer space,
I guess we gotta let Japan deal with it.
They've forced our hand.
And so we get to...
Hi! My name is Honda Beruno.
And this guy here is Koitsu.
Hi!
Hey, hey!
Why do you keep calling me "this guy?!"
Not my fault your name is "Koitsu!"
Oh, I see.
So my name was "this guy?"
Well now, young people.
It's bad taste to use the same joke twice.
Wow! You're American,
yet you speak such good Japanese!
You see, the secret I've been hiding
all this time is that I'm actually Japanese!
No way! Contact lenses?
Doesn't it hurt to wear these kinds of things?
It's fine.
Since they're soft contacts, it's okay to play frisbee with them every now and then.
Who the hell just threw that?!
Oh, was it you? Well, don't think
I'm just gonna overlook it!
Just a moment!
What are you doing to my friends?
Ah, it's Alia!
Wh-Who are you?
No, please spare me!
Thank you, Alia!
Don't mention it.
Call me whenever you're in trouble.
Strong as ever!
That destructive power is something!
Speaking of destruction,
don't you know where the professor is?
Come to think of it, there was
a strange laboratory on the hill.
Yeah, it looks interesting.
Let's go there.
Damn...
Big A Genie Research Institute
Professor, what do you make of this monster?
Hm, this monster...
According to the legend I heard from my great-great-great-grandfather, it's Killing Kitora.
[Parody of King Ghidorah, a kaiju from the eponymous series of films]
Killing Kitora is its name.
Killing Kitora?
Is it really that dangerous?
Who knows? We're only a small research institute that's just been established.
I'm merely a retired crepe wholesaler.
[Referencing Mito Komon from the eponymous historical TV drama (1969-2011)]
I don't understand the difficult stuff yet.
Hey pops, did you miss your IV drip or something?
If you want someone well-versed in that area,
try asking Professor Kuribayashi Kimie.
Hi! Nice to meet you.
Kuribayashi Kimie,
a beautiful female teacher, is here.
What Killing Kitora is...
...it is a very violent monster!
It might destroy everything in the universe!
Professor Kuribayashi, I have a question!
Isn't there any way to defeat Killing Kitora?
You cocky girl!
Of course not!
Even the Self-Defense Forces are helpless!
What if we asked Golajit or Moras?
It'd all be for nothing without Mr. Shobizu!
No more free entertainment for you.
This is the Pluto explorer ship.
We're currently monitoring
Killing Kitora near Saturn.
Ah! What's that?
A strange planet is approaching.
Ah, Saturn's rings!
Incredible gravitational force!
Ah, Killing Kitora too!
Look! It's sucking Killing Kitora in!
Great, the Earth is safe now.
Huh?
The size difference is staggering!
Why is everyone running away?
It's all the same, no matter where you run to.
Ah! Up in the sky!
What? Killing Kitora is already here?
I can't see a thing.
Water fleas are flying everywhere!
That's in your eyes only!
Oh my, you're right—
they're moving together with my head!
Water fleas flutter, water fleas flutter...
Back!
That was real scary, you know!
Real scary, sir!
Speaking of scary, I wanna eat tuna!
[otoroshi = terrible (Osaka dialect);
toro = fatty cut of tuna]
Let's go to a sushi place!
Ah! Wait!
Tsk. I messed up again?
Damn you three goofballs,
the star of the show will be me—Master Simon!
[Parody of Simon Belmont, the protagonist of Castlevania (1986)]
I'll snatch the spotlight for sure!
Damn it... How did I end up like this?
Conveyor belt sushi
Madam, we'll start with sushi rice!
Gotcha! Coming right up!
Leave it to our sushi house!
Battle begins!
What's she doin'?
The chief here is a bit of a weirdo.
Sushi roll squad, advance!
Um, I don't mean to complain,
but could you stop this smoke and ruckus?
Our front-line troops are taking heavy losses!
There's only so much the sushi rolls can do...
All right...
We must step up our game!
Deploy the squid and octopus units!
It's so stiff!
It's like eating rubber!
Good, good!
And without any further ado,
send our main force—
full wasabi assortment—into battle!
And now for our masterpiece!
Our large army of decorative dishes
will deal the finishing blow!
How about it?!
Thanks for the meal!
UNIT ANNIHILATED
So...
Right, it was tasty!
You three goofballs,
go all out while you still can...
Go, Whiplash B-35!
What's that?
It's comin' this way!
The three of you can go to hell together!
I-It's him!
The lead of the next story, Master Simon!
What are you doing?
Oh? N-No, don't mind me.
It's nothing.
Let's all get along well.
Get along, okay?
Getting along
is great
See? We can all be friends!
And
now...
Hurry up and evacuate, all of you.
And
now...
Ah, retiree!
Professor Alia is here too.
Hurry, the Killing Kitora is approaching.
Huh?
Look!
The Moon...
It's all over for us, it seems.
Leave this to Master Simon!
It's my time to shine!
With this, I'll be the star of the show!
Let's go, Killing Kitora!
It's coming...
It's finally here...
It turns out Killing Kitora
just happened to be passing by Earth.
The Shape of Happiness.
Wonder Oh
(Parody of Wonder Momo video game (1987);
also "wan" is "woof" in Japanese)
I'm the lead in this one!
I saw it in a dream.
It's company-paid entertainment.
You don't know what you're talking about!
Shut up! You're so annoying!
Now you've done it!
Beruno!
Good morning.
Good, you're awake.
We're having your favorite, sardine hamburger, for breakfast!
Mama, mama.
Yes?
Could you stop dropping the fried egg every morning?
[Reference to the manga "Shimeji Simulation"]
Oh my, sorry.
Come quickly!
Geez, Mom...
Glance
Papa! Kurio!
Is it really that fun to watch your daughter change?!
Fun! Absolutely fun!
When you say it so firmly,
you know it's impossible to argue.
Anyway, leaving that aside,
That aside!
we're here because we had something important to tell you.
Wh-What? Something important to tell me?
We've been hiding it from you
ever since you were born.
It's about your true identity!
Is it Wonder Oh?
Ugh! How did you know?!
Even a monkey could read that title card we saw earlier!
Wonder Oh
Buddhist altars from Hasegawa!
So...
So, do you know how to transform already?
I don't know.
Let me teach you, then.
First, wear this.
Is this Wonder Oh?
Not at all.
But you look lovely in it, Beruno.
Say, how about this?
Are you stupid?!
Is this Wonder Oh?!
Really? Do I have to wear a kimono and untie my obi to transform?!
That's a ridiculously long transformation!
No, I was just mixing in
some of my personal kinks for now.
All you have to do is spin.
Die!
Change! Wonder Father!
Same here! Wonder Kukudai!
And don't forget Wonder Mother!
And just like that, we've always been
the transforming family.
Beruno, you stand here too
and pose with us.
I'm going to school.
Heh.
I'm late!
Ah! You too, Omae?
Hey, Beruno!
Ah! And Koitsu too!
Howdy!
Ah! The school gate is closing!
We won't make it in time!
[geinu = unaccomplished person]
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
Geinu
High
School
It sure was close today, eh?!
You're too loud-oh.
I had a bit of a situation at home-oh.
And today we'll be talking about monk-type magic...
I should probably keep Wonder Oh
a secret from Omae and the others...
I guess it's more satisfying when it's not clear who the hero is.
Let's keep it a secret.
Honda.
Yes!
What is the effect of the monk spell "Tekeretsu no Pa" and how much MP is consumed?
[Traditional rakugo spell to drive away the shinigami;
MP = magical points]
What kind of random crazy question is that?!
How much?
Ask me a proper question-oh!
I don't know.
If you don't even know
something that simple...
Go and spin over there.
Wh-Why's that?!
C'mon, you spin me right round, baby!
I didn't expect this story
to take such a goofy spin.
Oh, come what may!
And now, the next question...
Wonder Oh appears!
Ah! Who are you?
Awesome!
'Sup, miniskirt lady!
A super girl of justice
who protects freedom and peace-oh!
That's all the things I'm not-oh.
Dumbass
I expected that much.
Oh? By the way, what happened to Honda?
Ah, good point.
Beruno is gone!
Hey! Beruno!
Beruno! Where are you?
Beruno! Come out, won't you?
Hey! Beruno!
Have you seen Beruno?
I-I can never tell what's on their mind-oh...
Oh, that's right. Miss Wonder Oh,
why don't you look for Honda?
Very well-oh.
Hey, Beruno, are you here?
Yes!
Oh? But where's Miss Oh?
Give me just a minute-oh.
Here I go!
And now...
Teacher!
The teacher attack.
Oh?
But where's Honda?
Give it a rest already!
Osomatsu.
[Means "We're sorry [for a tasteless skit]" (like in Osomatsu-san)]
It's just like in that movie!
But man, to think Beruno
was Wonder Oh!
Yeah, that completely caught us off-guard.
Are you serious-oh?
Well, at any rate...
This will be your final appearance
at this year's school festival.
Eh?
Without further ado, let us begin the Year 2 Happy Squad performance "Wonder Oh"...
Howdy!
Howdy...
I can't hear you!
One more time...
Howdy!
Howdy!!
OK!
My name is Honda Beruno.
Cleaning up this park is my job.
But that's only my disguise to fool the world.
Actually, my true identity is...
A dog!
Who're you calling a dog?!
My true identity is...
Wonder Oh!
My true mission is to protect the world
from the evil secret organization "Nibonibo"
that is plotting to take over the Earth!
Today, I got information that a Nibonibo agent will be operating in this park,
so I'm here undercover!
Sing for the birth of our nation...
Time to work...
Time to work.
No you don't!
The homeroom teacher is launched.
He's the ballistic teacher now—get it? (I don't)
It's a little painful, though.
Could it be that you're the agent of evil?!
So I'm exposed, huh?
I'm the homeroom teacher Ruge.
As part of our plan for world domination,
I was sent to this park
to undermine public morals.
Now streaking!
Get back here!
Off limits
I'm gonna roll on the grass
where it says "Off limits!"
Off limits
It tingles and feels so good, oh, I can't stand it.
No-no-no-no!
Off limits
I'm gonna pester the lovebirds!
They're bouncing!
Look at them go!
All right...
Change!
Now, dear viewers,
let's call Oh by spinning that Wonder sign!
Oh!
Wonder Oh appears!
Take this!
Ring Attack!
It connected...
Oh, for those who dare to throw things
at their homeroom teacher like that...
[Signature pose of actor Tani Kei]
Pedagogic Blast!
KACHUNK~
WOOOOSH~
SPROIIING~
Homeroom Murashinji Assault!
[Parody of singer Tanimura Shinji]
THANK YOOOUU
OH, LORD ABOVE!
A-All his attacks are stupid puns!
Now I'm angry!
Squid Ring of Anger! Take this!
[ikari = anger; ika ringu = squid ring]
Ah! You can't speak for others...
Take this—another Squid Ring!
Homeroom Snail Defense.
[tannin = homeroom; tanishi = pond snail]
Another stupid pun!
Fine, if you wanna be a snail that much,
I'll cook tsuboyaki with you.
[tsuboyaki = shellfish cooked in its own shell]
Now, look, you can't cook
tsuboyaki with homeroom snail.
If you want tsuboyaki,
then you need Sazae-san.
[sazae = turban shell;
Sazae-san = long-running anime sitcom]
While you're trying to process it, the hot water here sure feels nice coming down on a sunny day.
["biiba non non" is a line from the 1968 song by The Drifters
"Ii Yuu Dana" (The Hot Water is Nice)]
I feel so refreshed after that bath.
You can't do that!
You kicked me again.
You kicked me in the back of the head,
yet you kicked me again.
Eh? My groin?
[mata (又) = again; mata (股) = groin]
Now then...
When I look at this, for some reason...
I wanna eat rice.
[It reminded him of a nori leaf]
So what of it?!
Ah? This tastes so bad!
You want me to eat this?!
Come on, wife.
At least try to cook something delicious.
I'm not your wife!
For a wife who defies her husband like that...
Saki Dai-chan Attack!
[Referencing the 1964 TV show "Saake Dai-chan," probs]
North Atlantic Beans Organization attack!
[natto = fermented soybeans]
Tonkatsu-enjoying Horse Attack!
[tonkatsu kutte = eating pork cutlet​; ton ga tsukutte = "to bonk"
umakatta = "it was tasty"; uma katta = "horse kicked"]
Didn't I tell you I'm not your wife?
Oh well.
Toothpicked Squid Ring!
[tsuma = wife; tsumayoji = toothpick]
I'm like Charredile Dundee...
[kurokoge = burnt black; kurokodairu = crocodile]
So, do you repent now?
Please be my homeroom teacher.
[Parody of stock phrase "kannin shite kure" = "Please forgive me"]
Fine.
Let me just tell you one last thing.
What is it?
I homelook forward to your next report card...
Don't break character!
We're in the middle of a spectacle!
How spectacular!
You're strong, Oh!
Fight, Oh!
Your school record is abysmal!
But education doesn't matter for a champion of justice!
Didn't I tell you it's not so?!
The Shape of Happiness.
That mannerism is incredible!
Did you mean to say "magnetism?"
That was too long...
Where are you going at night?!
No, the feeling is different...
Don't teach me!
Shut up!
Who do you think you are?
Teacher!
Teacher attack~
This is the NASA—American Aeronautics and Space Administration.
Poss! It's a thisaster!
What? The base?!
What's base * height / 2?
The area of a triangle.
The length on the top
plus the length on the bottom...
Huh? I don't know!
Eh! Those are huge contact lenses!
Doesn't it hurt when you wear these?
It's fine, they're soft contacts, after all.
Hi! Nice to meet you.
Kuribarashi Kimie,
a female teacher, is here.
Professor Kurihara, I got a question!
It's Kuribarashi!
Is there a way to defeat Killing Kitora?
Hey, let's go!
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
Bonus
Only for you...
Such a nice wind...
At times like this
I want you by my side.
Not step over me-oh!
[Shimeji Simulation again]
Raw
Translation & typesetting
Editing
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkcart
wowmd
Kafka Tamura
Anonymous
Next episode preview
This time, we're diving into sports and suspense!
Includes:
Disappearing in Okhotsk!?
Showdown! Super Tennis
Look forward to it-oh!