Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
Whoo!
Nothing beats a pool in midwinter!
It's a feast for the eyes!
Hey! Look there!
Oh! Excellent!
Bravo!
Sorry to have kept you waiting​!
Episode 14 Part 1
Poolside Unlucky Men
Irresistible!
Akina-chan!
Yum-yum!
Hi!
Akina-chan! Come play with us!
Whee!
Yahoo!
What is this?!
Sea cucumbers?!
Two huge red sea cucumbers stuck together?!
This isn't the ocean, you dimwit!
Don't get close to it! Run away!
Who're you calling a sea cucumber?!
How rude! One can't even be left alone while he enjoys some leisurely swim!
I'm gonna go back to my room and sleep!
What kind of swimming style was that?
It must have been
Undersea Humanoid Ragon!
Hey! It's Toyotomi-kun!
Watcha doin' there?!
You all went in without me...
It's your fault for lazin' about!
So you came to swim with us too,
Toyotomi-kun? I'm relieved!
Anyway, it'd be nice
to have something cold to drink!
Yeah! Toyotomi, don't just stand around
and buy us something!
I'll go get us something!
That's unnecessary!
You just sit with us, Akina-chan.
Here!
Go now, and get us four colas!
One, two, three, four...
Watcha doin'?! Get on with it!
There's only enough for four...
Yeah, that's what I told ya!
Are ya deaf or what, ya dolt?!
What about mine...?
Know your fucking place!
You can pay for it from your own money!
My own...?
But I'm totally penniless!
Whoa, he's crying now! A guy in his 20s
is crying over a can of cola!
That's why you don't come to the resort hotel penniless!
I'll buy it for you!
Akina-chan, if you spoil him,
he'll get used to it!
Here, buy yourself something nice!
Akina-chan!
Geez, that guy is hopeless...
DELICIOUS YAKITORI
Hey pops, cola please! Five cans!
Here you go.
Thank you!
Ah... It's you...
My teacher Ozawa Takeshobo!
Ozawa Takeshobo (age unknown)
Ozawa Takeshobo, famed as the user of the deadly rage overload technique,
The Invincible Rage Overload Technique
that can even make the crying child deal in,
Correlation between anger and luck
Ridiculously lucky
Normal
Luckless
Zugan
Zugaaaaan
Fuuu ratio (Anger points)
Time
Luck
he is an invulnerable player, who had come back from the dead many times over!
Master... You're alive...
You were alive after all!
What should you mean by that?
Come on, you don't need to pretend!
You old prankster!
You must have mistaken me
for someone else.
I am certainly not that loser
"Ozawa" you speak of!
Come on now! Then who are you?
Who might you be? Come on, tell me!
You got your cola,
so get out of my sight already!
And don't come near
my food stand again. Are we clear?
Pon!
There!
Like this...
Roll...
Bump!
What is it?
I'm bored.
Come on now, you need to behave.
Be a good boy and sit down over there.
Let me play next?
Watcha talking about? I'm busy right now!
I don't have the time to play with you!
DORA
Wow! Such a good hand!
Spare me your attention.
DORA
Whoa! Cutting that one?!
I'd cut this one instead!
And then cutting this would guarantee a yaku...
There, see?
DORA
If you did like I told you,
you'd be in 1-4-man tenpai now!
DORA
Riichi!
What?! Riichi?!
That's totally the wrong move!
Is it?
Ippatsu tsumo! Riichi instant Tsumo Tanyao Sanshoku!
Got it! Ura Ura!
It's baiman!
No way...
You were saying?
Ah, no... N-Never mind...
Yeah, nah, piss off!
Riichi!
Shit! I have no safe tiles!
All right, point read!
Akina's wait is definitely 3-6-man!
A 3-6-man wait, you say?
3-6-man!
All right!
3-man then!
Huh?!
Aww... Pass.
Ah, good grief!
I thought I had no safe tiles at all,
but luckily Toyotomi's reads are guaranteed to be wrong!
It's as good as genbutsu!
Hey! Stop ruining the game, Toyotomi-kun!
B-But I didn't mean to...
That's right, get out of my sight!
It's your bedtime already!
Ah... I'm bored.
What's this?
Ah! Is this...
Voucher for a lodging (luxury dinner included)
Up to 5 people
I found this!
Voucher for a lodging (luxury dinner included)
Up to 5 people
A voucher for a lodging
and dinner at this hotel?
Voucher for a lodging (luxury dinner included)
Up to 5 people
W-We should give it back to them...
I guess...
Well, Toyotomi, it's mahjong time!
I'll sit out, you guys have fun!
B-But I need to return this...
Nah, that can wait!
Sit down! Let's start already!
Come on now, chop-chop...
Imbecile. I'll beat him
and the dinner voucher's mine!
Turns out even that dumbass Toyotomi
can be useful sometimes!
After you all go back to Tokyo,
it'll be just me and Akina-chan in the same room!
We'll do this, and that!
DORA
Whoa, this is another great hand!
Pon!
Yeah! I can hear the military march already!
I drew it! Ryuuiisou tenpai!
Get this!
With this wait, 7-sou is just 5,200!
I'll call a 3-sou and wait on a 3-sou pair,
it'll come out easily with the 4-sou pon!
Goddammit! Chii!
How about this?!
Let's go!
So it came.
Tanyao Sanshoku Iipeikou Dora Dora! 18,000!
DORA
Zugan!
Wuh? He busted out before I got a chance to ron him?
The accommodation with dinner
voucher will be mine.
It's only a matter of time...
Toyotomi-kun...
It's gone...
Perhaps...
Could the ostensible owner of the luxury lodging and dinner voucher that Toyotomi found,
have been this dubiously-looking character, the supposedly late Ozawa Takeshobo?
Furthermore, what is the conclusion
awaiting Toyotomi and Akina in this story?
The turbulent second act will begin in about 80 seconds from now.
Please wait at the edge of your seat!
Now then, where's my comeback hand?
Comeback?!
How are ya gonna come back from minus 60,000?
"Comeback" is not a word to be used lightly.
W-Well now, everyone should have a right
to have hopes and dreams!
Yeah, that's right! Even guy like him
deserves a draw in human rights!
Yep, whether you're a frog, bug,
or poor as a church rat, you deserve to live!
Exactly! We're all friends, right?
Stop making fun of me!
Episode 14 Part 2
The Return of Ozawa Takeshobo
All right! Let's check 'em!
That's it! Let's go!
Cut 2-sou for a 1-pin 3-sou shanpon!
Cut 3-sou for a 1-4-sou ryanmen!
This one and...
Riichi!
If I get Ippatsu Tsumo and Ura 3, it's baiman!
And then, with just one hand...
I'll be at minus 44,000!
Are you just feigning confidence or what?
C'mon, draw it!
What now?
Zugan!
If I had cut the 3-sou, I would have drawn it on ippatsu!
Get out-squid'd!
Nice, I got to tenpai...
I'll finish first if I win this!
It came out...
Thank you very much...
What's your deal?!
Riichi!
Hm? No other words after "riichi"?
What, just a riichi only?!
Don't be stupid!
I have to look at the ura first!
Got it!
Ura 1!
Ura! Ura! Told you so!
Yeah, sure, how impressive,
howl-howl impressive!
That's 2,600, right?
Wrong!
3,200! 3,200! I get extra points!
Take a better look, mister!
If I get scammed out of my points every hand, there ain't no business to be done here, no sir!
Rounded up to
It's 50 fu! 50!
Shut up!
With 2,600 or 3,200,
your end score is still minus 107!
Time out...
Ron! Mangan.
What the hell, Toyotomi?!
I-I just saw a weird guy
outside the window...
But there isn't anything out of the ordinary.
No, I'm sure he was just there!
You were daydreaming, weren't ya?
So weird...
Goddammit, that guy just likes
to make a fuss out of nothing.
Cut it out, you!
Chii!
Who the hell are you all?!
That's our line!
Who the fuck are you?!
Wait...
I'm sure I've seen him
before somewhere...
Ah! Got it! It's Ozawa Takeshobo!
Yes, correct!
Much obliged.
Master!
Master! I've missed you so much!
Oh, if it isn't my disciple!
I knew it—the curmudgeonly
old man at the food stall was you!
I see you youngsters
were playing mahjong?
Yes! Would you like to play too, Master?
Please show your true power to them!
Well, I don't know...
C'mon, don't be shy, gramps!
My, if you insist, I suppose, I might as well
sit down for a game or two...
Ah, it's a good feeling
to be holding the tiles again...
What's that? Hmm, hmm? Oh, I see, I see...
You're telling me to cut this one?
All right!
He's talking to himself, right?
I wonder what he's doing.
Wrong!
An ascended player like myself
can clearly hear the voice of the tiles.
The voice of the tiles?!
Indeed. The tiles are alive and have a heart!
Only if you can live your life by the way of the tiles, without being bound by common sense,
like the flow of water,
can you call yourself a true player.
So true, Master!
Hmm, I should try listening to the tiles too.
Do you believe in god?!
While you're trying to be funny,
I'm calling riichi.
Hmm, these youngsters
are always calling riichi too early...
Which one? Hmm... I see.
Your wait is on 3-6-pin!
Did I hit the bullseye?
H-How did you know my wait?!
H-Holy shit!
The discards have a voice of their own.
And they whispered to me that 3-6-pin is your wait!
Ippatsu! Riichi Ippatsu Tanyao Iipeikou!
Young man, may you die a good death...
Ron! Pinfu Ittsuu, 5,200!
Ron! Honitsu Ton, Mangan!
Ron! Riichi Chanta Sanshoku Dora Dora!
Horrible!
Don't you have any pity
for a frail old man like me?
I've never seen young people like this!
W-We're sorry...
Don't worry about it!
At this rate, Master is guaranteed to come in last!
It's time for my...
Riichi to confirm 3rd place!
You underestimated me, Toyotomi...
As your master,
I have been secretly waiting for you to take advantage of this opportunity to attack me...
Apoplexy riichi!
Wh-What's that?
You want to know?
Think again... do you really want to know its meaning?!
Listen, then. Apoplexy suddenly attacks you one day and then...
If you call, you're almost certain
to fall over dead.
Eh! This one's high calorie!
Apoplexy!
And I told you to pay attention
to your calorie intake countless times...
Oh, I'm in tenpai again...
Let's make it a Riichi.
H-Hold up! That wait is...
Look closely, old man! There!
Oh, I see... But I guess it's still fine!
Ippatsu Tsumo Alzheimer Tanki!
Eh?! Furiten Tanki?!
How do you tsumo that?!
Old fart... I'll show you the power
of the youthful spirit!
Subarachnoid Hemorrhage Riichi.
Social Security Chase!
Oh?
Super Express Retirement Home Return!
Riichi Ippatsu Honitsu Shousangen, Baiman!
Victory for the young!
Secret technique: Bedridden Old Man.
Quit foolin' around!
Master!
It seems that death
has come calling for me...
I only ever wanted
to eat a hotel dinner before...
Wh-What, really?!
We have just a...!
No! That's for me and Akina!
Th-This is...!
My luxury lodging and dinner voucher for five people!
You were going to pocket it, weren't you?
Man, the food's great
and the entertainments are awesome too!
It's good!
Yeah, good!
That's true, gramps!
Thanks a lot for treating us!
Don't mention it.
I believe that all humans are friends
as long as they're virtuous.
Come on, have some more!
Toyotomi-kun...
And now, tonight's special guest,
the terrifying fire man...
Mister Zugan!
"I'm innocent!"
The outcry of Toyotomi's heart was drowned out by the flames
of the burning limbo
and the cheers of the crowd.
Toyotomi, let me offer these lines to you:
"Fireworks might be compared to a storm,
but the only thing I say goodbye to is life."
Just kidding.
Three men show up at Toyotomi's flat
every night to play mahjong.
Toyotomi's life is in danger!
Next time:
"Zugan Lantern Ghost Story",
"I Want to Win!"
Definitely watch it!
I'll never forgive you if you fall asleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa