Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Hey! I'm back!
The work was unforgiving today.
You're still sleeping?!
I can't believe my eyes,
I missed school!
Why didn't ya wake me up, mate?
Why should I care, you twerp?
Ugh! Bugger!
Stop sleeping so damn much!
I'm... I'm feelin' the buzz, mate!
Episode 11 Part 1
Nothing Beats the Buzz
Who the heck sleeps 16 hours a day?!
Well, let's go for some gamblin' then.
No way, I'm broke!
I only have 20 yen left!
I'm goin' for it!
I've got 17 yen.
If ya win I'll give ya 2 yen!
No, you keep it!
In that case, why don't we bet our entire fortunes on a single roll of the dice?
Agreed.
Bloody hell! I got a pair with one!
This is as good as won!
Let's go! Cee-lo!
All right, it's a triple of ones!
Zugan!
Here you go.
Good kids don't gamble for money!
Right-o, that's one down!
Whoa, are we really going
to a parlor completely broke?
Too right, mate!
With this mood, we'll definitely win!
And we're not going there broke.
I've got 37 yen, remember?
That's what it means to be broke!
I...
I've felt the buzz, mate!
The buzz is all I need!
Phew! Static electricity...
Idiot.
Cheers!
Welcome! Oh my!
If it isn't Toyotomi and his disciple!
Howdy!
Shall we play, mama?
We've just had a Tengo player leave.
Mama-san, it seems you'll never stop
underestimating me.
Are you really trying
to make me play at Tengo?
Huh?
I...
I won't feel the buzz at a measly go!
I'll do 'pin!
A man can only feel alive at 'pin!
I see...
Mama! One open seat at the 'pin table!
C'mon, let's get on with it!
Hey boss, none of 'em look like they pose any danger.
R-Really...?
Pon!
Dora
Double East Dora 1! Not bad!
Riichi!
I was waitin' for that shaa!
No way. I can't cut the 7-pin.
Fine by me. Go on, mate.
Hey, you!
That's a foul pon!
Why'd you have to be
so petty, mate? It's nothing.
Ugh, to hell with it! Dora 9-pin!
Crikey! If I'd called the shaa I'd have won with a dora tanki!
Now this is the real buzz, mate!
Oi, what's this?
Don't need it!
Ron! Riichi Haitei Haku, 5,200!
Why did you have to ron me there, mate?
It's a live tile.
You could've cut that shaa...
Why would I?
I ain't came here to win, mate.
I came to feel the buzz!
Next round
Would'ja look at this!
A hand with guaranteed Tanpin Sanshoku!
This is great, all around!
Time for a lil' dama...
No, wait! If I riichi this and draw it, it'll be a haneman!
No, wait... If I draw it on ippatsu and get an ura, it'll be a baiman!
Th-This is...
This is making me feel the buzz
just by imagining it!
Get on with it and discard!
Riichi! I'll win this time!
Crikey! Such tight folding!
Mate! Ya've never felt the mahjong buzz before?!
Huh?
Nice, I drew it! 300/500!
Bloody hell, mate!
This is all the buzz I need, kid.
As if that was the true buzz!
Hanchan end
Well, in any event I'm first.
No... not like this!
I need to... feel the buzz more!
Feel it tingling in my every atom!
Mama-san, I'd like a loan.
Eh? Need a loan already?!
Surely you weren't playing broke?
Oh man...
Ya don't get it at all, Mama-san...
Remember: playing without a brass razoo
is the surest way to feel the buzz!
What are you even on about?!
Please, Mama!
It's the only thing I'd ever ask for!
No!
If I lose all my money, my boss will work here for free for a month, howzat's sound?
Then we have a deal!
Eh?! H-Hold up, dammit!
If you lose, I'll work Toyotomi-kun
to the bone and he'll have no breaks!
No way...
Truly me and my boss
are two hearts beating as one!
Hey! We're making a Ryanpin table!
Won't somebody come play?
Ugh?! When did they...
All right, coming right in!
No, no, no, no you don't!
Don't you realize
who those spongers are?!
No worries, mate.
I don't feel like losin' today.
You said that last time, and yet...
Hey, hurry up! You wanna play or what?
Sure thing!
Will he be okay?
Now Ryanpin, that's a real godsend...
Riichi!
Dora
This one!
Pass.
Crikey! Just one push and I'm already tingling with buzz!
Heh. Coming without a brass razoo
and playing Ryanpin rate...
It's like fighting with your back to the wall—a suicidal strategy.
Letting your flesh be cut
to break the enemy's bone! That's right.
That's just my way of life.
So cool! I'm feeling the buzz just from describing my way of life!
Get on with it and discard.
Imbecile...
Let's go!
8-9-man...
Those fairly safe tiles are what an amateur would cut...
But mahjong is and always has been...
about battling straight on!
Powerful.
Here we go!
I got that ippatsu!
Yahoo!
What is wrong with you?
With the 3-man you'd have Sanshoku! You could've drawn a 5-pin dora!
2-5-sou for Iipeikou! You had 3 kinds of improvements!
My true mahjong starts now.
Ron! 18,000! 8,000! Tsumo! 2,000!
Whoa! A huge lead!
That's me, aight.
Pon!
Kan!
Aha! The dealer's going all in!
What's that? You should be folding just about now, you!
Lemme tell you, if we were to have a calling contest, I wouldn't lose either!
Chii!
Pon!
Dumbass! What are ya gonna do as first place with such a short hand!
The fear and pressure of defending with such a small hand
are making me feel the buzz from the bottom of my...
Why does it have to be
at the cost of my livelihood?!
The dora Chun!
Stop!
A tile like that is 90% certain to deal in!
A normal bloke couldn't cut this tile...
But I...
I want to...
Please reconsider!
cut the tile that makes me feel the buzz!
Pon.
Buzzing!
H-Howzat, Boss? Even the audience
must've felt the buzz by now.
Yeah... You buzzed me all right,
to my heart's content.
C'mon, tsumo!
Hatsu!
Phew. Finally a tile to make you fold...
L-Let's go!
Ah! N-No! Stop!
If you cut that it's not mahjong anymore!
Don't try to stop me, boss!
It's a rare chance to feel such a buzz!
Like that!
Pass.
Whee! This buzz shouldn't be legal!
C'mon now!
What's this crap?
Ron!
Shousangen Honitsu Dora 7, Kazoe Yakuman!
All right! Electric massage service for everyone left!
Damn! This is a good one!
Damn right!
Mama-san, thank you!
It'll be a special service
for the next month!
No way...
Zugan!
Half a year passes buzzing
and the other half passes sleeping.
Ah!
Exciting mahjong
is the core of a man's life!
Still, we trust the discerning viewer
to never try it for himself.
December 24th
Episode 11 Part 2
Santa's Wait's Come to Town
I'm hungry...
Boss!
I'm sick and tired of this life
without a brazz razoo.
I'll go lookin' for someone a little richer
so I wish ya a ripper Chrissie!
By Kenjin.
Goddammit! He's so selfish!
Which reminds me—
it's Christmas Eve today!
I haven't called Akina-chan
in a long time...
Let's call her!
Hello, you called Hayami!
I have a very important
rendezvous today, so I'm not home.
If you have an important message for me,
please leave it after the beep.
An...
An important rendezvous...?
Merry Christmas!
So, how about some
Merry Christmas mahjong?
C'mon, get up, chop-chop!
C'mon, man, we gotta go!
Heave-ho!
Mahjong parlor
Lonely Heart
Zugan...
What's wrong, Toyotomi?
You look even more dispirited than usual.
Did something happen?
We're worried, you know!
You're lucky to have friends like us who really care!
Look!
Suck on these and cheer up!
Takuma
Drops
Whoa! Drops! They're drops!
Here, open wide!
What flavor did you get this time?
Yay! It's strawberry!
I got strawberry!
He looks happy.
Yeah.
We're such good pals, ain't we?
Yep.
Which means, it's no sin
to disappoint him a bit afterwards, right?
Huh? Well, that's one way to put it!
I don't wanna spend the Christmas Eve playing mahjong...
Stop whining! It's your turn!
Don't need this one!
Toyotomi...
Look...
Your hand is all drops!
Not all of it yet.
Don't try to bullshit me!
Riichi on the 9-pin!
Whoa, it's full of drops!
Shut up and discard!
This one!
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Chinitsu!
Zugan!
Hi, everyone!
It's Santa-san!
Ho.
Huh?
It's Santa?
Oh, I've seen him in a magazine.
Apparently, this geezer has never won
a hand in his 30 years of playing mahjong.
Look, Toyotomi-kun!
It's Santa-san!
For real?
Very much so.
Why do you keep playing mahjong?
I like it.
Huh?
I...
enjoy mahjong
from the bottom of my heart.
That's why every Christmas Eve
he becomes Santa
and visits all the luckless players in Japan!
Seeing me, the unluckiest person in the world
will certainly give all those youngsters
a boost to their self-confidence!
In other words,
my present to you all is myself!
Aight, gramps, let's do it!
What a funny Santa.
But the bar to clear is high!
We might as well...
Santa! Is it true ya've never won a hand?
In heavens' name, it's true!
That’s not exactly something
to brag about, is it?
As expected of Santa!
An incredible garbage hand!
My tiles are good tonight...
Oh?
They're usually 5-shanten,
but this one's somehow 4-shanten!
He's here, he's here!
I can feel him coming!
A powerful luckless player!
Not him...
Not him either...
I-It's him!
My god... What an advanced level of luckless energy!
The spirit of luckless flowers
is weighing heavily on his shoulders!
Riichi on the 7-pin!
Oh no!
Such a garbage hand and no safe tiles!
Ron! Merry Christmas!
Ouch!
Me too, me too!
Jingle Bells!
Clang!
Drops!
Oh no, I brought Santa-san
specially for you, Toyotomi-kun...
What are you doing?
Let's see...
Whoa, what a nice hand!
Wh-What's happening?
I'm... in... tenpai...
For the first time
in seven years!
Yes.
It was on Christmas Eve seven years ago.
I...
I made it...
I got to tenpai!
The first time in twelve years!
Wh-What a joy!
I almost forgot how enjoyable
mahjong can be!
Riichi!
Ron! Sorry, old man!
Mentanpin Sanshoku Dora Dora, Dealer's Haneman, 18,000!
And now, again...
S-Such a nostalgic feeling...
Riichi.
The dora...
Dora
All right! My opponent is Santa who's never won a hand! It's time to give it my all and...
Wait... If I deal into Santa now,
I'll become the guy who gave him
his first ever win!
Wh-What's wrong, Toyotomi-kun?
He-he...
Ah!
Ron! Chanta only.
Ugh...
Come on! At least look
at the others' discards sometimes...
Hey, Santa! But at least you were waiting on the dora 6m, right?
No...
I was on 7p penchan!
Whoa! Amazing!
Two consecutive riichis for me!
Win.
The urge to win is flaming up within me!
Riichi!
Damn it!
Th-This time I won't fold!
Let's go! Riichi!
Riichi only...
What's with all the special effects
over a measly Riichi only?!
R...
Ro...
Ron!
Ron! Riichi only!
Zugan!
Santa-san, how does it feel to have won your first ever hand?!
Uh? Well... I guess, I could say,
"This is what winning feels like, huh?"
Zugan.
Oh, right, I almost forgot.
I'll give you a present
for dealing into me.
Here.
Whoa! They're drops!
Drops! Drops! Yay! Yay!
Drops!
He's hopeless.
This guy is absolutely hopeless.
"Drops! Drops!" Toyotomi's voice echoes across the snowy town.
Whilst snow falls on Taro's roof...
Tonight too you sleep alone.
No matter what happens, Merry Christmas.
A large 1-pin floated down the river.
A boy was born from it
and named Zugantaro.
Next time: "New Year's Zugan"
and "Once Upon a Zugan."
Definitely watch it!
Don't you fall asleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa