Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
It is said that a drowning man will even clutch at a straw.
In times of hardships, humans always rely on things other than God to see them through.
Depending on the person,
it can be love, religion, or many other things.
But there is one thing
that you can by no means rely on.
The Devil.
Let us observe the fate of one
who chose to sell his soul to the Devil.
Episode 13 Part 1
A Devil to the End
I finally got my hands on it...
The Illustrated Guide to the Black Magic!
With this book, I shall summon the Devil...
And wreak my vengeance on Shintaro and the others who've been bullying me for so long!
The time has come.
I shall now seal my contract with the Devil by blood!
Elohim Essaim, Elohim Essaim,
Eko Eko Azarak, Eko Eko Azameraku, Donguri Korokoro, Donburiko!
Come forth, O Prince of Darkness!
Could it be... the Devil?!
Toyotomi!
Good evening!
Speak of the Devil!
Whatcha still babbling about?
It's your turn!
Ron! Same wait!
Zugan!
Hey! Rie-chan, make us some tea, would ya?
Okay.
Tsk! Of course you can't trust
the mail-ordered books on black magic...
Really? You're still reading that kind of stuff?
'Course he does!
He's the kind of guy who'd fall for the
"selling embarrassing photos of myself" thing!
I thought you did that.
Damn it! I'm out of luck today too!
If the Devil was real,
he'd at least give me some good luck!
What's wrong, Toyotomi?
I-It's here! It's the Devil!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
D'ya bump ya head or somethin?
Get a grip, Toyotomi!
Hot! Hot!
Turn it off!
Are you okay?
So hot...
Ya can't even light a fire properly?
No! I just turned the switch like always...
Nothing unusual.
What?!
Well, it's Toyotomi's house anyway, so no big deal if it burns down! Isn't that right?
Are you trying to start a fire or what?!
Easy now. Nothing serious happened, so let's continue.
Huh? Is this the hand I had?
All right...
Riichi!
All right... I have a 3-4-5 sanshoku!
Pass!
Ron!
Riichi Ippatsu Ryanpeikou Dora 2!
Give me a break!
Ya dealt right into Toyotomi's haneman!
Huh?! Why the hell did I cut a 3-pin?
You're such a dumbass!
This obviously called for a 5-pin discard!
G'day! Howsit goin', everyone?
What's that you bought this time?
I nicked this from the Keio Uni!
But what are you gonna use that thing for?
Boss! Ya din't know?
Nowadays we live in a society where if ya ain't got a computer, you don't mean a rat's ass!
Aren't you just gonna play porn games on it?
What was that?!
I play regular games too!
So in the end,
it's still just for games, huh?
My hands are unusually good today...
Oi, boss! That's a hell of a hand!
Already bored of your laptop?
Ah! Boss! Pon it!
Shut up, you!
Pon!
When the 8-sou comes out, pon it!
I know, you nag!
Oh man... That's a real waste.
I've only got to play for 10 minutes!
Well, deal with it, all right?
Be a man and get over it.
Ron! Chinitsu Tanyao Toitoi!
Bloody hell! An' I just bought it!
Shut your ass up already!
I'm far worse off, compared to you!
So get your shit together and stop whining!
Started already?
Ah! Master!
Oh my, what may have happened?
The laptop I just bought...
All man-made things will go to ruin one day,
all who have life shall die.
Accept it.
Master!
I'll make some tea,
so please pinch in for me.
I've got your back!
Oh ho? My word, this is very good indeed!
Riichi!
What's that, old man?
Riichi already?
Impressive.
Wh-What's with you, grandpa?!
Croak...
Grandpa! Grandpa, grandpa!
He's dead.
What was his hand?
Chuuren Poutou... Tenpai!
What was his draw?
The cheaper out.
Goddamn weakling!
It's a baiman though.
Wh-What are you doing?
If you die, you lose!
Losers get their clothes stripped off!
And winners get to wear double!
Are you fucking stupid?
Raw garbage
Now the gap with Toyotomi's become even wider...
It's strange...
Haneman, baiman, then sanbaiman...
Whenever I won a hand, Rie burnt her hand,
Kenjin's laptop was smashed, and Master died!
It's like I'm sucking up
the luck of everyone else around!
Wh-What is this hand, even?!
Ugh! It creeps me out!
It's only turn 2...
But I'm not gonna draw the dora 9-man...
Oh no! I drew it!
But it's only turn 3!
This hand can be better than baiman!
Got it!
Chinroutou Suuankou!
It's the Devil!
The Devil is real, after all!
Yes, hello?
Ah, hello, this is Hayami.
Eh? Akina-chan?!
Toyotomi-kun,
something happened,
and I ended up in the hospital.
H-H-Hospital?!
They said something's not right
with my kidneys.
I'm due a complete examination now,
but I'm not feeling very optimistic.
Wh-Which hospital?
What room?
Yeah. Got it!
Wut? How could that phenomenally lucky Hayami lass get sick?
Wanna go there now?
Nah, it not so urgent
as to leave this hanchan unfinished.
Got it!
But what... what if it's going to be Akina-chan who'll have to pay for me winning this hand?
Akina-chan!
Hey, get on with it!
Devil, you... So you're out for Akina's life this time around?!
That's cruel! So cruel!
That's it! My contract with you
is over!
Ron!
Pinfu Ittsuu Dora 1!
Menhon Chiitoi Dora Dora!
Zugan!
Hell Wait Hospital
It turned out to be nothing serious.
I'm sorry for making you all worry.
Good for you!
Then you can eat some of this, right?
Look, I bought you this interesting book!
These are my feelings for you.
U-Um...
S-Sorry, I gambled away all my money...
Don't be silly, Toyotomi-kun!
Just seeing you come to check on me
is enough to make me happy!
Akina-chan!
There is a territory
that humans must never set foot into,
lest the balance of universe will be disrupted.
It might even exists right there, next to you.
What about us?
Well, excuse me!
Zugan.
What's that?
A present for your boyfriend?!
Yeah. I wanted to give it to him for the New Year, but I was too slow.
Really? You should've said so!
You didn't have to go shopping with me!
It's fine! After all, I got to see you again after such a long time.
What's wrong, Akina?!
You look so pale! Are you okay?!
Y-Yeah, I'm fine...
H-Hey! Akina!
Episode 13 Part 2
Cold-catching Zugan
Akina-chan!
Wow, you sure came here quickly!
Toyotomi-kun...
Are you okay?
Well now, seeing how your prince in shining armor has arrived,
I'll leave you two to it
and won't interrupt you.
Oh geez... Her imagination is always going places...
How bad is your fever?
Yeah, quite bad...
Ah... That's better.
How about some medicine?
Ah... Are you hungry?
Don't worry! I can take care of that myself.
I'll get better in no time if I rest a bit.
No way! You need to eat
before you can take your medicine!
I'll make you something!
Even if it won't be anything special...
Still, what gives?
To think Akina-chan could catch a cold!
Did you spend all night playing again?
That's not good for your health!
I don't recognize my Toyotomi-kun!
Here, Toyotomi's special—stamina-udon!
Wow, thank you!
Say "Ah!"
Ah!
Ish it good?
If you want anything else at all, just say it!
O-Okay...
Now, Akina.
Don't hold back and fall into my arms.
I...
What is it?
I want to eat a melon!
Why? Jesus...
I can't?
Oh, I know!
I've got a melon for you! Mom mailed one to me from the countryside!
Melon! Melon! Melon! Melon! Melon!
Melon! Melon! Melon!
Eh? It's... gone?!
The melon's gone!
You're late, Toyotomi!
We were bored so we helped ourselves to your fridge!
Assholes! That melon was...
That melon was...
A Yuubari melon, right?
Hell no! Well, it was technically a Yuubari variety,
but this melon was not from Yuubari!
Where's it from, then?
Listen here, you...
No good! This guy didn't come with brains included!
We'll settle this with a game!
Yeah!
Great god of mahjong,
please just let me win this once!
If I win, I'll make them buy another melon and bring it to Akina!
It's strange to see Toyotomi implore the gods.
Too bad, but your prayers won't work on us!
Ron!
Wh-at?!
3,900! Fold the creases of your fingers together for good fortune! Akahanmyara parashiitaa!
Tsumo! 1,300/2,600!
Ron! 6,400!
Tsumo! Tanyao Pinfu Sanshoku Iipeikou assortment!
First place in all last!
Wuh?! Toyotomi's first?!
I-Impossible!
Heh. That's what happens
when I play seriously!
Kan-ji-zai-bo-satsu...
But he doesn't have that much of a lead! I'll overtake him!
Riichi!
Blast!
If Shintaro draws 4,000 all,
he'll overtake me!
And if I can't give her another melon,
Akina-chan will...
Akina-chan! Hang in there!
To-Toyotomi-kun...
I just wanted... some melon...
A-Akina-chan! Akina-chan
Shut up. It's your turn.
Look, I'm calling a pursuit riichi.
Stop spacing out and get on with it!
Right...
I won't risk it now.
Let Yasu take care of it.
That's game-making!
Oh no, the ura suji!
Yasu is waiting
for the outcome
C'mon, deal in!
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
Ugh, the dora neighbor!
This time for sure!
Yasu is waiting
for the outcome
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
Eh! The dora itself!
C'mon, bro, start moving!
Yasu is waiting
for the outcome
Yasu is waiting for the outcome.
Tsumo!
4,000 all!
Back to the top!
Fold the joints of your fingers together for bad fortune!
What the hell is your problem?!
What's your deal?!
It's a shanpon!
But the 1-sou is already dead...
Why didn't you cut the 6-pin
and go back to iishanten?!
In my mahjong, there's no going back.
I only go forward.
I'm such a dumbass
for ever relying on this guy!
I knew it! Everyone else is my enemy!
The only thing I can trust is my own skill!
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Dora 1!
Tsumo! 2,000/4,000!
Riichi Pinfu instant Tsumo! 2,600 all!
Let's go! Second hanchan and I'm first place in all last again!
Impossible!
It can't be helped. That means
I must also bring out my special skill!
Pon!
Chii!
DORA
The dora is the 4-pin...
I'm 19,000 points ahead of Yasu...
DORA
I can deal in for 8,000 and still be first!
So even if he has a concealed dora triplet and wins off me with a 2-sou tanki, I'm safe!
Kan!
Tsumo!
Rinshan Tanyao dora 6!
Baiman! 4,000/8,000!
First place by 1,000!
Zugan...
A poem:
Best outed he stands on cliff's edge of the fjord
which hath scraped the peaks of the tun-dora.
A hypermeter.
Yes, this is Hayami.
Help me, Akina-chan...
Come on, you know I can't...
I have a fever so I'll just draw your initial hand...
No, please play too!
I can't anymore... You do it...
Menpin Dora 3 iishanten?!
With this even I'll be A-OK!
Yeah, I'm not going to take this Riichi only.
Huh?
Tsumogiri!
No! What the hell's going on?!
9-man!
Chii!
Huh?!
Oh! Nice call!
Pinfu Ryanpeikou Tsumo!
For real?!
Maybe I should draw the starting hand
and Akina the draws...
What?
Whoa... Your chanta sanshoku?
Riichi!
That just can't be real!
If the 2-5-man come out, it's just San-ankou!
Don't want it.
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Suuankou Tanki!
Without any waste!
Oh? I suddenly feel like I'm not ill anymore!
That's great!
Here now, you should get some rest
if you have a cold.
Here, put on this scarf.
Akina-chan, this is...
Try to get warm
and you'll get well soon!
Yes. Thank you!
Yasu?
Unlucky in the game, lucky in love!
The breeze blowing through the alleys was still cold,
but for those two, the spring looked like it was just about to come.
Achoo-dammit! And what about me?! Eh?!
The hotel where we all went has a heated pool.
But there's a mysterious figure at the shop.
And what is this thing Toyotomi-kun found?
Next time:
"Poolside Zugan,"
and "The Return of Ozawa Takeshobo!"
Definitely watch it!
I won't forgive you if you fall asleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa