Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Tommy? Are you there?
Akina...?
I'm sorry, Tommy.
Why?
I was being mean to you on purpose, Tommy.
I thought that doing so would motivate you
and help you beat those three.
Tommy, please forgive me!
Hm. Don't worry, I'm okay.
Tommy, do you hate me?
Oh, Jesus!
What if you and me...
Tommy! I love you, Tommy...
Episode 09
Gambling Trip Zugan
A-Am I dreaming?
If you think about it, there's no way Akina would dress up as a bunny girl...
If it's a dream, I need to be quick before it's time to wake up!
Let's go!
No!
No, Toyotomi-kun!
You're rushing things too much!
She's stark naked now!
H-How rude!
Wake up! Wake up right now!
Not so fast! Take some responsibility before waking up!
That was quite a nightmare.
Oh man, I've got an explosion on my head...
Even after being betrayed so much,
I guess I'm still not over Akina...
Shall I go on a journey?
So I suddenly found myself at this forgotten place in the middle of nowhere...
Art thou mayhaps a traveler?
I've come looking for my forgotten self.
Gaze upon the sea.
At suchlike times, it is best for men to gaze upon the sea.
North Button
Hello.
Everyone seems to be getting chills
from the vibe I'm giving off.
Glose that door abready!
Yeah! 'Dis fucking cold!
You banna freeze us all to death, by guy?
Ah, s-sorry!
Dat guy's got a body dat's as big as his head and is wearing a trench coat that looks awful on him.
And dat scrawny face...
He must be an easy target.
Hey kid, come over here.
No way, Jose! I was just leaving here,
you'd be way more welcome at our table!
We're the weakest table in here!
I guess I was born with makings of an idol...
I'm popular no matter where I go...
Well then.
May I join this table?
He had to approach them of all people...
They're the strongest members of our parlor...
He joined the table of three drunkards!
"Whisky and water" Utsuki
"Whisky and water" Utsuki!
"Hoppy" Toubara
"Hoppy" Toubara!
And "High Sour" Gento!
"High Sour" Gento
These three appeared to be a bunch of alcoholics at the first glance...
But they were actually all ex-pros
who have played in the capital in their time.
They had abandoned their ambition...
But their technique was still something an amateur could not measure up to!
What's up with those messy discards!?
I got it!
Pinfu and up to sanshoku Dora 1 with 9p!
Dora
It'll come out in no time with this gang...
But first I'll dama a bit!
Yes, it came!
Oh, silly me.
I'm discarding not that...
But this!
Your glass is almost empty.
Lemme help you...
Oh-ho! Yes, much obliged!
Much obliged, friend...
Tsumo!
It's a tsumo nomi.
Too bad.
9pinは　切れねえ　さげなァ
Yeah. Hey.
Oh? Hey, young man, what's with that fear-stricken face?
Down here 'tis the ABC of mahjong, really.
Well, now. Here.
A drink will help you.
They're strong!
Hey, Toyotomi!
He ain't here!
Hey!
Ah? He left a farewell letter here!
That dumdum, he thinks he can get away with a farewell later.
He wants to run away from us!
Tch, what an excuse of a man!
Toyotomi-kun...
So? What does it say?
H-Hey! Hayami!
Where are you going?
Toyotomi-kun!
Dear Akina...
Soon, I'll travel to the north to gamble...
No matter where I go, I shan't forget you...
Toyotomi.
Limited express to Yukitsubaki
Hayami!
Shintaro-kun...
So you don't even call me
Shintaro-san anymore?
I...
You're going to leave me, aren't you?
I-I'm sorry.
But I just couldn't...
Don't say it!
I see it now!
You only got close to me to rouse that imbecile Toyotomi?
I was...
I was just a convenience to you?!
Right, so how about this nape?
Ah, I cut too much on the right!
Ah, now on the left!
Ah! Whoops! Silly me...
You...
I was just a contrivance to you?!
Contrivance
I'm sorry, but...
I have to go.
Attention. The 14:40 express Yukitsubaki 32 to Kitaguni will depart from platform 14.
Ron! Takame
Zugan!
Toyotomi-kun...
Just wait for me...
It's a Ron. Dun nan dora dora. Mangan
Hang in there, Toyotomi-kun!
Until I get there, please...
Please don't get busted out!
Godspeed, Akina!
Toyotomi is nearing the bust-out!
Toyotomi, hang in there!
Hold out until I get there!
Gambling Trip Zugan
Discard already.
How long are ya gon' be thinking about it?
Tanpin sanshoku...
But he's already tenpai...
That being said, dora is 4p.
I shan't cut the dora soba 36p against dealer riichi ippatsu...
To hell with it.
Now's the time...
"To endure the unendurable
and suffering what is insufferable!"
Even if I have to go for tanyao nomi, I have to cut 5p!
Ron!
Riidi ibbadzu menhon iddsuu
Zugan!
No way...
I'm 18,000 in the black.
What do you know!
You've dealt in again.
I wanna go home!
Really? He's regressed to childhood!
Stop being so spoiled!
Wait just a moment!
I'll be right back!
I'm sure it was Baba-kun!
If you think about it,
I still don't know a thing about Baba-kun.
What on earth was it...?
It wouldn't be until sometime later that Toyotomi began to realize
that Baba might've been
just a ghost with big lips.
Well then, time to go back to Tokyo.
You're not going anywhere!
SMACK!
We'll see about that!
Running away mid-game?!
C'mon, bring him in—
we still have two rounds left to play.
We really do!
Zugan!
This is the town!
I can hear his voice from this town!
This way!
Zugan!
He's close...
That's a Zugan flower!
Here too!
There too!
Mahjong Parlor North Button
Here it is.
Toyotomi-kun...
Akina-chan?
How did you know I was here?
North Button
It was...
It was love.
Akina-chan!
Toyotomi-kun!
Sir, you're bothering other clients...
We're a gentlemanly establishment.
Mommy, look, those uncles've
been bullying me!
Now, now sweetie.
You'll be fine now.
C'mon, blow your nose!
Wold it be quite all right if I continued this game in his stead?
Those capital snobs don't even know any manners, dagnabbit!
All fine by me!
Be our guest!
He's 20,000 yen in the red, though.
Really? That much?!
What's more, we're already in All Last.
What the hell?!
Stop! Ouch!
C'mon, Gento, apologize.
At this rate, the lady will bounce
before she gets a chance to play with us.
I s'pose....
At any rate, I can only renchan now, right?
Fug  Yuo gand renchan if we wins
Yuo wins jaguman nuow?  Ebin
1p kan!
Fug suugandsu DD
6s kan!
Fugging gaaaaaan
Wdf yuo doings
Gan dis
Kan!
Oh?
What do you know! Another kan!
Which one should I cut?
This one!
Whatever I could cut?
She gebd fugging 2s too de end Fug 1s is dangeruos
She wend fugging doidoi  So gand be middle dile
If it came to this, how about this...
Huh?
Oh!
Lucky me! It's a Ron!
Kyaa! Look, look! It's a suji trap with 2s and 8s!
Yes!
Hey, it's quite alright.
Just keep hitting.
It's but a scratch, bud.
Jusd end her delear ruond
Pon!
Utsuki went for tanyao.
Pon.
Toubara went for haku nomi.
Dabörii D
Gento called turn 1 riichi.
Not bad!
The flow is perfect now.
Right...
Here, lemme help you.
Yeah, not bad, not bad!
They're all so lucky!
They all didn't deal in.
S-So she was in tenpai, huh?!
4m...
I shan't discard it!
4m kan!
Even with pinfu tanyao sanshoku dora dora...
What a waste...
Yay! I tsumoed!
Tanyao tsumo rinshan, with 3p kandora, dora 3!
What is this, it ended up as a dealer haneman anyway!
Ganning my winning dile and dzumoing de lasd 5m  Ebin
Pon!
Ron!
North Button
Pon!
Ron!
North Button
I did it! 8-honba!
Now anything you win is a yakuman!
Here! Riichi!
Sorry!
Riichi ippatsu menchin!
Uhh... ura 3.
Sheesh!
It was a yakuman anyway and I get menchin ura 3!
Shit is rigged!
Thus, Toubara died.
I have to conserve my flow!
A 1 han hand is fine too!
Be merciful, please!
Sheesh, not again!
Ron! Tanyao sanshoku iipeikou!
Rigged like hell!
Thus, Gento died.
By god's name, let this pass!
Now... this is a real waste!
Real waste!
Junchan dora 3!
Eep! Rigged all the way through!
Thus, Utsuki died.
A cig after gambling
is always so awfully bitter...
I wanna go home!
But I don't know where home is!
Incredible!
"Back-to-childhood" phenomenon!
They're such a bother...
We don't have any moolah!
I'm sorry, Toyotomi-kun.
I'm over it already. Don't worry.
We meet again, old man.
Didst thou find what thou wert looking for, traveler?
Yeah!
I feel like something's changed
deep inside me!
Shall we go home? To Tokyo.
Yeah.
With the unoriginal final scene,
the train carrying the two of them
departed for Tokyo.
A haiku:
O haku nomi, are you not sad?
Wandering without calling kamicha's hatsu or shimocha's chun.
Thank you for listening.
Isshu Soden, with its ultimate technique,
Mukafun Daiten, which can even discard a​ crying child's winning tile.
Toyotomi-kun is back!
Next time: The Invincible Rage Overload Technique and Toyotomi's Counterattack.
Make sure to watch it!
Don't you fall asleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa