Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to tree years.
Toyotomi Hideyuki, the world's foremost busting out machine. From Chiba Prefecture.
Oda Shintaro. A one-hit wonder who is ignorant of theory. From Chiba Prefecture.
Tokugawa Yasube. An absolute ignoramus who doesn't know when to stop calling. From Chiba.
Akechi Koichi. The expert in by-the-book calculative and rational playstyle. From Chiba.
Hayami Akina.
Technically Toyotomi's love interest.
Born with incredible luck.
From Chiba Prefecture.
Sir? There's a delivery for you.
A delivery for you, sir.
Right, thanks.
Now where did I leave my seal...
No, it's all right!
Rather, would you please take good care of this package?
Thanks for your work...
What the?!
A baby?!
Episode 7 Part 1
Baby Player Ponta
No! This is bad! Come on! This is very bad! How did it come to this?!
Man, yer noisy!
What's all the ruckus for?
Yeah, that's a baby alright!
Aww, he's heaps cute, boss!
Where'd you find him?
Isn't he yours?
My kid?!
I'm tired. He's your problem now.
t. Single Mom
He had this letter with him!
It's definitely not for me!
I'm tired. He's your problem now.
t. Single Mom
Ain't no way! I'm still a virgin!
How could I have a kid without having sex!
Oops. Gotta go to my college now.
H-Hold it! How come this is the only day
when you go to college?
I'm actually a diligent and serious student.
Ya should also probably hand the little one over to police as soon as you can.
Byes now!
Dammit! He's such a douchebag!
Poor fella.
Let's see if I have any toys around.
I only have this...
Look! Come play, they're building blocks!
Chinitsu...
You know mahjong?!
O-Of course not... Then, what's your wait here? Can you tell? Can you?
What?!
I-It's just a coincidence, right?
All right...
What's the cheaper out for this hand?
He's a genius!
Mahjong Parlor
Rombers
And that's what happened.
Hm? So Toyotomi's got an illegitimate child, huh...
Akina-chan, it's about time ya forgot that rake and be happy with me!
Preposterous.
Do you really think our Toyotomi-kun has what it takes to father an illegitimate child?
Who knows... Oh, that's ron!
Riichi Ippatsu Menchin!
Whatever you say, I bet you're very upset, Akina-chan!
Well, speak of the devil.
Toyotomi, is that baby related to you in any way at all?
Great question!
This kid is a gift from God,
my wonder baby!
Why, you!
Slam
So it really is your baby, after all?!
No it's not...
This is a heaven-sent baby,
Ponta the mahjong prodigy!
Ponta the mahjong prodigy?!
Well, just watch.
Pft. Toyotomi, you dumbass.
There's no way a baby can win me in a mahjong parlor! Are you messing with me?
All right, turn 3 damaten. I got this in back.
Wow, what a nice draw!
Dama! Dama!
Wow! You think uncle Shintaro is in dama?
D-Don't say nonsense!
Oh! A 3-man wait!
Have ya really stooped so low that ya have to rely on that brat?!
Since you say so, Oda-kun,
seems he hit the bull's eye!
Your voice is a pristine vibrato!
Look, riichi!
That jerk...
Discarding the dora...
Don't you look down on me!
Mentanpin Ippatsu Sanshoku Dora Dora Iipeikou!
Wow, and we got double ura!
Dealer's sanbaiman!
So! Have you realized his true power?!
Ya got too cocky thinking it was just a brat, Shintarou.
What?!
There's no place for mercy in the world of gambling.
You can't afford to go easy even on women or children.
Oh, it came out!
Sanshoku Dora 1, 5,200!
Ugh, noisy brat! Stop it, you crybaby!
Give me my point sticks already!
Ow-ow-ow!
What's this brat's problem?!
T-This is strange!
Why is Ponta being so difficult?
Your ass is already wet.
You're right!
All right, let's get you cleaned up!
Why do you have to do it here?
Okay, we're done!
Look! As soon as I cleaned your butt,
your draws are good again!
Riichi!
I said you can't go easy on them.
If he calls Riichi then I'll call.
Chii!
Wait! Don't eat the tiles!
Give it back! Or we'll make you puke it up!
He's really chewing on it!
Ew, it's all dirty!
I don't need that shit anymore!
If you don't call...
Ippatsu tsumo!
Impressive, Toyotomi-kun.
You're leveraging the baby's strengths to help you win...
You two really are parent and child!
That's not true, Akina-chan!
No use for excuses, boss.
Your combination is that
of a father and child.
But what if I severed off that bond?!
The white's only been cut once.
Perfect!
Riichi!
Whassat?! I was in tenpai too!
Crikey! Could have swapped my pair with the 1-pin...
Ron!
Riichi Nico Nico Honitsu! Haneman!
Ow nyo!
I-I won! Against these guys too!
He's the real deal!
Ponta is a mahjong prodigy!
All right! In this case, I'll raise you to be the world's strongest mahjong master!
Daisuke!
Wh-Who are you?
I'm Daisuke's mother!
Please give Daisuke back to me!
Ponta-kun's mom?
I don't think we should call him that anymore.
It's my Daisuke!
Please give him back to me!
He's the Mahjong Prodigy Ponta, not Daisuke!
I'm sorry. I'll never pose as the delivery service to get rid of him again. Please give Daisuke back!
Lady's right, mate!
Not happening! I'll raise Ponta myself!
Toyotomi-kun...
Ponta, Chiita, or whatever,
you gotta give him back!
No means no!
All right, I know what to do.
Toyotomi Hideyuki vs Ponta's mother.
You'll hold a duel and consider the winner the true parent!
Splendid! Another case closed!
Riichi ippatsu be careful of fires!
What do you say?
I'm in!
Like hell I'll lose!
Chun!
It came out! Menhon Shousangen!
I see, Daisuke...
Ronning your mommy like that...
You despise your mommy
who threw you away?
Ponta is a mahjong prodigy!
He'll win anything for me!
Ah... I see...
3-sou pon!
Whoa, lady! You can't show your hand before winning!
Daisuke! Deal in with the 3-pin!
Come back home to your mommy!
Ponta will never deal in on purpose.
Wh-What are you doing, Ponta?
N-No you can't!
Ron! Tanyao Dora 3!
Mommy!
Daisuke! You came back to me after all!
Mommy will never leave you alone again!
Ponta...
Boss! Now ya got me instead of Ponta.
Another case closed by me.
Riichi ippatsu and drive safe.
Ponta...
Thus, the baby returned safe and sound to his mother.
Left alone in the city, Toyotomi feels his heart overfill with jealousy and longing.
With bittersweet memories brought back to life, Toyotomi thinks
about writing a long overdue letter to his mother back home.
Mommy!
Point stick blade!
Riichi!
Crash!
Chii                               Ron                                      Pon
Report!
Episode 7 Part 2
Jongputer in a Pond
Oh no! I lost...
Riichi Ippatsu Honitsu Hatsu Sanankou Dora 3, baby!
You're really strong...
That's right! I'm strong.
Incredibly strong!
It'd be a shame to leave such strength lying around unused! Isn't that right, my baby....
I love strong guys!
Let me reward you...
Got it, baby!
Now there's only one thing to do...
Become a pro mahjong player
and make everyone go
"Wow! A promising supernova was born!"
Wait.
Municipal library
That jerk!
You'd never think he'd be hiding out in such a place.
He's trying to outsmart us, huh?
Like hell we're letting him get away with it.
Toyotomi-kun...
He's here! He's here! He's here! He's here!
Hey!
Wait!
Just calm down and come with us
for a moment, won't you?
Somebody help!
What's this whistling?!
O-Over there!
Who the hell are you?
S-State your name!
I am the one who has defeated all jongputers far and wide: the hidden genius mahjong star!
Have you got the guts
to gamble with me, gentlemen?
Let's get going, then.
No! I don't wanna come with you!
Yeah, time to go.
Calm don't won't you?
Whoa, whoa, wait a bit, baby!
What is it?
I told you to include me in your lineup too!
Nobody asked.
Just go to a parlor or whatever
if you really want to.
Wait a second, Shintarou...
Mark my words,
this guy could be an easy mark.
Maybe you've hit the mark...
Indeed.
That means...
One of us will have to skip...
So it seems...
First to say something.
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
Mahjong
parlor
Junkie
You should have just let me join from the start, baby...
What's this? Nonsense!
Riichi!
Already a haneman, success guaranteed!
What could it be...
Fold.
6-sou!
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Menhon Ton Hatsu!
Why the hell did ya cut a 6-sou against these discards?!
Don't go easy on the jongputer kid!
What could I do?
I was in closed honitsu tenpai too!
If you let this guy steal your flow,
that's no good.
Riichi!
Take that!
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Menhon Iipeikou!
Why the hell did you cut the 3-sou?!
You're the one getting your flow stolen!
Don't be stupid!
I was in tenpai!
I had no choice.
All right! My camouflage is perfect!
Riichi!
Toyotomi's wait
Don't you know how to fold?
If I deal in, it's worth the same anyway!
Oh, I see... This guy's what they call a "jongputer specialist."
Mahjong video games have been getting better lately, but they're still mainly one-on-one.
That's why dealing in and getting tsumo'd is usually worth the same.
Naturally, it means you have to push like a bull.
There!
Dora
Here you would normally cut the 9-man and go for either sanshoku or ittsuu...
Obviously cut the 9-pin and go for instant riichi!
I was right...
How about this?
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu only!
Zugan...
It keeps coming out...
This kind of head-on players are scary when they get lucky!
Riichi!
I'm luckless so better just match the 1-pin!
Ron! Ippatsu!
Zugan...
Not so fast! Look!
Shintaro cut it right before me!
Huh?
No huhs, you were in furiten!
I-I was only looking at my toimen...
An obvious trap for a jongputer player.
Dora
All right! Let's get those sticks back!
Take this!
Chii!
You can't chii from your toimen,
you numbskull!
Ouch...
1,000 point penalty!
Mahjong against humans is unforgiving! Look!
Chii!
Don't let him call tiles you know he needs!
Yasu never looks at the discards.
Huh? What are ya complaining about?
I'm in tenpai, you know!
It's my turn now!
Riichi!
Dora
All right! I made it to tenpai, baby!
Go!
Ron! Riichi Ippatsu Menhon Iipeikou!
Shake it, baby!
See? It doesn't work with humans, baby.
Nope. Keiko and Shio from Family Mahjong were even stronger.
Huh? In that case...
Riichi!
Were they at least this strong?!
This is still nothing, baby!
Well, in that case...
Riichi!
Riichi Ippatsu Tanyao Chiitoi!
Huh! Still not even close, baby!
Riichi.
Well, then I'll riichi too.
There!
Just Riichi Ippatsu!
Why won't you cut a safe tile with such a shit hand?!
A win is a win, you know.
Then you're no different from this young man!
It would be the same head-on computer mahjong!
I know well what you want to say. However...
It's faster this way after all.
Riichi.
Obstinate fools!
I'll show you how it's done!
A human playstyle,
by humans for humans!
Here!
It's a Ron!
Ron...
A resounding roll...
Hi!
Akina-chan, come swap with me!
They're the perfect players for you!
Oh no! You've only got 1,300 points left...
Just you watch, jongputer kid!
I'll show you the ultimate human jongputer!
Chii!
Pon!
Naked tanki! Yay!
Ron! Haku only.
No! No!
Come on, undress! Get undressed, baby!
This isn't the strip mahjong at the arcade!
I bet you're happy with it!
With the skill I've honed at the jongputers, I'll certainly get this girl to strip!
Pon!
What are the odds... But I've got a Kokushi too. I'll take the gamble.
Pass!
Ron! Daisuushii Tsuuiisou!
Shake it up baby—two!
Zugan...
The dreadful jongputer kid was vanquished by the even stronger human jongputer Akina.
However, the fight is not over yet.
There is no telling if a second or third jongputer kid will appear.
Until the day people reclaim the soul of mahjong, hang in there, Akina!
Fight on, Super Zugan Toyotomi!
This next story is a little hard for me to tell.
I thought I was doing it for Toyotomi-kun,
but it seems I went a little too far.
I'm sorry, Toyotomi-kun.
Next on Super Zugan:
Tsumo-Jong to Make You Cry:
Part 1, Part 2.
Make sure to watch it!
You can't sleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa