Article 186 of the Penal Code:
A person who engages in frequent gambling can be subject to criminal penalties, including imprisonment for up to three years.
Episode 12 Part 1
New Year's Zugan
He drew it!
But he needs to discard a 1-pin or a 5-pin against 3 riichis...
Which one will ya cut, boss?
YASU
AKECHI
AKINA
Pass.
I want to... see the sea.
B-Boss?!
Wh-What the bloody hell happened to ya?
Tsumo!
Suuankou Tanki.
As dealer, that's 96,000.
Th-That's strong!
He's a whole different man!
Completely different
from last year's Toyotomi!
H-How did it come to this...?
December 31st, 1992
For juice, is grapefruit fine?
Okay, Okay!
Whoa! Why don't I buy
the New Year's soba noodles?
I love the Donbei Noodles!
I'm a stickler for tradition no matter what.
Eh! It's gone! Gone! All gone...
They always run out of cup noodles on the New Year, you dumdum!
Sell me some...
All right, 500 yen a cup.
Zu... gan...
Oh come on, Toyotomi-kun...
You shouldn't have to eat
only the cheapest cup noodles!
Akina-chan!
Will you maybe treat me
to you own homemade soba?!
Sure!
Baby Zugan
Zugan
Look! They've got a new wrapper!
Baby Zugan
Zugan
If you get hungry, help yourself to these!
Baby Zugan
Zugan
Zugan!
Shintaro-kun's gone to his hometown,
I wonder what he's doing now...
Playing mahjong no doubt!
Yeah, that guy's got
no brains for anything else!
Not a single good thing's
happened to me this past year!
Ah, wait a second, you.
Uh... Y-You mean me?
That's right.
You have the look of lucklessness on you.
I'll read your fortune for the coming year
with my guitar fortune-telling!
In '92 you were luckless epitomized!
But it'll all go your way in the coming year!
Ah... Rake in, rake in!
Well, I...
You fell right for it!
Naive idiot!
Oh? You've eaten already?
Well then, now that we've all been replenished, how about a game, huh?
What? You wanna play already?
Obviously!
Chop-chop now, pick your seat!
EAST 1 TURN 8
Riichi!
Crikey! Riichi on the dora!
Tsk. Fold.
What a windfall!
Akechi's discards
The 4-pin is safe, so cut the 7-pin and wait on the dora which just passed!
It's a superb wait! Hm?
Weak!
That's piss-weak, mate, I'm spewin'!
Y-You think so?
Okay! A safe tile!
If the 7-pin passed, you'd have won 6,400!
Cretin! Don't whisper it so close to my ear!
Pretty spiffy!
Now cut the 3-man and with the 9-pin it's Riichi Chun Iipeikou for 5,200! She'll be right, mate!
Let's fight!
Piss-poor!
If ya'd kept the chun ya'd have hit the 6-pin with Riichi Ippatsu Chun!
Cutting chun for Iipeikou only dama...
couldn't be worse, mate!
Dora!
Crikey! He's even breakin' his tenpai!
I overestimated ya, Boss.
From today my new boss is Hayami-san!
No backseating.
You don't have to be so cold, do you?!
I was even willing to tell you his tiles!
I can handle it just fine myself!
That ain't looking hot, Boss!
That's dicey, mate, bloody dicey!
Riichi!
Tenpai!
Ron!
Riichi Ippatsu Chanta Sanshoku!
Haneman, mate!
Zugan!
By the way, Akechi,
what was ya hand, mate?
I had a Mentanpin 2-5-8-man wait with Sanshoku...
That makes sense!
Both the 7-pin and 3-man would have passed!
Shut up!
Pon! Pon! That's a pon!
Riichi.
Yasu's discards
5-pin... The dora!
Come on! Fold with suji!
Ron!
The cheaper out...
Riichi Ippatsu Tanyao!
I'm at 3,200 in the red...
This 5-shanten hand will be this year's last...
This year's last riichi!
Ron!
Happy New Year!
Riichi Ippatsu Ittsuu!
Zugan!
Riichi!
Toyotomi, I hope you'll do
the needful this year too!
What's wrong, Toyotomi?
U-Ura suji...
P-Pass...
All those dangerous tiles...
Pass...
Riichi.
Ron.
Mentanpin Iipeikou.
S-Strong... He's not the Toyotomi he was last year!
Whatever! Won't believe you.
Riichi!
C'mon, Toyotomi, deal right in!
Riichi, huh...
Ura suji!
Bah! Pass.
I have safe tiles...
But I cut the 4-man on purpose!
But why?
Yeah, why?
That's because...
Because I'm feeling confident!
Matagi suji!
Pass.
Suji!
3 times out!
Pass!
Riichi on a safe tile!
So confident!
Those discards with this hand!
Boss's been reincarnated into a terminator!
That fortune teller was right!
Wuh?
Ron!
Riichi Ippatsu Tanyao!
But boss!
Ya might have wiped out
Akechi and Tokugawa...
But until ya wipe out Hayami-san
ya aren't the real deal!
TURN 10
DORA
Closed Honitsu Iishanten!
She made it!
Cut the 5-sou for a closed 8-sou...
Or the 9-sou for a closed 6-sou...
But the 6-sou is the dora...
No one will discard it...
Push the haku!
Pon!
Dora!
The hatsu and chun...
haven't been cut at all!
There's no doubt this is Daisangen!
I can't discard this...
I'll fold with...
Ron! Haku Dora 1!
Cutting a dora from that hand...!
Ya nincompoop!
It's the new dawn...
The sun rises on 1993,
the year of Toyotomi!
Here!
Ron! Sanankou Chanta Honitsu Hatsu Chun Ton!
Boss! As expected of my boss!
Ya're the only one in the green!
What?!
Yasu, -1!
Akechi, -1!
Akina, -1!
Toyotomi, +3!
Shit... It's 'cause we decided
to let you rejoice just today.
Amazing, Toyotomi-kun!
The sole winner...
It's so trifling when you look back on it...
Hey, Toyotomi, since you're the sole winner,
why don't ya treat everyone else?
It's New Year after all!
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
Restaurant
Golden Axe
Silver Axe
I'll have the calf steak,
spicy devilish!
I'll have a large foie gras
with extra egg!
I'll have the 3,000 yen
full course menu!
Fine if I wrap my laughin' gear
round the same as Hayami-san?
And some pickles for me, please.
Certainly, sir.
Thus ended the turbulent year of 1992.
And heading towards the dramatic climax,
Toyotomi's year 1993 began!
Three months remain until Super Zugan's final episode!
And to you, dear viewers,
Happy New Year!
Riichi!
Wuh? Riichi on turn 4 already?!
Pass!
Tenpai!
What should I do now...
Cut the 2-pin and call riichi with up to Pinfu Iipeikou Dora 1?
DORA
The 2-pin should pass...
No... it's only turn 4...
It's also possible to cut the safe 1-pin and go for Tanyao!
Whatcha waiting for?
Just cut something!
Toyotomi!
I can draw the 3-4-sou for Sanshoku...
But can I afford to slow my hand
down that much?
Toyotomi!
Toyotomi...
Toyotomi?!
Toyotomi!
Zugan!
Episode 12 Part 2
Once Upon a Zugan
H-Hey, guys! Stop it!
Wuh?
Who's you?
Say it again!
N-No, I'm just saying
it's not nice to bully animals...
Please... Show mercy!
If you mistreat animals,
th-the WWF won't stand for it!
What was that?!
We won't have you look down on us!
Get him!
Zugan...
Tsk, he's no match for us.
All talk and no bite!
Let's go!
Tangs! Tangs for kelping me!
Gratitrout
As a thanks, let me roe you
to the Dragon King's Palace!
Affec-tuna
Why don't you perch yourself on my back?
Seajourn
The Dragon King's Palace?
Is that where "the sea breams and flounders dance"?
Indeed.
Then surely enough
it has a finbulous princess too!
Findeed
Dace right, chum!
Crabsolutely
Lucky!
Sorry for the wait.
That's the Dragon King's Palace!
High-end Mahjong Parlor
Dragon King's Palace
Free Mahjong
You can play with us too
Tsumo! Chiitoi Dorado Dorado!
Oh roe!
Sharks to be you!
There were a great many minnows and whales in that mahjong parlor.
Princess, I brought a customer!
Welcome!
I'm Otohime, working as manager
of this establishment!
W-Want!
Only if you win at mahjong, okay?
I've seen these guys somewhale before...
Wutcha yappin' on about?
C'mon, chop-chop, let's go!
Like I'll ever lose
against minnows and whales!
Riichi Ippatsu Dora Dora Bang-bang!
I won't give up on Otohime
after just a mangan!
Ron! Honitsu Ippatsu Haku Dora Dora! Baiman!
Not yet!
Ron! Riichi Tanyao Dora Dora, as dealer that's 12,000!
YOU CAN PLAY WITH US TOO
Zugaaaan!
Here, your jewel box!
Zugan...
After that, Urashima Taro's hair
has turned all white...
Oh?
My, such a big 1-pin!
From that 1-pin, a baby boy
cute as a button was born.
Zugan! Zugan! Zugan! Zugan! Zugan! Zugan!
So they gave him the most appropriate name of Zugantaro.
15 YEARS LATER
Dear me, he keeps eating
through all our rice!
Thanks to him,
we're in the red this month again!
Why don't we get rid of him somewhere?
Yeah!
Uhh... I'm going to exterminate the demons
and bring back a lot of treasure.
Bloody oath, Boss!
We're countin' on ya!
Bring home as much loot as you can!
Look! Special point stick
millet dumplings!
And thus, Zugantaro set out on his quest
to exterminate the demons.
Where are ya goin' in that hero getup?
Must be carrying some tasty stuff.
Hand it over, Zugantaro.
Th-They're the precious millet dumplings
my granny gave me!
I won't ever let you lot have them!
Well how about this...
We play mahjong, and if we win,
we get the dumplings.
And if I win?
We will be your retainers
and follow you to Demon Island.
There's no way in hell
I can lose against these animals...
Let's go!
Tanyao Pinfu Sanshoku, Dealer's Mangan!
Zugan!
Bring it on!
There's no way I'll lose against animals!
Scree! That's my wait!
Chinitsu Pinfu Dora 1, Baiman!
Please... Let this pass...
Ik ook!
Suuankou tanki!
Zugan...
Well now, how about we have some
of those dumplings?
Yeah, let's eat!
At least leave a bite for me...
Really, kid? You're still alive?
Here, have a bite.
100 points.
Zugan!
And thus, Zugantaro
never made it to the Demon Island.
Little Red Zugan! Little Red Zugan!
Yes, mom?
I have an errand for you.
Okay!
Won't you carry these tiles
to your sick grandmother?
Yeah, but... Look... These are mahjong tiles,
Akina-chan—it's not in the script!
Don't talk back.
Also, call me "mother."
And as you might've figured out already...
We three...
will play the wolf!
Excuse me! It's the newspaper!
Is the sick grandmother here?
Hi!
Oh my, what cute three little boys!
Just as I've got some time to spare.
Why don't you come in?
Riichi.
Wuh?
Th-That's obviously a 4-7-sou wait!
Your reading skills are no big deal...
Really?
In that case, 4-sou kan!
Riichi!
Awrooon! Riichi Tanyao Ippatsu!
C'mon, come to daddy!
Whoa!
I have a kan of 4-sou, so 8 ura. Sanbaiman.
Zugan!
Well well, looks like we're
in charge of this house now.
Someone's here! Hide!
I came to check on you, Grandma!
Ah, you're so sweet...
How are you feeling?
Whoa!
Grandma, why do you have hands so big?
Oh, that's to grab a lot of riichi sticks!
Grandma, why do you have eyes so big?
That's to better see your discards!
And your mouth—
why do you have it so big?
Well, that's...
To better say ron!
Toyotomi! Hey!
Wake up, Toyotomi!
How do you even fall asleep
playing mahjong?
Seriously! Do you even wanna play or what?
Cut it out or we'll stop playing nicely.
A-A dream?
I see! I can't let myself be misled by Akechi's discards!
These guys are all beasts!
I'll avoid ippatsu and go for tanyao, cutting the 1-pin!
Safe tile!
Ron!
Akechi's safe tile is a big hit for me!
Junchan Sanshoku Pinfu Dora Dora!
Zugan...
Tsk...
You're out of luck, bro.
And thus, Little Red Zugan
was all eaten up by the wolves,
with great gusto.
And they all lived happily ever after​.
Happy New Year!
I hope everyone is having a great year!
This year too, I'll do my best together
with Toyotomi-kun, so wish me lick!
Next time: "Devil in the Bottle"
and "Cold-catching Zugan."
Definitely watch it!
Don't you fall asleep!
Yo! Check out this new style, Super Zugan!
If you think mahjong ain't happening,
get down with the midnight fever Zugan Zugan!
Zugan! It's time for that point of the eternal!
The international star of pop,
Minami Haruo!
Don't rush, don't fuss, don't panic
Grab a tile and dream a Sengoku romance
Whatever fortune may bring, call riichi
Don't stop me, toimen-san
You just got to go Zugan!
Riichi ippatsu pinfu ittsuu!
Shimocha and kamicha are both my mahjong buddies
But when we're gambling I'll snipe them without mercy
Aren't you a great lucky charm to your man?
Why don't you tsumo a mangan with me?
With zugan, the happiness is within reach
Super Zugan!
A heart waiting for a yakuman in the dark...
Will it soar and bloom into cherry blossoms?
Super Zugan!
This is the time for a three-sided wait
Let's go with kanchan, the final battle for a Kokushi Musou!
Crashing through without even a tsumo payment lost
The beer tastes the best after winning!
Zugan can decide a man's fate!
Super Zugan!
You just have... You've got to go Zugan!
Encoding
Translation
Translation check & TS
Mahjong translation check
WOWmd
/mjg/
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Eternal_Blizzard