No way!
What?
The heat haze of times immemorial
reflects the melody of the Milky Way,
High School Aurabuster
The Awakening of Light
Part 2
The path you walk,
your gaze, yearning for eternity
A long time ago, there was a war that divided the heavens and the earth between the "Celestial Ones" and the "Demonic Ones."
However, 900 years ago, the head of the Celestial Ones, King Kara, sealed away the head of the Demonic Ones, Kunaki, by sacrificing himself.
The battle was stopped halfway through, and in the present day, King Kara was reincarnated as a young man, and the seal was once again
My love, I've been waiting for you here
all this time, all these years
I'll be watching you from now on and forever,
just as if we're snuggling up,
until the day you return to zero
lifted.
Jyukuro-kun...
Could you open the window?
It can be bad for your health.
Is this a hospital?
That's better!
Say...
That boy...
How is he?
Stop it, Mizusawa.
It's annoying.
How many times do you need to try?
You know...
Back then, didn't you think it would be nice
if we all simply lost this power altogether?
Idiot.
So? Is Saeko better?
Yeah, she's out of the woods now.
I'm sorry for making you wait here for so long.
Thank you. I'll handle it from here.
There's no reason for you to thank us.
Had we been showered
in his light at the park back then,
we'd both have ended up
bedridden together with Saeko.
Ki-san, you're so dirty!
D-Dumbass!
Still, information like that is something you'd want to know in advance.
Did you know, Jyukuro?
Nope.
Really?
Saiga-san didn't tell me anything.
Only...
Him...
He told me to watch him closely.
So I guess Shinobu
didn't know everything either?
I wonder.
Sometimes the more important
something is, the more we try to hide it.
Power Neutralizer?
I wasn't sure, though.
So you say, but...
I won't stand for you
blaming Miga's death on me.
Oh no, did it come across that way?
There wasn't helping it, right?
For the sake of Kunaki-sama's revival,
it's a small price to pay, isn't it?
What troubles me is that he fell into King Kara's lap.
But at least now we know for sure, right?
Could I ask you for a favor?
I'm at your service.
But I wonder if our little boy
is going to behave.
We should be fine for a little while.
After all, it was him
who failed to protect Miga.
That spoiled Young General...
What's losing a subordinate or two
if it's to fulfill Kunaki-sama's request?
You still don't understand?
It's too late for him to regret his carelessness.
Next time, he'll pay for it with his own life.
Yes, it's Kanbara.
Ah, Sakiya-kun?
What happened?
Huh? Yes, got it.
It's all right.
Be there in a moment.
Sakiya-kun!
Sorry! Did I make you wait?
Sakiya-kun?
What's wrong?
Why are you shaking?
Sakiya-kun, what happened?
And then, when that woman burned to a crisp,
she turned into a beautiful stone.
That stone was then eaten by a black cat.
I don't remember exactly what happened after that,
but I feel like I had seen
the same scene long ago.
Same scene? Deja vu?
No. I don't think so.
I can't say why, though...
It's always been hard for me to tell the illusions and reality apart until after the fact.
Ah... Sorry.
I dumped this at you all at once...
There's no way you'll believe me.
You're right.
The fire coming out of a hand,
swords crushing on the barrier of light...
It sounds like science fiction novel stuff.
I wouldn't believe a word...
If it wasn't you, Sakiya-kun!
Ai-chan?
I was so pleased!
Eh?
When you...
Called me on the phone...
This late at night.
You're right, I'm so sorry!
I just needed someone to hear me out...
Was it me?
Was it me who you decided to call
on the spur of the moment?
Sakiya-kun if you become uneasy,
if you get worried,
and lonely...
If you...
if you ever feel like that again...
If you do,
don't hesitate to call me.
Me, before anyone else.
Ai-chan...
Thank you.
The only thing I know for sure is that we can't let his power fall into their hands.
Is he our trump card?
Feels more like a double-edged sword.
We don't need to concern ourselves
with thinking about that.
Won't you agree?
How about we catch him
and drag him to Saiga Shinobu?
Oh man...
Next time, Ki-sama will be paying
8,000 yen a day for the hospital bed.
Do you really think he's that powerful?
You're not like your usual self, Ki-san.
I think we're past the stage of doubting it.
Kisara, don't brood on it too much.
Mizusawa, pay attention to his surroundings.
Just say you want me to stand watch.
Kisara will replace you when night comes.
If someone comes and pesters me,
can I knock his face in?
No!
You are to follow your orders.
Are we clear?
Sakiya-kun, got any plans
for the afternoon today?
Eh?
No, I should be free. Why?
Well, I was hoping you'd go shopping with me.
Shopping?
I'll treat you to a Big Mac. Let's go now!
O-Okay...
Is this why you brought me along?
There's only one more store I want to check out. Deal?
Don't "Deal" me in this situation!
I'll just take a look at what's there first!
Wait... Ai-chan!
Thank you very much!
Did you get extra pocket money or something?
This stereo system is top of the line!
I recently broke the CD tray
on the one I have now.
I thought I might as well buy it now.
Really, that didn't matter
to me all that much.
Eh?
I wanted to listen to your story.
No, I wanted you to tell me!
I want to know!
What happened after what you told me, what you're thinking about right now,
and what you're planning to do now! Everything!
I want you to tell me.
I just want to know.
If... possible.
Ai-chan...
Are you looking for something?
Eh? Yeah...
I was wondering if you have this in size nine.
Size nine, ma'am? Okay.
Madam...
This one is size nine.
Ah, silly me!
Could you wrap it up for me, then?
Certainly. Thank you.
C'mon, stop distracting me!
I've met them ever since I was little.
I must also be one of them.
Being like them, having abilities that set me apart from regular people...
It sickens me!
Just seeing and sensing them,
who are not like the rest of the people...
Just that...
But I hate being alone!
You're not alone.
Sakiya-kun,
you're not alone!
A-Ai-chan?
What are you talking about?
Well, Ki-san told me you wanted to see me...
Ah!
That sly Ki-san!
Jyukuro-kun.
Mizusawa, where is he now?
Thanks for your business!
You're welcome!
Come on... How did I end up shopping on this assignment?
It's him...
That's why I'm saying
that I only need a moment with you.
I'm not planning to do anything to you!
So you're saying that I'm gonna
have to force you?
Please stop!
It's rude! You just come up and
make demands without explanation!
Who'd ever agree
to follow someone like you?!
Why don't you just leave me alone already?
I don't get what you people are fighting for,
and frankly, I don't want
to have anything to do with it!
Stop!
Too late.
There's no going back for you anymore!
That's not how you do it, Kisara.
Stop it!
Please stop trying to force him!
Go!
Hurry up and leave this place!
Do you want your precious princess
to be dragged into it?
Sakiya-kun, let's go.
What? Why did you just...
Sakiya-kun!
C-Coming!
Now you've definitely done it...
Who the hell are you?
It was you who got in my way.
Won't you get lost real quick?
I'm willing to let you go this time.
Don't mess with me!
What do you need that for?
To chop your head off!
How impertinent.
Heart—one sword.
It'll be over soon.
Kisara!
Kisara! Don't fall for it!
It's just an illusion!
Illusion?
Are you okay?
I-It was... an illusion?
A mere psychic is able to resist it?
Impressive that you saw right through it.
To give credit where it's due.
Is showing some lousy illusions
the best you can do?
My Suzaku sword is a lot more real!
It's useless, Mizusawa.
It's just another one of her illusions.
The real one is probably with Sakiya.
Go and get her!
Ugh! Why does it have to be so complicated?
So you even know that?
No, I don't know.
I feel it!
Seriously? Covering the whole mall with the barrier?
Too weak!
Ai-chan!
Jyukuro...
Don't let her trick you...
Nothing's going to happen.
You should be able to see through it.
What?
Where is she?!
Ai-chan, hang in there!
What's your plan?!
Why is Ai-chan now involved too?
A single "Thank you" wouldn't go amiss!
You're not bad for a psychic.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm one of the Three Demon Generals,
Phantom General Kou!
Kou?
Consider this information a present for the afterlife.
Here I go!
You really are quite something!
But if you're faced with a
stronger barrier, you'll die!
Hey, psychic, you narrowly
escaped with your life.
Jyukuro!
The Three Demon Generals?
Yes.
First the Flame General,
now the Phantom General Kou.
Where's Suguro?
No sign of him...
Is he hesitating?
No...
He doesn't even want
to hear anything about it.
Sakiya Ryosuke...
There's no way we can give you up.
Despite all that commotion,
I feel like nothing happened...
Even those wounds have disappeared.
Even though I still remember how they hurt!
Come on, let's be friends!
Just leave me alone!
I don't want my parents to notice!
Go away.
C'mon, my dude,
what's there to think about?
Just play along and help us
crush those bastards!
Please leave!
You're so cold to me, dude!
That's no way to talk to a friend.
How about you give it a rest?
Don't you understand you're bothering him?
It's you...!
What makes you think
you can just come here?!
Sakiya-kun, isn't it?
Sorry about today.
We didn't want to drag you into this.
Are you kidding me?!
You're still at it?
You wanna start a fight here?
Go ahead and let him see your true nature.
It's to kill our kind and eat our life orbs.
Is that what you want
to get him involved for?
Is that true? Are your motives really that vile?
Shut up!
You'll regret this, Suguro!
Sakiya-kun.
There's a lot of things I want to ask you.
Please go away.
Snow?
It's you?
When did you...
You and me are the same.
We'd both prefer not to have this power.
I want to protect you.
Well played.
Come here and open the window
and we'll meet and make a promise
The truth I saw in the corner of the classroom
There are also some real things I can't tell anyone
Searchin' angel night
Behind the door
The hidden love
Flyin' on flyin' out, it's awakening
Callin' birth of light
Only kindness
Will reach your heart
What remains the same as we grow up?
I wonder if the more I worry, the stronger I become?
Even if we're apart, we can just say
Things we know for certain
one by one with our lips
Feelin' future sight
The waves crashing
deep in my heart
Ridin' on ridin' out I call out to you
Callin' birth of light
Even sadness
will melt away in your eyes
Searchin' angel night
Behind the door,
the hidden love
Flyin' on flyin' out, it's awakening
Callin' birth of light
It's so dazzling
I can't look at you, only you
Feelin' future sight
Deep in my heart
The waves crashing on the shore
Ridin' on ridin' out, I call out to you
Callin' birth of light
Let's start walking
In the pouring light, you and me
RAW
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkonius
Shinjinotikari17