It's you...
When did you...
You and me are the same.
We'd both prefer not to have this power.
High School Aurabuster
Come here and open the window
The Awakening of Light
Part 1
and we'll meet and make a promise
The truth I saw in the corner of the classroom
A long time ago, there was a war that divided the heavens and the earth between the "Celestial Ones" and the "Demonic Ones."
However, 900 years ago, the head of the Celestial Ones, King Kara, sealed away the head of the Demonic Ones, Kunaki, by sacrificing himself.
The battle was stopped halfway through, and in the present day, King Kara was reincarnated as a young man, and the seal was once again
There are also some real things I can't tell anyone
Searchin' angel night
Behind the door
The hidden love
Flyin' on flyin' out, it's awakening
Callin' birth of light
Only kindness
Will reach your heart
lifted.
Poor thing...
It must've been really heartbreaking for you.
You're a very kind-hearted young man.
Hatred and strife,
this blood-stained world,
they don't suit you.
It's hot...
Come on... Get it over with already.
Gosh, he's a nuisance for sure.
Can I leave this to you?
Good luck!
It's cold!
Why did you have to get Ai-chan involved?!
I'm fed up! I don't wanna see
any of that stuff ever again!
I swear...
Looks like I'm in a bit of a bind, huh?
But I'm not going down without a fight!
What?
He's back with his friends.
You'd better not stick around here.
Won't you come with me?
B-But...
We can't let your family
get caught up in it too.
Bastard! Do you want to turn this town into a sea of fire or what?!
Why don't you sheathe that sword?
So you want us to fight bare-handed?
Think you can do it?
Let's go to my office for now.
You mean the company?
Fumihiko-sama, are you sure?
Hamaguchi.
I don't have secrets from Sakiya-kun.
L-Look, I don't mean to cause you trouble...
I'm sorry.
You got it wrong.
We're the good guys.
It hurts me...
It hurts me just thinking that you...
got caught up in this.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You won't have any doubts after this.
You're fragile... Too fragile.
That fragility is what pisses me off the most!
Oh? What a shame.
The man’s hysterical—what a sorry sight!
I've decided
how I'm gonna kill you.
The time has come.
There...
You're the president here?
Surely you do realize
it's my father's doing.
Still,
we are topping the weekly viewership ratings.
Last week marked six months
since we rose to that position.
Not too shoddy, I'd say.
It's because you have me,
wouldn't you agree?
We have plenty of serious programs too.
Now that's rude!
What do you mean by that?
I-I've been watching your show.
Really? Wow! I'm so happy!
Working for the TV is nice, isn't it?
It's a busy job.
but sometimes it saves you in return.
You can give up now.
You don't have to get up anymore.
I must keep kicking and screaming
until the end...
Since you're probably too strong
for me to have any hope of winning...
I'll only get... once chance!
Close one.
You almost had me.
Remember that it was you
who broke the rules.
Can you hear them?
The footsteps of your buddies.
If only they had come a little sooner!
Asshole...
Asshole!
Ryo!
Mizusawa!
Sakiya-kun?
Is this... The effect of the resonance?
Such enormous power?
Get to my office for now.
Where are you going?
Kaoru-kun?
What's wrong?
Kaoru-kun, we're starting!
Call it off!
President?
We'll change the news anchor.
Hamaguchi will host this one.
Got it?
Y-Yes.
Escort her out at once.
To the street.
And drive her home.
At least I've got to fight him...
I thought I had to do something...
Idiot.
But I ended up in this sorry state...
And that's all I got for it?
Just looking beaten and lame?
Try not to talk, Mizusawa!
Is demonic poison that strong?
The Flame General's Fire
is highly concentrated demonic magic.
It's not some ordinary toxin.
Then what is the detoxifier?
There is none.
So this is it?
I always wondered
what to say when this time comes.
Let's see...
How about "I'll treat Saeko-chan to a delicious dinner next time"?
I'll treat you to anything you like, every day.
Did you hear it, Jyukuro-kun?
Yeah. Good for you.
Then leave detoxicating to me.
What do you mean?
It's a poison only Saeko-san can cleanse.
What?
So? Feeling better already?
Are you kidding me?!
Why'd you make me say all that?
Well, Jyukuro-kun asked me to do it,
as a penalty for rushing in on your own.
One more thing, Mizusawa.
I won't tolerate you
acting on your own ever again.
Your life isn't just for you.
Got it?
Yeah.
Thank you, guys...
Hey, now's not a good time.
What are you trying to do,
bringing that liability here?
If you have any good ideas,
I'm all ears.
Are you implying that having him here is dangerous?
Look at you, acting all scared!
Just try basking in that light of his once.
We'll see how you talk then.
See to it that she gets home safely.
Okay.
So you're coming?
Right here?
Are you okay?
No... It was you, wasn't it?
So you figured it out?
Hey, tell me, who have you
been talking to just now?
Eh?
Don't play dumb.
You've been talking to someone
ever since we brought you here.
In your head.
It's the first time...
This is the first time it's happened to me...
So what were you talking about?
Nothing in particular.
Just...
Who?
Who are you?
Me? I am... Kudo... Kudo Kaoru.
What's this?
Kou! Put everyone in the building to sleep.
That's too sudden!
What does this mean?
We'll be back in a minute!
Sorry, but we've got
an important guest coming.
I must welcome him appropriately,
without any distractions.
What will you do?
I'll go and take him back.
You shouldn't be there.
Do you accept, King Kara?
If we fight here,
you're not getting out alive.
I'm sure you know it too!
The only way now is forward.
Again... Why must you hate and fight each other?
And nothing else!
I've had enough of this!
Stop... stop bothering me!
Sakiya-kun, I need your help,
I need your power.
It's a lie!
"We'll keep you out of it."
"We'll keep you out of it now."
Isn't that what you said?
And yet...
you're the ones who started the fighting.
I knew you're the brains of that team.
I'm delighted.
It's up to what he feels and what he decides.
What we can do...
He's just a gutless weakling.
He's not worth risking our necks.
Glad to hear that.
If so, why don't you just give him back?
Oh? So you crave his power that much?
Cowards and weaklings flock together.
Don't make me laugh!
It's for Jyukuro.
Do you think your flame
will be the best out there forever?
What was that?
Again... They have to fight.
I can't do it!
I can't be the one...
who ends it!
Where are you going?
All on your own—how unfriendly!
Stop it, Mizusawa!
Get away from him!
He... He...!
Enveloped in the soft light,
you try to shut yourself away.
Don't be stupid!
Are you also following him, Mizusawa?!
Of course I am.
I promised Ryosuke to be his friend.
Let me go...
Who knows what'll happen to you
if you follow me!
Ryosuke, your perception of this world
is different from ordinary people's.
In your eyes,
I can only see the things you hate.
It must've been tormenting you
for a long time.
But there's something else I want to see there,
other than your gripes.
You can look deep inside me.
If you don't believe me,
you can drag me down with you.
But I want you to never give up
looking at the world
with your own eyes.
Why?!
Why'd you go this far for me?
Is it because they ordered you to?
If you're following such a dangerous order,
you really are out of your mind!
I'm not following orders.
There's only one promise I made to Shinobu that I have to keep.
It's that I won't die.
The Demonic Ones eat the people.
The Celestials Ones eat the demons.
And fight them too.
We are the Celestial Ones.
Will you still run away?
From this power?
From yourself?
Can you?
To accept that destiny is Shinobu's job.
Because no one can run away from himself.
He needs you, Ryosuke.
Not as the blade that breeds conflict,
but for your true strength.
Do I... Do I really have it in me?
It's fine now...
Staying here...
Is good enough.
Sakiya-kun!
Sakiya-kun...
Don't forget.
You're actually all on your own.
I don't want Sakiya-kun
to expose himself to danger.
But...
I don't want Sakiya-kun
to be no longer able to smile even more!
So you have awoken?
Good morning!
It's time for the weather and news
first thing in the morning.
Then, allow me to start
with the weather in the Kanto region.
Today is expected to be generally sunny
and calm with no wind.
Precipitation probability is 0%
for both morning and afternoon.
10% after 6pm.
Welcome!
The heat haze of times immemorial
reflects the melody of the Milky Way,
The path you walk,
your gaze, yearning for eternity
My love, I've been waiting for you here
all this time, all these years
I'll be watching you from now on and forever,
just as if I'm we're snuggling up,
until the day you return to zero
The pure sunlight filtering through the leaves
divides the two worlds
Let the song of the soul resonate,
the flames of torn sorrow
O gentle times, when I entrust
my wounded heart to you
There are more important things than quarreling,
floating gently until the day when love comes around
My love, I've been waiting for you here
all this time, all these years
From now on, I'll be by your side forever,
just as if we're snuggling up
until the day you return to zero, and forever
Let's entrust the endless spiral
with the lost child's light
The shooting stars fill the night sky
Love comes round softly, just like a dream
I pray...
RAW
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkonius
Shinjinotikari17