It's scattered again.
I see.
Would you still like to continue?
No.
I'll walk my own path.
If that's your heart's wish...
A long time ago, there was a war that divided the heavens and the earth between the "Celestial Ones" and the "Demonic Ones."
However, 900 years ago, the head of the Celestial Ones, King Kara, sealed away the head of the Demonic Ones, Kunaki, by sacrificing himself.
The battle was stopped halfway through, and in the present day, King Kara was reincarnated as a young man, and the seal was once again
The heat haze of times immemorial
reflects the melody of the Milky Way,
The path you walk,
your gaze, yearning for eternity
My love, I've been waiting for you here
all this time, all these years
lifted.
I'll be watching you from now on and forever,
just as if we're snuggling up,
until the day you return to zero
Kiba.
Milord?
Maybe a bit of determination can bring this to a close.
I pray...
Yes, Shinobu-sama.
High School Aurabuster
The Awakening of Light
Part 1
For some reason,
you can't help but look at it.
You're late!
Sorry, Kisara.
What's your deal?
Why did we have to meet at a place like this?
Jyukuro... Look at me when I'm talking to you!
Huh?
Sure...
There's something special about him.
Yeah...
Don't you think so?
It's you...
What?
Young General,
we're at such a chic place, and yet you're scowling.
Is that alcohol?
You're always so overly serious.
I just can't stand sloppiness.
Please don't worry.
I'm sure you'll easily be able to tell from here.
Whether he is the one.
Is that...
Why don't you ask him directly?
Sakiya-kun, what's wrong?
What?
An earthquake?!
Keep calm, everyone! The Tokyo government is prepared for this kind of emergency!
Don't panic and stay calm!
Please evacuate according to the staff instructions!
Sakiya-kun!
Don't worry about me.
Just go, Ai-chan!
What are you saying?
I can't just leave you here!
Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
Ah... No.
Where is he?
Don't play with me!
We need to get him to safety first, Kisara.
Yeah.
Can you stand up?
Y-Yes...
Sakiya-kun...
It seems like you're in pain.
I'll walk you out.
So much for "grabbing lunch together."
You knew this would happen all along!
Sorry.
I'll make it up to you.
Damn right you will!
Even so...
They straight up attacked!
Have you noticed anything different
about your surroundings lately?
Anything different?
What happened at the towers—
did it have something to do with Sakiya-kun?
Ah, no. Most likely not.
Anything that's different now...
Does he know something about me?
I should've said it then and there.
I often see things that others can't see.
Every day...
More importantly...
What are you saying?
I can't just leave you here!
Pathetic...
Good evening.
What the hell?
I just keep seeing weird stuff today!
H-Hey...
Don't make a fuss.
It's your own fault for not noticing.
No, you did notice me,
but you decided to ignore me.
Don't you know how hurtful that is?!
You...
I'm Mizusawa Ryo-chan.
And what about you?
Sakiya.
Sakiya what?
Ryosuke.
Ryosuke-kun, then? Ryosuke-kun.
Still feels a bit stiff...
Ryosuke! Yes, let's go with just Ryosuke.
And you can call me just Ryo.
O-Okay...
It seems you've had quite the day.
Ah!
Wh-What is it?
You've got a fridge here!
Talk about luxury.
But no booze in it...
Well, whatevs.
Can I have this?
Huh?
Did you want it for yourself?
I didn't say that.
Do you think I'm a burglar or something?
I didn't say that either.
Are you scared?
Am I really that scary?
No... But you gave me a shock!
Randomly barging in through the window...
Oh, I see. That makes sense.
But you won't have to worry...
now that Ryo-chan is with you!
That's all I wanted to tell you.
Well, thanks for the water!
Oh? So he got in the way?
But he's merely a psychic.
He did it to not allow us to get closer,
that is clear enough.
I wonder if it's so...
So what do you make
of that strange presence?
If there's a chance that it's Kunaki-sama,
we can't ignore it!
Didn't I tell you to hold your horses?
You'll just get hurt if you take action on your own, kid.
It won't end well for you
if you get too excited.
Suguro...
Aren't you still one of the Three Demon Generals
who swore loyalty to Kunaki-sama?
Oh, so you didn't know?
Should we hammer this into your head so you won't forget, kid?
What was that?
How unseemly...
Kou?
You don't believe in the resurrection either?
At the very least, I have no desire
to take part in your childish quarreling.
I've had enough!
I warned you not to get ahead of yourself.
Don't cause any trouble, got it?
Who are you to order me around?!
Good grief.
What are we going to do about him, Maki-chan?
Oh, I guess it's the problem of a certain Takagi Fumihiko, the lazy son of this TV station's owner.
Hamaguchi Maki-chan, an unpopular idol,
has no interest in acting bossy.
Good luck.
I'm quite content with the spectator's role.
Ciao!
I wonder what'll come out
if you poke at the bush.
Good morning!
Oh, good morning.
Shin-Kichijoji Station
What's up? Couldn't sleep last night?
No, I wouldn't say so.
Shin-Kichijoji Station
Really?
Sakiya-kun, you're so brave!
Shin-Kichijoji Station
I still skip a beat whenever I think about it.
Outlet
It was a bit like a disaster film, wasn't it?
I-I guess...
To tell you the truth, I was thinking
that I need to be more dependable.
No way! What are you talking about?
You were doing great.
Sakiya-kun...
In that moment, you were thinking more
about others than about yourself.
It's because...
You're a kind person.
Maybe even too kind.
I wouldn't really say so.
Sakiya-kun!
It's him...
Please let me through!
Sakiya-kun! Sakiya—
Don't move, I'll make you feel good now.
Um...
Don't worry.
I'm used to dealing with this.
Just leave it to me.
How is it?
You look better already, Ryosuke-chan.
"Ryosuke-chan?"
Oh, did I get it wrong?
No, he is in fact "Ryosuke-chan."
So I entrust him to you! Farewell!
A-Ai-chan...
No! You can't move yet.
Just a little more.
Okay...
Ah, I'm Nanase Saeko.
Nice to meet you.
You can just call me Saeko-chan.
I can't answer yet.
Is that so?
We'll need to keep a close eye
on him for the time being.
That's that person's request.
Sakiya...
Ryosuke...
Should Suguro-sama order it...
Shall I go and confront him instead?
I would take the blame for you, Young General.
Miga, this is my own personal choice.
But it was also my choice
to dedicate my life to you.
You can use it however you like.
That is my only wish.
The only person who can truly peek
into your mind is Kunaki-sama...
Young General...
Sakiya-kun?
Ah... Ai-chan?
Why?
Why does it happen every time?
Whenever you're facing a difficulty,
you always try to shut yourself off.
It's like you're deliberately pushing me away.
N-Not at all! I just...
You just...?
I don't really understand it either.
Then I can't advise you on this matter either! Farewell!
Th-That's not what I mean!
But it's true that I don't understand...
It's him...!
Who are you?
Answer me!
You!
You haven't answered
Young General's question.
Hurry up and tell us!
Didn't I tell you you're safe with me around?
You're that guy...
So you didn't believe me?
That's so cruel!
Oh? Was there some danger?
Stop fooling around, Mizusawa.
Yay! Ki-san!
Another psychic?
So what of it?
Impertinent brat.
Ki-san, this guy is not your average
run-of-the-mill Demon.
I don't care!
I can't stand arrogant pricks like him anyway!
Ryosuke-chan...
This way. Quick!
Miga.
Ah! That girl sure is trying to cling to him!
Can I leave this to you, Ki-san?
You think I'll let you?
I'll make you pay
for your insolence.
It's no use.
Stop.
Don't you hear me? I said, stop!
What's your deal?
Why were those psychics protecting you?
P-Psychics? What's that?
I don't understand any of that!
Playing dumb, huh?
I've put up a barrier.
You...?
You think you can break that barrier?
Why are you interfering?
It's our job to help anyone
who the Demonic Ones are after.
Who is he?
Do you think I'll answer?
Even if you're about to disappear.
Or perhaps this is your way of alerting your allies?
Do you really think mere psychics
can defeat me?
He's not joking...
This guy really isn't your ordinary demon.
What did I tell you?!
Young General...
Miga?
Oh my! Did he leave the stove on?
Jyukuro!
Yes?
Young General...
I will always...
Will always watch over you...
Bastards...
Bastards...!
One of the Three Demon Generals...
I, the Flame General...
Am pissed off now!
He's not holding back.
That's true.
Stay under my barrier.
Why'd someone like him
appear here all of a sudden?!
No...
This needs to stop...
I...
don't want to see this!
Ryosuke-chan?
No way!
What?
Come here and open the window
and we'll meet and make a promise
The truth I saw in the corner of the classroom
There are also some real things I can't tell anyone
Searchin' angel night
Behind the door
The hidden love
Flyin' on flyin' out, it's awakening
Callin' birth of light
Only kindness
Will reach your heart
What remains the same as we grow up?
I wonder if the more I worry, the stronger I become?
Even if we're apart, we can just say
Things we know for certain
one by one with our lips
Feelin' future sight
The waves crashing
deep in my heart
Ridin' on ridin' out I call out to you
Callin' birth of light
Even sadness
will melt away in your eyes
Searchin' angel night
Behind the door,
the hidden love
Flyin' on flyin' out, it's awakening
Callin' birth of light
It's so dazzling
I can't look at you, only you
Feelin' future sight
Deep in my heart
The waves crashing on the shore
Ridin' on ridin' out, I call out to you
Callin' birth of light
Let's start walking
In the pouring light, you and me
RAW
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Darkonius
Shinjinotikari17