PRINCESS
Presented by Orphan Fansubs
The busy week is finally over
I watch the roadside trees quiver
I make every day count,
even when I can't see you
Now I'm on my own,
but I'm still holding on
To the smiles of that day
I look into this big blue sky
So that even when we're apart
I can believe in you, beyond the sky itself
Surely, it'll soon be sunny in your town too
Ladies and gentlemen, we are arriving at Tokyo International Airport.
Returning home?
Yes.
As for the reason, perhaps...
It was to meet you?
H-He's so wonderful!
Hey, let's get going.
Okay, Daddy.
You still have much to learn.
WEDDING
AIDA
Aida School
of Judo
Really, I'm so lucky. I get to spar with you right here, at your home dojo!
Next time they bar us from the school gym,
we'll gather here.
Talking during sparring might leave you with a bitten tongue, Yuya!
Aida!
Kumada-senpai, will you cut that out?
Really, what'd you expect,
grabbing her like that?
Yuya, damn you!
All right, all right! I get it!
That's what you get!
Don't give him a break!
F-Forgive me, Nonoka's brothers!
I won't do it again!
Seriously...
AIDA
It's been a long time.
Aida School
of Judo
Can't you go a bit easier
on me, Nonoka?
Tokugawa-kun, let's switch.
Okay.
Come now, Hashiba!
All right!
Yuya, Tokugawa-kun, fight!
Hashiba, your arms are so brawny.
Hold me closer, Hashiba.
You're disgusting!
You're so cold.
Hey! Don't come any closer!
Let's grapple on the ground, Hashiba!
What the hell are those two doing?
Since when did Japanese judo
become a slapstick routine?
What did you say?!
My gorgeous lady, please leave
these morons and join me for some tea.
Excuse me, but who are you?
Hey, hey, hey!
Outsiders aren't allowed
in our sacred dojo!
When I see my reflection in your eyes,
I think of Pierrot.
Hey, you!
With these supple hands,
you threw my heart to the ground.
I'll show you what it actually means when you're thrown!
What?!
What's wrong? Weren't you
going to throw me?
This man...
is very strong!
Hashiba, what's holding you up?
Just throw him already!
You piece of shit, take this! Now!
Yuya!
So fast!
R-Ridiculous!
No teeth at all.
So this is the best you guys can do?
Okay, I'll be your next opponent!
As you wish.
Nonoka-chan, do it!
Send him flying, Nonoka!
She did it! 18th strongest in Japan!
An Ippon Zeoi!
Oh man, that hurt.
You're as strong as ever, Nonoka.
Are you... Hajime-chan?
Nonoka knows him?
Ichijo Hajime, just back from the Netherlands.
I'm home, Nonoka.
That son of a bitch!
How many years has it been since Seichiro's passing?
Seven years.
Uncle Ichijo, we're truly glad
to see you again.
Koji-kun, Akira-kun, Satoru-kun,
you've grown up so wonderfully.
Seichiro would have been proud of you.
Nonoka-chan, you and Hajime are the same age, right?
Y-Yes.
I see. My, how big you've grown.
Uh... Right...
To tell you the truth, we've returned to Japan to visit his mother's grave.
For that... and one additional reason.
Ichijo Yuji is a famous judoka.
He's been heading the International Judo Organization in the Netherlands for years.
I think he was also the best friend of the late Seichiro Aida.
That creep.
I didn't stand a chance.
And what's worse...
Shit!
Hashiba, you're so beautiful when you're angry.
You're annoying me!
You're so cruel to me!
AIDA
What?!
Marriage?!
Exactly.
I am convinced that Hajime and Nonoka-chan must marry.
I-I have to marry Hajime-chan?
J-Just hold on for a moment, Uncle!
What do you mean by that?!
Actually, it was the last wish of your father, Seichiro.
Huh? Dad's?
My father wanted that?
Yes, it was on that day...
H-Hey, Seichiro!
Isn't this quite a pathetic sight?
Don’t talk, Seichiro!
Yuji, I have a request for you.
What is it? Ask me anything.
Please take care of them.
Seichiro.
Dad!
Koji, and the rest of you,
you'll only have Ichijo to rely on now.
Yuji, I'm especially worried for Nonoka.
Make sure that Nonoka
becomes your daughter.
I will.
Thank you.
Seichiro!
Dad!
When I thought about
what he said back then,
I realized that Hajime and
Nonoka-chan should get married.
I believe it's the only way I can
fulfill my promise to Seichiro.
Since then, my deceased wife and I have brought Hajime up in a strict manner,
to mold him into a future husband worthy of Nonoka-chan.
What do you say, Koji-kun?
If Nonoka-chan gives her consent,
I'd like to begin the preparations.
Only if Nonoka gives her consent...
Koji!
This is all such a bother...
Asamizo Private High School
Music Room
Shinobu-kun, you're good.
I-I'm sorry. Did I interrupt you?
Not really.
Anyway, did you need something?
Um... Yes. I guess I need your advice with something.
Advice?
Asamizo Private High School
So handsome!
Sorry! Uh...
Hi, sweetie. I'm here to see a girl named Nonoka.
Know where she is?
Nuh... Nono? Ah, you mean Aida-san?
Yes.
So that's about it.
If this continues, I might end up getting married to Hajime-chan.
And what do you want me
to do about it?
Do you dislike this Hajime guy that much?
I... No, not at all. Why would I?
Hajime-chan has been my friend
since we were kids.
Then I don't have a say in this.
Shinobu-kun.
Howdy, Nonoka!
I've been searching everywhere.
Hajime-chan! What are you doing here?
That's quite obvious.
I couldn't stand being away from you
any longer, so I rushed here!
W-Wait a minute, Hajime-chan. Stop!
Regardless, come this way!
Shinobu-kun, I'm sorry!
I'll see you later.
Bye bye.
Hajime-chan!
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Really, you can't do that!
Nonoka?
Crud. Why am I even hiding?
Hajime-chan, you can't just enter
a school that you don't attend.
But I had a good reason.
I want to be with you all the time.
Hajime-chan, please. Be more serious!
I am very serious.
Uh... Anyway... I meant to say...
Just forget it, we'll talk at home.
Please leave now.
Please leave!
You look even cuter
when you're troubled, Nonoka.
Hajime-chan!
Okay, okay.
I'll wait for you at home, Nonoka.
I'll take a shower.
Hajime-chan!
Jeez, that Hajime-chan...
Hey, Nonoka!
Yuya? You startled me.
What's the deal with that guy?
Y-Yuya, you were watching just now?
Yeah, I saw plenty.
Including how happy you looked to receive a kiss from him.
Yuya, are you jealous?
Wh-Where did that come from?
I'm just saying you act flirty when you're with him.
I did not flirt!
Oh yeah? Funny you say that
after looking so pleased.
That wasn't intentional.
And only because he's a childhood friend I haven't seen in a while!
Are you saying I can't be
on good terms with Hajime-chan?
I was just about to consult you about Hajime-chan.
I don't wanna hear anything about him!
Jeez, then forget it!
Yuya, you're an idiot! And I hate you!
Who's the idiot here?!
Damn it all!
I don't wanna go to practice today.
Whatever! I'll skip it!
Music Room
Shit!
Hashiba-kun seems rougher
than usual today.
Nonoka isn't here. Maybe that's why.
Nonoka... Dammit!
Kumada-senpai, one more time!
Ichijo Family Plot
Mom, I finally went to see Nonoka.
She's become a very cute
and wonderful girl.
Hajime-chan, Nonoka-chan's going to be your bride in the future,
so you have to be strong for her.
Come what may, you have to be able to protect Nonoka-chan.
Hajime-chan, that's all wrong.
That's how you do it!
Ouch...
Hajime-chan, are you okay?
Dammit... When I get big, I'll be stronger than you, and don't you forget it, okay?
Come what may, I'll protect Nonoka, Mom.
AIDA
Aw, I hope Shinobu-kun isn't angry.
And then there's that Yuya...
Aida School
of Judo
I knew it! But I...
I'll never consent to Nonoka
becoming someone's bride!
Couldn't agree more.
She's only 15 years old.
But perhaps we could let them
be engaged for the time being?
Koji, don't tell me you're okay with marrying Nonoka off!
Our precious Nonoka...
Look, you two.
I know exactly how you feel.
But think of everything Ichijo-san did for us after our parents died.
Nonoka's
R-Right!
Is that you, brother?
Nonoka-chan, let's go out and play.
Hajime-chan...
Oh! You're even more attractive in your pajamas.
L-Listen now...
By the way, Nonoka, where are we going to hold the wedding?
I suppose a church doesn't sound bad.
And then we'll have a wedding party
with over a hundred guests.
H-Hold on a minute, Hajime-chan.
I'm not ready for marriage yet.
I knew it. You're disgusted with me!
So that's how it is?!
No, I'm not, Hajime-chan!
Oh, do you love me then?
Huh? B-But...
But then, you should marry me, Nonoka.
I meant to say, give me more time.
Is there someone else you love?
Now that you mention it...
It seems like Yuya and Shinobu-kun couldn't care less if I got married.
Hey, Nonoka, what do you think about me, honestly?
I've always loved you,
ever since I was a kid.
And then, seven years ago,
my mother and father
told me that I must become a man strong enough to protect you.
So I couldn't think of anything but you ever since then!
Hajime-chan...
Nonoka, I will protect you!
You're mine!
Hajime-chan!
I'll never let anyone else
have you, Nonoka!
Nonoka...
Ha... Hajime-chan...
No!
After school, after it rained
When I opened the classroom door
To get my bag
That girl was there
Opportunities always come
When you least expect them
So I thank God
For letting me be here and now
HMPH!
My heart suddenly starts to race
After her finger accidentally touches mine
But I can't even bring myself to say
That I love her
And now my heart is racing again
I panic, my chest gets unbearably hot
But I still can't get a single word out
To say that I love her
Original Subtitles
Transcription
Translation Check &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Anime-Fury
Darkonius
Perevodildo
Collectr
Intrepid
ImAWasteOfHair
Anonymous