PRINCESS
Presented by Orphan Fansubs
The busy week is finally over
I watch the roadside trees quiver
I make every day count,
even when I can't see you
Now I'm on my own,
but I'm still holding on
To the smiles of that day
I look into this big blue sky
So that even when we're apart
I can believe in you, beyond the sky itself
Surely, it'll soon be sunny in your town too
Nonoka, I will protect you.
You're mine!
Hajime-chan!
I'll never let anyone else
have you, Nonoka!
No!
WEDDING
No, Hajime-chan!
Hajime-chan, no!
Nonoka...
Guess I can't do it.
You became so stiff,
I lost my motivation.
Jeez! Motivation for what, exactly?
Why, you...
Nonoka, you may say
I'm a little too pushy,
but I'll make you mine for sure.
Hajime-chan...
I had no idea
you were so well endowed.
Hajime-chan!
Oh, Hajime-chan.
But to be fair, I'm a bit attracted to Hajime-chan myself.
I won't lose her to Hashiba or anyone.
Nonoka, you're mine.
Nonoka, to the Netherlands?!
When he was still alive,
Seichiro used to say,
"Nonoka-chan is
an outstanding athlete."
Nonoka's gifted, all right.
We all know that. But still...
All I want is to develop Nonoka's potential to the maximum extent possible.
And to do that, I need
to take her back with me.
This time, I came to Tsuguru
intent on seeing a certain person.
I think of that person as my mother and can't forget her face,
although it's been close to thirty years.
You may say I'm a little too pushy,
but I'll make you mine for sure.
Okay, next fragment. Aida.
Aida!
Y-Yes, sir.
Shinobu-kun...
Page 97, line 6!
H-Hajime-chan!
Hi, Nonoka.
Y-You!
Please don't mind me. Continue.
Hajime-chan...
Come on, we need to have a talk!
Jeez, what do you think you're doing?!
Didn't I tell you not
to come to my school?!
What a cold thing to say to your fiancé.
M-My fiancé?
See? You shouldn't lie to yourself about your feelings.
Those who love each other
always want to be together.
Wait a minute, Hajime-chan.
Here, Nonoka, the proof of my love.
You're at school.
We can't let an outsider come in
and trample on public morals.
Shinobu-kun!
H-Hold it... No...
I love Nonoka.
If you also love Nonoka,
you can try for her here and now.
Huh? Shinobu-kun...
I'm a full-fledged human
who uses reason and logic.
I won't be lumped together
with an animal like you,
who lets his instincts run rampant.
My, oh my. I've been told off.
Shinobu-kun!
Shinobu-kun doesn't care
if I stay with Hajime-chan.
Now, Nonoka, where were we?
Knock it off!
Hi, Nonoka!
Hajime-chan!
Nonoka, you're the cutest one there,
you know that?!
But when spring comes...
Hi, Nonoka.
This is definitely not a place
you can enter!
Bucket: For Bathroom Use
Hashiba-kun still hasn't
regained his cool.
Shit!
Kumada-senpai, one more time!
W-Wait!
I get it already!
Nonoka!
No!
Nonoka, there's no need
to be shy, my dear!
It's him!
Nonoka!
Hajime-chan, I'm fed up with this!
Jeez!
Now, Nonoka, why don't you give me a passionate one?
N-No, Hajime-chan!
Hey, you!
Oh? You're that judo amateur,
Hashiba-kun, right?
What?
Hashiba-kun, why don't you step aside from there?
Nonoka and I have something to discuss.
Like hell I will!
Oh, scary.
Yuya!
Wanna settle it in battle?
Fine. I'll take you on.
I take it you do realize
there's no way you can win?
What?!
Yuya!
You've gotta be stronger than that
to be able to protect Nonoka.
What a pity, Hashiba-kun.
It seems you're not qualified for it.
Nonoka, let's go.
Yuya.
Won't you try to stop me either?
Now, Nonoka...
Shit!
Nonoka-chan?
Nonoka-chan!
Nonoka-chan, are you listening?
Nonoka, I admit to overdoing it a little.
I'm sorry.
So please don't be upset anymore, okay?
It wasn't your fault.
Just...
Hajime-chan?
I want you to understand
that I really love you.
I don't want either Shinobu or Hashiba to have you.
H-Hajime-chan!
I'm going home first.
You can take your time.
Hajime-chan can say right out loud that he loves me.
But not Shinobu-kun or Yuya...
AIDA
Aida School
of Judo
Betrothal ceremony?!
Nonoka's going to the Netherlands?!
Ceremony? The Netherlands?
Don't tell me you've approved it too, Koji!
Why didn't you refuse outright?!
Koji, don't you love
our little Nonoka at all?
How can you live with yourself,
knowing you let Nonoka get away?
Not on my watch!
I will never agree to that!
Never!
No! No! No!
Shut up!
I do love our Nonoka. I don't want anyone else to have her either.
I would never have approved of her going away.
Th-Then...
Why?
This is Nonoka's life, not ours.
Nonoka needs to decide for herself!
Softness overcomes hardness
Nonoka!
Koji!
Nonoka, did you overhear us just now?
Nonoka, you don't have
to go anywhere.
We'd much rather
you stay with us forever.
That's right. There's nothing special about going abroad.
But the Netherlands might just be good for me...
Is that true, Nonoka?!
At last, Nonoka!
Let's go to the Netherlands together!
Nonoka-chan, I'm also delighted to hear that.
It has long been my dream that...
you unite with Hajime and
become my daughter-in-law.
U-Um... Uncle Ichijo...
Then it's settled.
Let's not waste any time.
We'll exchange the betrothal gifts tomorrow, Nonoka.
Yes, that sounds good.
Right, all's well that ends well.
Aida School
of Judo
Wait for me, Daddy.
Aida School
of Judo
Now what?
Asamizo Private High School
Won't you try to stop me either?
Hashiba!
Wh-What?!
UGH
Hashiba, you've got to do something!
If you don't, Nonoka will end up
going to the Netherlands!
Huh? The Netherlands?
I've been waiting for you, Oda-kun.
Why?
When I called your house,
they said you hadn't returned yet.
What do you want?
I'll cut to the chase.
Nonoka's betrothal ceremony is tomorrow.
Her partner is Ichijo Hajime-kun,
the son of our family's benefactor.
Shortly afterward, she'll move
to the Netherlands.
So what of it?
Nothing. I simply wanted you to know that, just in case.
After all, you've always been protective of Nonoka.
I don't see how it concerns me.
So long.
Oda-kun...
This discussion is over.
AIDA
An exchange of gifts,
and then a wedding, huh?
Oh, whatever! Que sera, sera.
Besides,
there's nothing wrong
with Hajime-chan.
And he's said countless times
that he loves me.
But...
Mother, I'll succeed in keeping my promise, it seems.
We are extremely grateful
to everyone gathered here today.
Let's leave the formalities aside
and proceed straight to the exchange
of betrothal gifts between
the Ichijo and Aida families.
These are our betrothal gifts to you.
Please accept them.
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
Gifts
Betrothal
Money
May they serve you for years to come.
Nonoka...
I...
Hold it right there!
Yuya!
Who are you?
You say only a strong man can protect Nonoka, right?
Yes.
Then grant me one more chance to prove myself.
If you win this duel, Nonoka is yours!
Very well.
Hajime-chan. Yuya.
Begin!
Out of bounds!
I absolutely can't afford to lose this.
For Nonoka, and for me.
Hashiba, you'll never understand
how much I've thought about Nonoka for these last seven years.
I'll never lose to you.
Begin!
I got you!
Damn it, this determination...
Out of bounds!
Lucky bastard.
Just as I thought,
Hajime-chan's too strong for him.
That was pathetic, Hashiba.
What was that?!
Oda?
Shinobu-kun?
He's anxious to win quickly,
so he rushes forward
at every opportunity.
Wait until he tries to grab the back of your collar, then counterattack.
Shinobu-kun...
Yuya...
Begin!
Yuya and Shinobu-kun
are both protecting me
like their lives depend on it.
Just like that boy did eleven years ago!
They both want to protect me.
And...
I...
Think I'll ever let you have Nonoka?!
This is the end!
Now!
What?!
Yuya!
Ippon!
I did it.
Yuya!
Did you see, Nonoka?
Shinobu-kun!
Aida School
of Judo
Shinobu-kun, thank you.
I didn't have a clue what to do next.
Really. My heart was in my throat too.
So where is he now?
Oh, he returned to the Netherlands,
but he promised that he'd be back.
Crap, what a persistent bastard.
By the way, have you
thanked Shinobu-kun?
Doncha worry!
I couldn't have won
without him back then.
Right.
Music Room
Shinobu-kun?
Hi, Nonoka!
Hajime-chan...
Y-You again?!
Told you I'd be back, didn't I?
Well, I'm back, Nonoka.
Oh... Hajime-chan, you nutcase.
After school, after it rained
When I opened the classroom door
To get my bag
That girl was there
Opportunities always come
When you least expect them
So I thank God
For letting me be here and now
HMPH!
My heart suddenly starts to race
After her finger accidentally touches mine
But I can't even bring myself to say
That I love her
And now my heart is racing again
I panic, my chest gets unbearably hot
But I still can't get a single word out
To say that I love her
Original Subtitles
Transcription
Translation Check &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Anime-Fury
Darkonius
Perevodildo
Collectr
Intrepid
ImAWasteOfHair
Anonymous