Orphan Fansubs presents
The Calling Dragon
Soaring Dragon Chapter
That's it. Chanta Sanshoku Dora 1, 8,000 points.
Hey, how 'bout we do
an uma this last round?
How's 2,000 sound?
The difference's at 70,000 now.
You'd need to win two yakumans for that.
All right. I'll take that.
Kan.
Pon.
Pon?
Tanyao Toitoi, perhaps.
Kan!
Tsumo.
C-Calling Dragon?
South fourth, all last.
Dragon's hand was Tanyao Toitoi
Sanshoku Doukou Sankantsu Rinshan Dora 9.
With so much han, it fetched 46,000 points, with one honba.
And then, seven honba.
Pon.
Quit messing with me! Take this!
That's where the last pei is.
Ain't the fourth one gonna be his draw? That ain't good.
Hurry up and play.
My time isn't yours to waste.
Sh-Shut it!
B-Boss!
You fool! A cheap trick like that doesn't deserve to be called cheating.
Calling Dragon, I was looking for you.
For me? Let go of his hand
and maybe I'll hear you out.
Ron.
You said that you hate the Yakuza.
But being a pro gambler is even worse.
The Yakuza don't deceive other Yakuza.
But for gamblers like you, it's a way of life.
They're lower than dirt.
Well, maybe once you're in front
of the president, you'll learn to stay in line.
Dragon, take off your sunglasses.
And put out your cigarette.
Won't you give me the ball?
Hey.
Y-Yes, sir!
Thank you.
I gotta go, little missy. We can play some more once the grown-up talk is over.
Hey, Murota! You came by yourself?
Where's your boss, huh?
I see. So his wife's in the hospital?
That's tough for both of them.
But she was taken in by ambulance?
In that case, it must be serious.
Guess Kawachi's gone soft.
His wife is more important now
than a promise between bosses?
Shouzou! One's wife takes precedence.
My apologies. Once my boss is done with
the formalities, he'll come here immediately!
Murota, that's enough.
More importantly, hurry up
and call in the Dragon.
Yes, sir!
Hurry up and greet the president!
Cretin!
Kneel down and pay your respects!
It's fine. No need for greetings when we're about to face off.
You know what they say: might makes right.
Don't they, Calling Dragon?
Tsumo.
Pinfu Itsuu.
That was too quick, Shouzou.
I was about to get a yakuman.
That's quite the joke, President.
It's your turn.
Oh, my bad.
Tsumo.
Pinfu Itsuu.
Another quick win, huh, Shouzou?
You'd better watch out.
Next time, I'll get my yakuman.
Tsumo.
Tanyao Iipeikou.
2,000 all.
Aren't you supposed to be a Yakuza?
What did you just say, young man?
Isn't it considered shameful
for Yakuza to deceive others?
Why don't you take those sunglasses off?
Looks like the fun and games are over, Shouzou.
Guess I'm losing my touch. Didn't think I'd be caught by a kid, of all people.
Hey, not bad, kid.
Now...
It looks like Murota didn't even notice.
No offense to you, though, Murota.
He was putting his winning tile on top of the wall and switching it out.
How about that kid, huh, Shouzou?
I want him.
President, it's been so long since I met a guy that I absolutely have to get my hands on.
Shouzou, I'll give him to you.
Refine his skills.
Understood.
The Calling Dragon, huh?
Hey! Boss Kai has called for you. Come back!
If he needs something,
he can come to me himself.
What was that, you jackass?!
Hey! Dontcha lay a finger on him.
That guy is mine.
I'm feeling great today, little missy.
I'll play ball with you until you get sick of it.
Okay!
Dragon, guess I've come to you,
just as you asked.
All right. I'll hear you out.
Gangster Blood Feud
At that time, war was threatening to erupt in the east.
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Gangster Blood Feud
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Gangster Blood Feud
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Gangster Blood Feud
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Gangster Blood Feud
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Gangster Blood Feud
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
Influential
Sakurado Gang
Mobilizes
A member of the Shimazu Syndicate,
a part of the Oudou-affiliated Kai Group, was stabbed to death.
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
The assailant was M from the Miyoshi family, a rival of the Oudou Syndicate.
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Gang member Morita
brutally murdered on street!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
It goes without saying
that the Oudou Syndicate
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
immediately retaliated
against the Miyoshi family.
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Retaliation by the Sakurado-
affiliated Kai Family?
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Miyoshi family executive Takada (38)
shot dead at mistress's house!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
The Oudou Syndicate boasts of having forces throughout the entire Kanto area.
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
Murder in broad daylight!
Assistant to Miyoshi family
lieutenant Ishii (41)
shot dead!!
Miyoshi family suspect Morita (22)
It is the most widespread crime syndicate in eastern Japan.
That's what being a Yakuza is all about.
If someone hits you, you hit them back,
several times harder.
I'm not here to listen to your bragging.
Stop wasting my time.
I'm quite certain you have it in you-
what I'm looking for. That's a big deal.
You're mine, Dragon.
Sorry, but I answer to nobody.
I'm not anyone's property.
Dragon, I'm carrying the burden
of 2,000 Oudou and Kai members
on my back, you know.
So?
Stop making fun of me.
I need to set a good example for them!
Shouzou, how did that dispute with the Miyoshis turn out?
They're as good as dead! If we keep it up,
they'll be completely wiped out by next week!
Now's the time, Shouzou.
You need to stop.
Huh? B-Boss!
It seems that the Miyoshis are getting the western syndicates involved.
If the east and west go to war,
there'll be no end to it.
It's time, Shouzou.
Understood.
Hey! I'm getting off at the next exit.
B-Boss, this is insane!
You can't go walking out alone right now!
I need to tell the car in front.
I don't care. I'm getting off.
I can win with that one.
What the hell are you talking about?
Shit!
That's pretty nasty, isn't it?
The boy over there playing like that.
Chii.
No matter how much manzu he has,
a third one is unlikely.
Take this!
You're naive.
H-Huh?
Who the hell is this guy?
MAHJONG
Dragon.
Oh? The fuck was that sound?!
Gunshots?
Huh? Hey, what'd you just play?!
Ron.
Dragon!
D-Dragon!
Give me your luck!
Give it to the boss!
Wh-What was that?!
Dragon went with Miyoshi?!
Where? Where the fuck are they going?!
Mahjong Club
Peaceful
I run a gambling den for the Miyoshi family.
I've heard the rumors
about you, Calling Dragon.
Apparently, you're a pretty good gambler.
But rumors aren't always true.
Seeing is believing, they say.
You know what I mean?
Let's play just one game. I want to get this over with as soon as possible.
Really?
Pon!
Got no time for a kan... with that 6-sou?
It's ron.
Chinitsu Toitoi Tanyao.
So you're Miyoshi-san?
Looks like the cat was out
of the bag from the start.
Now that I've seen it, I believe it.
You really are an amazing gambler.
Don't take this the wrong way, Dragon.
It just so happens that this parlor
is one of the boss's hideouts.
That's all there is to it.
Don't get cocky.
I'm getting used to the Yakuza's idea of entertainment.
Wh-What?
What was that sound?
Probably just some punks
getting into a fight.
Nobody knows that I'm here.
Come on, let's resume the game.
Going for suukantsu, huh, Dragon?
Like that'll ever happen.
Riichi.
Well, now!
K-Kai! You're supposed to be dead!
As you can see, I lived. And indeed, I'm as alive as ever! I'm immortal!
Long time no see, Dragon.
You know him.
Dragon, I was able to find
Miyoshi here, thanks to you.
I'm truly grateful.
I don't need your thanks.
Just call off the dogs that keep following my every step, and we're square.
You haven't changed a bit, my boy.
Oh! Pardon me butting in.
I didn't mean to interfere while you're in the middle of a game. Please go on.
I believe it was your turn?
Sh-Shithead!
Kan.
Dragon, you're just one step away from suukantsu!
Motherfucker!
Now then, it seems it's Miyoshi's turn.
Hurry up and draw!
Kan.
It's over.
Dragon! Where are you going?
The game's not over yet!
You forgot the rinshan tile!
Listen, keep your eyes on Dragon
at all times, got it? He's my treasure!
I won't die before I get
my hands on that guy!
The fact that Kai Shouzou of Oudou's Kai Group assassinated Miyoshi himself
sent a shockwave through the underworld.
It showed that the Oudou Syndicate was a force to be reckoned with.
But more importantly, it was an exclamation
that put Kai Shouzou's and
the Kai Group's names on the map.
Meanwhile, the Miyoshi family, which had lost its leader,
was on its last legs.
Their destruction was inevitable.
Due to Kai's actions, the conflict came to a tentative end.
However, as time passed,
unsettling noises seemed
to start breaking the silence.
Don't think I've seen him.
He's probably never been here before.
Silk Hat
Fuck if I know. We've not seen him lately. No, it's the truth!
I don't know.
I really know nothing!
When I woke up this morning,
he was already gone. That's all I know.
I should be the one asking you.
Where is he?
Will he ever come back to me?
It's useless, Dragon.
You can't get away from me!
Just you wait, Dragon.
I'll be seeing you real soon!
Inn
A-Are you sure?!
There's no mistaking him.
It's the Calling Dragon.
You can't forget that irritating face of his.
Th-The Calling Dragon!
But why is he playing in a place like this?
Riichi.
D-Did he just riichi?
Dragon declared riichi!
N-Now that I think about it,
he hasn't called even once yet!
Riichi Ippatsu Menhon Honroutou Chiitoi, b-baiman!
Restroom
Th-The Calling Dragon? There's no way!
Why's he in a gambling den like this?
I've got no idea either,
and it's creeping me out!
And it seems like the Oudou gangs are always on his tail.
The Oudou gangs?
Listen up! You absolutely must not lose.
Underestimating the Yakuza is a surefire way to die!
What's wrong? Your hands are shaking.
Shut it!
Kan.
The bastard. He started moving.
He started moving...
Waiting on a fanpai?
Or is it a 123 Sanshoku?
Pon!
What a pity, all four are visible.
That means it's not a sanshoku.
Not an itsuu, so it's either a chun or a hatsu.
You're the Calling Dragon, aren't you?
Why'd you come to this backwater den?
You're not gonna find anything worth your while out here.
Kan.
I just felt like it.
Calling Dragon, can I ask you one more thing?
Why haven't you called before?
If the rumor's right...
D-Did you say Calling Dragon?
I-It can't be true! Prove it!
Riichi!
Kan.
I feel like my life grows shorter
every time I call.
Just one call should be enough against you guys.
Sanankou!
Sanankou and Sankantsu!
On that day, Dragon glided deftly through the silence.
It was as if he had abandoned
his fate to the flow of time itself.
Dragon, I've been waiting
for you to come out.
That was quite a long game.
Did you have fun?
Dragon, stab me with this. Here.
You weren't trying to run away while I was gone, were you?
Now come! Hurry up and stab me!
I wasn't running away from you.
I just felt like going out.
Dragon, I've had just about enough of playing this cat-and-mouse game with you.
Isn't it about time to settle this
once and for all?
Dragon, have a match with me.
A match to end all matches.
If I win, you're mine.
If you win, you can take my life
and do whatever you want with it.
Dragon! If you're a man, then put your life
on the line and come at me!
Come and put your life on the line!
"Come and put your life on the line?"
Really now, Shouzou?
Did you seriously expect him to come here
just because of those words?
He'll come. I know he will.
Dragon's mahjong isn't half-hearted.
He's always gambling with his life.
I guess it's just his bread and butter.
It's in his blood, even.
He knows that fighting is the only way
he can continue to exist.
Snack Yukie
He's going to keep fighting
until it finally destroys him.
Snack Yukie
Because that's his destiny.
That's just how Dragon is.
Dragon... You're late.
The passage of time
means nothing to me.
The first round began under
the strangest of circumstances.
Pon.
Dragon, your playing style's unusually fast.
Apologies, that's a pon for me.
Shouzou, now you're calling too?
It sure is a strange evening.
Pon.
A battle of pons! How fascinating!
Maruko, did you teach Shouzou this tactic?
If you want to catch a tiger,
you have to enter its den.
Seems like you could've made daisangen, Dragon.
Tenpai.
It looks like you're out of luck today, Dragon.
Chii.
Pon.
Ah, 2,000, 4,000.
Dragon, you're going to lose today.
The heavens are on my side!
Chun. Honitsu!
Mahjong
..........841
There was no doubt that Kai Shouzou
had the heavens on his side that night.
It was as if he was drawing tiles at will.
Pon.
Shouzou, are you okay?
You're sweating a lot.
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
I just got a little scratch that's itching...
I'm taking this pon, Dragon.
I'm going to win this game, Dragon.
You're already mine!
What's wrong, Dragon?
Can't decide what to play?
Or is your hand too messed up?
Chii.
A closed 7-pin wait.
Is that chii really a good idea, Dragon?
You can't win unless you get a haneman direct hit or sanbaiman tsumo.
I'm not stealing tiles with my calls.
I'm imbuing them with life.
Stop meddling in my affairs.
Another 7-pin.
What is Dragon waiting on?
Could he have another 7-pin wait?
That would be...
I'll be fine. I'm in luck today!
The heavens are on my side!
Shouzou!
What's wrong, Shouzou?
I-It's fine.
Please sit down.
Dragon!
It's do or die!
It's over.
Dragon...
Hey, Dragon!
Shouzou! H-Hey!
What a wonderful victory!
Hold it, Dragon.
You still have one matter
to settle, remember?
A promise is a promise.
Take my life!
Not so fast, Dragon kid.
If there's a shred of humanity left in you,
how can you leave without even acknowledging Kai's words?
My poor daughter... Kai's wife,
She didn't tell anyone else, but...
A lead bullet was lodged in his lung.
It needs to be taken out as soon as possible!
However, he only has a fifty-fifty chance of surviving the operation.
He's absolutely refused
to have the operation!
If only you could see how bitterly she cried as she held on to me!
He only has three months left.
What Kai did was...
bet those three months on you!
Hey, pops, don't say another word.
You're making me look pathetic.
What's wrong, Dragon?
Hurry up and take my life!
Aren't you carrying the burden
of 2,000 people on your back?
Cherish that burden.
Dragon!
Ch-Chief!
Wh-What did you say?
The Chief was shot?!
Why didn't anyone protect him?!
Where were his bodyguards?!
Wh-What?! Kai was with him?
What the fuck was he doing?!
That morning, 36 of Oudou's upper leaders assembled in secrecy.
The pressing topic was
the shooting of the Oudou Syndicate president the previous night.
The meeting was chaotic from the outset.
The anti-Kai faction pinned the blame
for the incident on Kai.
They demanded that he step down from his position.
Kawachi Koichi, the leader of the anti-Kai faction, said:
So... how about it?
Should we hold a secret ballot to reach
a consensus about this incident?
Nah, no need for a vote.
I'm ready to accept the consequences any time.
However! I need to pay them back first.
Until I'm finally satisfied...
With those words from Kai,
the meeting was adjourned.
One week later,
a man's corpse was found
on Mount Takao, brutally murdered.
The corpse was identified as S, 36 years old,
a member of the Miyoshi family.
It was confirmed that he had shot the Oudou Syndicate president.
Whoa, I'll be taking that pon.
Boy, I hope that didn't affect you.
Kan.
Buddy, flip the new dora, will ya?
Oh, that's another kan.
Would you look at that?
Today's my lucky day.
Honitsu Toitoi Dora 4, baiman.
You...
Huh? Are you talking to me?
You're not in this for much longer.
Pon.
Look, kid, I don't understand you mean by
"Not in this for much longer."
But if you keep talking shit,
you're in for a world of hurt!
With it, the Sankantsu is done.
Huh? What'd you just say, kid?
It's a ron.
Ron?
You fucker, didn't ya just pon the 3-sou?!
Please stop!
P-Please!
Stop it!
The Kai Group, over 2,500 members strong, counting the low-ranking ones,
began a massacre under
Kai Shouzou's command.
Listen up! We're gonna kill every last one
of those Miyoshi bastards!
A dora pon. Not bad, buddy.
But there's a reason I discarded the dora.
It was for you to call it.
7-man, 6-man, and 4-man.
Are you going for fanpai, bud?
That playing style is naive.
Oh! Here we go! I really needed this one.
Buddy, this one will pass, right?!
Ron.
T-Triple?!
What the fuck were those discards?!
I went this far so that the president
would become the greatest boss in the whole country.
What am I supposed to do,
if... if he's gone?
What have I been living for
this whole time?
Please! Don't let him die!
I'd give my own life many times over!
Just don't let the old man die now!
I'm begging you!
For the first time, Dragon felt
a certain kinship with Kai's soul.
Mr. Toimen.
Earlier, you said that I'm not in this for much longer, isn't that right?
I'd really appreciate it if you explained what the fuck that meant!
You don't carry the burden of even a single person on your back.
Stop pretending to be a Yakuza.
Perhaps the true meaning of this phrase could only be revealed
to those who follow the path of destruction.
Ron.
It was as if Dragon could now hear Kai's cries clearly.
Give me your luck!
Give it to the boss, Dragon!
Hey, pal, discarding even the dora
for a pon on the chun?
Letting you call that chun was my mistake,
and you taking it wasn't very nice either.
I'm done, if you have the other 3-haku.
Tsk.
I can't play this one.
Pon.
D-Dropping a pair of dora?
Did he switch from a Pinzu Honitsu to a Tsuuisou?
That's it. That's gotta be it.
He has no dora, so he has a shanpon on the haku and a letter tile.
Tsk, but this guy smells of trouble.
I'm saved. I got another haku.
The tiles are coming one after another.
I'll go for an Iipeikou here.
Honitsu Honroutou Toitoi, b-baiman!
From that day on,
Kai Shouzou lived in the Dragon.
Mutual Aid Hospital
At the same time, Ishikawa Takashi,
the second Kai Group boss,
showed up at a hospital
somewhere in Tokyo.
Of course, he was there to visit
the Oudou boss, Sakurada Michizo,
who had been admitted to the hospital
as a long-term inpatient.
But for Ishikawa,
it was also part of the plan
to fulfill an important expectation
that had been placed on him.
You guys wait here.
Namely, that important expectation
had been the last wish that his predecessor,
Kai Shouzou, had bequeathed to him.
Nice work, everyone.
How about you let me in?
With all due respect, sir, this room is for Kawachi family members only.
No one is allowed inside
without the boss's permission.
Oh, really? I didn't know that.
I am Ishikawa, second boss of the Kai Group.
You still won't let me in?
Ishikawa, these will probably be
my last words, so listen carefully!
As long as the Oudou Syndicate exists,
the Kai Group will be its wall of iron.
The Kai Group is the backbone of the Oudou Syndicate.
Do you get it, Ishikawa?
Neither the Kawachis nor any other group can be that iron wall!
The Kai Group must carry
the Oudou Syndicate on its back!
The Kai syndicate is the iron wall
that protects the boss!
Hurry up and let me in already!
More aggressive calls, huh, bud?
You're gonna mess up
the flow of tiles if you do that!
Let's go with riichi for the time being.
Whoa! A ron!
When others get to tenpai, you gotta be careful, pal.
You could've held that 5-sou,
so why did you discard
that tile from your hand?
Weren't you going for pinzu? Let me see it.
Th-This guy, he held onto the 8-sou and broke off his 4-7 wait for a closed 7-sou one.
How stupid!
But why did he play that tile for me?
Now, now, it's been a while, Boss Kawachi.
You've been getting pretty full of yourself these days, Ishikawa.
The president's room is Kawachi territory.
It's off-limits to the likes of you!
I'll get straight to the point, if I may.
I was told by the missus herself
to come visit the president today.
Madam Sakurada told you?
Well, fine. Have a seat, Ishikawa.
Or should I say, "new Kai boss"?
You've received quite the promotion.
Now listen up, greenhorn.
I don't know what Madam Sakurada told you,
but only his closest officials
can see the president.
Well, no helping that, I guess.
It was decided at the executive meeting, after all.
You never received the cup of sake directly from the boss, either.
You see, in the Yakuza world,
you can only be admitted into the family
by receiving a cup from your superior.
Don't take it personally.
Get it, Ishikawa? You'll just have to work
your way up as the new Kai boss, bit by bit.
I understand.
I understand, but I'm not backing down!
In fact, I came here today
in order to share sake with the boss.
Until I share a drink with him,
I won't move a single step from this spot.
I-Ishikawa, what the...
Later, Kawachi's close associates revealed that at that time,
Ishikawa stood before them, looking as fierce as the yaksha tattooed on his back.
From his discards, this guy is definitely going for a souzu hand.
He's a man who'd hold onto the 5-pin the entire match.
He'd play everything except souzu.
All right, let's make these souzu shine!
I knew it. I knew it!
Riichi!
You can play anything but the dora indicator.
I got you now.
Kan!
A kan on the white.
But are you sure you'll play the souzu?
Those are very strong tiles.
You...
Huh?
You won't be winning
at mahjong any time soon.
Wh-What was that, you little shit?!
Shousangen Honitsu Chanta Dora 1.
Baiman.
W-Wait a minute!
Who the hell are you?
Dragon.
I-I see.
His souzu gathering was his last attempt
to counter my playing style.
In this all last, if I had played honestly...
But man, can you believe this?!
I've played against the Calling Dragon!
The Calling Dragon himself!
In a gamble, losing means death.
Continuing to win is life.
Kai Shouzou himself once said that.
And now, the Dragon once again renewed
his search for life-or-death gambles.
In the end, it truly was just in his blood.
It was his destiny, and he couldn't change it in a thousand years.
Until I share sake with him,
I won't move from this spot!
Kai Shouzou had left one last person for Dragon: Ishikawa Takashi.
It was then that the battle to decide their fates truly began.
Translation
Mahjong Consultant
Timing
Editing
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Eternal_Blizzard
Paul Geromini
Collectr
Eternal_Blizzard
anonymous