Maruyamakasa No. 1
Ishikawa!
Motomiya.
Motomiya!
If you're gonna shoot, do it!
Don't try me, Ishikawa!
Ishikawa Takashi and Motomiya Haruki.
The two of them used to be disciples of the Kai Group leader, Kai Shouzo.
They were close friends, raised together.
Kai Shouzo rose through the ranks of the Oudou Syndicate,
the best-known organization in the Kanto region, and eventually became its leader.
There was one man in this world whom Kai desperately craved to make his own.
His name is Dragon.
Dragon...
Dragon!
Give me your luck!
Give it to the boss, Dragon!
Shouzo...
Missus, I beg you.
Please take good care of Ishikawa.
With time, he'll be strong enough to carry the burden of Oudou's 10,000 members.
The only thing able to defeat him...
is luck!
If he had luck, he'd become a man who is second to none in Japan!
Enter Ishikawa Takashi,
underboss of the Kai Group.
Just as his predecessor did,
Ishikawa wanted the Dragon for himself.
Dragon...
You're the only one who kept refusing even Shouzo Kai.
But I, Ishikawa, will definitely make you mine!
If I had your luck, I could become the strongest man in Japan.
I haven't given in to your luck yet.
Furthermore... I'm not so foolish as to rely on the luck of other people.
Ishikawa killed all who dared to rebel against him: first Murota, then Kawachi.
The Oudou Syndicate was essentially his undivided possession.
That was when a huge castle wall
rose in front of Ishikawa.
Stationed in Kyoto, with all the Yakuza of Western Japan under his sway,
Kaitou Takeshi was there.
Kaitou's shadow
crept inside the Oudou Syndicate, unnoticed.
Motomiya-han, when my boss says something,
he means it. You can trust him.
When he takes control of the Kanto region, Motomiya-han,
he intends to put you in charge
of the eastern part of the country.
But there is one condition for that.
Ishikawa Takashi... He wants you to do away with that man.
I know you hate his guts too,
since he usurped the role
of Kai Group underboss.
So why don't you take that man's head
as a souvenir, to the delight of both you and my boss?
Of course, Motomiya knew that he was no match for Ishikawa.
Not because of a difference in organizational abilities,
but because of a certain "star" everyone is born under.
Ishikawa!
Despite that, Motomiya still wanted to fly higher than anyone else.
Motomiya, why won't you shoot?
Why aren't you dealing me
the finishing blow yourself?!
Ishikawa...
How long do you plan
to keep on humiliating me?!
Gimme a gun.
Hurry up and get in.
The rain keeps splashing water into the car.
Ishikawa! Hurry up and shoot!
Motomiya...
Boss Kai is crying in his grave.
Motomiya! Open your eyes!
You need to come to your senses.
Motomiya Haruki, 33 years old at the time,
went on his own to meet the don of Japan, Kaitou Takeshi,
but lost his life in vain.
The Calling Dragon
Flying Legend of Mahjong
Dragon Wolf Chapter
W-Wait a minute!
I'll pon that.
Thanks to you, I, the "Murderous Masu," am at full power now!
Kamicha buddy, hurry up and give me some good tiles, will ya?
Hey, bud, have you gone mad?
It's an overflown tile.
If you wanna call it, hurry up.
I don't know of any situation you'd discard a chun here.
What a bother...
You must have one hell of a hand.
Toimen, buddy, don't you agree?
Hey, what's the matter?
We're not done playing yet.
Wait a minute, won't you, old hag?
Long time no see, Motomiya.
Madam, I apologize for not seeing you for so long.
If I had known you were coming here,
I'd have sent someone to pick you up.
What are you talking about, Akio?
I've left those formal greetings behind.
I apologize.
Ron.
Back then,
my family used to say that
among the underground mahjong players, there's one interesting man.
Oh! Hey, lady,
that makes a pon for me.
That man's calls weren't like anything else.
When he would kan,
he'd get three or even four dora.
Hey ma'am, could that "underground player" story be about me?
Don't make me laugh.
Oh, really?
And even Sakurada ended every conversation with it:
"I want that man.
I want that man's luck."
I'll kan that!
Aren't you gonna call?
Why, you...
Kan!
My husband also said this:
"With that man's luck,
I could take over the world.
I'd take it over for sure."
That man goes by the name of...
the Calling Dragon.
I've heard that name before.
He protected my brother in his last moments.
Dragon... If I may.
Please tell me
about my brother's last moments.
Around 3:30 a.m., a shootout between rival gangs
occurred near the west exit from the Shinjuku station.
The target of the attack was the top executive of the Oudou Syndicate,
Ishikawa Takashi.
Ishikawa...
According to our latest info,
Ishikawa Takashi is currently unconscious.
Shinjuku Police Station immediately launched an emergency investigation
into the internal conflict surrounding the personal affairs
of the second leader of the Oudou Syndicate.
A-Akio... Don't tell me it was you...
That brat, Ishikawa Takashi...
killed my brother.
He left my brother to die.
Kan.
You're...
not in this for much longer.
Doesn't matter...
Dragon!
You truly are a symbol of good fortune.
Isn't that what Ishikawa said once?
Things turn out just as they should
when I'm sharing a table with you.
That's right.
That's right,
things will go smoothly now!
Dragon, thanks to you,
Ishikawa's lousy head is...
Motomiya!
Motomiya...
Dragon!
Hold it. You still haven't told me
how my brother died.
Some lives we wish to cherish, others we wish to discard.
Your brother
was looking for a place to die.
And so, the snow turns to sleet.
Then, before you know it,
it disappears completely.
Oudou and Kai are the two strongest organizations in Eastern Japan,
with undisputed mastery
over the Kanto region.
That makes the Kai Group,
with 2,000 men in its ranks,
the most important group in my organization.
Right. They won't tolerate anyone messing with their "night" businesses.
If you hit them, they hit back two or three times harder.
That's the Yakuza for you.
I'm not interested in listening
to your boasting.
I'm going home.
Wait, Dragon.
Come on, Dragon. You know I'll make you mine.
I'm quite certain that you have what I'm looking for.
After all, you're absolutely fearless.
That's an important gift.
But not as much as your extraordinary luck.
I knew it ever since we first met at the boss's mansion.
You're a monster that lives by fighting alone.
So? Why don't you become mine
and keep growing as a player?
It seems the boss also admires you a lot.
Sorry, but I answer to nobody.
I'm no one's property.
Dragon, I carry the lives of 2,000 members
of the Kai Group on my back.
What of it?
Dragon, you shouldn't humiliate me
like that with your rudeness.
I need to set an example for everyone, you know!
That encounter with Kai
came back to life in Dragon's mind.
Aren't you a Yakuza?
Hm? What'd you just say, kid?
Isn't it considered shameful
for a Yakuza to deceive others?
Why don't you take those sunglasses off?
Looks like the fun and games are over, Shouzo.
It seems I'm losing my knack, boss.
To think I'd be caught by a kid of all people...
Not bad, if I do say so myself, kid.
I'm not stealing tiles with my calls.
I'm imbuing them with life.
Stop meddling in my affairs.
Shouzo!
Shouzo, what's wrong?
I-It's nothing.
Please sit down and relax.
Dragon! Let's settle this!
It's over.
Dragon...
Dragon... Hey, Dragon!
Shouzo, what did you...
What a wonderful victory!
Hold up, Dragon!
You haven't forgotten about the settlement, have you?!
A promise is a promise!
You must take my life now!
What's wrong, Dragon?
Hurry up and take my life! Dragon!
Didn't you say that you're carrying the burden of 2,000 people on your back?
Cherish that burden.
Dragon...
I beg you humbly.
Don't let boss perish now.
All I've done up to this point was to expedite his ascent
to the position of the strongest boss in all of Japan.
You may claim my own life
several times over!
But don't let the boss perish now!
Please! I'm begging you humbly!
With your luck, I can become the best in Japan.
That day, slips of paper were distributed to Oudou-related organizations
and other influential groups throughout Japan.
Breaking
Off
Relations
Former Director of the Group, Motomiya Akio
It goes without saying,
this sent aftershocks throughout the Oudou Syndicate.
The news of the unexpected attack on Ishikawa Takashi
reached more than just his direct associates.
Even the top executives could not conceal their turmoil.
On that day, Motomiya Akio sent letters of condemnation
to leading organizations throughout the country.
That same day, a new emergency meeting was held with the direct executives
of the Oudou Syndicate.
At the meeting, in recognition of Chairman Yamauchi's role as acting leader,
Koizumi Yutaka said the following...
At a time like this, we must choose
a new leader as soon as possible,
in order to solidify the organization.
What the fuck?!
When our boss Ishikawa is on the verge of death, this is inappropriate!
Boss, something happened...
Sotoda, hurry up and return to your men.
Another one of your boys was found.
It looks like Motomiya did it.
A single piece of paper.
Yes, just a single piece of paper
turned that lone man into an instrument of revenge.
Motomiya Akio.
Ever since he was born,
he looked up to his big brother Haruki,
even though they were raised separately.
He was 15 years old when he drifted to Yokohama.
His brother Haruki was the only chivalrous man he had ever known.
The man who walked the path of battle.
Gun.
S-Stop! Don't shoot me!
I never wanted to shoot you.
Get away from the fence!
Say, bud, aren't you having fun?
Calling that chun and discarding the 5-man, 6-man, and 7-man,
but that's too obvious.
By continuing with that way of discarding...
you'll only hit the wall.
Another middle tile, huh?
What a brat.
Hey, kid. Is it just me,
or are you fucking trying
to make a fool of me?!
Okay, listen carefully.
You only made one mistake in your life:
bowing to Ishikawa.
Nothing personal. I need you dead.
N-No way...
It just can't be!
Th-That tile just...
Kan.
I-It shone.
D-Don't tell me... Y-You're the C-C...
Calling Dragon!
Yokohama
Shinjuku
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to hurry up and close the curtains?
Fucking hell... You ever gonna learn or not?
The sun is shining hard.
I hate getting up early.
My head is killing me.
Oh? Calling again, kid?
That was when Akio saw a vision.
I-Ishikawa!
First the ton, now a pon on the xia.
Say, kid, you're not waiting
on any more wind tiles, are ya?
I can't discard it.
He might have a Shousuushii.
Oh well, I'll content myself with a Chiitoitsu.
Hey, kid.
You didn't just snort and chuckle at me, did you?
I don't think you did.
Surely, you won't be making fun of me?
What?
B-Bastard!
Akio was still seeing that vision.
The man before him was definitely Ishikawa's projection.
Ishikawa.
You discarded a pair of nan and called a kan on the pei?!
H-Hey! What the fuck...
Akio, I want to discuss something
with you in private.
Not as the acting chairman of the Oudou Syndicate,
but as a simple man Yamauchi.
Akio, why won't you turn to me?
I don't suppose you've forgotten me already?
Me, Yamauchi Yoshikazu?
Now that I've met you, Akio,
I have something to discuss with you.
It's about your whole "condemnation" thing.
It was all the work of Ishikawa's Group.
I was opposed to it until the very end.
See?
Come on, Akio, try to take my place.
Akio...
Ishikawa...
Ishikawa!
Don't fuck with me!
You cheated, didn't you?!
Breaking apart that Shousuushii...
What was the reason?
It'd be a yakuman!
3-pin, no need for that ruckus.
He's not some cheapskate fraud
who'd need to cheat against you.
He's... the Calling Dragon.
Th-The Calling Dragon?!
3-pin, let me tell you something.
Do you know why he discarded the nan?
If he hadn't discarded the nan,
he would have...
dealt into my hand with the 9-man.
It's been a while, Dragon.
It's me, the Kai Group's lieutenant, Sotoda Yuji.
On behalf of my boss,
I came to take your luck.
Around that time, Ishikawa Takashi
was in a room in one of the hospitals overlooking the Shinjuku skyscrapers.
But presently Ishikawa cannot see that view or even catch a glimpse of it.
Akio...
Motomiya Akio's vision cleared up.
At that moment, Motomiya Akio's body was flying through the air.
He floated in the air as if melting into the azure sky.
Dragon, please accept this duel.
If I win, you go visit my boss.
In his delirium...
he keeps chanting your name.
Dragon, please accept this duel.
Please accept this deal to give your luck to boss...
I have no luck to spare for others.
Furthermore...
I'm not so foolish to entrust my life to my own luck.
You're...
not in this for much longer.
Enough prattling, Dragon!
Ron. Ryuuiisou.
Hurry up and start the boat!
Motomiya! Motomiya!
Motomiya!
Motomiya, you coward!
Come back here!
Come back!
Motomiya!
Dragon, are you gathering manzu this time?
The manzu just got harder to discard.
If I go for a pinzu Itsuu, the manzu will overflow.
I'll have to go for a manzu Iipeikou.
I'll try for pinfu!
Junchan, maybe.
Dragon!
Kan.
Tsumo.
Dragon, do you have a hint of humanity in you?!
A single man is now wandering through death, calling out your name.
Dragon... Dragon!
If you just said just one kind word to him,
that would be enough!
Dragon,
you want trouble with the Yakuza?!
All last.
Kai Group Lieutenant Sotoda Yuji
felt like he finally understood it.
Why does Ishikawa Takashi go to such lengths
to make this man,
the Dragon, his own?
It's not just for this demonic possession he has, his extraordinary luck.
It's because this man continued to fight despite terrible odds.
For this man, continuing to fight is the ultimate manifestation of life.
Wasn't it because to a human being, to a man, his way of life
seemed so pitiful and endearing?
Time flies, seasons flow.
Was it perhaps because he had seen the extremes
of living in such an all-too-common situation?
Hey, hurry up and play.
Time is not yours to waste.
Time flows, seasons flow.
And eventually, the eras change.
Dragon...
Dragon, it's a 1-pin.
Kan.
At that moment, a certain scene came to Sotoda's mind.
At the time, Dragon's toimen was Boss Ishikawa.
Kitajima was Dragon's kamicha,
and I was Dragon's Shimocha, like I am now!
Kan.
It's the same! Everything is the same
as it was back then.
The tiles Dragon discarded,
even the order in which he did it!
Dragon... You really are quite strange!
You discarded the same tiles as me in the last two rounds as well!
They're even in the same order.
Dragon!
Is it a coincidence, or is there some purpose to this matching game?!
Show me your hand!
The tiles one discards are the outer world.
The tiles in one's hand are the inner world.
One's insides are the one thing that can't be shown.
Dragon, I want to see those "insides" of yours!
Tsumo.
Dragon, I finally understand.
You're an incarnation!
An incarnation sent to me by a god!
Is it just a one-in-a-million coincidence?
Or could it be that he...
Dragon... Are you really
an incarnation sent by a god?
Or perhaps...
Perhaps...
That's right...
At the time, the boss discarded the 3-sou,
and the Dragon won off it.
B-But if something like that happens now,
it'll be a one-in-a-million coincidence...
I'll make it a Ryuuiisou.
If I don't make this Ryuuiisou, I have no shot at winning.
Sotoda! Put that 3-sou down! Discard the 4-sou.
Cut out the 4-sou and outwit the Dragon!
Aye-aye, boss!
Dragon!
Dragon changed his wait!
Oh, Dragon changed his wait.
Sotoda! Cut that 4-sou.
With it, make it a 2-sou and 3-sou shanpon!
Dragon changed his wait yet again.
Dragon... Dragon!
Are you really a god's incarnation?
Or perhaps it's a devil's, after all?
Wh-What did you say?!
Boss...
Died...
Dragon.
I came to claim your luck for myself.
Translation
Mahjong
Consultant
Timing
Editing
Typesetting
QC
RC
Raw Provider
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
Eternal_Blizzard
Paul Geromini
Collectr
Eternal_Blizzard1
ImAWasteOfHair
Uchuu
Colllectr
WOWmd