I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 8
Aww, it's Dieting Season Again
I finally realized it...
I've reached enlightenment!
If I eat and don't exercise,
I'll get fat!
Stretching to lose weight?
All right!
"You will see the result in 3 months?!"
I don't have that kind of time!
You gain weight because you can't think ahead, isn't that right?
No matter what read, it's all down to working out every day, it seems...
I didn't know which one to eat first!
Why isn't there some way to lose weight
by just sleeping or something!?
I'll say it:
you are secretly a supermodel!
Huh?!
Come to think of it,
everyone turns around to look at me!
Before I know it, I'm like super slim
and I look good in whatever I wear...
Koume, about your schedule for The Paris Collection...
What?
Wow, I am a supermodel for real?
Seeing dreams like that
is bit depressing...
Am I stupid?
Koume, you're trying to lose weight?
Yeah.
Look.
It's not like I'm trying to lose a ton at once.
But seeing all these,
I feel that I've gotta do something at least...
Indeed...
I've put on some weight since my college days...
Yeah, me too.
I used to be a lot skinnier.
Were you doing sports or something?
No, it was thanks to the magic water.
What!? You can lose weight
by drinking water? Was it Contrex?
No. You know, the one they put in the vinyl toys.
What? You are on a diet?
But you're not fat at all!
R-Really?
I think you look just right the way you are now.
Is that true?
Screw this diet, then!
Morikumi is cute, isn't she?
She is just my type!
Shoot... So Kei's type is this?
It never is easy, is it?
Ads of gossip magazines for women -
Confessions of infidelity
What happened to the passionate couple?
100 extreme office diet tips
they can be quite fun if you don't take them seriously.
What a load of bull!
I know what's in those magazines even without buying them!
"Losing 28 kg in 3 hours?"
How does that work?