I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - Eri Hara
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 1
A Serious Girl
Caramel Ribbon Co.
Good morning!
Oh, good morning, Koume!
Morning!
Good morning!
Chief, look at this new character I drew!
Okama-san, 42 year old,
ordinary office worker by day
Pit-a-pat...
Are you serious?
Chief, I made one too.
Wow, Kimi, it's so cute, I love it!
Have you already thought of a name in case we start commercializing it?
How should I name it?
It's a rabbit, so how about Rabbiko?
A good name must leave an impact.
How about Gero?
Huh? Why that and not Shou or Gin?
No, Koherekkerebi or Opipenipon is much better!
My oh my, you're both joking too much...
Serious
Then... How about Tack or Johnny?
How about Burubura No.2?
Celekencelemin? Chochorinagon?
This morning on the train, I ran into my hot junior high school senpai!
Huh? What was he like?
He was my first love.
I still carry his photo with me...
Show me!
Here.
Totally delinquent
Isn't he totally cool?
He's the squatting guy in the center.
A-And the blonde girl right next to him is...
Oh, that would be me!
U-Um... Kimi?
What is it, Nakatani?
Is it true that you were once a delinquent?
Oh no! How can you say that?
I'm too cute for that, am I not?
At best, I could steal a scooter and join a group ride, or break the school window...
Maybe even hang out of lowrider windows at night or participate in small-time cons...
Koume!
Good morning!
Good morning, Kimi.
I've got this for you.
What is it?
I thought you liked my senpai's photo, so…
I reprinted it in large size for you.
What am I going to do with this photo?
Keeping it is clearly out of the question.
Should I return it?
No! Get rid of it altogether, then?
Well, with my family, I can at least laugh it off, so I'll take it home.
Chief!
Yes?
Please take a look at my new character idea!
Drowned-kun
Pit-a-pat...
Do I have to say it?
We're looking for a more "cute" image.
A cute image?
What do you think?
Don't you think it's cuter?
Drowned-Chan
You missed the point entirely!
I meant something like rabbit or bear kind of cute!
Koume, look...
Yes?
Why did you choose
this fancy goods design company?
If I don't belong here,
why did you hire me?
No mutual understanding
Chief! Please take a look!
Pit-a-pat...
Drowned Pals