I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 4
Happy Cherry Blossoms Party
What fine weather.
It's decided! We'll shut the office tomorrow and go cherry blossom viewing.
Yes! Hooray!
Under a sakura in full bloom,
with freshly baked biscuits and milk tea in a pot...
I can't forget my friend Teddy, of course!
Just let me.
Just let me dream, okay?
Sorry I'm late!
I got held up in a traffic jam.
Traffic jam?
So you have a driver's license?
No.
Oh, so you took a taxi?
Did someone give you a lift, then?
I don't need any of that,
I'm good enough at driving as it is.
Hello, neighbor! It must be fate that we are sitting next to each other here.
You guys wanna drink with us?
Oh my, what's with the teddy bear?
His name is Teddy.
Right, I see. Little Teddy, drink with this old man, won't you?
Chief, he seems to adore Teddy a great deal.
That's right. An old guy like him can understand the cuteness of Teddy.
It's coming back up...
T-Teddy...
Enemy. Confirmed, old men are enemies.
Aye! God, I'm so drunk!
You gotta drink back everything you puked!
Yeah!
Say it with me! Drink up!
Those two are already wasted.
And it's still so early...
I suppose...
We're just starting to drink, right?
Oh? Empty already...
And that guy is taking his sweet time...
Ah! There he is!
Sho! What took you so long?
Yeah, sorry, I don't know the place, so I got lost.
This is the guy I mentioned the other day.
I'm Kinoshita Kei.
Nice to meet you.
Sup! Didja say Kei?
Alright, come over here and drink with us!
There's no stopping her any longer...
You were right,
I'm finally starting to feel somewhat drunk.
Hey, Kei! Drink up!
You don't trust my choice of sake?
Say, Kimi. Did you bring Kei to...
Yes, to introduce him to Koume.
I don't think she'll be in condition for introductions for much longer...
Wow, she looks so energetic!
You don't have to go that far, Koume...
That's right,
you won't have to dance around like that,
if you just drink normally, like everyone else,
until you can no longer tell the hot from the cold.
Whoa! This is wonderful! So romantic and fantastic, isn't it? Everyone!?
Enough! Cherry blossoms are falling!
So you know what that dimwit Tachibana did?
He just went and broke the guy's hand.
I'd do the same!
How are you doing, everyone?
I'm having so much fun!
Hey!
No one is looking at the cherry blossoms...
Earth is spinning!
The sky too! Make it stop!!