I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality checking - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 6
Boss's Favorite Things
So good!
How's your work?
Hm. Well, fine, more or less.
I was hired as a designer but all I do is serve tea...
Huh? That's my boss's job at my company.
Really? That's cool.
He must be a capable boss.
Well, not exactly that...
Here you go.
It's Earl Gray for you today.
Yes, thanks...
I think that's just what Chief Tanni likes to do the most.
Speaking of which,
we had a newcomer this year...
She brings flowers and makes cookies —
all to underscore her womanly qualities.
She'd be like "I don't know if it's any good, but please try it, everyone, I've put my soul into these!"
It's because of her that the boss now constantly pesters me:
"You never bring flowers and such."
Can you believe it? Boss picks on me just 'cause I ain't the same kind of person she is.
You don't really need to do that...
Look! Isn't it beautiful?
Oh, I brought some cookies too.
I'll share it with everyone later.
Sure...
I wish I worked at your company.
Huh?
It's impossible to concentrate
on my designing job!
Ah, I wanna design instead of serving teas!
Truth be told, my boss does come across as quite a sissy,
but he lets me do my job as a designer...
Rain...
Hydrangea...
There it is! Revelation!
Konjac-Chan!
What?
A willow...
On the other hand - frog...
Yes! I got it!
Egg and String-Chan!
Again... What?
But my designs just aren't good.
Maybe it'd be better if I was just serving tea...
Koume, Let's drink up!
Yeah!
Koume!
Tomorrow is the boss's birthday, remember?
Do you wanna go buy a gift for him today?
A gift, huh?
Hm. His tastes are a mystery to me...
How about a polo?
Sometimes, simple is good, right?
Yeah, I think he will like the pink one!
Good morning! I'm wearing it today!
A stiff collar and gold necklace!
A poach and brand belt!
Weirdly patterned pants and pointy white shoes!
That's our boss!
Second to none in his fashion tastes!
We got married...!!
I think he's yearning for this woman
he once knew.
I wonder if they were dating?
I thought he wasn't into girls.
That's no good...
That dress is such a kitsch.
If I were her,
I would dress more like...
I've long been wondering about the folders on his desk...
I wonder what it is...
What the heck!?
Is this a design of a dress?
Stop! Don't look!
I'm so embarrassed!
You peeking pervert!
Boss...
Don't look at it ever again!
It's my secret!