I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 7
A Woman's Sigh
So pretty...
I like the color of this lipstick...
Would you like to try it?
Sure!
How do you like it?
Looks completely different...
Right, I believe a darker color will suit you better...
Let me know if I can help.
Size 7... Huh?
Size 13
Maybe it's better that I just go home today...
Soul-kun
Listen, I think I told you this
like 274 times already.
Can't you come up with something cuter,
based off a cute little animal?
Yeah! I got one!
Look at this guy!
He is a chicken wing!
What...
Bear stuffed animals are hot on the market recently, so we'll make one too.
So I need everyone to come up with a design.
Okay!
What should I do?
Koume...
Don't you think there is something off about a bear knocking off a salmon?
Eh?
I feel down as a girl...
This pale pink is so cute!
Would you like to try it on?
Pale pink clothes make my darker skin stand out even more.
I even bought whitening creams.
It was expensive!
Your skin is nice and white, Kei!
But white skin makes my freckles stand out...
Don't be a snowflake!
I get freckles with darker skin, too!
It's just that you can't see them even if you wanted to!
I tried taking vitamin C too.
It was expensive...
Do you take vitamin C, Kei?
I only eat kiwis sometimes.
Assume a kiwi is 80 yen...
And a pill of vitamin C is...
I finally bought this newly released lipstick!
It looks pretty good on me and I'm happy!
Wow! I love that color.
Looks good on you!
Thanks! Wanna try it?
How is it?
But it's still just as frustrating to see that it looks better on someone else...
I like it! I might buy it too.
Ah, I didn't get enough sleep
and now I got dull skin.
There's nothing quite like sleep
for your skin's health!
Also, a massage to improve blood circulation.
Just a light press can make a big difference!
Hm?
Ah, right! I have a good concealer of Yves "Faint" Laurent!
Do you wanna try it?
Oh, I...
Should I comment on his joke?
My boss uses a concealer.
Concealer?
It's a foundation to cover
dark circles and blemishes.
Oh, maybe...
This?
A girl from my class gave it to me,
so I'm using it now.
Yeah, that's it.