I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 5
Go for it, Nakatani!!
I can't just watch her from the side forever!
What!? A high school girl?
I see her on the train every single day...
Forget about the school girls!
Besides, it's against the law!
I'm not going to force her or anything...
First of all, they're stupid, cruel, vulgar,
harebrained, and loud!
On top of that,
they have long arms and legs!
Besides, Nakatani,
I thought you had a crush on Kimi.
M-My chances with her are nonexistent...
Oh my, Nakatani!
Did you fall in love with a high school girl?
You need to be dressed to the nines, then!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
Wow! You look mind-blowing, Nakatani!
Good!
Good, right...
You know that the key to winning girls over is looking stunning, right?
Kimi, you don't know what you're doing.
Really?
His look screams "virgin" currently...
I heard your love story, Nakatani!
Please allow me to help you get dressed to the nines!
Wow! You look like a chick magnet, Nakatani!
Good!
"Good" again?
You can't beat this!
Fine! Today is the day!
Hey, Shiroishi! Morning!
You're early today, Miura.
That math class today...
It was the worst, wasn't it?
Damn right! That bald prick
suddenly gave us a test!
He pisses me off!
Yeah, you're right! Did you know that his wife was a former student of his, too?
What? Seriously?!
I'm telling ya!
I always knew guys with that kind of head were up to no good!
He is bald and fat!
And he's earning peanuts too.
I'll never date a guy who's under 170 cm,
fat, bald, or poor!
Agreed!
Nakatani!
Did you manage to talk to her?
No.
Huh? Well, that was completely natural!
Right. She's a high school girl, right?
After all, that's what all high school girls think, right?
Talking like that is a norm for them.
You should've heard
how I talked when I was in...
Ah! Enough already!
Let's eat!
This store make really good bento.
By the way, Nakatani's words say one thing about him —
he's an dimwit for judging women by appearance alone.
I can't just stand and watch!
This time for sure!