I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Translation check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 9
Here comes Takako!!
I'm home.
Oh!?
T-This is...
H-Here too...
Is it....
Welcome home, Koume.
Auntie     Momma
Hey! You're back at last.
We've started without you!
For some reason,
I just can't hit it off with auntie...
Auntie, what's this!?
It's convenient, isn't it?
Not at all!
I liked it the way it was!
I know she has no ill intent, but man...
I don't want it!
With a puppy on it, or without it!
Oh?
Do you have some tissues?
This is the last box.
I'm taking it.
Wait up, Koume.
Take my cover off before you take it.
Huh?
You don't deserve a cover on your tissue box.
What do you mean I don't deserve it?
No! So dirty!
I need some strong chemicals to clean it!
This one too!
When did you clean it last time?
I can't believe this mess!
When you spill something,
why not mop it right away?
Did you hear me?
I'll be back next Saturday
to wax the floor, so move everything up so that the floor is not obstructed.
Okay...
Auntie is obsessed with cleaning...
What's wrong, Koume?
My auntie is staying at my place
and she puts weird covers on everything...
Weird covers?
Right! She sews them herself with lace
on red gingham check patterns.
Ah, those are the worst!
I know, because I often make
woven accessory bags myself.
Satin fabric is the basis of handicraft, you know?
Koume? Are you there?
Hm?
Maybe it's about time you got yourself a proper chest in your room, don't you think?
I thought about it too.
But I haven't found one I like yet.
Don't tell me...
Lucky you!
I bought one for cheap!
I came to help!
She bought me the chest,
even thought it wasn't to my taste...
Now she also came to organize my clothes...
It's as if it wasn't
an hour-long journey for her.
She even brought her own food in tappers
and dust cloth for cleaning...
On top of that, look how happy she looks...
Just what is going on in her head?
Ah, she even put a cover
on the empty cookie can...
Are you really okay with it?
I can free myself from thinking about the interior design, if I don't have to clean up myself!
You wanna free yourself from it,
but what about me?
Animal print slippers...
Koume...
Look! I made you a cover for the phone!