I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Translation check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 10
Summer is here!!
Summer is here!
UV protection!
Sunshade!
Koume! Looking nicely tanned!
Did you go to the sea?
Wow!
Do you go to the gym, Boss?
Yep! Because you know,
when I go there,
everyone has such ripped bodies!
So I feel like I gotta work hard too!
Hey, do you think the boss is...
Ga...
Ga!
N-Nothing, forget it!
V! I finally got my bonus!
What am I gonna buy?
A bathing suit?
A dress?
A hat and bag?
Aww, but I want shoes too!
Thank you.
Huh? It's all gone!
Momma! I wanna ask you something!
When did you buy that AC?
It's your fault for leaving your card in the open.
I'm thinking of going to Hawaii for the Bon festival vacation!
Really? Hooray! Yeah!
Now, my passport...
I didn't book a room for you.
Eh?
Besides, how could you possibly afford it?
How could you afford it yourself?!
Come to think of it, my bonus
was more than the price of the AC...
I'll get you macadamia nut as a souvenir,
does that sound good?
Well, without a boyfriend,
it'd be a boring Bon festival vacation anyway...
Oh, what about Kei?
He's not into me, it seems.
Really?
So, you don't have a problem
if I make him mine?
Easy! I was just kidding...
This is where you're supposed to laugh!
Koume!
For the Bon festival vacation,
I'm going abroad with my boyfriend.
He will pay for everything.
He makes good money
and buys me anything I want.
He took me to a Sushi restaurant the other day
Koume's Dream Diary
Toro and uni were great!
He'll get me a boiled fugu next time.
That's pretty miserable, you should stop...
Which one should I get?
Oh! I already have this one!
I guess you should get the other one then.
That means we can exchange them later!
Uh... Okay
Lucky! I always wanted to look at that one too!
Welcome!
I can't get used to that part of him just yet...
Your total is 880 yen.
Thanks for tagging along.
I don't have the courage to go to the women's bathing suit area by myself...
Are you buying a gift?
No at all. You know, the men's suits are limited in colors, so I'll buy a bikini to use the bottom only.
Actually, I have some stuff to do today!
Excuse me? Can I have this one?
Certainly!
Are you buying it as gift?
Yes, of course...
Can I try it on?
Ah, I mean, my girlfriend and I
wear the same size...
Sir, that would not be possible...
No, then?
Chief... is terrifying.