I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 3
Koume goes to Tokyo!!
I've noticed this long ago,
our chief is kinda a pansy.
You're cute today too.
Boss!
Oh hey, good job.
Any questions on that?
Boss.
Are you an okama?
Oh my! Of course not!
Why did he pause?
Gee, why can't you draw anything better than that?
Can't you just draw something cute straightforward!?
Straightforward and cute?
Oh, like Yukhoe?
Yukhoe?
The yellow from an egg, red from meat, and green from green onion.
They make up the fashionable Rastafarian flag.
Should I fire her, after all?
Me? Going on a business trip to Tokyo?
I wonder if I can handle it alone...
You're such a hardworking girl, I'm sure you'll manage. Besides, it's just a simple meeting
Hardworking, huh?
Taking a break from designing more of those
will probably be good for her...
Plus, I can relax while she's away!
I'm going to Tokyo!
Ugh... People walk too slow here.
They don't even walk on the escalator?
They even obey traffic lights here!
I'm getting impatient...
It's no good. Girls need to smile.
Still, I'm getting nervous about the meeting.
Excuse me!
Are you with Caramel Ribbon?
Y-Yes!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Izawa. Thank you for coming.
Right, the pleasure is mine...
By the way, is it just me,
or is it a bit colder in Tokyo, after all?
You think so?
I'm just awful worried 'bout catching a cold!
Because I'm so nervous,
my Osaka dialect is getting stronger...
Have you had lunch yet?
Uh? No... Not yet.
She is with the company that coordinates our designs.
Nice to meet you.
Y-Yes! It is mutual,
This is nice that I was able to meet you...
By the way, how is your son?
Does he still need a lot of attention?
Need attention? Is he a cactus?
He's grown quite big,
but he is still a child inside!
Is your son a Konaki-jijii or something?
Kids his age "soar up" the moment you take your eyes off them, don't they?
Soar up? Is he a bird now?
Ah, it's so hard to keep that all to myself.
Would you like something for dessert?
I'll have a banana sundae.
I'll have a chocolate sundae.
Very well, I'll have a Beautiful Sunday then!
Oh? Is that on the menu?
Maybe I should take that one instead too?
Now... Where exactly is it on the menu?
I'm back!
Welcome back, Koume.
Thanks for your work.
Oh, I know what this "gokurou" is about!
It's those guys with punch perm and shaved hair, and tattooed backs.
That's "gokudo!"
This is it! This is the problem!
'Tis us, da women who 'ave to live with dis!
Da treasure of Japan, her pun comedy is dying!
Her dialect wasn't that strong before, was it?
I'll work even harder now!
And, I'll bloom money flowers!