I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 11
To the Sea
Seaside hotel
This year's company trip is to the sea!
Beni Azuma Sales Office
❌⭕🔺⬜ Corproration
Caramel Ribbon
Alright! We are here!
What's in this bag?
Is this your swimsuit, Kimi?
No.
Hey, Koume...
I think the bag where my swimsuit is
got mixed up with yours...
A flashy bikini...
A gold necklace...
And tanned skin...
His beach look is just as I imagined it...
I went to the tanning salon
right before the trip.
Wow! Cool!
Boss!
I just came up with an idea for the new character design!
What's that?
Yay! Yay! It's the beach!
Feels good, doesn't it?
I'm telling you!
By the way...
Where are you guys from?
Oh! We are from Osaka!
We are on a company trip now!
And you must be a student?
Yes, 2nd year in high school.
The sea...
I had a friend who died at sea.
My friend from junior high school.
He... sniffed glue,
got high and fell in the water.
Just be careful,
that area is rocky
and the tide can be quite rough.
Okay.
Hey, Koume?
How about a dare?
No.
Fireworks that Kimi prepared for us.
Firecrackers
It's not working...
What if I give it a try?
What? Why are you staring at me?
No! I...
It's not like I was wondering why you are good at handling fire
and why there are firecrackers among fireworks!
What?