I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
I heard high school girls
have cell phones nowadays.
Episode 12
Ah, high school girls... Kumiko's appearance
What for?
It must be for contacting
their sugar daddies!
Koume...
There, there, what is it?
Where is your mother?
Now, don't cry, little one.
What a kind girl she is...
Tsk.
Damn spoiled brat!
What the heck are his parents doing?
I'm hearing things!
She didn't say that...
No way she just said that...
I also heard high school girls have high-end brand wallets nowadays
What?
It must be their sugar daddies
who buy those for them!
Y-You're probably overthinking...
When high school girls are alone...
But as soon as they become two...
That guy is the worst!
I know, right?
Ever since I realized how they are,
I try to only fall in love with high school girls
who have no one else around.
So... You're deceiving yourself?
Cu...
Cute!
Now I'm seeing things too!
There's no way she would be wearing black underwear!
I can't just watch her forever...
Hey, do you wanna grab a tea together
if you have time?
Huh?
If it's on you, sure.
No!
Girls who follow guys so easily aren't the type I'm looking for!
Oh?
No way. You two know each other?
Hey, sis!
She is my little sister, Kumiko.
This is Nakatani, my coworker.
Hi there.
Still, what were you guys doing here?
Huh? Well, he was hitting on me, and...
No! I was just gonna ask for directions!
Jeez... I can't keep up this conversation...
W-Why don't you tell me
what kind of kid Kimi was?
Huh?
Well, she kinda killed frogs and stuff.
Kids can be cruel, you know.
And you used to bully our neighbor boy
all the time, remember?
Yeah, I sure did!
Ah! And remember that
when you were in middle school?
Oh, that that?
Wh-What's "that"?
Huh?
You know...
Ah! Never mind!
You look good!
I also wanna wear
something like that sometimes.
Then why don't you?
The men aren't fond
of these kinds of clothes, though.
I know.
The men who like these kinds of clothes...
"Why the hell haven't you baked and brought me
a single cookie yet, you woman?!"
They talk like that
and get mad at every little thing.
You must be overthinking again...
You're looking cute today, Kimi!
Are you also the type of guy
who sees a girl in a dress like that
and things she must bring you cookies and be obedient?
I actually prefer to bake them myself,
so not really.
That makes sense...
Ah! But wait...
Making them with my girlfriend
and spending time together should be fun too!
T-This guy...
never ceases to amaze me.