I'm ripe, C-B-A
A-B-C,
Which way do I start?
Hold up, let's wait till my heart is ready to go
Here Comes Koume!!
Translation - loadtup
Quality check - Perevodildo, WOWmd
Papa said men
are all wolves
Still, momma loves him that much!
Anytime, I go my way
Misunderstandings never stop
Going forward carelessly
Episode 2
Go, go! Kimi-Chan
Kimi is so cute.
She is the one I love!
She is thoughtful. And girly!
Hand-made purse,
napkin, and home-made bento!
She is a perfect family woman!
But she used to be a delinquent
and can be vulgar sometimes.
Stop it! I don't wanna hear that!
Hello!
Yay! It's the delivery!
Thanks a lot!
Smells great.
Ah.
It's the delivery guy's...
He forgot it here and left...
I'll go find him.
Mister, your Hecchin!
H-Hecchin?
No, your helmet.
Hey, Kimi.
Yes?
What kind of music do you listen to?
Let's see.
I mainly listen to Johnny's Jr.
J-Johnny's Jr.?
I used to be a huge fan of the "Hikaru Genji" band in my junior high school days.
Me and my friend
used to ride a moped together...
We chased Hikaru Genji's van on the freeway and got scolded when we finally caught up with them.
Brings back so many memories!
But I swear I stopped doing that when I transferred to high school.
R-Really?
When I entered high school,
I was smacked with SMAP.
I used my parents' savings
to chase them all over the country.
I felt really bad for making my mom cry.
But it was a whole lot of fun.
But that ended with my high school.
I made a switch to TOKIO when I was in college.
I-I've heard enough...
Her perfume is too strong.
And look at this messy hair —
the ends are all split!
Girl, your split ends are out of control.
You should get a haircut!
Your perfume is too strong as well!
You're so cool, Kimi...
Kimi...
Is there a good way for me
to get closer with her?
Ah, I thought you reminded me of someone when I saw you.
Now I know it's my classmate from my junior high school!
This is my chance!
Oh? Was he your friend!?
No, I used to bully him,
so he didn't have any friends.
Oh no! Kimi is in trouble!
I-I need to muster some courage...
Kimi! That guy does looks scary.
Y-You there! Stop it!
Ah, it's Nakatani!
Ah! You are here too, Koume?
H-Hi...
This is my boyfriend.
Whadja mean when you yelled me to stop, huh?!
R-Right...
Don't do that, Sho. He is Nakatani, the designer of that Lovely Bear.
What the hell?
You made that fucking bear?!
Y-Yes!
I'm a huge fan of your work!
You should've told me sooner!
I'm Sho! Please keep up the great work!
Sure...