World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
on that starry starry night
I will not let out of sight
Kono tomoshibi o keshi wa shinai to
Never in my life I will put out this beaconing light
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
under the crimson daybreak
I will not misrecollect
Wakaba ni somaru haru o yobou to
With the voices of new leaves, the spring is summoned
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
The sounds of axes chopping trees
is a song rumbling on the broad roads
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The chest trembles in blissful ease,
echoing with mountain peaks
Kono oozora no niji ni naritai
In this sky of endless blue I want to be a rainbow too
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
To be reaching for the hope, I want to become a rainbow
Episode 3
Oddball
You have... quite a cute-looking face.
Listen, please don't be mordacious.
What is the matter, Billy?
What are you doing?
Can you be quiet for a minute, please?
This fellow won't budge a bit!
I am definitely keeping you!
My little sister Lucy-May was immediately
head over heels for the cute animal from the tree top.
She decided to keep him no matter what.
On our way home, an aboriginal family
appeared out of nowhere in front of us.
Hands off!
Lucy-May, chin up!
You'll have another chance to find that animal.
Sis, sis! Did you see it?
The way he was clinging to that boy.
I saw it.
What a truly adorable lad.
I will find him.
And then no matter what anyone says, I am keeping him!
I'd keep him as well.
Well, it's about time we hurry back to mom.
This has already taken us indecently long.
Good call. Let's hurry.
Lucy-May!
You are carrying your bucket yourself!
My bad, my bad!
Even though you finally brought the water,
I can but to scold you for how indecently long it took.
We ran into aboriginals.
Aboriginals?
Yes. A spear-armed ones.
Spear-armed?
Then, did they do anything to you...
The aboriginal child plucked off me
the cute animal we've caught earlier.
But that child also seemed to be caring for it.
He had a solid proof, so there was no room for objection.
Exactly what type of animal?
I don't know what it is called, but it had a large nose,
the cottonous fur and the cutest ever appearance!
What did you plan to use such an animal for,
had you caught it?
I thought I would keep it.
Was bringing along your hamster Mosh
all the way from England not enough?
Even with your dad and mom pleading you not to!
I had to, because Mosh is a dear friend of mine.
And that is why Mosh is more than enough.
To adopt a yet another new animal would be ludicrous!
When I told her so,
this child wouldn't give an ear!
Out of question.
It's completely out of question, Lucy-May.
Having a squabble in raised voices, are you?
How is your fever?
Reducing already?
Yes, it seems to be gone.
It does. You are way colder than before.
But it's best that you don't wander around yet.
But everyone is in such a hustle.
I'm the only one to be snoozing.
Totally excusable for someone ill.
But I want to be in any way helpful!
Then it's one more reason
to spend today resting peacefully.
Because that is your mother's order.
Okay.
Mosh!
I wonder what such an animal even feeds on.
Nuts, probably.
Why else would it climb a tree?
That must be the case.
I will by any means catch that cute creature.
When that happens, get along nicely, will you?
My little sister Lucy-May
is really into extreme animals.
That's why she often knows the names
of animals she had never seen.
However, we didn't yet have any chance
to know about koalas, indigenous to Australia.
As it was revealed to us later,
koala's menu consists exclusively of eucalyptus leaves.
Well, well, this tablecloth is permeated with mold.
No wonder since it spent three months
inside the humid ship underbelly.
Is that the trunk dad brought from the ship?
It is.
Then, dad and Ben are off to Adelaide?
No.
Where are they, then?
Mr. Parker's tent collapsed for no particular reason,
so they are putting it back together with Ben.
Now, Ben. Get ready!
Okay!
Heave-ho!
That should do it.
Alright, now the other side.
Okay!
Are you sure you don't want me to help?
It's fine if you just stop wobbling
and get seated out of the way.
You think so?
Alright! Pull now, Ben!
Then, I'll take your word for it.
Yes, yes. That's the way.
I'll secure it on this end first!
If you give it a thought,
I'm rather a towny type of man.
Which makes my ineptitude in tent hanging
perfectly justified.
I guess so.
Last night, when the tent poles gave in and it collapsed on me,
I barely caught any shuteye!
You should have tended to it earlier.
Good grief, I finally landed in Australia just to spend
the initial night awake, propping up the tent poles!
That will make a good memory for the future you,
living in a magnificent house.
Magnificent house?
Like the one you will build in the city of Adelaide.
No, I am not going to Adelaide.
I will be doing trading right here!
Here?
Exactly. The flow of immigrants will be growing steadily.
Before long, a proper wharf will be arranged.
A trading post will be indispensable then.
No doubt, my business will rise and prosper here!
You can't know if it'll go this way.
No, it will definitely be so!
Hey, Ben! I untied the rope here to pull it once more.
Do the same on your side!
Okay!
Then tie a sturdy knot, this time for good.
If we don't secure it tightly now, Mr. Parker
will have another sleepless night of propping up the poles.
That's right, Ben!
Please secure it well!
They're here, here!
Looks like it is already almost done!
Brother! Are you done already?
Yeah. Did you come here for something?
We came to see how you are doing.
Don't say nonsense.
It's true! Mr. Pettywell is also having dire times now,
breaking his neck trying to fix a tent!
When Mr. Pettywell's tent collapsed on him yesterday,
we couldn't help bursting into cackle!
But Mr. Pettywell got so mad!
Naturally!
But Mr. Pettywell had such an ascended look
while the tent was slowly descending upon his head...
Hey, Ben! You should stretch it harder!
Okay!
Well...
Can I ask a small favor of young ladies?
What is it?
Here is some lamb meat.
I received it just recently. The freshest meat.
See?
Today your side, namely your father, provided me service
of fixing my tent. This meat is my means of payment.
This meat has not been salted yet?
Of course not! It's fresh meat!
I hate salted meat most of all!
It always has that weird smell.
This meat is not mixed with any weird smells at all.
Now, would you take it to your mother?
Sure, sir.
Goodbye!
I can't remember the last time we had fresh meat!
All the meat they served on the ship was salted.
It must have been more than a hundred days ago!
I think so.
Surely, you said your looong thanks to Mr. Parker?
Did you say it?
I said it.
No, all you've said was "Goodbye", and nothing else!
Baloney! I said "Thank you!"
It was sis who clearly didn't say anything!
I think I probably expressed all due gratitude.
It's only natural when receiving goods from other people.
But sister positively never uttered any gratitude!
I can swear to God it was you who said nothing!
Give me a break, you two!
Mom, I'll leave it here.
When your dad's party returns, we'll start cooking.
Could you go look after Tob, Clara?
Okay.
Now, now, it's alright, Tob.
What's the matter?
I wanna back home!
This is our home now, Tob.
Wanna home!
We have to be patient while we're here.
We brought a marvelous prefabricated house
all the way from England to build it in the city of Adelaide.
Somebody... Somebody catch that dog!
Kate!
Look out!
My, that's bad!
Somebody get that dog!
Stop right there!
Catch it!
Mom! Hurry! Hurry up and catch that dog!
What happened, sis?
There! See that dog?
That dog stole the meat you were paid with!
Heck!
Catch the damn thief dog!
Gotcha!
Wait! Wait!!
Catch it!
Catch that damn dog!
Here, here!
You're not getting away! Take this!
Hey, what's the matter, Happy?
Something hurt you?
I say, what is this all about? What made you think
you are entitled to be collectively bullying my dog?
That dog of yours is a burglar!
He is a burglar? You could make up a better slander.
Pardon my bluntness, but this dog is better fed than you are.
Right, Happy?
Here! You can see for yourself!
Dog did this to our hard-earned meat...
My, my, Happy,
you feel like playing pranks today, do you?
This transgresses any idea of prank, Mr. Pettywell!
What is it you are trying to say, then?
Are you implying I have to pay you the price for that meat?
What price do you want for it, boy?
Well...
Wait, Annie.
Dad...
Now, the three of you can return home.
Mr. Pettywell, that meat was priceless to us.
That's why I'm willing to reimburse it.
I'm not afraid to assume responsibility for my dog's tricks.
Even by paying for it, you won't earn our pardon!
I don't understand one bit what is it you want then!
Are you oblivious of the very concept of apology?
What is the logic behind me
apologizing for dog's misbehavior?
Mr. Pettywell!
I have no words for you but...
Dear...
Let's go home, dear.
We can no longer eat it, can we?
After such a long time,
we were hoping to taste some genuine meat again.
Is it really inedible now?
Let's throw it away, mom.
No.
But what do we do with it, mom?
We'll wash it to edible.
The fresh meat is too precious to us.
But to wash it...
The sea is great for washing it.
After that, we can eat it.
I can wash it!
I will go too!
I can do just fine alone!
I said I'll go, so I'll go!
You'll get in the way if you come!
Sis is a meanie!
Be careful now.
Ben, can you come along?
Sure!
It's fine, I can go alone.
Kate, that much washing should be enough.
It is so much smaller now.
When we just received it from Mr. Parker,
it was actually this big!
Fibber.
Who?
You, of course!
What makes me a fibber?
When we received it from Mr. Parker,
it was already this shrunk.
It was about that size.
Right, bro?
It never was that big!
It was really
this sizeable!
This inconsiderable!
Wrong! Big like this!
That was more than enough!
What a fibber you are!
Sister is the only fibber here!
Except it's you!
Sister!
Just how I remember it,
the unsalted meat is delicious.
Actually, the slice was so small,
I barely grasped the taste.
I think it was totally delicious!
I wonder, when will be the next time
we get to stuff our tummies with some fresh meat.
No, I don't believe it will take too long.
This country's lands are ample; the climate is favorable.
It fits stock breeding greatly.
At the moment, I am devoted to building us a new farm.
Though if we end up running a ranch, I won't mind either.
Therefore, my first step towards it
would be going to Adelaide tomorrow.
I will pay a visit to general Light in the surveying office
to decide on our own plot as soon as possible.
Dad, are you going there alone?
No, you are coming with me. If you memorize
the road to Adelaide, it will come in handy later.
I want to go too!
Me too!
Not happening.
This time it's just Ben.
Our whole family is going to Adelaide soon anyhow.
Until then, you have to be patient.
Can't we see you off even part of the way?
Unless you want to be credited with misbehavior!
This means, after you return from Adelaide, we will unload our luggage and prefabricated house off the ship's belly?
The ship will be anchored for another 5 days...
Well, there's really no point telling you that.
John would hardly omit that, talking to you.
What is it, Lucy-May?
Nothing.
Get back to sleep soon.
I am certainly catching it!
When Billy grows up,
he dreams of becoming an explorer.
So to promote it, we embarked on an expedition
to the other side of the cape.
Next time in Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
First Explorations. Join us again!
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
On an eucalyptus tree there's a baby Koala
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
With his mom poking around, climbing branches up and down
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
For us to have a feast, let's find a lot of leaves
Kaze no yurikago ohiru ne yo
As I take a nap of ease, coddled by the breeze
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Mizube ni asobu waraikawasemi
There is a laughing Kookaburra playing by the waterflow
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
All he does is merry laugh, so his spirits don't go low:
Itazura sarete mo uha-ha-ha-ha
He is up to mischief again, uha-ha-ha-ha
Misetaina misetaina mori no dōbutsu
Let us go and look, let us go and look at the creatures of the woods
Misetainaa
Let's go look at them!
Timing, translation: Perevodildo
Quality check, editing: Ziusudra
The Sorcery Party