World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
on that starry starry night
I will not let out of sight
Kono tomoshibi o keshi wa shinai to
Never in my life I will put out this beaconing light
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
under the crimson daybreak
I will not misrecollect
Wakaba ni somaru haru o yobou to
With the voices of new leaves, the spring is summoned
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
The sounds of axes chopping trees
is a song rumbling on the broad roads
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The chest trembles in blissful ease,
echoing with mountain peaks
Kono oozora no niji ni naritai
In this sky of endless blue I want to be a rainbow too
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
To be reaching for the hope, I want to become a rainbow
Episode 2
Cute Fellow
I wanna eat!
Sure, sure.
I'm getting up soon.
Yesterday we arrived in Australia.
So, we spend our first night
sleeping in this settlement near the shore.
With my little sister Lucy-May, I slept in the barrel because the tent was so poky.
- Tob! Is everyone still sleeping?
- Sleepy.
Lucy-May, wake up!
I have not slept enough.
You were the one waking me up this night!
I'm not waking up!
You were awake!
I were awake,
because I saw such a weird animal!
It was jumping like that,
hop-hop, with its two legs only.
You sure it was not a rabbit?
Of course! There are no rabbits like that.
What are you doing, Lucy-May?
While she was sleeping last night,
Lucy-May saw some animal that was like a giant rabbit!
It was nothing like a rabbit!
But you say it was hopping like one!
It was only hopping on two feet, not four.
Here, it should be plenty of animals
that are not met in England.
Take those birds, for example.
They look like parrots.
They do.
I'm sorry, but could you two gather some firewood?
We already ran out of what was gathered yesterday.
Can't big sister go again?
Clara still has a fever.
She would be better off getting some rest.
You are still quite feverish, sis.
Ben, moisten her forehead to cool her down.
Ben, I am fine.
I will get up now.
Don't exert yourself, sis.
That's right, get more sleep.
I really am such a nuisance.
Just as we finally made it to Australia...
We still have a lot of luggage
to bring from the ship, right?
Clara, it's best that you don't worry about that.
It is so, sis.
Now...
Clara, get some sleep. I believe we are to face a whole bunch of challenges in the near future.
When that happens, you will have to lend your mother a helping hand.
So until then,
you need become as healthy as you can.
Okay...
Look at this!
Some driftwood washed here too.
Here.
Hey. I have something to say to you.
What is it?
How about instead of asking me to pick it,
you just put down that hamster?
But I thought
I would let Mosh play along the seashore.
Why won't you do it then?
Yes, I will right now.
Okay, Mosh.
You are good to come out.
Start gathering firewood now.
Okay, I am gathering.
Until later.
Yeah.
Hey, sis, can you take this firewood off me?
You picked it up yourself,
but you cannot carry it?
It is because I have to collect Mosh on our way back.
I cannot do that with firewood!
Not my concern.
It is John!
What are you two doing?
Gathering wood for the fire.
Want me to help?
Thanks. But won't you have to return to ship soon?
No. Today I'm on a furlough until noon.
Say, John, can you take this firewood?
Sure thing.
I cannot carry both it and Mosh.
You really are such a slyboots!
Here you go then.
Mosh, let's go.
Come on, Mosh.
How is Clara doing, Kate?
Sister is having a fever again.
Tob, caught something?
Come on. Let me take a look.
What, a lizard? Okay, okay,
now take it away from me. Hurry!
I will be visiting the ship again later.
We are somewhat worried about the luggage.
That ship will be anchored here for another week.
You don't have to be hurry-scurry unloading your luggage.
No, I don't mean unloading it today.
Our belongings are probably piled up with the rest of cargo,
so I'm planning to get it all out in one big trip.
Yes. That way it's the least hassle.
You see, we brought along
a whole prefabricated house from England.
Are you assembling a house here?
Of course not.
We are assembling it in the city of Adelaide.
Then, you are moving that prefabricated house
all the way to Adelaide?
That's the only way we assemble it.
But how are you going to move it there?
As usual — with carriages and oxcarts.
Here, both of those are not abundant.
I have been here before, so I know well.
Oh well. We'll figure something.
John...
Would you perchance like to have breakfast with us?
Thank you, but I already had one on the ship.
Then, maybe just some tea?
Well, it's finished, dear.
That helps a lot.
Well...
I heard Miss Clara is ill again.
May I see her?
Sis, wait!
John is such a rascal!
In the end, he did not help me one bit!
You are still too small to understand his mind.
John had to go ahead
because he is worried about sister's illness.
I am also worried about her!
John's worry is a special one.
Why so?
You need to grow just a bit bigger to understand.
Why are you being so puffy? You could just say John is in love with Clara and be done with it.
The same goes for Clara as well, is that not so?
You are growing unexpectedly fast.
Clara.
Is that you, John?
You are still ill. Feeling better?
Just a small fever. No big deal.
There are no small deals here,
with not a single physician around.
I'd be glad to bring you tea
if you want to drink some.
I don't want any.
What's more important, John,
when are you leaving here?
In a week.
I see.
Once you leave here,
we won't meet again. Ever...
Will you be able to go ashore every day until then?
Not every day.
Because I'm just a deckhand,
I am up to my eyeballs in work.
I see.
In just a week...
I made up my mind.
What is it?
I'm leaving the ship.
Just not right now.
After I return to England, I will leave for Australia at once,
but this time with my little brother.
Really?
Both of our parents died.
My only relative is my brother.
That is why the two of us will come to Australia.
And then, we'll meet again!
John...
Father is talking to Mr. Pettywell.
Out of question, Mr. Pettywell.
There is no way I am selling that prefabricated house.
I am willing to pony up
twice the price you paid for it in England.
Twice the price?
That's right. It's enough trees here
to cover all your needs.
For such an artisanal fellow, constructing a house is a piece of cake.
We will only get that prefabricated house in a few days.
I want to be living in a proper house straight away. Sleeping in a tent has already become unbearable.
How long will it take for you to assemble that house?
Let's see, in about two weeks I should be...
No... No! Not selling it. Period.
Maybe with some more on the table...?
Not happening.
We will assemble that house in the city of Adelaide.
It is just as unbearable for us
to be indefinitely sleeping in tents like this.
Well, I'll leave you with some more time to think it over.
I am not going to sell it.
I was in such a suspense until you said you are not actually thinking of selling it.
Sell it, huh?
Ben, as soon as we have eaten,
we're going to the ship to arrange our belongings.
Okay.
Mom said to bring along the trunk with tablecloth from Grandma.
But I don't have any idea which trunk it is.
I do.
- Fetch water?
Where do we go for that?
A river is flowing in those woods.
There is no dangers in there, right?
Why, of course.
Had there been any danger,
I'd never send you two for mere water fetching.
There's just...
Just what?
Those woods are home to aborigines.
While going to fetch water myself yesterday,
I ran into some of them.
What is an aborigine?
We call that the people who lived here long before us.
I thought Australia is the place
no one lived in until the English turned up!
Well that is not entirely so.
In Australia, you cannot even go to school or church to make the life more exciting.
All we do is getting an errand after an errand.
True.
Hey, imagine we meet some of those aborigines!
Yeah.
I want to meet them!
What kind of people you imagine them?
I'll know when I meet them!
The way you gibber,
they'll think you're out of your mind.
A pretty bird!
We might even run into the animal you saw last night!
That strange fellow!
What's wrong?
Someone is here.
You think it's an aborigine?
An aborigine?
I am so scared!
What now?
Did you not just say you want to meet one?
Why, it's Billy!
Ain't it Billy!
Fetching water as well?
Yes!
- Wait for us, Billy! Let's go home together!
- Go home together!
Sure.
Say, Billy, have you seen the aborigines?
Yeah, seen them.
Hand it over. I'll fill it for you.
Thanks!
What kind of people are they?
Uhm... The undressed kind.
Undressed?
Yeah, just like that.
Come to think of it, being undressed is the easiest way
to cope with how hot this place is.
Makes sense.
And what else? Hey, what else is there?
They are rather dark.
Sunburnt maybe?
Certainly!
Can we rest a little, sis?
You are such a spineless one!
Say that again!
You really don't have to force yourself.
I will manage! I work hard!
Relax, let's take a rest.
I am not resting!
You're such a stubborn.
Take a rest I said!
Too tired to walk, are you, sis?
You really took it to heart!
We deserve a break, you kid!
I do not need to rest!
Take a rest!
I am not resting!
I've had enough of that, both of you!
I wonder if we will have to come all the way here
to fetch water every day.
It's a bit remote.
You are not staying in this area forever, are you?
Dad said we are going to the city of Adelaide.
We even brought along a prefabricated house.
We will carry it to Adelaide to assemble!
That sounds amazing!
One can make a small fortune
catching birds here and selling them back in England.
What can that be?
What?
There! See the spot where that branch splits?
True! What is that thing?
Where is it?
I don't see.
Looks like a bear.
Bear?
I see, I see! Really resembles a bear!
Bears can climb trees?
Who knows.
But this one is incredibly small for a bear.
Let's catch it!
How do you plan to catch it?
I will climb this tree!
Think you can climb that high?
Billy can climb it.
He is a boy after all.
Can you climb it, Billy?
There's nothing I can't climb...
Climb it then!
Come on, Billy, please!
I want to catch that cute fellow!
If I don't come back to my mother with water soon...
Fine. Forget it. I'm climbing it myself.
Lucy-May, you gotta stop!
I sure hope it's not mordacious...
Catch it for me, Billy!
John, may I do the rowing?
Yeah, be my guest.
I'm sorry to waste your precious free time
tending to our trivial matters, John.
No, I'm happy to be useful.
That's a no way!
Plunge the oars deeper into the water.
Like that. Keep it up.
What are you doing, Billy?
I think he might be dead!
Is he dead?
Relax, relax. Just very sleepy.
Then catch him quickly!
How do you know it's not mordacious?
It's alright, alright!
You're the one saying that.
You... have quite a cute face, you know.
Listen, don't bite me, okay?
What is the matter, Billy?
What is going on?
Can you be quiet for a minute, please?
This fellow won't budge a bit!
Well, what a lad! You startled me!
Amazing!
He is adorable!
Awesome, Billy!
Now, please be cautious not to drop this child!
It's alright. He is clinging to me really tight.
What an intrepid guy!
I can't wait any longer!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!!!
I wonder what Kate and Co are up to.
Whatever they are doing, it's taking them long.
Lucy-May, what do you intend to use him for?
Keeping!
Did you forget you already have Mosh?
The food is not in a surplus. Not to mention dad, who would be upset at the news of you keeping such an animal!
But such a cute animal is by all means rare!
It really was so. This creature called Koala
was yet another animal not met outside Australia.
We will make sure to remember this one.
I'm definitely keeping you!
He's cute, no fuss about it.
To top off our tribulations,
Mr. Pettywell's black dog ran off with our meat.
Trying to settle that,
dad quarreled with Mr. Pettywell.
Next time in Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
Oddball. Join us again!
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
On an eucalyptus tree there's a baby Koala
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
With his mom poking around, climbing branches up and down
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
For us to have a feast, let's find a lot of leaves
Kaze no yurikago ohiru ne yo
As I take a nap of ease, coddled by the breeze
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Mizube ni asobu waraikawasemi
There is a laughing Kookaburra playing by the waterflow
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
All he does is merry laugh, so his spirits don't go low:
Itazura sarete mo uha-ha-ha-ha
He is up to mischief again, uha-ha-ha-ha
Misetaina misetaina mori no dōbutsu
Let us go and look, let us go and look at the creatures of the woods
Misetainaa
Let's go look at them!
Timing, translation: Perevodildo
Quality check, editing: Ziusudra
The Sorcery Party