World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
on that starry starry night
I will not let out of sight
Kono tomoshibi o keshi wa shinai to
Never in my life I will put out this beaconing light
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
under the crimson daybreak
I will not misrecollect
Wakaba ni somaru haru o yobou to
With the voices of new leaves, the spring is summoned
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
The sounds of axes chopping trees
is a song rumbling on the broad roads
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The chest trembles in blissful ease,
echoing with mountain peaks
Kono oozora no niji ni naritai
In this sky of endless blue I want to be a rainbow too
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
To be reaching for the hope, I want to become a rainbow
Episode 1
To the New Land
Mother, let's have some tea.
Say, Mary... you aren't hiding anything from me, are you?
I have nothing to hide from you, mother!
Don't you really have some news?
News?﻿
Half a year passed since Arthur left the village with my grandchildren.
No, even seven months have passed.
They did it last August.
It is so.
The letter of them arriving to Australia was supposed to come long ago.
Mother! Did I not tell you
England and Australia are very far apart?
The one is the edge of the Earth for the other. It's more than three months of sailing.
You keep saying that...
I hope news come soon of them arriving safely.
It seems my husband is back.
He was to town, right?
I hope he figured to stop by the post office.
I guess he did.
It's cold!
Tonight it will definitely heap up!
You didn't put the horse into the stable?
I will, naturally. But before that,
I figured to give this to your mother.
Now, behold the long-awaited letter from Australia.
Well, mother!
Good Lord!
Read it for me, Mary.
I have some kind of inexplicable fear.
I don't think there is anything to fear of.
It was Clara who wrote this letter!
She turned sixteen while onboard the ship.
I'm reading, mother.
"Grandma, aunt Mary, and finally, uncle Fred, how are you?
Our family has made it to South Australia.
We spent ninety five days aboard
until we could at last tread the soil again.
We have been trapped in the confined cabin
for over three months.
To determine the order of passengers going ashore by boat, we drew lots."
Boat preparations are finished!
Okay! Next group, please.
That would be us.
Let's go, sis.
I'll lend you a shoulder.
Thank you, Ben.
No, you're waiting.
Our family goes ahead.
Excuse me, Mr. Pettywell, but the lots we've drawn say it's our turn now.
My wife's state is deteriorating. She cannot comply with that order.
Now, let us go.
As well as my daughter's state.
My family is different from yours.
I paid a fortune in fares for taking this ship all the way from England.
Naturally, this includes my wife and servants as well.
I have a privilege over those
who came here on government expense.
Is that so, boy?
Yeah...
Make sure you don't forget any luggage.
Can't be helped.
We'll wait for the next.
What a rotten person!
Kate...
How can I not say it
if Mr. Pettywell is such a rotten person?
I thought so before too.
Be quiet, Kate.
What now? He queue-jumped in front of us. Can't even make fun of his pompousness!
That fellow Mosh is probably dying in there...
Why is he supposed to be dying?
You should know it yourself!
Hamsters hibernate during winter.
Back in England, the winter is already in full swing by now.
But here it's summer.
Therefore, Mosh cannot hibernate and it drives him crazy, I believe.
Mosh will be fine! Australia reinvigorated him!
Feeling better, sis?
Yes, thank you.
The sea breeze reaches me even down here.
Father yielded our turn to Mr. Pettywell for whatever reason.
Can't be helped.
He is rich after all.
Why did we come all the way to South Australia then?
Father told us this place is full of freedom and equality.
"Unfortunately, on the first day of landing,
I was feeling a bit ill.
It must have been heat.
However, everyone else was in high spirits.
Especially Kate and Lucy-May,
whose spirits were over the top.
Too enthusiastic about riding a boat,
Lucy-May tripped into the sea.
The one who followed Lucy-May to rescue her
was a young sailor named John.
Throughout the voyage,
he has been the most cordial to us.
It's almost summer in these parts.
Thanks to that, Lucy-May never caught a cold
after tumbling into the sea."
Say, what is she talking about, Mary?
What, Mother?
Here it's snowing all over the place, but in Australia they have summer?
Mother, winter and summer periods in Australia
are reversed in regard to England.
How come?
It's on the southern side of the globe.
How does the southern side explain the seasons reversed?
Even I don't know everything.
Winter and summer reversed, then?
I’m glad anyway.
At least the ship didn't sink on the way,
I was so worried it would!
But the struggle is still ahead.
They are now in a virtually uninhabited place.
Everyone would have to blaze their own trail from here on.
Build lodgings and eventually towns.
Then there are plots and pastures.
The worst part is, I'm never seeing my adorable grandchildren again.
Mother!
You two! Have I not told you not to stand up?
You two can't sit still, can you?
This time, no one is helping if you fall in the sea!
Right, John?
Uh-huh.
Are you not cold, Lucy-May?
Not one bit!
Mosh is already fully dry!
Those girls have not changed one bit
from what they were back home.
They are the most buoyant.
I am only a bit worried about Clara.
By the way, what is the plan after we are ashore?
To begin with, we will arrange sleeping quarters in the vicinity.
There, you can see it yourself.
There are such camps all over the place.
Is that where Adelaide is?
No, the city sits in some distance from the shore.
South Australia capital is Adelaide, is that so?
Even though it's the capital, it only has about 300 residents at the moment.
Thank yon, John.
This is the land we spend the rest of our lives on.
It feels great!
So fun!
It's Australia!
It's Australia for you!
Now, everyone! Take whatever you can carry.
We will unload it on top of that dune.
Okay!
Father, when are we retrieving
the rest of our luggage from that ship?
I don't know yet.
There are only bulky pieces left,
so boats will have to bring them in several rounds.
I will be back!
Clara.
You should not exert yourself since you have a fever.
Just watch over Tob and our luggage.
Okay. I understand.
"While sitting there, thinking, I could appreciate,
to my surprise, how desolate is the surrounding scenery.
I couldn't help wondering
how can human live in a place like that.
Still, I have to do my best.
Grandma, from now on, I will make sure to secure a letter for you whenever there's a ship returning to England.
Take care, and good bye.
November 7th, 1837, from South Australia, Clara Poppel."
It's summer over there...
Now, hold it tight, Ben.
Heave-ho!
Father, you are such a handyman.
Farmers have to be Jacks of all trades.
Where did mother go fetching the water?
This is like a birds realm.
Let's go!
Look, over there!
Mr. Pettywell is building himself a house.
Alright, that much of driving it in should do fine.
Now start pulling it on this side.
He could do some work himself,
not just give orders!
We have not been doing any work either.
Good point. How about we stop wandering around
and offer father some help?
I am little, so it is okay for me to be playing.
But you can help...
Not happening! If I am going to work,
you are working along with me.
Alright, that's enough.
Start carrying our luggage into the tent, you two.
- Okay!
- Okay.
Hurry up, you rascals! Hurry up!
The sun is about to set!
Why, you...
Why are you standing here looking at me idly,
you blockheads?! Start by rebuilding it!
Until this is fixed, no one is getting their supper!
Get to work, loafer breed!
What are you doing in such a place?
I have been looking for you!
Sis...
There... There!
And then "Slam!"
No playing around!
I am not playing around!
Just making sure it does not hurt when you use it!
Does not hurt, does not hurt!
I thought so!
What a smell!
I am so hungry I just cannot stand it!
So do I!
Mom!
Please wait just a bit longer.
The salt pork soup is on the way.
It needs some more seething.
Mom, we laid enough straw in the tent.
You can sleep well wherever you want.
Is that so?
Then could you go to Clara and Ben to tell them we don't need more?
Sure!
Father is bringing along that thing.
My, that's a large barrel.
It was lying on the shore nearby.
The bottom is gone, so it's not gonna hold any more water.
Why did you bring it here, then?
That tent cannot accommodate us all sleeping in it.
Then, someone will be sleeping inside here?
Father, who will be sleeping in it?
Lucy, you want to sleep here?
Me?
Afraid to be here alone?
Yes...
But together with sis, I will be fine.
The two of you can sleep here no problem.
Maybe it would be better
if Ben sleeps here instead of girls?
I want to sleep here!
Sis is back.
Sis!
We will be sleeping inside a barrel!
Inside a barrel?
Yes!
Let me have that straw.
Mother, did you say the tent interior is done?
You did well.
Please lay the remaining straw inside this barrel.
Inside the barrel?
Me and sis are now sleeping in here!
Are you sure, mom?
Well, we're still to hear what Kate says.
Of course, I will sleep here!﻿
Sleeping in a barrel must be lovely!
Let me have that straw.
Here! Let me finish the bed for us!
Sister, you are mean, mean, mean beyond belief!
Dad, they should sleep here instead of me.
This way I feel relieved.
Your mother said so too.
That's right. In such a place,
those two can brawl all they want.
Right, mom?
I guess...
We are sleeping in the barrel!
Before we proceed to eating,
I have something to say to all of you.
Aside from Tob,
who probably won't understand a word of it,
I want everyone to listen closely to what I say.
We have all made it to Australia safe and sound.
You are all well aware of my purpose for coming here —
to build a farm much bigger
than the farm we had back in England.
And I'm sure it won't take long.
But until that happens, I want everyone
to endure bravely all the hardships that we are to face.
After all, we are not staying in this area forever.
Tomorrow or the day after that, I'm walking to Adelaide.
Adelaide is about 10 kilometers inwards from this shore.
A capital of South Australia, it is now being erected as a glorious city, devoid of any disgraceful stains.
With the parts I brought from England, I am planning to build a magnificent residence in Adelaide.
So that, once I buy a sizeable plot,
we could see it turn into a magnificent farmland.
That concludes my address.
Now, shall we finally eat?
Here.
Here you go, Ben.
While sleeping in that barrel, what may happen to you in the dead of night? You never know.
What may happen to me?
Maybe spirits of the dead will rise?
You're such a buffoon.
Wanna know for real? This place is still full of wild dogs.
They look like wolves and really are ghastly.
Liar.
It's true!
Well, well, well?
You really are a buffoon.
That is Mr. Pettywell's black dog.
That is bad manners!
I have an urgent message for brother.
What?
Regardless of what you say to Lucy-May, she is determined to sleep in the barrel.
Suit yourself!
Mosh! Mosh, what is the matter?
We don't want you to be crushed. Go back to the basket.
Sis!
What is it?
Wake up! A strange animal
stopped by to watch us just now!
Strange animal?
It resembled a rabbit somehow,
but an enormous one!
It was hop-hopping on two legs!
So a rabbit after all?
Go back to sleep soon, Lucy-May.
So it's some kind of rabbit, huh?
We later found out the animal my little sister Lucy-May saw was an animal, only inhabiting Australia, which is kangaroo.
We never had any idea such an outlandish animal
can even exist somewhere.
On our way back home from the water spring,
we found this absolutely adorable and docile animal.
Next time in Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
Cute Fellow. Join us again!
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
On an eucalyptus tree there's a baby Koala
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
With his mom poking around, climbing branches up and down
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
For us to have a feast, let's find a lot of leaves
Kaze no yurikago ohiru ne yo
As I take a nap of ease, coddled by the breeze
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Mizube ni asobu waraikawasemi
There is a laughing Kookaburra playing by the waterflow
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
All he does is merry laugh, so his spirits don't go low:
Itazura sarete mo uha-ha-ha-ha
He is up to mischief again, uha-ha-ha-ha
Misetaina misetaina mori no dōbutsu
Let us go and look, let us go and look at the creatures of the woods
Misetainaa
Let's go look at them!
Timing, translation: Perevodildo
Quality check, editing: Ziusudra
The Sorcery Party