World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
on that starry starry night
I will not let out of sight
Kono tomoshibi o keshi wa shinai to
Never in my life I will put out this beaconing light
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
The words I vowed
under the crimson daybreak
I will not misrecollect
Wakaba ni somaru haru o yobou to
With the voices of new leaves, the spring is summoned
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
The sounds of axes chopping trees
is a song rumbling on the broad roads
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The chest trembles in blissful ease,
echoing with mountain peaks
Kono oozora no niji ni naritai
In this sky of endless blue I want to be a rainbow too
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
To be reaching for the hope, I want to become a rainbow
Episode 4
First Explorations
This is our third morning
after the arrival to South Australia.
Good morning, Mr. Poppel.
Morning, Mr. Parker.
How is your tent doing?
Thank you, it has never been better.
I am no longer anxious.
Let's see.
Last night I slept in it like a log.
It will stand even if a storm comes.
Going to the city of Adelaide, are you?
Yes. If we don't hurry,
we may not find a site to assemble our house.
I'm sure you'll find a fine site.
Thank you. Still...
What?
No, nothing at all.
Since we left England, we've been through
a whole bunch of unforeseeable hardships.
- Even now, it's not yet time to be fussy.
- That's right! We should all do our best.
Well then.
Come, Ben.
Okay.
Don't get lost on your way to Adelaide.
Thank you!
Lucy-May! Quit playing lest we will never get it done!
I wonder if dad's party
has already made it to Adelaide.
You are a dum-dum. To get to Adelaide,
you have to cross over ten kilometers of forest.
There's no way they arrived.
How long is ten kilometers?
Well, it's like going from our home in England
to the city of Burton.
Then it's not really that far.
But they have not paved a proper road yet.
Folks get lost in those woods every now and then.
Our dad would never get lost in the woods!
Maybe so.
Exactly so!
I expected this road to be rather more sophisticated.
There is, by far, not much of a choice. This is the only road
linking the seashore to the city of Adelaide.
Hey, dad.
Why did they found the city of Adelaide
not next to the sea?
I thought adjoining a city to the harbor
is a common practice.
That is so.
Even I don't know all the details.
Whether or not the city should be founded
away from shore is always a subject for hot debates.
It seems utterly inconvenient for carrying miscellaneous
goods off and on the ship when a city is away from harbor.
The local surveyor-general Light
seems to be very assertive.
Following the general's lead, the city was founded inland,
about ten kilometers from the sea.
General Light?
The general is striving to build Adelaide
into a perfect model colony.
It seems the city is being built
in strict compliance with the city plan.
I wonder how will the city of Adelaide fare.
Ben, don't set high expectations.
They are merely starting to build it.
It's just some isolated houses
among forests and fields for now.
Not many people live in it, right?
Yes. There are mere 300 residents.
However, the immigrants will keep flocking in our steps
at an ever-increasing rate.
In a blink of an eye, 300 turn 600.
600 turn 1200.
1200 turn...
2400 men.
Yes, yes. It will be growing steadily from now on.
Sis, it seems we won't have to fetch any more water.
Yes.
We are excused to go play, then?
Ask mom first.
Where did mom go?
To Ms. Jamling's place.
She was invited for tea.
Even while living in tents like this,
they are still in the mood for tea parties?
With sugar?
Yes, one spoon.
Delightful.
I think you will appreciate this black tea
when you better taste it.
How about another cup?
Thank you. If only a half then.
You don't have to restrain yourself.
See? I have a whole tin can full of it.
- Mom!
Sis said we won't have to go fetch any more water!
Can we go play now?
What is it with you two?
You didn't even greet Mrs. Jamling properly!
- Good morning!
Good morning. Billy should be somewhere around.
Want to play together?
Yes!
Can we, mom?
Let's see. Ever since we disembarked here,
the two of you did me a great deal of help...
Fine then.
Let's say you have a vacation today.
Then, I will be playing together with Billy!
Wait for me, sis!
Can't you play alone every once in a while?
I cannot!
Your family is moving to Adelaide soon, is it not?
It seems like the most probable course.
I'm sure my husband will find a good plot there.
My spouse had left for Adelaide yesterday
and has not returned yet.
My, you mean he didn't even spend the night at home?
Yes, although he said
he would be back by yesterday.
It sure takes him longer than expected.
It sure does.
If you enter the woods after dark,
returning home might get tricky.
I thought so as well...
That's right!
There's nothing to worry about.
How about another cup?
Dad, I wonder if we are already halfway there.
Why? Tired of walking?
Just a bit.
We can rest a little.
It's alright.
Let's get out of the woods sooner.
This is probably the right way... I believe.
Dad, what did you just say?
I'm saying that we did not take the wrong road.
Are you sure it's all alright?
Probably, yes.
But mind you, I'm going through here for the first time.
Which reminds me,
we have not met anyone in a while.
Let's take a little rest after all.
Are you thirsty?
What's wrong?
It's like I've heard a human voice now.
Human voice?
I heard no such thing recently.
Okay...
Dad!
Now I heard something too.
It sounds like a growl.
Aborigines may always be around.
Aborigines?
Evidently, the sound came from this direction.
Those woods are home to aborigines,
so that probably was one of them.
Dad!
Someone is definitely calling for help.
We'll go to check, right, dad?
We will.
What, just a rabbit?
Ohh, it startled me.
That voice again.
This way!
You can go play there,
but promise me you will listen to Billy.
But Billy is just five months older than me!
At this age, even five months make the difference.
Either way, don't stray too far away, will you?
And don't forget to look after Lucy-May, okay?
I cannot take responsibility for that as well, mom!
How come? Why are you saying
you cannot look after your little sister?
This child is not like other kids!
Once she lays an eye on a peculiar animal,
nothing has any sway over her daze.
When we're in a hurry, this is especially unbearable.
Today you are heading to the beach, right?
Should she see a peculiar creature there,
she can watch all she wants.
If she sees a cute one, that's perfectly tolerable.
But instead, be it a centipede, a lizard, or a caterpillar,
Lucy-May gets dazed by their peculiarity regardless!
Even by caterpillars?
Lucy-May, be so kind to only adore cute things.
But caterpillars are cute!
There, see?
You feel inclined to take this along?
Mosh would also be happy to play on the beach!
He'd be slowing us down.
It's fine because I will be carrying him!
Billy turned up!
Sorry I kept you waiting!
I entrust them to your care then.
Sure!
Then, we'll be on our way, mom.
- On our way!
Billy!
What about your father?
Has he not returned from Adelaide yet?
No. Not yet returned.
Take care!
Okay!
Help me! Is there someone?
Mr. Jamling!
I wonder just at what point could I stray off that road.
No wonder, considering it was pitch black.
Should have stayed overnight in Adelaide.
My household probably went crazy worried
when I didn't make it home last night.
I'm immeasurably sorry, Mr. Poppel.
No, no.
We've just got back on track.
Indeed.
Put me down somewhere around here.
Get ready then.
I sure hope you did not break your leg.
It's probably alright.
Just a sprain, I think.
Now then, how do we get you back to your tent...
Oh, no! You were on your way to Adelaide,
didn't you, Mr. Poppel?
I can't abuse your hospitality. Somehow, I will...
Right! I will come crawling back home.
Now that I can see the road,
I won't trouble you any more.
With that leg, there's no way you return by yourself.
We don't mind going to Adelaide tomorrow.
Still...
At any rate, you are too feeble for it now.
Mr. Jamling, if you cling to my shoulder,
you can walk home using one leg only.
Ben, don't forget to carry along Mr. Jamling's belongings.
Okay!
Now, let's try to stand up, Mr. Jamling.
Thank you, Mr. Poppel.
Forget it.
Sand is not suited for walking at all.
It really isn't.
My legs already start to sore.
We did not even walk terribly far yet.
But at least, no other kids ever go to that place, right?
Lucy-May!
Did you forget your promise not to fall behind?
I remember it!
What is in there?
An adorable bug!
A bug?
Look!
What a disgusting bug!
Toss it away at once!
Never!
Hey.
Now that I think of it,
probably no one has ever been beyond that cape.
Right. Why won't we hurry, then.
Walking in those has become so painful.
I should go barefoot.
Mom said we should not
be walking barefoot here!
Of course she did.
But unless you spill it out, mom will never know.
This feels so much better!
I can walk a dozen that way!
Away you go!
You threw away your shoes?
Of course not. Just deposited.
We'll go back the same road, after all.
I still don't understand.
It's fine. Just remember those rocks, will you?
I'll take mine off too.
Except I'll carry them along.
Now, let's hurry to the other side of that cape!
Exploration is finally underway!
Wait for me, sis!
I really can't stress enough how sorry I am
for compelling you to waste your whole day tending to me.
You really should stop prattling like that.
Besides, your leg is worn out too. You'd better
spend the rest of the way on my back. Here, get on.
Please forgive my weightiness.
We'd have a good deal of carriages passing by us in England.
But here, it's no one to pass by.
Oh, it reminds me!
Left something behind?
No, not about that. I believe, eventually,
you are transporting all your belongings to Adelaide?
Without a doubt. I was going to Adelaide today
in order to hire a wagon for that.
About that —
Adelaide is not exactly rich in wagons.
There are no wagons?
How am I supposed to move my luggage then?
No, I didn't say there are none. It's just that they are scarce.
Only a few people lived there until recently.
In absence of wagons, a cow will do.
I don't mind an ox cart.
Ox carts are few as well.
You mean, even if I go to Adelaide to hire a cart
next morning, I won't find any?
That is very likely so.
Does this mean we will have to go on
living under tents in that beach camp forever?
Well, eventually, there will be some carriages.
I went through the numerous difficulties
of bringing a prefabricated house here from England.
But in the end, I'm unable
to even carry it to Adelaide from the shore.
Rome was not built in one day either.
The surveying is behind the schedule, not only in the city.
The allotment surveying is hindered as well.
Applicants are not getting their plots.
Allotment surveying is delayed?!
That's right.
My new farm here, in South Australia...
I came here with an idea of building an unmatched farm...
But now, seeing how I cannot even get my hands on the land,
what in the world
did we come all the way to South Australia for?
What in the world for...
Dad!
Please don't.
Here! Look, here it is!
Don't be so noisy, sis!
Are you sure, Lucy-May?
I can do it!
You're just a sad sack.
This time I'll do it for sure.
Ships don't seem to ever pass through here.
We have a pretty big gulf, don't we?
We do. It was first discovered by captain Flinders.
They called it St Vincent Gulf.
I know that story too. Next, general Light arrived here.
He sailed around the bay and mapped it.
The one responsible for Adelaide planning
is general Light as well.
He is a great person, isn't he?
You bet! When I grow up,
I will be going on expeditions here and there as well.
Then, it will befall on me to search for places
captain Flinders and general Light never set foot on.
I will go on expeditions too.
They'd never permit a girl to join!
I'm a resourceful one.
Forget it!
I will not do that!
Do it!
Not!
Do!
Something there!
It looked like a human.
What could it be?
Don't say nonsense!
This place is never visited by any folks.
But I swear, I saw a head behind that cliff!
That was just a trick of your eyes.
I'm sure of having seen it!
Look! Something is peeking over it again!
Now I have this feeling it too,
but I still see naught.
Hey Billy, can you go take a quick look?
Me? But this place was never trodden by any folks!
Exactly what an adult explorer would long for!
I could go if there's two of us...
No need if we're three!
This voice is telling something.
Certainly not in English.
What it this animal called?
Must be sea lions.
I don't think those are seals.
Sea lions?
Their mugs are kinda cute.
You'd never tell.
It looks at us!
They are not mordacious, right?
It's fine! If we don't act funny here,
nothing will happen there as well.
But aren't they scary?
There's nothing to be scared of!
I'll go take a closer look at them!
Don't! Look at those impressive teeth!
Lucy-May, looking from up here is just as good.
I'm going there alone.
Come to your senses, don't go!
Just a little peek and a touch.
Don't!
Lucy-May!
We knew all too well the extents
of Lucy-May's love for animals.
But as she was approaching that bizarre animal
called the sea lion, we were really quaking in our barefoots.
Look out!
Lucy-May...
To have the naval surgeon Dr. Dayton examine Mr. Jamling's leg,
dad had to row the boat out in the storming sea.
Next time in Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
Sunny After the Rain. Join us again!
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
On an eucalyptus tree there's a baby Koala
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
With his mom poking around, climbing branches up and down
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
For us to have a feast, let's find a lot of leaves
Kaze no yurikago ohiru ne yo
As I take a nap of ease, coddled by the breeze
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Do you know? Do you know? Do you know?
Mizube ni asobu waraikawasemi
There is a laughing Kookaburra playing by the waterflow
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
All he does is merry laugh, so his spirits don't go low:
Itazura sarete mo uha-ha-ha-ha
He is up to mischief again, uha-ha-ha-ha
Misetaina misetaina mori no dōbutsu
Let us go and look, let us go and look at the creatures of the woods
Misetainaa
Let's go look at them!
Timing, translation: Perevodildo
Quality check, editing: Ziusudra
The Sorcery Party