Episode 5
Clear After the Rain
It's dangerous down there, Lucy-May!
Please come back!
Lucy-May's love for animals made her approach the flock of sea lions mindlessly and completely deaf to my importunities.
Look out!
It's alright. Keep сalm and I won't startle you.
Therefore, you better not startle me either.
Keep quiet!
Lucy-May! Flee! Flee outta there, quick!
Lucy-May! You alright?
Everyone escaped into the sea.
What were you thinking standing idly,
surrounded by sea lions?
I thought how sea lions faces
are absolutely cute from near!
Were you really not one bit scared?
Not at all.
You spooked me.
I was so afraid they would eat
you or something even worse.
Ridiculous!
It starts to rain hard!
Let's find a shelter somewhere soon!
Under those rocks would do. Move!
Turns out sea lions hate thundery rain as well.
Easy, we're already home.
My, you are not wet at all!
I was sheltering from rain at Jamling's.
But I figured it won't stop shortly.
Has Mr. Jamling returned home at last?
No, not yet.
I heard he went to Adelaide yesterday.
And he certainly was not planning to stay there...
Ms. Jamling seems to grow really worried.
Now it's also the wind.
This rain is hardly stopping any time soon.
I sure hope your dad and Ben
did not get sodden in Adelaide.
The wind picked up, Mr. Jamling.
We should get home sooner.
But if we head out now,
we'll get soaked to the skin.
My wife is probably pulling out her hair.
It's not so far from here to the tents.
But not with that leg...
I'm sure there is no fracture.
It's but a small sprain,
nothing to hinder me from walking.
When we get back to the tent,
we should show you to a physician.
Physician?
I thought there are no physicians around.
There are no ashore,
but one is stationed on the ship.
Ah, the naval surgeon.
The man that never gets sober.
He is the only doctor we have.
Mr. Poppel, we should head out.
Getting soaked does not bother me.
Sorry to trouble you furthermore,
but would you mind to find a branch for me to use as a cane?
You want to go home by yourself?
Yes.
Careful.
You did me an invaluable favor
by bringing me all the way here.
I have to manage the rest by myself somehow.
Therefore I need a cane.
Mr. Jamling, you will go there together with us.
But you'll get wet.
Here. Please mount my back.
Mr. Poppel...
This rain is not going to stop.
How do you know?
Intuition tells me.
I think it will be stopping shortly.
Why so?
Intuition tells me.
Don't be a copycat, Lucy-May.
But that's how I really feel!
Wait all you want,
the sea lions are not coming back.
We're getting soaked here anyhow.
Let's head out.
I guess. Mom might also start worrying.
That's right.
Mom and I had our mighty share of worrying
when dad did not return from Adelaide last night.
At a time like this,
the sooner we return, the better.
Lucy-May, catch up quickly!
Kate, you remember the place
you left your shoes, don't you?
Perhaps.
You don't sound terribly confident to me.
Yes, I am not confident.
You'll help us look for it, won't you, Billy?
Like I have a choice.
Mr. Poppel.
Yes?
Will your tent weather this intact?
I think so.
If the wind grows any stronger than this,
some of the tents are bound to get blown away.
As for our tent,
it will certainly be safe and sound.
I believe, ours has nothing to fear as well.
Our uncle has always been an inborn carpenter.
Thanks to that, our dad, though a farmer by trade,
is a universal handyman.
Therefore, our tent is drum-tight.
I also helped to stretch it.
Oh, I see. I sure hope when Billy grows up to your age,
he makes just as helpful assistant to me.
Billy is ten, right?
He is the same age as our Kate.
For now, it's impossible.
Kate, for instance,
is good for nothing in comparison to me.
You caught a cold already?
It's not a cold.
Just some bug flew into my nose.
Just as Clara is finally getting better,
I'm about to get another older sister come down sick.
I am not getting sick, you hear me?
Don't you think this rock looks familiar?
That's about where sis tossed her shoes.
You think so too?
It's here alright.
It's here, alright.
It was certainly this way...
That's odd, it should totally be around here.
Rather than standing there idly,
help me look for it, you two!
Whatcha said?
I stepped on it...
On what?
I don't know yet.
But it's so slippy to the touch...
Can you pull your leg out?
I guess.
What was that?
It went to this side!
Where is it, where?
What is this thing?
I don't think it's a snake.
Are there even snakes like this?
It has proper legs.
Then it's a lizard.
I guess, must be a lizard.
It has like two heads.
It really does...
What a peculiar fellow.
I hope it will come out again.
I need to find out if it really does have two heads!
It can be a biting species...
Did it bite you, sis?
See? It did not bite even after being stepped on.
It's a good one.
This could be averted
had I heeded to mom's advice on safety.
What advice?
Those parts are full of dangerous insects.
She told me to stay in boots at all times
so as to not get stung.
The head must be on the side it is walking forward with.
This one right now was no insect.
Peculiar as it is,
I still think is was a lizard.
A lizard is even graver a case!
I totally should have not taken off my boots.
Lucy-May! Start looking for my boots!
There's no way I'm setting an unshoed foot
into that grass ever again!
Boots?
Your boots are right here.
You found them in that place?
I was sure to have tossed them yonder...
Someone must have brought 'em here, then.
Right! No other way around!
But who would do such a thing?
Doesn't seem like any of the immigrants reached here yet.
Why would anyone fool around
with some boots in the first place?
I figured it!
I know who fooled around with boots.
Who?
Don't look at him.
Sideways behind me,
someone is hiding behind the rock.