South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 02 - A Cute Fellow
I wanna eat!
Sure, sure.
I'm getting up soon.
Yesterday we arrived in Australia.
So, we spend our first night
sleeping in this settlement right on the shore.
Together with my little sister Lucy-May,
I slept in a barrel because the tent was too cramped.
Tob! Is everyone still sleeping?
Sleepy.
Lucy-May, wake up!
I'm still sleepy...
You were the one who woke me up this night!
I didn't wake you up!
You did wake me up!
I didn't...
I was awake.
Because I saw a very strange animal!
It was jumping like that,
hop-hop, with its two legs only.
Are you sure it wasn't a rabbit?
Certainly! This is not how rabbits do it.
What are you doing, Lucy-May?
At night, while we slept, Lucy-May
saw some animal that was like a giant rabbit!
But it totally wasn't a rabbit!
Didn't you just say it was hopping?
It was only hopping on two feet, not four.
This country must certainly have plenty
of animals that you won't see in England.
There!
Take those birds, for example.
They look like parrots to me.
That's true.
Ah, I'm sorry, but could you two
go gather some firewood?
We've already ran out
of what we gathered yesterday.
Can't Clara go do it?
She still has a fever.
We'd better let her get some rest.
You've a strong fever, Clara.
Ben, moisten her forehead to cool her down.
Okay.
Ben, I'll be fine. I'll get up now.
Don't exert yourself, Clara.
He's right, get back to sleep.
Really, I'm such a nuisance...
Just as we finally made it to Australia.
We still have a lot of things
to bring over from the ship, right?
Clara, it's best that you don't worry about that.
That's right, sis.
Now...
Clara, get some sleep.
Various challenges would rain on us
starting now, I believe.
When that happens, you'll have to
lend a helping hand to your mother.
For that, I need you to get a good rest and fully recover.
Okay.
Hey, look!
Some driftwood got washed up here too.
Here.
Hey. I have something to say to you.
What is it?
Next time you ask me to pick up some driftwood,
how about you put that hamster down instead?
I just thought I'd let Marsh play along the seashore.
Do it then.
Right, good idea.
Well, Marsh. You can come out now.
Start gathering firewood now.
Okay, I'm gathering.
Until later, then.
Yeah.
Hey, Kate, can you take this firewood off me?
You picked it up,
why don't you carry it yourself?
But I'll also have to take Marsh on our way back.
I can't do that with firewood.
Not my concern.
Ah! It's John!
Hey.
What are you two up to?
Gathering wood for the fire.
Need a hand?
Thanks. But don't you need to return to ship now?
No. Today I'm on a furlough until noon.
Hey, John, can you take this firewood?
Sure thing.
I can't carry it all because of Marsh.
What a slyboots you are, I swear!
Here you go then.
Marsh, come.
Oh, Marsh!
What is Clara doing, Kate?
Lying in bed with a fever again.
Tob, caught something?
Come on. Let me take a look.
W-What, a lizard? Okay, okay,
now take it away from me. Hurry!
I'll be visiting the ship again later.
We're a bit worried about our things.
That ship will be anchored for another week.
You don't have to be in such a hurry
to unload your things.
No, I didn't plan to unload them today.
But I'm sure the rest of our things are in a disarray.
So I just wanted to bundle all our things together.
Yes. That'd be the best thing to do right away.
You see, we brought with us from England
a whole prefabricated home.
Will you assemble it here?
Of course not.
We'll assemble it in Adelaide.
Then, you need to transport that prefabricated home
all the way to Adelaide, don't you?
How else will we assemble it?
But... With what means will you transport it?
Obviously, with a wagon or an oxcart.
Around here, both are rather sparse.
I've been to this area before so I know.
Oh well. We'll figure something out.
John...
Would you perchance like to have breakfast with us?
Thank you, but I already had one on the ship.
Then, maybe just some tea?
Well, it's finished, honey.
Ah! That'll help a lot.
Um...
I heard Clara is unwell again.
May I check on her?
Kate, wait!
This John is such a villain!
In the end, he didn't help me one bit!
You're still too little to understand it.
John had to go ahead
because he's worried about Clara's health.
I'm worried about her just as much!
John's worry is a special one.
How?
You need to grow up just a bit more to understand.
Why are you being so puffy? You could just say John is in love with Clara and be done with it.
Then the same goes for Clara. Isn't it so?
You can be surprisingly precocious.
Clara.
Is that you, John?
You're still unwell, huh? How bad is it?
Just a small fever. No big deal.
It's all a big deal around here,
with not a single doctor around.
Yes.
If you'd like a tea, I can bring you some.
I don't want any.
What's more important, John,
when are you leaving?
In a week.
I see.
Once you leave here,
we won't see each other again. Ever...
Could you at least go ashore every day until then?
Certainly not every day.
Because I'm just a deckhand,
I'm up to my eyeballs in work.
I see.
In just a week...
I made up my mind.
What do you mean?
I'm leaving the ship.
Eh?
Just not right now.
After I return to England, I'll take my little brother
and leave for Australia at once.
Seriously?
Yes.
Both our parents are dead.
My only family is my brother.
That's why we two can easily move to Australia.
And then, we'll meet again!
John...
Oh! Dad is talking to Mr. Pettywell.
Out of question, Mr. Pettywell.
There's no way I'm selling that prefabricated home.
But I'm prepared to fork out
twice the price you paid for it in England.
Twice the price?
That's right. This country
has enough trees to cover all your needs.
For such an artisanal fellow,
constructing a house is a piece of cake.
Even so, it'll be a couple of days
before we get that prefabricated home...
I want to be living in a proper house straight away.
Sleeping in a tent has already become unbearable.
How long will it take you to assemble that house?
Well, I could maybe do it in two weeks...
No... No! Not selling it. Period.
Maybe with some more on the table...
Not happening.
We'll assemble that house in the city of Adelaide.
We also can't sleep in this tent indefinitely.
Well, I'll leave you with some more time to think it over.
I'm not going to sell it.
All the way until you said you're not actually selling it,
my heart was going pit-a-pat!
Sell it, huh?
Ben, as soon as we've eaten,
we'll go arrange our things on the ship.
Okay.
Mom said to bring along the trunk with tablecloth from Grandma.
Hm.
But I don't have any idea which trunk it is.
I do.
Fetch water?
Fetch water??
Where do we need to go for it?
There's a creek meandering through those woods.
There's nothing dangerous there, right?
Why, of course.
If it was even slightly dangerous,
I'd never send you two there to fetch water.
There's just...
Just what?
Those woods are home to the aborigines.
While fetching water yesterday,
I ran into some myself.
What is an aborigine?
We call that the people
who lived here before us.
I thought no one lived in Australia
until the English turned up!
Well, that is not entirely true.
In Australia, you can't even go to school or church to make the life more exciting.
All we do is getting an errand after an errand.
True.
Hey, imagine we meet some of those aborigines!
Yeah.
I wanna meet them!
What kind of people you think they are?
I'll know when I meet them!
They'd probably go nuts from talking to you.
Ah! A pretty bird!
We might even run into the animal you saw last night!
Ah! That curious fellow!
What's wrong?
Someone's there.
You think it's an aborigine?
An aborigine?
I'm so scared!
What now?
Didn't you just say you wanna meet one?
Why, it's Billy!
Isn't it Billy!
Hey. You came to fetch water too?
Yes!
Wait, Billy! Let's go home together!
Go home together!
Sure.
Say, Billy, have you seen the aborigines?
Yeah, seen them.
Give it here. I'll fill it for you.
Thanks.
What kind of people they are?
Well, the undressed kind.
Undressed?
Yeah, just like that.
Come to think of it, being undressed is probably
the simplest way to put up with this place's hotness.
Makes sense.
And what else? Hey, what else about them?
They're rather dark.
Sunburnt maybe?
Gotta be it!
Can we rest a little, Kate?
How can you be that weak?
We'll see about that!
You really don't have to force yourself.
I'll manage! I can do it!
Relax, we can take a rest.
I'm not resting!
You're such a stubborn kid!
Take a rest I said!
Ah? Hey, Kate, I can't see you walking!
Oh, what a nasty kind you are!
I was serious about...
I don't need no rest!
Take a rest!
Not resting!
I've had enough of both of you!
I wonder if we'll have to come all the way here
to fetch water every day.
It's a bit far.
But you're not staying in this area forever, are you?
Dad said we'll be moving to Adelaide proper.
We even brought along a prefabricated home.
We'll go to Adelaide and assemble it there!
Oh... That kinda sounds wonderful!
One can make a fortune catching birds here
and selling them back in England.
Oh?
What could that be?
What?
There! See the spot where that branch splits?
True! What is that thing?
Where is it?
I don't see.
Looks like a bear.
Bear?
Ah, I see, I see! You're right, like a bear!
Bears can climb trees?
Who knows.
But this one is pretty small for a bear.
Let's catch it!
How do you plan to catch it?
By climbing this tree!
Think you can climb that high?
Billy can. He is a boy after all.
Can you climb it, Billy?
Well I won't say I can't climb it...
Climb it then!
Come on, Billy, please!
I want to catch that cute fellow!
If I don't come back with water soon, mom will...
Fine. Forget it. I'm climbing it myself.
Lucy-May, you'd better stop!
I sure hope it doesn't bite.
Ah...
Catch it for me, Billy!
Good.
John, can I do the rowing?
Sure. Be my guest.
I'm sorry to waste your precious free time
on our errands, John.
No, I'm glad to be useful.
Not like that!
Plunge the oars deeper into the water.
Okay.
Good, good. Keep going.
What are you doing, Billy?
He seems kinda dead!
Is he dead?
Relax, relax. Just very sleepy.
Then catch him quickly!
How do you know it doesn't bite?
It's fine, fine!
Tsk. Of course you say that.
You... have quite a cute kinda face.
Listen, don't bite me, okay?
What's wrong, Billy?
What's going on? Hey, hey!
Can't you ever be quiet, please?
This fellow just won't budge!
Well, look at you!
You scared me to death!
Wonderful!
This is wonderful!
Incredible, Billy!
Please be cautious not to drop this kid!
It's alright. He's clinging to me real tight.
What a calm guy!
Ah! I can't wait any longer!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
What are Kate and Lucy doing?
It's not supposed to take them that long.
Lucy-May, what will you do with him next?
I'll keep him!
You know you already have Marsh, don't you?
We don't have a whole lot of food for them.
Besides, dad wouldn't be too happy
about you keeping such an animal!
But it's not every day that you meet an animal this cute!
It was exactly so.
This creature called Koala was yet another animal
that you won't find anywhere outside Australia.
Though we only learned about it much later.
I'm definitely keeping you!
He's really is cute, hands down.
To top off our tribulations,
Mr. Pettywell's black dog ran off with our meat.
Trying to settle that,
dad quarreled with Mr. Pettywell.
Next time on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Exchange".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you