South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 37 - Robbers on the Prairie
It sure is getting hot again.
Summer has come again.
This would be our fourth summer
since we came to Southern Australia.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
You leg hasn't fully healed yet,
so you shouldn't work in the field.
It's too hot for me to stay home doing nothing.
But...
My leg is all fine already.
Yay! It's over! It's over!
Goodbye, teacher!
That's right, starting tomorrow, I won't be passing through here, for the time being.
And... I wonder if it was this tree.
Or was it this one?
Previously, Lucy found money
in the bird nest on the tree.
"What if it'll have money in it again?"
At that time, she was clinging tight
to that naive thought.
It was this tree for sure.
Hm?
Kate, are you doing well?
Ah! Brother!
Hello, Little. I see you're doing well too.
How come you're you riding a carriage today?
Ah. That's cause I came
to run some errands in the city hall.
Then, you'll have to leave again soon?
I have some time, but only a bit of it.
Ah, that was scary. I'm sure it was that bird just now.
The one that found the money.
There it is!
None here.
Such a too-good-to-be-true thing
couldn't possibly happen to me twice.
You sure there's no mistake, Adam?
Yes. There's no specified time, but master
will transport the money in the afternoon.
Is he bringing along that stupid bulldog?
Probably.
That's bad.
That dog will cause trouble.
We've gotta do something about it.
I'll see what I can do.
Doctor! Doctor Deighton!
Oh, Lucy!
Are you going to our house, Doctor?
That's right. I need to examine your father's leg.
Are you returning from school?
Yes.
Knowing how much you detest going to school, it's admirable how you do it without taking any breaks now.
Can't be helped. But at least
we've vacations starting tomorrow.
Eh?
Summer vacations, Doctor!
Oh, really? No wonder it's so hot today.
Doctor, did Mr. Pettywell
tell you anything else since the last time?
About the house?
Yes.
He sure as heck did. Every day,
he comes to tell me to vacate the house sooner.
Yesterday, he said I've only four days left
until one month runs out.
Mr. Pettywell did?
He doesn't do it himself.
Always sends his agent.
Usually that servant Adam.
Ah!
Huh?
I saw that man a while ago.
He might come to my place today as well.
What'll you do if they drive you out of that house?
Even if you persist in saying you're not going anywhere,
I'm sure Mr. Pettywell won't hesitate
to tear that house down.
Probably.
What will you do, Doctor?
I'll think of something.
Thanks for all that concern, Lucy.
Oh! A carriage stopped in front of our house.
So it seems.
I'm back, Little.
Tell me, Little, who came in that carriage?
Father, I'm leaving now.
Hm.
Try not to exert yourself just yet.
I should be fine, doing this little.
Mother told me.
About what?
We no longer have any money in the house, right?
Well, I've not been working for the last month.
Well, I thought there is still some saved up.
You should know the prices
have been growing like mad these days.
Yes. So far, I've been taking it easy. From now on,
I'll be bringing as much money as I can into the house.
Up to now, you've already been doing
more than enough for us.
Once I can work again, we'll figure something out.
Don't worry about that.
But with a leg like that...
Yeah, it still aches a little.
Just as I thought, you shouldn't be using it yet, father.
Damn it...
Brother!
Hey. You're back too?
Father, I'm home.
I see, welcome back.
Doctor Deighton also came with a visit.
Eh? This could be very bad.
Get ready for a lecture from Doctor, father.
Huh? Yeah...
When do your school vacations start?
Tomorrow.
I can finally play as much as I want!
Your nonchalance is one thing that never changes.
Ben, did you come here by carriage?
Yes, that's right.
Since you have vacations starting tomorrow,
how about I give you and Kate a ride to the port?
To the port? I like this!
The port changed considerably.
It looks all great and gorgeous now.
You've not been there for a while, have you?
Yes.
Return before nightfall, okay?
Okay!
I'll be sure to catch a ride back for them,
so don't worry about that, mother.
I'm counting on you.
Little, behave and wait patiently!
How about we depart, then?
Go ahead.
I'll come home next Sunday!
I'll be waiting!
Let's go! Giddyup!
Be careful, you two!
We're off!
Bye-bye!
Silver, come.
Adam! Hurry up!
Ah... Yes!
Right...
Alright. We can leave now, George.
Giddyup!
There aren't any kangaroos here?
Ben, have you seen any kangaroos on your way to the town?
I haven't.
Even though there are talks about kangaroos
swarming this area recently.
You think someone could've
slaughtered them for their meat?
You didn't have to say something so brutal, Ben.
Beef and pork have been
increasingly expensive recently.
It seems, some folk switched to eating the meat
from kangaroos, sheep, and even opossums.
Stop! Stop! I don't want to hear that.
It's been a while since we last ate bacon either...
Kate.
Our family is in a tight spot right now.
As a part of our family, you should render
any assistance possible to dad and mom.
Okay.
I know you're shrewd so you probably
already understand the situation, more or less.
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
What is it, Lucy?
I can render assistance as well!
Of course you can!
Why aren't you also counting on me, then?
You're still too little...
But I'm counting on you.
Not recognizing me as a grown-up was rude of you!
For God's sake, Lucy!
That's dangerous!
I get it! I'm recognize! I recognize you!
Oh my, seems like a carriage
is catching up from behind.
You're right.
That's Mr. Pettywell's carriage!
Pettywell's?
Giddyup!
We can by no means lose to him, Ben!
Alright, I get it. Hang on tight, you two!
Okay!
Giddyup!
Giddyup! Giddyup!
You can do it, Ben.
Don't lose to Mr. Pettywell.
Damn it!
George, strike the horse more!
Already did, sir!
Do it more! More!
Giddyup! Giddyup! Hey-ah!
Giddyup! Giddyup!
Ben!
Forget it. If we spur it any further,
the horse will collapse!
So frustrating!
Damn it!
Keep such lousy things out of your mouth, Lucy!
But you said it multiple times just now.
Well, that... I'm a man, so it's alright for me.
Damn it!
Damn... Frustrating.
Damn... it.
We can play around for two more hours, right?
Listen, come back to here when you're done.
I'll take you to the stagecoach station.
Got it. Kate, let's go to the end of that embankment.
Okay.
Take care, will you?
Sure.
Wait, Lucy!
The port was nothing like what it's been
by the time of our arrival three years ago.
What are you doing, Lucy?
I don't want to see any bugs again.
It's not a bug.
Look, it's a seashell.
Ah, so pretty!
Say, Kate. It wasn't this place
where we disembarked, was it?
It was more to the south.
Remember how when we first set foot on the ground,
we repeated after dad and thump-thumped it?
Alley-hop!
Yay!
Thank you, John.
This is the land where we'll spend the rest of our lives.
Now...
Feels so nice!
We're in Australia!
I forgot all about it.
Did we really do that?
I couldn't forget it.
When we first disembarked,
we still had a hope burning bright in us
that we'll get the land straightaway,
and build an enormous farm.
That hope left for somewhere else now, didn't it?
That's not true.
You're right. Without hope, everything is lost, isn't it?
Yes.
I think it's best that you stop at that, Mr. Popple.
I suppose drinking is bad for my leg, isn't it?
When it comes to alcohol, I can't speak too harshly about it, but still, too much of it won't do anyone good.
If I don't drink a cup or two,
I might be unable to take it, Doctor.
But you can get right back to work
once your leg heals up.
Save for continuing to work at that godforsaken place,
my prospect for future are less than bright.
Just give it some time.
That's what I've been telling myself until now.
If you give way to despair,
what do you think will become of your family?
You sure like eating well, Marsh.
My family...
Hey!
Go!
Goodbye!
Wish we could play by the sea for longer.
We should've gone fishing.
We should've gone swimming.
In the end, all we gained was this seashell.
Really, that's a beautiful one.
Yes.
Hey, you still haven't fixed it?
Sir...
Hurry the damn up! Hurry up!
Master! A stagecoach is coming.
You can return to Adelaide on that.
It doesn't look like you can fix it
any time soon, does it?
Yes. Terribly sorry for the delay...
Why, you...
Adam, what will we do about him?
I don't suppose they'll let him into the stagecoach.
But I wanted to return today,
together with him and the bag. Today!
Well, I'll ride with you,
so don't worry about the bag.
You don't strike me as all that reliable.
Master...
Fine, go stop that stagecoach for me.
Okay!
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Whoa!
As you can see, we're in a bit of a trouble.
But Master would like to return to Adelaide sooner.
Alright, get in.
Toss your bag on the roof.
No, we'd rather keep it.
Giddyup!
Um... Excuse me.
Yes, thank you.
Oh my, if it isn't Mr. Popple's daughters?
Good afternoon, Mr. Pettywell.
Good afternoon.
Earlier, your carriage was completely unable
to keep up with mine, wasn't it?
But it seems, yours broke down as a result.
Huh?
Giddyup!
Whoa!
Ah! It's a robber!
Stop!
Huh?
Go!
We're the robbers! Everyone out!
Kate...
Lucy...
What's going on?
They're robbers!
Robbers?
Make it quick before I killed everyone!
Get off faster!
O-Okay.
You get off too!
Now, you people come this way.
Come on, start walking, everyone!
Kate...
We'll be alright, Lucy.
Hey, you! Collect everyone's
money and valuables into this bag!
I can't do no such thing.
We're short on hands here,
so I need your help with it.
But if you keep being uncooperative...
No! No! No! I'll do it!
Good, that's what I like to hear.
Then, begin by putting your money
and that ring into the sack.
Okay...
You still have more money on you!
N-no, I absolutely...
Shut up!
And what's this called?
Ah! T-That's...
You scum!
You get it? Get all your money
and valuables out, people!
Now, get up and collect it!
The way you've been clutching onto this bag
suggests there's something important in it.
Ah!
No... Um...
Hey! Give it here at once.
Ah...
Don't you value your life at all?
Right... Here.
Ah! Not that! That, I definitely can't give up!
Hey! Get back to the others!
I can't give it to you!
You don't need your life or what?
I can't give it up!
I'm never giving it to you!
Master, think about your life...
Yes. There's no specified time,
but master will transport money in the afternoon.
Are you sure there's no mistake, Adam?
Is he bringing along that stupid bulldog?
Probably.
Hey! Move away from there!
Or else you'll lose both the bag and your life!
Ah... No...
Alright, you have until I count to ten to move away...
One!
Kate, I'm scared!
It's just a method of threatening!
Two!
I'm scared.
Three!
Four!
"What exactly is it that Lucy is so afraid of?"
Five!
Six!
Back then, I didn't know the answer yet.
Seven!
Eight!
Nine!
I know who was the robbers' accomplice.
But the guys in police wouldn't believe me!
I should do what I can to catch them myself!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Lucy, the Detective".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you