South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 13 - Ben Has Arrived!
Come out, Sticky!
Sticky? Sticky!
Where did you go, Sticky?!
Sticky!
Did something happen
to the goat, Lucy-May?
Sticky has disappeared!
You're right!
She probably already had a baby!
Ah! That must be so.
Even though we prepared just the place for her
to have a baby, laid down all that grass there!
Where else could she go?
Kate, we should find her!
Agreed.
You start there, near Mrs. Mac's house,
and I'll go check behind,
all the way to the river.
Sticky!
Lucy-May, what's all this yelling
so early in the morning?
Sticky disappeared! And I thought her baby goat
is supposed to be born today!
That's true.
Then help me look for her, dad!
Okay. Clara, you go search as well.
Father, just where in the world
could a goat go to give birth?
It can do it wherever.
It just gotta be someplace safe.
Which means she wasn't comfortable in that tent?
With two girls were sleeping there
in front of her eyes.
Might be the case, too.
Sticky? Sticky!
Stop hiding and come out, girl!
Sticky! Show yourself!
Don't tell me she was feeling thirsty
and went to the river again.
Ah?
Sticky!
Sticky! Where are you?
Come out please!
Ah! Mr. Pettywell brought along this dog.
It'd better not be that you
tried to take a bite of our Sticky!
Everyone, here! Hurry! Hurry!
The babies are born!
Huh?
Come quickly! There are three of them!
Three babies are born!
You can do it!
Keep trying!
Did it!
Remember, it's almost time for breakfast.
Okay.
Lucy-May, what's going on?
Are you fine?
I'm fine, and this feels good!
Are you all right, Lucy-May?
Dem-zuckin-ma-vingers-beelz-zdrange
bud-zdill-good!
Oh?
Don't come near here!
When there's nobody around,
Mr. Pettywell's dog might try
to make a move on Sticky and her babies!
But think of it, Kate. The dog doesn't have any reason
to do something like that.
That dog will find a reason!
Well, at any rate, once we're done with the breakfast,
I'll make an enclosure for the goats.
Thanks, dad.
I'll go relieve Lucy-May.
What are your plans for today after this?
Hm? I'll ask around if there's any oxcart for hire.
We need to hurry with getting Ben
and our luggage to here.
Yes. I wonder if Ben
is managing all right there.
Now, make way, you two.
Well now, do you plan to stay inside there?
I've finished already.
Yay!
This way, they'll always be safe, Kate.
You're amazing, dad!
To build something like that with a breeze!
True!
Remember when he promised to make that house
big one day? I bet, it'll be just as easy for him!
Yes. It totally will.
Could those be the prefabricated home materials?
Good morning to you, Mr. Popple.
Good morning.
Am I correct in saying those are the prefabricated home
materials you brought with you from England?
Yes. Precisely so.
However, I no longer have anything to do with them.
Going somewhere?
Yes, I was hoping to procure an oxcart,
one way or another.
We never have enough oxen and horses
to pull the cars here.
Right...
Come on now, you two.
You need to find me a skilled carpenter.
If he's already busy with other job,
tell him I'll pay him twice the usual rate.
Okay.
All right. Leave immediately, then.
Eh?
No, wait a moment.
It looks like you won't have to go anywhere at all.
Hey! Good Morning, Popple!
Good morning, Mr. Pettywell.
Have you changed you mind,
by any chance, Mr. Popple?
On which matter?
Well, about assembling
that prefabricated home, obviously.
No.
Huh?
Alright, I heard you.
How much do you want?
Name your price, loud and clear!
I don't want any money.
My goodness.
At any rate, I refuse to do
any house-assembling work for you.
Oh my, oh my.
I already have my hands full
of my own house matters that I need to tend to.
Now excuse me.
How can you do that to me?!
After this, I'm heading to the office.
How is your sister's husband looking?
The fever just won't subside, as usual.
We definitely need to have a doctor examine him.
I hope you find one soon.
But that doctor doesn't exist.
Many things like oxen and horses are sparse here,
but the doctors are the sparsest of them.
Ah. I think it's best that we load this one first.
Here.
Oh? I see the loading is almost done.
Good morning, doctor.
How does it look?
Am I going to have to walk all the way to Adelaide
by myself, or is there a vacant seat, after all?
Well as long as your hindquarters are sturdy enough,
I'm sure we'll find some spot to seat you at.
If my hindquarters end up a bit sore,
then so be it.
I don't mean to be nagging,
but doctor, are you serious?
About what?
About staying to live in Australia.
Aye. My mind is made up.
Forever?
Well, more or less.
I'm sure, my tardiness to the ship
was the manifestation of Lord's will.
That's what I'd like to think.
All right! In that case, doctor,
let me take care of the rest for you.
Eh? Take care of what?
For you, doctor,
I can build a magnificent clinic in Adelaide.
What did you say?
Yes, sir. Because I'm such a shrewd merchant,
my undertakings never end up being unprofitable.
No proper doctors here
for thousands of miles around.
If we open a clinic in the middle of it,
there would be lines upon lines of patients.
We could even get away
with charging a little extra.
What do you say if you and me
halve the profits?
Yes. Yes.
Yeah, yeah-yeah.
Idiot.
Huh?
I didn't become a doctor to make money from it!
But don't you need the money
to buy the booze that you love so much?
Naturally. And I'm fine
with being paid just a smidgen.
Just a smidgen!
Very well. But at any rate,
please don't forget about what I proposed.
Sure.
And thanks a lot for letting me
stay at your place yesterday.
Ben, are you ready to set out?
Yes. I'm sure we'll surprise dad a great deal.
Uhm. I bet he never managed
to scout another oxcart in Adelaide.
It's only thanks to you that we scouted this one.
Yep. That's because of my natural knack
for making deals.
Oh, what am I saying?
It's lies, all lies.
I scouted this oxcart purely by chance.
Well, one way or another, we should just be glad
you'll reunite with your family soon.
Yes.
Well then, Doctor,
please get on.
Okay! Okay-okay-okay.
He-he.
Eh? Here? Alright.
Thanks for looking after us.
Goodbye, Mr. Parker.
Right, take care now.
Give my regards to your dad and mom.
And tell them, I'll also be coming
to Adelaide one of these days.
Okay.
Move it!
And say hello from me
to children as well, will you?
Okay, 'kay, 'kay.
Kate! Lucy-May!
Where are you?
Come out now!
You idiot, what'll we do if she finds us?
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hmm.
Mom.
Hm?
When I gave then the list of tasks I got for them,
girls ran off for somewhere, looking appalled.
They're just hopeless.
Well, so be it. We'll do it as two.
Right. So how does it look?
Can still use that stove?
Doesn't seem to have anything wrong with it.
Then, want me to boil some water?
We can do that later.
First, let's arrange the dinnerware
in the right order.
With this, we'll be able to cook inside the house
for the first time in ages, right?
But that sure is a cramped kitchen.
I'm starting to miss
the kitchen we had back in England.
Mother, it's a bit late to be saying that now.
I guess you're right.
Well, let's take the dinnerware out now.
We should be allowed that,
once in a while.
Since our arrival to Australia,
we're only ever being given a list of tasks.
Right! Let's play away the rest
of today, without rush.
What do you want to play?
Anything is fine by me.
You should be the one choosing.
You choose, Kate.
I can't help wondering what was it
Clara was calling us for.
Well, obviously, it was to give us
some new list of tasks, wasn't it?
Must be you're right.
What's wrong? You were the one who proposed running away before Clara gives us a list of tasks, weren't you?
Yeah, that's true.
But now, having pulled off
such a successful escape, what should we play?
Eh? You got something you wanna play?
That's for you to choose.
You choose!
I guess we're returning, then.
Huh? Hey, look!
And here it's just the two of us, huh?
Not having a lot of friends is boring.
Think they'll ever let us join in the fun?
Ah! That girl is so good at climbing trees.
She seems very determined,
despite being a girl.
I can probably do that, too.
Being just two is boring.
True. Hide-and-seek and even tag
are both boring when played by just two.
Do we stop playing, then?
Yeah.
And I still wonder why was Clara
calling us back then.
Hm.
Mom and Clara have their hands full of work
because we've just finished moving.
We'll feel bad for it later,
if we don't try to help at least a bit.
So we ended up doing exactly that.
Ah!
Huh?
A fire?
It might just be!
We need to hurry, Kate!
Uh-huh!
Mom, wouldn't it be best
to take out the firewood that's so damp?
Of course.
Ouch!
This won't do!
We've got Tob sleeping over there.
I'll take him outside now.
Clara, is it a fire?
Where have you two been
all that time?
Uh... Went to the river.
But more importantly,
what's with all that smoke?
Something's wrong with the stove.
The chimney won't draw out any smoke.
There must be something stuck inside it.
The chimney is clogged...
Say, Clara, where's mom?
Eh? Ah! Still in the house.
The two of you stay out.
I need you to look after Tob.
The chimney looks completely clogged.
Barely any smoke is coming out.
Just as I thought.
It looks as though there is some draw, but the smoke
is actually returning into the room through a crack.
I'm afraid it will be easier to rebuild this house
from ground-up than to repair.
Seems so.
Is it just me, or is our house
shrouded in smoke?
Hm? A fire!
A bump?! Can't hold!
Ah!
Are you hurt, Doctor?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Where were you hurt?
In the head?
No, it ain't my head.
Then, it's the leg, isn't it?
Yeah...
Ah! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
At this rate, I guess, it might even be broken.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Up now...
You're a doctor, aren't you?
Instead of guessing, won't you know for sure
once you examine it yourself?
Well, as much as I would've liked to,
it hurts to even touch.
Ouch! Ouch-ouch! See?
That's nothing worth fretting over.
Ugh... Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Hurts-hurts-hurts! Hurts bad.
Eh? Uh?
Oh?
Ha...
Is it broken after all?
No, apparently, it was all right all along.
That's good.
We're almost in Adelaide, Doctor.
Okay.
I guess the house was more busted
than what I liked to believe.
We'll have to do something
about the stove, won't we?
Yeah. At any rate,
it'll require a fundamental repair.
If I do it with Ben's help,
it wouldn't take all that long.
Probably, yes.
But we can't get Ben to come here any time soon.
Unless you've found an oxcart
to carry the rest of our things here?
Hm? Not really.
I don't seem to find a single one.
Then, for how long will Ben
have to stay over there?
We can't do anything.
Which means we can't start the repairs
any time soon either.
We're in trouble, that's for sure.
Whoa!
We gotta think of the names for the babies.
You go think of it.
Well, of course I will.
What you want to be called, little one? Hm?
Ah! You're so cute.
Well, aren't those darn heavy?
Thank you, darling.
Mr. Popple.
Why, you're back already?
Although I've just returned,
I have a favor to ask already.
If there's something I can do, I will do it.
I need you to accompany me
to Carrington Street.
To Carrington Street? What for?
My brother-in-law is getting worse.
I want to show him to a doctor,
who lives on Carrington Street.
Can't that doctor come here instead?
That's impossible.
People come to see him from far and wide.
Very well.
How do you intend to carry him there?
I figured me and you
could carry him on our backs by turns.
I guess our hands are tied,
since it's our only option.
Dad!
Mom!
Hey!
Ah! Ben's here!
Ben!
You've finally come! You're here!
He managed to scout an oxcart by himself.
Ah! But for now, Mr. Bernard,
let's make haste.
Just a minute please.
Can't we use that oxcart
to carry the patient there?
I brought the rest of our things.
Good work with that.
But for now, Ben,
we've got a patient here.
Can we lend that oxcart for a bit longer?
We need to find something
to carry him to the doctor with.
I think it'll be alright for you to lend it.
But if you need a doctor...
Hey... Howdy?
Doctor Deighton?
Hey, Mr. Popple.
My throat is as dry as a desert.
I was hoping you've got
some booze at your place.
Doctor Deighton, truly, you couldn't
have come at a better time.
Eh? You do have some booze?
Oh, mark my words, it's an opportune time
for you to come to our place. Bernard, hurry up!
Eh? So you have it, huh?
Mr. Bernard, this man is Doctor Deighton.
He's one hell of a doctor if I do say so myself.
Oh? Well, it's an honor...
Ah, thanks. But I'd still like to remind you,
my throat is as dry as a desert.
Is it in your house
where they got some booze, young man?
It was unimaginable to us
that we'll get reunited with our brother so soon.
It was the most delighting news.
In addition, bringing along Dr. Deighton
was really well-thought out of him.
While returning from my trip for firewood,
I ran into Mr. Heracles.
I felt obliged to thank him
for saving my life the other day.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A Stout Man".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you