South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 08 - The Eve of our Departure
Help me!
By the time we noticed,
brother was already swept away all the way out
into the open sea, clutching onto a barrel.
Help!
We gotta hurry up and help Ben!
Let's go save him in that boat!
Do you know how to row?
I don't, but Billy must know, right?
Sorry girls, but I got nothing.
We're in trouble...
Just a bit more...
Guess we've no choice,
but to ask those guys for help.
They're thoroughly drunk.
Still, this boat belongs to them, after all.
My brother needs help! Please!
Aye, we tol' him not to go, dint we?
That kid just went to fetch the barrel all by himself.
I understand that,
but I'm asking you to help him now!
Just row the boat for us!
We're in no condition to do any'ing now.
Ain't that obvious? I'm feeling sleepy...
Hey mister! We helped push your cart before, innit?
You could at least row the boat in exchange!
Too bad, kids, but I don't know a thing
about rowing boats.
Then, we also won't help
any of you ever again, understood?
Huh?
Why won't he just let go of the damn barrel
and swim back on his own?
I told him we don't need that kinda barrel!
Ben looks exhausted already!
Help!!
Help me, please!
Help me!
Ain't nothing we can accomplish
with grown-ups who are so drunk!
But Ben...
I will row the boat!
Really, Billy?
I'll try something, at least!
Way to go, kid! That's what a proper boy oughta be like!
And... here.
He drifted further away into the sea!
Lend us a hand!
Let's go!
No need. Kate, you just wait here.
I'll try rowing it by myself.
I think we'll go faster if we both use 1 oar at a time.
I want to go, too!
Be a good girl and wait here!
Let's go, Billy.
What are you doing?
Ben is over there! Over there!
We know that! Stop yelling!
Right, right! It's moving now!
Don't give up, Billy!
Hey, those kids are rowing your boat.
I hope they don't capsize it.
What's going on?
We haven't advanced an inch!
You can't know for sure.
All right!
Umf!
That would be the last one
of your things, Mr. Popple!
Thank you! You've helped us a great deal!
Very well! Take care and farewell!
Mr. Popple, are you sure you want to leave
that prefabricated home behind?
Yes. Mr. Pettywell will later come pick it up himself.
Huh?
You sold it to that man?
It's good to have a surplus of money.
And the one who is the most interested
in that prefabricated home is Mr. Pettywell.
I'd rather you not sell it to someone so ill-tempered.
That's why I also wasn't even considering
selling it to him at first.
But in the end, he was the one
who offered the best price for it.
But still...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Can you see it? Something like a barrel
is floating over there.
Yes, I see it.
And there's also someone clutching onto it.
Huh?
Ah! You're right!
Should we get closer?
Of course, John.
Hey! Ben!
Oh! It really is Ben!
Hey, Ben!
Dad...
What are you doing all the way out here?
Didn't I tell you to look after our belongings, Ben?
Yeah...
This kind of rowing won't get us anywhere!
We're only getting drenched this way!
It's you who has the sloppiest rowing here!
Well, if you say so, just lemme row alone!
Fine. If you say so, do it!
Looks like you don't know what you're doing.
What can I do? I haven't rowed a boat
even once up until now!
Ouch!
I can't see Ben anymore!
Huh?
Did he drown?
Don't get so worked up.
It must be that he's been saved by that boat.
Good morning, madam.
Oh, Mr. Jamling? Is your leg doing fine?
Well, you can more or less say so.
As you can see, I can walk now.
It'll be best if you don't strain yourself too much.
It seems, your husband hadn't returned yet, right?
Yes. He went to unload
our remaining things from the ship.
After all, it's been decided that we move
to Adelaide tomorrow, with all of our things.
Yes, I already knew that, but...
Is it true that Mr. Popple sold
the prefabricated home to Mr. Pettywell?
Huh? To Mr. Pettywell?
It can't be.
I heard about it from Mr. Parker.
Apparently, he was also vying for it.
But I was told Mr. Parker
offered to buy it for a good price...
To me, it's straight-up outrageous!
Mr. Pettywell was also the man who snatched
an oxcart your husband was planning to hire!
He thinks he can get whatever he wants with money!
Why sell your home to him, of all people?
Those materials were very heavy and bulky.
My husband judged that transporting them to Adelaide
would be more trouble than what it's worth.
It's true that oxen and horses strong enough
to transport things are sparse in this place...
It seems, we have no choice but to bring in
more oxen and horses from England.
Definitely.
But eventually, didn't Mr. Popple manage
to find a good oxcart for tomorrow's moving?
If only Mr. Pettywell
didn't snatch the oxcart he was originally...
Hey, Madam. Your husband's not back yet?
He's gone to the ship, Mr. Pettywell.
Ah, I see. I was also going to the ship now,
so maybe I'll run into him there.
Yes...
Madam, don't hold a grudge against me, please.
Mind you, I paid quite the fortune
for that prefabricated home.
I'm not holding any grudges...
Oh? In that case, sweet.
Now, then, it's about time
we unload my prefabricated home from the ship.
What a disagreeable man.
It doesn't seem like Bard
is going to wake up any time soon.
Even if he does, will he be able to speak right away?
Hmm... If he's that drunk, we're in trouble.
I had no idea this mister was also the one
who's supposed to transport our stuff.
Dad, isn't there anyone else you could ask?
I told you yesterday. Mr. Bard's oxcart
was the only one vacant around.
They're short of oxen and horses,
able to pull the cart.
It's just the way it is.
Immigrants keep coming one after another.
And so, everyone just dumps their stuff
here, on the shore.
They have no other means
of transporting it to Adelaide.
The shortest way from here to Adelaide
is still over 10 kilometers long.
Then...
We have no other choice,
but to have Mr. Bard transport our things, right?
Yeah. If we don't do that, there's no telling
when we'll have another chance to move there.
Mr. Bard seems extremely unlikely to wake up.
What should we do, dad?
At any rate, we'll have wait for him
to wake up, isn't that right?
We shouldn't load our things
on his cart without permission.
We're in trouble.
Clara!
Ah!
John, you shouldn't have startled me like that.
Sorry. I'll refill it for you.
They gave you a furlough?
I was helping your father get his luggage ashore.
In just half an hour more,
I'm expected back on the ship.
Half an hour?
So we'll have to part tomorrow...
I intend to keep my promise.
You'll take you little brother
and return to our southern Australia later?
You don't seem to believe it still.
It's just...
I want you to believe me.
This distance between here and England
is so unbelievable.
It takes 100 days to cover.
Your resolve will definitely fade in that long a time.
Me and my brother will migrate
to southern Australia together.
There's no revoking this decision, come what may.
And what if your little brother refuses?
The lad is still just a small kid, and because we've
no parents, I am his only guardian.
Brother will listen to whatever I tell him to do.
Then, we'll meet again?
Uh-huh.
And tomorrow we're not parting
for the rest of our lives?
Uh-huh.
Ah... I'm so glad!
Clara...
Oh?
Huh?
Sitting in such a place!
W-What is?
This creature my sister Lucy-May
has been looking for.
Huh? Where?
Look, at that tree's branch.
Where?
Where is it?
Look. Look, over there.
Ah! There it is! There!
A bear cub?
They say it's called a koala.
Oh? Cute thing, isn't it?
Catch it.
Huh?
Catch the koala.
But I mean... It's sitting so high up. And besides,
the branches around that place are all thin.
Lucy-May is crazy about getting it.
Please catch it.
Oh...
You want it no matter what?
No matter what.
All right. Then, I'll catch it for you.
Ah! Keep going!
Leave this to me!
What's wrong? Only one last push!
Tell me...
What is it?
This guy won't bite me, right?
Hmm.
I don't know for sure, but I was told it's peaceful.
You can do it! One last push!
All right!
Ouch! That hurt!
That was pretty rough.
But look, it's still not trying to escape.
Please try once more.
I can't.
Why so?
My time is up.
Ah!
Sorry, but I really have no time.
Sure. It's all right.
I'm the one who should apologize
for making you climb a tree for me.
You're not very good at climbing trees, are you?
Probably, yes. Ever since I was little,
tree climbing wasn't my forte.
Even now, I still struggle with masts...
It was inconsiderate of me.
I was asking for too much.
Don't mention it.
But now, it's really time for me to go.
I wanted to also help you carry the bucket,
but now I have to dash to make it in time.
Go, then. Hurry.
Goodbye.
I believe you, John.
Tomorrow morning, I'll also come to see you off
when you depart for Adelaide.
Wouldn't it be asking for too much?
I'll think of something.
Mom, I'm sorry it took so long.
You met with John, didn't you?
Yes.
What about Lucy-May? Still away?
So it would seem.
She said she'll take the goat for grazing,
but I wonder where she's gone off to...
Ah? Speak of the devil.
We're back!
You're such bad children, you know that?
Just where have you been for so long?
To the shore!
There, dad and Ben told us
they won't be returning until the evening.
Why so?
To start loading onto the cart our things unloaded from the ship, they'll have to wait until the evening.
And what are those two going to do until then?
Ben is looking after our belongings,
while dad went to look for a crate.
A crate?
A crate in which we'll put Sticky.
Why would we need to put a goat into the box?
Well, we can't have her
walk all the way to Adelaide, can we?
So she'll ride the cart, inside a crate.
You're bringing the goat along?
Of course we do! She's my Sticky, after all.
The goat milk would invariably
come in handy for us.
Ah! Actually!
Lucy-May.
A little while ago I saw a Koala.
Huh? A Koala?
Where?
Right by the creek. You know,
this place perfectly suited for gathering water.
But now that koala is no longer there?
It was still there by the time I turned back.
Actually, John even tried to catch it for me...
Hey! Wait a moment, you two!
At least help us out a bit down here!
I swear, those two are hopeless, aren't they?
You really could have kept it to yourself.
I'm sorry. What do you need help with?
In that case, I'm counting on you.
I'm running a bit low on the firewood.
Go gather some more, please.
Okay.
Could it still be there?
It must be there!
Wah!
Ah!
Which tree are we looking for?
Found it!
Where? Where?
Look.
Ah! It's really there!
Sister, you can climb, right?
Me?
I can't climb a tree that high.
I can't either.
So it's a no-go?
Looks like a no-go.
But I want to catch it, no matter what!
We'd have caught it if only we could climb.
I'll go get Billy!
Wait a moment, Lucy-May!
You wanna climb yourself?
That's not it.
Hey, Lucy-May.
Let's quit our catching mission for today.
But why?
Even if you catch it, what would you do with it?
Well, it's obvious. I'll adopt it.
I don't think so.
You can't take it with you to Adelaide, can you?
Of course I can.
But we can't pack the cart
with something so useless to us.
I bet, it would be packed full
with just all the stuff we already have.
You think dad would allow you
to pile an extra koala on top of it?
Dad agreed to take the goat in
because it can produce milk.
But with a koala...
I'll carry it myself!
But there would definitely be some other luggage
for the two of us to carry.
I see.
I'm sure those can be found in Adelaide, too!
If they live here, they probably live there, too.
Dad, there's another ship.
It must be that it's carrying
some new immigrants to here.
And now, a once-over of tomorrow's procedures.
Lucy-May, Kate, and Clara, once we finish
arranging all of our belongings on the cart,
you'll take your clothes and other lightweight luggage
and depart first.
You mean, we'll go ahead of everyone else?
Yes.
The cart would be packed full with furniture.
Which means, we, with the ox,
would be moving one step at a time.
You girls would go to Adelaide first.
There, you'll be waiting for our arrival on the spot.
However, we'll have no idea
where to go once we're in Adelaide.
You never told us where our house is.
Of course, I'll draw a map for you.
Once you get there, you'll see
that Adelaide is awfully easy to navigate.
You two make sure you endure such a long walk.
Father said it's no less than 10 kilometers, right?
Yes. Roughly 10 kilometers.
Does our new house
has any features to help us recognize it?
Features?
The entrance there is decorated
with a red bow-knot.
Honey, why is there a red bow-knot already?
Ah, a welcoming gift from our neighbor.
Dad, what am I supposed to do?
You'll get up early tomorrow
and bring Mr. Bard, the coachman, to here.
Probably, by tomorrow morning
he'll be sober already.
I hope so.
Also Ben, tomorrow, you might have
to stay behind for some while.
Stay behind?
I think, we might not be able
to load our belongings onto the cart all at once.
In that case, I would ask you to stay behind, here.
We can't just throw our things away, can we?
Yes, I understand.
Honey, would you like to add anything?
Let's see... Tomorrow is promising to become
a very long day for everyone.
Therefore, let's all go to bed early tonight.
Sister, you think there are koalas in Adelaide, too?
Oh... Good night.
The three of us departed for Adelaide.
But while on the way,
we meet someone we didn't expect to see.
Next time on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow,
"The Road to Adelaide".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you