South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 48 - Becoming a Well-Off Child...
It's about my family, you hear?!
We're moving to live on a farm!
Huh? What did you say?
Our family is moving.
Ah, well that's a shame, Tob.
We're going to see that farm tomorrow!
Huh? What was that?
We're going to see the farm tomorrow!
Oh? It's a great thing that you managed to buy a farm!
It's not like that.
What was that?
We didn't buy no farm!
It's Mr. Princeton's farm.
So Mr. Princeton bought it for you?
No he didn't!
Isn't it pretty?
I wanna be a blacksmith too.
Ben!
I see. So dad decided to work at Mr. Princeton's place?
We're going there to go see that farm tomorrow.
Then, you need to hire a carriage somewhere?
No. Mr. Princeton will show us around
on his own carriage.
Oh? That's pretty impressive.
Are you coming along?
I suppose. Since it's a farm that dad is gonna work at,
and also the place where you guys are gonna move to,
it'd be better for me to see it too.
But you won't be living there yourself, right?
Yeah. Dad is the one who's been hired, not me.
Clara, won't be living with us on the farm either.
Huh? Why?
Because she's getting married!
I see. Dad finally gave them his permission,
so she's moving to live here with John?
But I don't wanna!
Really? Just because you'll be made to attend school at Princeton's Farm, you don't want to move now?
That too. But if I stay here, I'll be made
to go to school anyway, so it's all the same to me.
I didn't say that I don't wanna move to the farm.
Dad and mom are actually delighted
to be moving to Princeton's Farm soon.
You think so?
I know that!
Even though that farm won't belong to us, Mr. Princeton
promised to run it according to dad's advice.
That much, I know myself.
Why, then, are you so bristled up against it?
Our family is getting scattered all across the country.
You're making a mountain of a molehill.
It's only Clara and Ben that we'll have to part with.
John too.
What are you saying?
John isn't our family.
But after he marries Clara,
won't he become a brother in law to us?
He'd be like family to us.
Well, that's true...
I wish there was a place
where our whole family could live together.
But Ben is currently working
at the customs office in the harbor.
He can only occasionally turn up home.
And that he does, every Saturday.
But after we move to Princeton's Farm,
it'll be too far away for him to be coming there.
Little, you need something?
We'll be done soon. What is it?
Ben returned!
Really? That sure was quick.
I see. So you came to let us know that?
Wouldn't it be really nice if you could talk too?
Mom, I'm home.
Welcome back. Are you hungry?
It's always the same story with you, mom.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm not a child anymore.
Greeting me with "Are you hungry, are you hungry?" whenever I return home is a thing from my childhood.
I wouldn't say so. You've only stopped
being a child recently. So, are you hungry or not?
Well, I am kinda hungry.
But I can wait until everyone else gathers for dinner.
Hey! Welcome back, Ben.
Welcome back.
Yeah, I just came.
Good job, you two.
Oh? Is that fresh goat milk?
Yes, it is. Sticky's and Pansy's.
Oh, can I have some too?
Dad, do you think this map is precise?
Yes. Well, it'll do for giving me a general idea.
I went to the surveying office
and copied the one they had.
This thick line marks the borders
of Princeton's Farm, right?
Yes.
It looks pretty vast.
Yes, it's about 100 acres or so.
Eh? 100 acres?
That's incredible.
Not only they're growing crops there,
they also keep cows and sheep.
Plus, some land that's yet to be
developed for cultivating.
I wonder if they'd be willing to share
at least a bit of that cheap land.
In your hands, even that land
can be turned into a thriving field, I'm sure.
Ben...
If we get a chance to build a farm of your own design,
I'd also quit my customs job and come to work with you.
John would be happy to help too.
Ben, this won't be my farm.
I'll be working for the good of Mr. Princeton's farm.
I don't know all the details,
but it's clear that the farm needs rebuilding.
If you're going to work on it alone,
I wonder if you even can pull that rebuilding off.
Mr. Princeton assured me that he doesn't have any problem with running the farm according to my vision.
But dad,
the manager of that farm, as well as other workers would probably be delighted at you joining them.
I thought about it plenty myself and concluded that the only way to know is by giving it a shot.
I see. In that case, I don't have to say anything else.
Tomorrow, I'm going with you to see that farm.
I'm not sleepy at all.
Okay...
I wonder what Princeton's Farm would be like.
You're right. I'm sure it's so.
I'm right about what?
We'll be taking a lunch with us tomorrow, right?
You're not really following what I say.
Good night if so...
You can sleep?
Seems so.
What a strange girl you are!
The place we're visiting tomorrow
would soon become our home for quite a long while.
I wonder if Clara is going with us.
I know Ben said he wants to go.
I'm sure she'll come with John.
Hey, Lucy.
Lucy, are you listening?
What is it?
Mr. Princeton probably has
a very comfortable carriage, right?
I wonder, exactly how much people it can fit.
I'm worried that Clara and John
would have to ride standing.
What do you think, Lucy?
You rode that carriage many times,
so you oughta know!
Ah... I'm sleeping.
Eh? What was that? What did you say?
Ah... Fast asleep already.
I wonder what time it is now, even.
I'm in trouble. I'm not sleepy at all!
Okay, come out now!
Why can't you lay just a bit more?
Ah, good morning, Little.
Lucy. Kate didn't wake up yet?
So it seems.
We won't be able to take Little along today.
I'm sure he wants to see it too.
Our future home.
Because it's so far, it's not easy for a horse
to pull the carriage all the way to Princeton's Farm.
Mr. Princeton's carriage runs under two horses.
Kate. Kate!
Wake up already!
How long are you gonna sleep?
I'm still sleepy!
Leave me along for a little longer.
Then, you wanna stay and watch the house?
Watch the house?
Mr. Princeton will come to pick us up soon.
We're going to see the farm today, remember?
Ah!
Say, you've had your breakfast already?
Everyone is waiting for you at the table.
Ah! Why didn't you wake me up earlier?
What are you saying?
I tried to wake you up time and again.
Oh, really?
I wonder when will Mr. Princeton arrive.
We didn't settle on any certain hour,
but well, it'll be around 10 o'clock I reckon.
If so, we've no time to spare.
I'm sorry for oversleeping.
I wonder since when are you such a late sleeper.
It's a special case today.
I've been thinking about going to the farm all night long
and lost my sleep completely to excitement.
All right, that's settled.
Shall we start eating now?
Yes.
Why is Little barking?
Probably someone is at the doorstep.
Don't tell me Mr. Princeton showed up already?
Should I go check?
I'm Max, Mr. Princeton's coachman.
Ah, truly, I'm so sorry.
We have just started eating the breakfast.
We'll try to be done with it at once,
so if you could ask Mr. Princeton to wait inside...
No, I can't do that.
Huh? But then, inside the carriage...
Master didn't come in that carriage.
You see, the Madam suddenly fell ill.
So Master found himself unable to leave the house.
The Madam is ill?
Yes. Therefore, Master stayed by her side to nurse her.
Oh... So that's what happened?
That's why Master sent me here to let you know that he'd like to give you an excursion on some other day.
Is that so?
That is all. Pardon the intrusion.
Yeah, no problem.
Can't help it if his wife is ill.
He said "some other day" but which day it would be?
Who knows.
He spoke with a great deal of uncertainty.
Enter.
Max has just returned.
Ah, I see.
He reported delivering your message
exactly as you said.
I see. Tell Max I appreciate his work.
Well...
Yes?
The other party seemed
considerably upset with the news.
Hm.
If you excuse me...
There you heard it.
I had to cancel my excursion through the farm
for Mr. Popple today.
But please listen well. Whatever it takes,
I set my mind on putting that farm straight.
If you, who had managed the farm up to now,
happen to have any solid idea
about what to do next, I'd like to hear it,
You don't have to do it right now.
But remember, I can't keep Mr. Popple waiting forever.
Yes, in two or three days at most,
I'd like to hear what you think.
How are you feeling?
Not great.
If your fever is gone, don't you think
it'll be better for you to get up and move a little?
I don't want to get up.
Well, that's not good.
I saw a dream.
Huh?
The same dream as always.
Hm. About having a child?
Yes. About playing around with a lovely girl.
The weather is good.
You think so?
All I want is for you to get better soon.
Actually, I had a trip to the farm
with the Popples arranged for today.
With Lucy as well?
Yes. Since Mr. Popple decided to work at the farm,
he's also taking his family there with him.
But you didn't go to the farm? Why?
I let Pepys handle the farm for now.
But he said he's against Mr. Popple
coming to take the reins there.
Why won't you dismiss Pepys, then?
I can't do that so easily.
But you want to assign Mr. Popple
to do Pepys's job, don't you?
I would probably end up doing that.
You can't question Mr. Popple's enthusiasm
in the matters of running a farm.
Lucy told me.
Her father made it all the way to Southern Australia
in order to build a farm of his own.
That's right...
That's right!
That's right. If you do that,
things are destined to go well!
What is it, Sylvia?
What is destined to go well?
That's it... That's just it, dear!
Hm?
Please, dear. Give a piece of land to Mr. Popple.
What did you say?
No matter what land it'll be.
Your farm in Gawler has plenty of land
still waiting to be reclaimed, right?
That land...
Sylvia, can you even hear what you're saying?
So foolish!
What do you mean?
Last night, I was so excited about going
to that farm today, I couldn't get any sleep.
I also wanted to go see it today.
Too bad, but now I won't be able to do it with everyone.
I wonder if Madam's illness really is that serious.
She always seemed to be a sturdy person.
But if it's really bad, you probably
gotta go check on her, don't you think?
After all, Madam dotes on you so much.
It doesn't seem like Mr. Princeton will come to visit us
any time soon, so I might as well do that.
Then I'm coming along too.
No need, I can handle it myself.
Are you sure? It's a long way to Northern Adelaide.
It's not that bad.
But it's really best that I come along.
You're too absentminded, you know.
I'll be fine!
It's always the same song with you two.
Listen, you two.
Don't quarrel over some petty things again, okay?
But it wasn't my fault.
Wasn't my fault either!
Oh, really?
You're the one only ever thinking about yourself here!
Oh my, look who's talking!
Give me a break, you two!
Oh, just do whatever!
Okay, we're leaving!
Giddyup!
Goodbye, Ben!
Come back next week too!
Goodbye!
Goodbye, Ben!
Bye!
Goodbye!
I wonder if it isn't too soon yet.
Yes. But if we wait any longer, we might end up
moving to the farm before harvesting them.
Won't you go there ahead of everyone else?
I don't know yet, though I considered that too.
But even if you go there,
you'll still attend my wedding, right?
Certainly.
Look, when it'll be time for dancing at the reception,
you could do it even here, at this very field.
After we've taken out all the potatoes.
You won't use it for anything else after this?
I'd rather leave that headache
to whoever buys this house.
I always wondered, what it's like
to ride a marvelous carriage like that of Mr. Princeton.
Better stop thinking about such trifles.
You only say that because you rode it
God knows how many times.
And I've never even approached
a two-horse carriage in my life.
But I guess we'll get to ride it
when we go to the farm next time.
He'll come on a different carriage next time.
You're so mean.
Good morning, little ladies.
I see. Then, I really don't mind giving you two
a leisure ride on this carriage today.
I don't really need it. Only Kate does.
I'd rather you ride it too, Lucy.
After all, I'll be having a very important talk
with your father and mother now.
Yay!
Wait for me!
There you go.
I go.
Max, drive them around the area for a while.
Okay.
Little, you wait for us here. Okay, boy?
He's washing his hands right now.
He just finished harvesting the potatoes.
I'm truly sorry for letting you down
on our arrangements for today.
Whoa! Whoa!
Thank you very much.
You silly thing.
Didn't I tell you to stay home and wait?
I apologize for the delay.
No need. I'm the one truly at fault
for what happened in the morning.
How is your wife's condition?
I appreciate your concern for her.
It's gotten considerably better since.
I see.
So, when will you give us a tour through the farm?
Well, I still can't say for sure, you see.
Actually, a small circumstance came up.
Are you saying that my employment
has to be canceled?
No, no. It's anything but that.
After all, I'm still putting my deepest trust in you.
It's just that...
What is it? Please say it.
To tell you the truth, I'm not sure
if I can muster enough courage to say that.
Please don't feel shy.
Whatever it may be, say it.
If so, I'll put it bluntly.
Could you let us adopt Lucy as our own daughter?
Adopt, you say?
Um...
It's only natural that you're so surprised.
For a matter like this, you'll need
to consult with your wife thoroughly.
We'd like to bring Lucy up as our own child.
We'd like to adopt Lucy, by all means.
Next episode of "Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow":
Clara's Wedding
Next time: "Clara's Wedding".
Don't miss it!
The Alps Story: My Annette
Next show - The Alps Story: My Annette.
It starts in the new year.
Don't miss it, okay?
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you