South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 11 - Our Small House
After everything that happened, we finally
made it to the hill, overlooking all of Adelaide.
However, the place we were looking at
there was hardly a handful of houses or roads.
The rest was untouched meadows,
trees and the river.
Adelaide was still rather a city-to-be.
You think we'll find our house fast?
Didn't you listen to what dad said?
The entrance is marked with a red bow-knot.
But what I'm asking is where this house at?
As for where...
According to this map, it should be
near the river, on Polly Street.
Polly Street, that's a sweet name.
I like it.
So, is this Polly Street nearby?
I'm getting very tired.
If we keep going this way, we won't miss it.
Lucy-May, hold out for just a little longer.
It appears, we've arrived at Polly Street.
Why don't we ask someone?
Where do you see them? That someone.
Like that! Keep walking straight, you slacker!
Mr. Bard, I can by no means see
how this ox can be considered slacking.
As soon as I stop encouraging him like this,
he'll turn into a slacker.
Maybe you're right. Personally, though,
I don't see the point in demanding so much from it.
And I do see the point.
Well, I guess you value this ox greatly.
Right, right. Mighty valuable fella to me.
Ain't you, little one?
Is it still a very long way to Adelaide?
No, it's not all that terribly long anymore.
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
The girls must have already arrived
to our new house.
Uh-huh. About time they arrive.
The red bow-knot is definitely there.
But I don't think this could really be our house.
That's what I thought.
But dad never said he bought a house.
Only that he bought a shack.
Then, are you saying that one is our house?
Could it be not it?
Lucy-May, can you believe it?
That run-down shack is our new home.
I can't believe it, but...
Then you tell me, sis.
Are you sure this is Polly Street?
It probably is.
Hmm?
Hm.
Hmm...
Let's go ask people from that house if it is.
You two go there, I'm so worn-out
I can't do no more walking.
Lucy-May, you think that shack
is our new home, after all?
I don't want to think so, but...
Ah! Someone from that house just showed up.
Looks to be some woman, right?
I'll go ask her.
I'm going along!
We've finally arrived, Marsh.
Seems like this would be our new house.
It's a rather tiny house, but still...
Could you be Mr. Popple's daughters, by chance?
Yes, that's right.
I've been waiting for you.
Are you Clara?
Yes.
I'm Ms. Mack. Jane Mac.
I live in this house.
And so, I'm your neighbor now, right?
Which means... That shack
really is our house, after all.
Houses are still sparse in our Adelaide.
This shack may look tiny indeed,
but I'm sure your father
will make it big and glorious over time.
Had our dad said so himself?
Yes, back when he made up his mind
to buy this house the other day.
And about us coming, too?
He said, "I might send children ahead."
Oh? But wasn't it three of you who came?
Lucy-May is resting over there.
Which means you must be Kate?
Yes.
You girls must be pretty hungry, I reckon?
We're making bread now,
I'll bring you some when it's done.
You've not entered that house yet, have you?
To be honest, we never expected it
to be that tiny a house.
You just need to bear with it for some while.
Well, you should just go check out the insides.
I'll be joining you later.
Thanks a lot, madam.
Let's go.
Even the floor is barely nailed.
Father, what were you thinking,
buying this house?
"Shack," remember?
I can see the river!
Huh?
At least the water situation is sorted out here.
If what the grandma next door said is true,
dad's planning to turn this
into a big and glorious house one day.
Perhaps building a new one from the ground up
would've been easier...
Sis.
Maybe we should clean it up a bit
before dad and the others arrive?
For some reason, I'm not one bit
in the mood for cleaning.
Yay! I'm saved, saved!
Because I'm so worn out,
I'd much rather take an afternoon nap.
In this house?
Na-ah. Underneath that big tree over there.
Good idea. That place looks way more
comfortable for sleeping.
Maybe I'll take a little nap, too.
Aren't you two hungry?
Now that you mention it,
I'm a bit hungry.
Our neighbor Mrs. Mac said she'd be so kind
as to bring us some bread, didn't she?
Bread?
Yes.
It's open!
Freshly baked bread!
Wow!
Thank you so much.
Wow! It smells so good!
Did you bake this yourself, ma'am?
Yes, that's right.
And you must be Lucy-May?
Yes.
Baking bread and other sweets is my passion.
Starting today, we're neighbors,
so let's all get along, shall we?
Yes!
This place doesn't have a table either,
so wouldn't it be better to lunch
while sitting on the grass outside?
Yes.
It's been literal ages
since we've eaten any bread that good!
You must be an expert bread-baker,
are you, ma'am?
Thank you. If you developed such a liking for it,
why don't I treat you to some of my bread
every now and then?
Please do!
Kate! Learn some shame, you.
It's fine.
As much as I would have liked to chat with you
for a little longer, I have to go home now.
Thank you for the treat.
My husband wasn't feeling too well,
so he went to sleep.
She does that for us
even while her husband is ill...
She must be a very caring person.
Even though our shack is so ugly,
I'm glad we have a nice neighbor, at least.
Hey, Lucy-May, we'll probably have to sleep
inside a barrel here as well, won't we?
There's no way we can all sleep in there.
But we've left the barrel behind!
We'll find another one, then.
This here is not the seashore, you know.
Do you suppose a barrel like that
could fall from the sky?
But that means sleeping in a tent, doesn't it?
I'm going to sleep right now.
I'm sleepy, too.
I'd have preferred a proper house
at least the size of Mrs. Mac's.
Eh, hmm? Now this is much better.
Alright, then. I'll stay here for a while
to catch a shuteye.
Doctor, are you not going
to return to England?
Yeah, returning is now out of my reach.
But for how long?
That ship wasn't the only one
you could use to return to England.
They'll let you board
if you explain your situation.
It was God's decision
that I should be late to the ship.
So I made up my mind.
I'm staying in Australia.
But don't you have a wife and kids back home?
My missus had joined god ages ago.
And my son enlisted in the army
and doesn't come home anymore.
Still...
Well, of course, I'll write a letter to son.
I'll let him know I moved to Australia.
Maybe I should open a practice
right here, in this barrel?
Well if you've seriously
made up your mind to stay,
wouldn't it be better
to go to Adelaide?
Adelaide?
You mean, what they call the capital
of Southern Australia state?
I see. Maybe I should go to Adelaide then.
Before long, I'm also moving to Adelaide,
together with these things.
All right. In that case,
I'm going to Adelaide with you as soon as I can.
Speaking of which, where do you think
I should go to get something to drink?
Tob, you should calm down at least a bit,
dad is very tired.
It's nothing. Besides, which one of us is more tired?
I'll be fine. We're already in Adelaide, aren't we?
Yes, on the outskirts of the city.
Look, that there is the River Torrens.
Our shack should be
around there, I think.
It's good to live near the river,
for different reasons.
Let me reiterate it once again
that you'll be disappointed at the sight of our house.
After all, that's one shabby kind of house.
Don't you worry about anything.
I promise that I won't be disappointed,
even if it's the ugliest home I've ever seen.
I hope so...
Dad!
Mom!
Kate and the girls
are running out of it...
Which means, that there is our...
See? What did I tell you?
That's why I asked you
not to be too disappointed...
More than disappointed,
I'm surprised.
That's one tiny house.
We arrived here three hours before you!
Oh my, that soon?
Then, what have you been up to?
I've taken a nap.
Oh dear, were you that tired?
Kate, have you met
our neighbor, Mrs. Mac?
Yes. A mighty kind lady.
She treated us to some bread.
I'm glad to hear that.
But where's Clara?
Went to fetch water from the river.
But you got no bucket, no nothing.
Mrs. Mac lent us a bucket.
Huh?
Oh! Hello!
Hello.
I don't think I've ever seen you before.
That's because this is the first time we meet.
Right, sorry about that.
My name is Bernard.
Bernard Mosley.
I'm Clara Popple.
Oh! Is that so?
That means Mr. Popple
had also arrived to Adelaide?
Do you know my father?
Yes. To tell you the truth, I was the one
who showed him that house.
My!
So you were the one who foisted
that run-down cabin on him!
Huh?
It's not like that! It really isn't!
Ah! Oh.
Listen, that house and plot
all belonged to government!
That house belonged to Mr. Simpson, who joined
the exploration party and went out into the hinterland.
And what happened to Mr. Simpson after?
He never returned.
Apparently, while one the expedition,
he got sick and passed away.
And he didn't have any relatives either?
At least not in Australia.
At any rate, that house
returned to the government.
That's why I proposed
for Mr. Popple to buy it.
The plot he got is even more
important than the house.
After all, what I wanted the most
is for our neighbors to be good people.
Your neighbors?
Then, that makes you...
Mrs. Mac's little brother.
I work in Colonel Light's office.
Ah, I finally know the full story.
Um... Aren't you cold?
Huh?
It's as though you're shivering a bit.
I've been swimming for quite some while,
so I was thinking of getting out soon.
Then you should get out quickly.
Um... Thing is...
Well if you wish to keep swimming, go ahead.
I won't ask you to get out against your will.
It's not that! The thing is, actually...
I'm stark naked!
Huh?
And I left my clothes on that tree branch
right next to you.
Oh my.
Hey! You!
If you want me to carry that bucket for you,
wait for me just a little ahead on the road!
That's it, start walking, you slacker!
Like that! Go!
That man is being unreasonably harsh with it again.
I guess it's in his habit now.
That's a nasty habit.
Let's just carry inside the house
the stuff we immediately need.
The stuff that we don't need urgently,
I guess, we could just sheet it and leave it outside.
We really can't bring anything at all
inside a house that small...
You have my promise.
I'll expand it with at least
two more rooms as soon as I can.
Even two more rooms won't suffice.
I'm just saying we won't have two rooms for long.
You've arrived rather soon.
Yes. Is this water good for drinking?
I thought it was suitable...
But there was a person swimming in the river.
Someone was swimming? Who?
Ah! I see everyone had arrived?
Oh, mother, this here is our neighbor.
Pleased to meet you, I'm Bernard.
I live next door,
together with my sister and her husband.
Ah, I see.
Mr. Popple! We've been waiting for you.
Yes, thanks for everything.
Even if my family seems to have developed
an universal aversion for this house.
So I thought...
It hadn't been used for quite a while
and fell into ruin.
Considering it was you who proposed it to me,
that sounds mighty irresponsible of you.
Well, let's not get so worked up.
Did you say it yourself,
"Anything would do," Mr. Popple?
With just a bit of work,
it'll become unrecognizable.
I'm also going to help you
with whatever I can.
Out of neighbor's reciprocity.
Oh, now that you mention it,
I remembered I've got a favor to ask right away.
If that wouldn't trouble you too much,
could you lent me a bit of a hand in stretching the tent?
Well, that was rather quick.
Mr. Bernard might be very busy.
As you can see, I only have
women and children here with me.
Right...
Ah... No. For certain, I will help you!
Hey! Wait, Sticky!
Wait! Wait!
Sticky!
We're telling you to stop! You!
How about this?
Hold on tight, Kate!
You cannot let go!
Lucy-May, do something.
Do something soon, please!
Here I go!
Why would you even want to run away from us?
It seems we can't keep her unleashed after all.
So it seems. Well, let's go back now.
Yeah.
And don't try to run away ever again, Sticky.
Ah!
No, Sticky!
Now, start walking.
Come on, Sticky.
Come on.
Come on! Move, you!
Ouch-ouch-ouch.
Ah. Sure is stubborn, our Sticky.
What's wrong with her?
Looks like she wants to go somewhere.
Maybe there are other goats this way
or something like that?
Oh! I know, Lucy-May.
What?
Where Sticky wants to go
is that clearing yonder.
To the river?
Yes, to the water.
She must've smelled the water.
Oh, is that so? You were just feeling thirsty?
Wait, Sticky!
Like that is good?
Oh. Wait a moment, Mr. Popple.
Ah. Just a little back.
Good, now press it down real hard, will you?
I need it stretched.
All right...
There you go.
Like that.
Ah! Wait! Wait a second!
It's dark!
Well, you ain't awfully reliable guy, you know?
Hello, Mr. Popple.
Oh, ma'am.
Thank you for looking after my children today.
Don't mention it.
Oh my, isn't it Bernard underneath there?
What are you doing in there?
Oh, how cruel of you!
Can't you tell by looking?
I'm helping to stretch the tent.
I highly doubt it somehow.
Usually, I can't bring you
to do any house maintenance.
Well, there are various reasons behind this...
And I can't believe it either.
Oh my!
This is Mrs. Jane Mac.
Ah, Mrs. Mac, I'm Mr. Popple's missus.
Children told me about what you did for us.
Thank you for everything.
No. I didn't do anything in the least special.
More importantly, we are neighbors from now on,
so I would be happy to help with anything.
The feeling is mutual.
Feel free to ask us of anything.
In a place like this,
if we don't look after each other,
any unforeseen difficulty
would render us paralyzed.
Yes, that's exactly what I thought.
Ah!
Hm?
Did you hear something just now?
It was like a shriek of a child.
Where's Kate and Lucy-May?
Let's see...
Ah! It's dangerous, Lucy-May!
Stop resisting, Sticky!
You'll fall into the river!
Calm down, Sticky!
I can't hold you any longer!
Ah!
They fell down!
Lucy-May!
Sticky!
Let go of the goat, Lucy-May!
Lest you'll also get swept away!
Lucy-May! Let go of the goat, please!
I cant! Can't!
Lucy-May!
Here! Here, stretch you hand, Lucy-May!
Catch on to me!
Eh? Kate! Help! Ah!
Lucy-May!
Ah! Sister! Help me!
Hang on there, Lucy-May!
Kate!
Help me!
Ah! Someone! Help us!
Someone, come here, please!
Somebody!
The one who saved me and the goat
was a man who was as big as a giant.
But he turned out to be a very kind person.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Night in Adelaide".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you