South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 01 - To a New Land
Mother, let's have some tea.
Say, Mary. You aren't hiding anything from me, are you?
I have nothing to hide from you, mother!
Isn't there really any news?
News?﻿
Half a year passed since Arthur left the village with my grandchildren.
No, it's been seven months, even.
It happened last August.
I suppose.
The letter of them arriving to Australia was supposed to come long ago.
Mother! Did I not tell you
England and Australia are very far apart?
The one is on the edge of the Earth for the other.
It's more than three months of sailing.
You keep saying that, but...
I only hope we receive some news soon
of them arriving safely.
Seems like my husband is back.
He's been to the town, right?
I hope he stopped by the post office.
I'm sure he did.
Ah! It's cold!
The snow definitely piles up tonight!
You didn't put the horse into the stable?
I will, of course.
But before that, I wanted to give this to your mother.
Here, the long-awaited letter from Australia.
Well, mother!
Good Lord!
Read it for me, Mary.
I'm too afraid of something.
I don't think there's anything to be afraid of.
Oh! It was Clara who wrote this letter!
She turned sixteen while on board the ship.
I'm reading, mother.
"Grandma, aunt Mary, and finally, uncle Fred, how are you?
Our family made it safely to Southern Australia.
We spent ninety five days aboard,
until we could finally tread the soil again.
That's right, we've been trapped
in the confined cabin for over three months.
To decide who is getting ferried ashore first, we drew lots."
Boat is all ready!
Okay! Next group, please.
That would be us.
Let's go, sis.
I'll lend you a shoulder.
Thank you, Ben.
No, you're waiting.
Our family goes ashore first.
Excuse me, Mr. Pettywell, but according
to the lots we've drawn before, it's our turn now.
My wife's health is deteriorating.
She cannot wait for her turn.
Now, let us go.
So is my daughter's health.
My family is different from yours.
I paid a fortune to board this ship and get here.
Of course, I also did that for my wife and my servants.
I have a privilege over those
who came here on government expense.
Isn't that right, boy?
Yes...
Make sure you don't forget anything.
Hm... Can't be helped.
We'll wait for the next one.
What a rotten person!
Kate...
But I'm saying it because Mr. Pettywell
really is a rotten person!
I knew that for a while.
Be quiet, Kate.
What now? He queue-jumped in front of us.
So puffed up! You can't be serious!
I'm really surprised Marsh didn't die in there!
Why would he be dying?
You should know it just as well!
Hamsters hibernate during winter.
Back in England, the winter is in full swing already.
But here it's summer.
Therefore, Marsh cannot hibernate and it drives him crazy, I reckon.
Marsh will be fine!
Australia can reinvigorate anyone!
Are you feeling better, sis?
Yes, thank you.
Some sea breeze reaches me even down here.
Did shouldn't have yielded our turn to that Mr. Pettywell!
Can't be helped.
He's rich after all.
Do you remember what we came
to Southern Australia for?
Dad said this is the land of freedom and equality.
"Unfortunately, on the day of arrival,
I wasn't in perfect health.
It must've been the heat.
However, everyone else was in high spirits.
Especially Kate and Lucy-May,
who were feeling too good, even.
Overly enthusiastic about riding a boat,
Lucy-May tripped into the sea.
The one who rescued her
was a young sailor named John.
Throughout the voyage,
he had been the most cordial to us.
It's almost summer in these parts.
Thanks to that, Lucy-May didn't catch a cold
after tumbling into the sea."
Say, what is she talking about, Mary?
What, Mother?
Here it's snowing all over the place, but in Australia they have summer?
Mother, winter and summer periods in Australia
are reversed in regard to England.
How come?
It's on the southern side of the globe.
How does the southern side explain the seasons reversed?
Look, even I don't have all the answers.
Eh! Winter and summer are reversed, huh?
But I'm glad anyhow.
At least the ship didn't sink on the way.
I was so worried it would!
But the hard times only start now.
They are now in a virtually uninhabited place.
Everyone would have to blaze
their own trail from here on.
Build lodgings and eventually towns.
Then there are fields and pastures...
And worst of all, I won't see
my adorable grandchildren ever again.
Hey! Hey! Mother!
You two! Didn't I tell you to sit tight?
You two just don't know how to behave, do you?
This time, no one is helping if you fall in the sea!
Right, John?
Huh?
Aren't you cold, Lucy-May?
Not one bit!
Marsh dried up already!
Those girls have not changed one bit
from what they were back home.
Buoyant as ever.
I'm only a bit worried about Clara.
By the way, what are we to do after we go ashore?
We'll start by arranging
the sleeping quarters in the vicinity.
There, look yourself.
There are camps all over the place.
Um... ﻿Is that place - Adelaide?
No, the city itself seems to be distanced from the shore.
Southern Australia's capital is Adelaide, right?
Yes. Even though it's the capital,
it has no more than 300 residents for now.
Thank yon, John.
On this land, we'll spend the rest of our lives.
Here.
Feels great!
So much fun!
It's Australia!
It's Australia for you!
Now, everyone! Take whatever you can carry
and unload it on top of that dune.
Okay!
Father, when are we retrieving
the rest of our things from the ship?
Well, I don't know yet.
The rest is only the bulky stuff,
so the boat will have to make several trips.
I'll be seeing you again!
Clara.
You shouldn't exert yourself since you have a fever.
Just watch over Tob and our luggage over here.
Okay. Will do.
"The scenery around us was surprisingly even more desolate than I expected.
I couldn't help wondering
if humans can live in a place like that at all.
Still, I have to do my best.
Grandma, from now on,
I'll be sure to send you a letter
whenever there's a ship returning to England.
Take care and goodbye.
November 7th, 1837,
from Southern Australia. Clara Popple."
They have summer over there...
Now, hold it tight, Ben.
Okay.
Heave-ho!
You're such a skilled handyman, dad.
Farmers have to be jacks of all trades.
Where did mom go to fetch the water?
This place is like a birds' kingdom.
Let's go!
Okay.
Look, over there!
Mr. Pettywell is building himself a house.
Good, drive it in a bit more and that should do.
Now, start stretching it on this side.
He could do some work himself,
not just give orders!
We've not been doing any work either.
Good point. How about we stop loitering around
and offer some help to dad?
I'm still small, so I should be allowed
to play around. But if you would help him...
Not happening! If I'm going to do any work,
you're doing it with me.
Alright, that's enough.
Start carrying our things into the tent, you two.
Okay!
Okay.
Hurry up, you rascals! Hurry up!
The sun will set soon!
Why, you...
Why are you looking idly at me, you blockheads?!
Start rebuilding it!
Until the tent is set, no one's getting their meal!
Get to work, you slacking breed!
Oh my, what are you doing here?
I have been looking for you!
Clara...
There... There!
And then "Slam!" Like that!
Hey! No playing around!
I'm not playing around.
Just making sure it doesn't hurt when you use it!
Doesn't hurt, doesn't hurt!
You fool!
What a great smell!
I'm so hungry it drives me crazy!
Same here!
Mom!
Please wait just a bit longer.
The salt pork soup is on the way.
Just needs some more seething.
Mom, we've laid enough straw in the tent.
You can sleep well wherever you want.
Oh? Is that so?
Then could you go tell Clara and Ben
that we don't need more?
Okay!
Dad is bringing along that thing.
My, that's a large barrel.
It was lying on the shore over there.
The bottom is gone, so it's won't be good
for holding water any time soon.
Why did you bring it here, then?
That tent cannot accommodate us all sleeping in it.
Then, someone will have to sleep in here?
Dad, who will be sleeping here?
Lucy, you want to sleep here?
Me?
Scared to do it alone?
Yes...
But together with Kate, I'd be fine.
I guess you two could sleep here together.
Maybe it would be better to let Ben sleep here instead?
I wanna sleep here!
Ah, Kate is back.
Kate!
We two will be sleeping in a barrel!
In a barrel?
Yes!
Let me have that straw.
Mom, the tent doesn't need any more straw, right?
Well done. Please lay
the remaining straw inside this barrel.
Inside the barrel?
Me and Kate will sleep in here!
Oh!
Are you sure, mom?
Well, we're still to hear what Kate says.
Of course, I will sleep here!﻿
Sleeping inside a barrel is a fantastic idea!
Ah! May I have that straw?
Here! Let me finish the bed for us!
Sister, you are mean, mean, mean! Oh, you!
Dad, shouldn't I sleep here instead of them?
Everyone would feel easier this way.
Yes. Your mom said so too.
Exactly. Leaving them together
in a place like this is a receipt for quarrel.
Right, mom?
I suppose...
We're sleeping in the barrel!
Before we proceed to eating,
there's something I'd like to say to everyone.
Aside from Tob,
who probably won't understand a word of it,
I want everyone to listen closely.
We have all made it safely to Australia.
I trust you are all well aware of my goal here,
which is to build a farm much bigger
than the one we had back in England.
I'd like to think it won't take too long.
But until that happens,
I want everyone to endure patiently
all the hardships we're to face.
Also, we're not staying in this area forever.
Tomorrow or the day after that,
I'm going to Adelaide.
Adelaide is about ten kilometers
inwards from this shore.
The capital of Southern Australia, it's being erected as a glorious city that no one can be ashamed of.
Once we finally make it to Adelaide,
I'll assemble a magnificent prefabricated home
with the parts we brought from England.
And so, once I buy a sizable plot,
we could see it turn into a magnificent farm.
This concludes my address.
Now, isn't everyone hungry?
Here.
Here, Ben.
Hey.
You never know what prowls the dead of night
while you sleep in that barrel.
What do you think might prowl here?
Perhaps, the spirits of the dead will rise?
You're such a buffoon.
Hey! Did you know?
This place is still full of wild dogs.
They look like wolves and are ghastly for real.
Liar.
It's true!
See? ﻿See? ﻿See?
You really are a buffoon.
That is Mr. Pettywell's black dog.
That is bad manners!
I have an urgent message for brother.
What is it?
Regardless of what you say to Lucy-May,
she is determined to sleep in the barrel.
Suit yourself!
Marsh? Marsh, what's the matter?
You'll get crushed down there!
Go back into the basket.
Kate!
What is it?
Wake up! A strange animal
just came and looked at us!
Strange animal?
It kinda was like a rabbit,
but an enormous one!
It was hop-hopping on two legs!
So a rabbit after all?
Go back to sleep, Lucy-May.
So it's some kind of rabbit after all, huh?
As we later found out, the animal Lucy-May saw
was an animal indigenous to Australia,
and only inhabiting it, called kangaroo.
We never had any idea such an outlandish animal
can even exist somewhere.
On our way back home from the creek,
we found this adorable and docile animal.
Next time on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A Cute Fellow".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you