South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 06 - A City Called Adelaide
Good! Lower it!
Good! It's lowered!
Ah! They're going at it with the dog!
- Hey! Jerk!
- Hey! Wait!
That's Mr. Pettywell's dog.
Did he steal something again?
But it makes me sad when they mistreat him.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
Let's go now.
- Okay.
The weather is fine today.
My father and brother
have gone to Adelaide.
Lucy-May and I will be
helping mother clean up and do the laundry.
- Wait!
- Wait! Jerk!.
Huh?
Hey! You're messing
with Happy again?
Well, that dog is a thief, sir.
What are you saying?
It's true, he filched a piece of
dried meat from our tent.
What a ridiculous accusation!
Happy is decisively not a thief!
Right, Happy?
We know everything.
Know what?
That dog stole
Mr. Popple's meat last time.
What did you say?
- Ah!
If there's no evidence,
I won't tolerate you saying such nonsense!
- Wah!
That dog is a thief!
And a thief dog owner
is by extension a thief, too!
Hey!
Damn brats! You'll pay for this!
Darling, what has happened?
You see, those brats just...
I don't care for what those children did.
Before anything else, you need to
go to Adelaide as soon as possible
and find us a proper house.
Living in these conditions
is unbearable for me!
It's unbearable for me as well.
But even if I go to Adelaide, I might not
find a good place there either.
Adam said he wasn't able
to find anything.
Darling, do you really trust
a servant's word?
You need to confirm it yourself.
Yes, I understand, I just need to go, right?
Damn it!
Darling!
As soon as we arrive here,
you're suddenly a kleptomaniac!
Tighter!
Mmmm.
Like this!
Good! Like that!
What are you two doing over there?
You'll rip the clothes apart
if you squeeze them like that.
Oh! Good morning, Mr. Parker.
Yes, good morning.
Your husband went to Adelaide today, correct?
Yes.
They left early this morning,
so they're probably already there.
I'm sure they'll find a good place.
Yes.
Mr. Pettywell has also gone to Adelaide.
I just saw him now.
Didn't he say he wants that prefabricated home
you brought over from England?
My husband made it very clear
he wasn't going to sell it.
I'm sure, in Adelaide they already have
some marvelous houses for sale.
Building a house from the ground up
will take some days.
That's why it's not hard to see
why he'd want your prefabricated house instead.
Oh! If you're here to do laundry,
you can put your clothes with mine.
No, it's not necessary.
After all these years,
I've gotten quite good with laundry.
I've lived on my own
for a very long time, you know?
Why do you think it is?
What is?
Why I haven't been able to find
that cute little bear again?
Lucy-May, by chance, did you see a koala?
Huh? So it's called a koala?
Yes, the natives call them that.
It seems to only live in Australia.
But around here,
there doesn't seem to be any.
We saw a native boy
keeping one as a pet.
Oh? I guess you can see some
over here then.
I see, so they're called Koalas, huh?
Ah.
Oh my, now we'll have to wash
those clothes all over again.
I'm sorry.
Go back to the river and wash them again.
It's just...
What do you mean "it's just"?
You got it dirty when you fell down.
Kate.
Please go with her too.
Lucy-May can't wring the clothes
well enough by herself.
What about this?
I can take that back myself, now give it to me.
In the end, you're a hopeless person,
you know that?
Let's go and wash it, Lucy-May.
Ah! Wait! Sister!
They're adorable.
Those girls are hopeless.
Marsh... Marsh.
Marsh.
Marsh! Marsh!
What's wrong, Tob?
Marsh.
You shouldn't mess with Marsh, you know?
Oh my, where did Marsh go?
Welcome back!
Have you set up the rope for the clothes?
What happened to Kate and Lucy-May?
Lucy-May! We need to hurry and
go wash those clothes, right now!
Just wait a moment.
I'm sure I saw it.
I doubt there's even a goat
around this place.
So let's hurry up.
Shhh, can't you hear?
You're right, it's a goat.
But why is it
in a place like this?
Hmm?
Ah!
You rascal!
Now I'll have to go and wash these
all over again.
Ah! Don't do that!
You'll hurt its leg even more if you do!
But if I don't,
then we can't free it from here.
Kate! Lucy-May!
Are you the ones over there?
Yes, it's us!
What are you doing?
Help us, Mr. Parker!
Huh?
Oh my, it's a goat.
Why is it here?
It was already like this when we found it.
Hmmm, it looks like it has
a nasty injury on its leg.
Mr. Parker, please help us
get the goat's leg out of the tree roots.
Sure.
Mr. Parker! The goat is in pain!
I see, but then what can we do?
Hmm. Oh! I know.
I always have it in my pocket.
I have a knife.
Ah! Thank goodness.
Mr. Parker! You can't!
Huh? Why not?
You're going to cut off
the goat's leg, aren't you?!
Huh?
Oh.
No, what I'll try to cut off is the roots.
It's going to be a while, but...
I can cut off even a root this thick.
Let's begin.
Good morning.
Hmm? Oh, yes.
Is Adelaide far from here?
This is Adelaide.
Huh?
There's not a single house in sight.
This is Adelaide.
This is a park area that surrounds the town,
now and in the future.
It was Colonel Light who drew up
the layout for the town.
A park surrounding the town?
That's right.
But for now, the town itself
also looks more like a park.
There aren't many constructed houses
and there aren't many people.
Isn't the population over 300 already?
That's right.
Still, so far, only the roads were built.
Only straight roads that run from east to west,
from north to south.
So only the streets have been built?
Speaking of which,
where are you guys heading for?
This must be Colonel Light's office, right?
That's right.
Dad, should we finish our business here first?
Or maybe we'll try to procure the cart first?
We're going to be here for a long while.
Then we should go and find a cart first, right?
You're right, Ben.
But not just any cart. It's an oxcart
that Mr. Jamling's managed to secure for us.
It's because an ox
is stronger than a horse, right?
Yes, even if we get a cart
what's the use of it when there's still
so few horses around?
Father, if Mr. Jamling had already
made a contract for an oxcart,
doesn't it mean we can tend to that later?
Let's settle on our plot first.
You're correct in what you say.
With this, it should be fine.
Thank you very much, Mr. Parker.
Are you sure you didn't need
that shirt, Mr. Parker?
Yes, this was just an old shirt, you know.
Anyway, are you thinking of taking the goat home?
Since I found it, then that means
I can keep it, right?
Yes, but only if the owner
doesn't show up, you know?
I'm sure that it got lost.
Then its owner
must be looking for it, right?
Most probably.
If the owner appears I'll return it,
but until then I'll look after it.
Hmm?
Oh my.
What's wrong, Mr. Parker?
Hmm.
Oh-ho, what do you know!
This goat got a baby goat in her belly!
Huh? Really?
When will it be born, Mr. Parker?
Well, you see... I'm not sure...
This is wonderful. Now
hurry up and be born, okay?
Lucy-May.
This goat isn't yours yet, you know?
Can you walk? Tell me, can you walk?
Are you okay? Now, let's try walking slowly.
Like that, slowly, slowly.
Let's go home now.
How will Adelaide look like in the future?
Here is our rough idea of it.
Surely, you don't intend to build
the same city as on this blueprint?
No, the Colonel's order was
to follow this blueprint exactly.
Presently, we're building the roads
according to this blueprint.
I see.
By the way, I was planning to run a farm here.
That's what we came to Southern Australia for.
Is there any similar map for the farmlands?
Actually, we haven't made much progress at all
in surveying the farmland.
What does that mean?
What I'm trying to say... well...
It will take a little longer for the farmland
to come into your possession.
How long will it take?
Well you see... I can't say...
After all, the surveying is lagging behind,
while the applicants are numerous.
Then, for how long do I have to wait?
One year or maybe two years.
What did you say?
Well, in either case, I can't say with exact certainty...
Then, who can tell me for certain?
Well... I don't think anyone knows for sure.
Not even the Surveyor General Colonel Light?
The Colonel is currently away
on a surveying mission in the northern parts.
But even if you could ask Colonel directly...
it's probable that he might
not be able to give you an answer.
That's not even close
to what we've been promised!
The reason I came all the way here
to Southern Australia...
was to build a splendid farm,
because you have plenty of land for it.
We were told that as soon as we get here,
you'll give us the land right away.
But sir, you have to understand: you can't just randomly subdivide land that hasn't been surveyed yet.
For now, there is just no other way
but to wait and see.
But then, what in the world
do you want me to do?
I've been a farmer for my whole life.
So I can't even imagine myself doing any other job.
Right now, they're constructing
the streets in the city.
In the mountains to the east,
the logging is in the full swing.
The craftsmen who build houses
are also in a very short supply.
What I mean is, we've got
plenty of jobs available.
It isn't just you, many are in the same situation.
In that case... I just want a piece of land in the city.
Are you planning to build a house?
From England, we brought along
a prefabricated home, although it's still on the ship.
How are you planning to bring it
all the way here?
By oxcart.
You'll have to divide it into several runs.
That might take up to a month of time.
Until then, are you planning
to live in a tent?
No, I never even thought
things might come to this.
How about I offer you
to buy not only land, but a house, too?
Actually, there is one that comes to mind...
Just land would be enough.
Well, if it's just the land you need,
you're free to settle wherever you please.
But we don't have much plots with houses.
Our housing can't really keep up
with the rapid population growth.
For me... the land is enough.
It's a rather small house, isn't it?
You can't really call this a house.
We can still build
our prefabricated home here, right?
Hmm? Yeah.
We could use that house for storage,
couldn't we?
Am I finally seeing my new neighbors?
Oh, no, we haven't decided yet.
I'm Jane Mac, nice to meet you.
Yes.
You've heard about this house
from my brother, right?
Huh?
My brother works
in Colonel Light's office
and my husband right now
is working alongside Colonel.
Ah! That means
the man we met earlier was...
I'm certain it was
my brother, Bernard.
I'm Arthur Popple,
and this is my son Ben.
I only came to see the house
because I was curious.
I always tell my brother,
"If you're inviting someone to become our neighbor,
make sure they're a good person first."
Yes, well, we're going to look
inside the house.
It can't be.
Then, what happened
to your contract with Mr. Jamling?
Mr. Jamling injured his leg
and can't move for now, correct?
How did you know that?
Someone told me.
That's why I canceled my contract with Mr. Jamling
and that oxcart now goes to Mr. Pettywell.
Did you say Mr. Pettywell?
Oh! I said it.
Well, you would've found out sooner or later.
That's right.
That marvelously strong ox
is to start working for Mr. Pettywell
the day after tomorrow.
But I'm very sorry for you.
Is there no one else with an ox in the area?
Well...
Pretty sure everyone had already
signed a contract for an ox.
Shouldn't be a lot of them, if any.
Then are you saying I won't find anyone?
I guess so...
But I was so relieved to hear Mr. Jamling
had already secured a contract.
Again with the same story as before?
I've made a new contract
with Mr. Pettywell.
Moreover, he paid in advance!
What did you say?
Negotiations went sour?
No, the negotiations
are already concluded, Mr. Pettywell.
Oh, I'm glad then.
Come on, boy, come here
and drink some more with me.
Thanks for the offer!
You heard what I said.
That Mr. Pettywell is the worst.
Whatever the case, let's try somewhere else.
The day after tomorrow, be it an ox or a horse,
we need some animal to move our things.
Hey, you!
I just remembered I've got
one wheelbarrow to spare. How about that?
Tsk, try to be friendly
and this is how you're treated.
I've put Tob to bed.
Thank you.
What do you think happened
to father and Ben?
They're simply a bit late, nothing more.
Do you think they'll manage
to get through that forest when it's so dark?
What should I name you?
Nobody has come to look for you,
so I suppose that means you're mine.
Lucy-May.
What is it?
You're so carefree, you know that?
We're all so worried about dad!
But you're only thinking about that goat.
I'm also worried!
- No you're not.
I'm talking to her because I worry about dad
and try to get my mind off it!
Liar!
You're an idiot, sister!
Why are you calling me an idiot?
I'm calling you an idiot
because you are an idiot!
What did you say?
That's enough, you two!
Mmm!
That ship that brought us here -
the day after tomorrow,
it departs for England.
The day after tomorrow?
They're running ahead of schedule.
That's what John told me.
Tomorrow, we definitely need
to unload the rest of our luggage.
You're right.
What happened to your father?
I wonder, too.
It became completely dark,
but dad and brother hadn't returned yet.
We were just sitting there silently
for what seemed to be an eternity.
I wonder what happened to dad.
Dad and brother never returned
even when it's gotten very late.
Could they have taken the wrong road and got lost?
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Ben's Bad Luck".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you