South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 38 - Lucy, the Detective
Never!
Anything... Anything but this! I can't give this up!
Hey! Move away from it!
I can become very mean
towards those who disobey me.
Master! It can get very dangerous, Master.
Master!
Never! I absolutely won't move away!
Oh?
I take it you don't need your life, then?
If you don't step away by the time I count to ten,
I'll drop the courtesies and do away with you.
Master!
Kate, I'm scared.
It's just a threat...
I'm scared!
The stagecoach that Lucy and me took to get home
got assaulted by a gang of tree robbers.
Mr. Pettywell, carrying a bag, and his servant Adam boarded the same stagecoach as we.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine...
They shot me!
Huh?
What now? You should've done that
from the very beginning.
Master, are you hurt?
Ah... No... No...
Hey! I recovered the bag!
How's it going over there?
All done except these children.
Children shouldn't have any money on them.
You never know.
Everyone did their part.
Hey! You do your part too!
But we don't have anything with us...
Don't lie to me!
It's the truth.
Please take this.
Hm? What's that?
Marbles.
What did you say?
Those are the marbles that I value very much.
Take them.
Get it away, you idiot!
These brats are making fun of grown-ups!
Hey! We've no time to play with some children now!
We've got the king's ransom.
The sooner we make a getaway - the better! Come on.
Okay. Got it.
Ah!
Ah! Dammit! That bag...
Ladies and gentlemen!
Thanks for cooperation. And now, farewell!
Giddyup!
Damn it! Damn it all! Ah!
Master, it's not money, but your life...
Your life is what matters the most!
Ah! The money! 50,000 pounds! Ah!
We should let the police know as soon as possible.
They took away my diamond ring!
Let's leave it to police to catch those goons.
Yes. Either way, we need to return to Adelaide first.
Do we really have to walk all the way on feet?
Hey, you, do something already!
Even if you say so, that'd be quite problematic.
Only god knows where my carriage is by now.
Let's return to the road and see.
Kate.
Hm?
I'm scared.
What are you saying?
The robbers left already.
They won't come back.
It's not that.
Eh? What, then?
Master. Get yourself together, please.
Adam, whatever it takes,
we gotta get that money back...
I suppose... It was 50,000 pounds, wasn't it?
50,000 pounds!
W-What's wrong, Master?
This is strange.
Mighty strange, I would say.
W-What do you mean?
How did those robbers know
the bag had money inside, huh?
Well...
That was because they saw me
holding it as something valuable.
No, those guys didn't look inside the bag even once.
And yet, I clearly heard him saying,
"There's a king's ransom inside."
D-Do you think so?
Without ever looking inside the bag,
these guys knew there's a huge sum in it!
Why's that, Adam?
Eh? Eh... Well, how am I supposed to know that, huh?!
Ah! Damn it!
Damn it!
Hey! I found the carriage!
Look, it's over there.
Ah! Thank goodness.
Everyone, I'll get the carriage back to here.
Wait there for just a moment!
At least, it seems you won't have to walk
all the way to Adelaide. Aren't you glad, Master?
After I just gave 50,000 pounds to robbers,
what's there to be glad about, you imbecile?
Ah... I'm awfully sorry.
Damn it!
I'm scared.
What's going on?
You've been going on "scared, scared"
for a while now.
I saw it.
What?
I saw it all!
Yes. The time is not specified, but Master
would be bringing the money in the afternoon.
Are you sure there's no mistake, Adam?
Is he bringing along that stupid bulldog too?
Probably.
What did you see, Lucy?
I can't say.
I can't say it now. I'm too scared!
Hm?
Hey! Hey! Who do you think you are
to stop your stagecoach in front of the police station?
I-It's bandits!
What?
While passing though the Hindmarsh Prairie,
we got robbed by three goons!
Eh... Seems like I ended up staying for pretty long.
Ah, that drink was good too.
Why don't you stay and have
dinner with us too, Doctor Deighton?
No, no, no, you've spoiled me enough as it is.
Oh no. You needn't be shy, Doctor.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
Right, welcome back.
Doctor, you're in luck. I'm coming home
with a fresh loaf of delicious bread today.
No, I was actually just about to have my leave.
Oh.
Well, goodbye, then.
Doctor, please be wary of the robbers.
What? Robbers?
Yes. They say a stagecoach was robbed today.
Oh?
Clara, at what time did it happen?
Just now. I saw that robbed carriage
in front of the police station myself.
It was a stagecoach going to the port.
Oh my!
What's the matter, mother?
Do you know what happened
to the passengers of that stagecoach?
Should be at the police station now...
Then, was someone killed or injured?
Who knows. But tell me,
why are you so inquisitive about that?
Well, you see, it's possible that Kate and Lucy
took that stagecoach, Ms. Clara.
Huh?
Ben stopped by today and took those two to the port.
No way...
I'm going to the police station.
Where's father?
I have to apologize.
He was drinking with me, but the fellow drank
one too much and is sleeping now.
Father... Was very thoughtful of him
to do that at such a moment.
Hey. Marsh, don't bother me.
Yes, that's why...
That's why, Inspector Clark,
the initial objective of those robbers
have been me and my 50,000 pounds.
I'm convinced it's so.
I'm gradually coming to see it this way too.
Still, one part of it just doesn't sit well with me.
How exactly it doesn't sit well with you?
That's the only possible explanation.
Supposing that as you say, Mr. Pettywell,
the robbers' objective had been your money,
How did the robbers know
you would be riding that stagecoach?
Huh?
You're saying that your own carriage broke down,
so you and Adam had to ride a stagecoach
completely by chance, right?
T-That's right! How could they possibly know
I would be riding that stagecoach?
I believe, I have the answer to that.
Eh? You do?
So what is your answer, Inspector Clark?
The breakdown of your carriage was prearranged
with the intention of getting you to ride a stagecoach.
I see.
But then, why would those robbers
go to such great pains?
Why not just assault my own carriage directly?
That's exactly it. That's one thing I can't figure out.
A while ago you said you saw something
that you were very scared of, didn't you?
Yes.
What did you see?
Tell me, what did you see?
Today, on my way back from school...
Yes?
On my way back, I climbed a tree, and then...
Ah!
Right, sorry to have kept you waiting.
Everyone else can now come inside too.
Ah, little ladies, sorry for the delay.
Unless there's anything important you could tell us,
you two can return home now.
It's getting pretty late, after all.
Lucy, you have something you could tell, don't you?
Huh? You have something?
No, it's nothing.
Then, you're free for today.
Lucy! Kate!
Ah...
Mother!
Now, then. You two sure been
through some scary stuff.
Hey, we've arrived to the mansion.
Come out, Silver!
Hey, make it quick, please.
I'm tired from walking all day!
So Mr. Pettywell lost 50,000 pounds, isn't that right?
It has to be it, after all.
Listen, Lucy. This is a very important point to make,
so I want you to tell us once more to be sure.
Are you sure the person
you saw under the tree was Adam?
Yes, no doubt about it.
Besides, there was also the other man
who called him Adam.
Alright. Let's sum it up, Lucy.
You believe Mr. Pettywell's servant Adam
was an accomplice of the Robbers, correct?
Yes. Besides, in order to separate Mr. Pettywell
from his bulldog, he sabotaged the carriage,
so that Mr. Pettywell would have to take a stagecoach.
Why didn't you tell any of this to the police?
Whenever I looked at Adam's face,
I was getting awfully scared.
Besides, what if the police doesn't believe my story...
I suppose. No, don't get me wrong,
usually, I wouldn't doubt whatever Lucy says.
But this story right here
is not backed by a single proof.
That's true.
The police would surely
want to see some proof, won't they?
But I believe it! And I think we'd best
retell this story to the police.
Yes, I think so too.
Even if there's no telling what the police
would make of it, I'll go there now.
Perhaps I've been a little too rash, after all.
If you think of it,
the prospect of Mr. Pettywell's long-time servant being in cahoots with the robbers is too unrealistic.
When I told the whole thing
to the inspector, he snubbed it.
But Lucy isn't the kind of child to be telling lies.
Yes, the person Lucy saw passing below
while climbing the tree was most certainly Adam.
But that's pretty much all we have.
I don't really think so.
Listen, we gotta watch our step from now on.
If we call Adam a robber without any solid proof,
that'd be the most outrageous thing.
You there, Lucy? Come in for a moment.
Inspector Clark is an idiot for not believing my story.
Lucy-May.
Father, you believe me, right?
Yes. But you know, without the evidence,
the police can't take any story seriously.
Good night.
Dad returned, right?
Even if nobody believes me, I'll do it on my own.
I'll find the evidence that he conspired with robbers!
I'll help you too.
Have a good day.
Without relying on anyone else, Lucy-May
made up her mind to find that evidence.
She figured, if she'd keep watch on Adam, one day,
he'll go meet with his accomplices to get his share.
And then...
Of course, I also came to help her with that.
We'd take turns in keeping watch,
and at times, even did it together.
I wonder who that was.
I'm sure it was a doctor.
There's no way he'd ask Dr. Deighton for help, right?
Of course! Not after he's been
mistreating him that badly.
But if they needed a doctor to come,
that means someone's ill, doesn't it?
Doctor Smith has arrived.
Why did you bring me a doctor?
Well... It was the Madam.
I don't need no doctor. Only the recovery
of my 50,000 pounds would cure me immediately.
Are those Robbers not captured yet?
I'll invite the doctor into the room now.
My 50,000 pounds...
Any abnormalities?
None. The only one going in and out is Madam.
And Adam?
Doesn't go outside either.
Ah, scratch that, he's going outside!
He's finally on the move.
I wonder the robbers would really
set up their hideout in a place so lively.
This way is to the River Torrens.
To our old house.
I wonder if Doctor Deighton
is the robbers' accomplice too?
Don't say such nonsense, Kate.
What now? You again? Need something from me?
Your time is finally up, Doctor.
Tomorrow, or the day after tomorrow at most,
please vacate the house, okay?
Never!
Well, we've no choice, then.
Want us to tear this house down with you inside?
You don't mind that, huh?
Seems like he just came to tell Dr. Deighton
to move out from the house.
Going back already?
So we were following him in vain?
Wait a minute. He stopped on his way.
He's going towards the river.
This time, is has to be it! He's going there to meet
with his accomplices. Now, let's hurry after!
Wait! If we get too close, he'll spot us!
He's going to that cabin, doesn't he?
On the riverbank.
Seems so. That must be it!
Things suddenly got interesting!
It's me.
It's Adam!
Sure no one saw you coming here?
Of course.
That cabin is where the robbers hide. I'm sure.
S-So that really is where the robbers are hiding, huh?
What's wrong?
W-We gotta call someone from the police.
Me and Little will stay here to keep a lookout,
and you go get help.
Right. I'm going...
Huh?
Hold it.
Shh.
Inspector Clark?
The robbers are in that cabin, aren't they?
Yes.
And you must be Lucy?
Thanks to your testimony, we could put together that Adam was an accomplice of robbers. It was of huge help.
But Inspector, aren't you the type of person
who wouldn't believe a child's story?
No, it's just that I had to put on airs of disbelieving,
even if that was rude towards your father.
That's why Adam, only slightly worried,
paid a visit to his buddies here so soon.
If Adam would've suspected that the police
was on his tail, he'd panic and try to flee.
They came out!
Damn it, they came out
much sooner than I expected.
The reinforcements haven't arrived yet.
You can count on Little's strength.
Little, you must drive those men
back into the hut.
You get it!
Go!
What now? A stray dog?
Damn you! Such insolent dog!
Hey!
I've had enough!
Splendid. Just splendid!
You there! We have you surrounded!
Lay down your arms and come out!
Come right out!
Thus, all of the robbers were arrested.
Nearly all of the stolen money
was found with them.
You don't need it?
Are you saying 100 shillings as my token of gratitude
are too few for you?
Not at all.
We're saying Lucy didn't do anything
that'd warrant a gratitude.
I see, you're teaching your children to be humble?
Then, I don't suppose you mind
if I take these 100 shillings back?
Mr. Pettywell.
What is it?
To tell you the truth,
I'd like to ask for a reward.
Lucy-May.
Right, right, being honest like that
is the best way, Young Lady.
No. It's not about money.
Huh?
As a reward, I'd like to ask you
to not drive Dr. Deighton out of that house.
"That house," you mean...
Dr. Deighton's clinic, right?
That's right. Please do that for me.
That, I can't grant.
That train already left, young lady.
Huh?
Doctor Deighton was driven out of his brick house.
And so, he came to our house
to live with us once again.
Doctor Deighton is going to the city of Gawler.
We won't see him again any time soon.
But then, there's one more sad parting on the horizon.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Two Partings".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you