South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 46 - The Wombat in the Pit
Together with dad, we went to see the mine.
That was where we found the wallabies.
Maybe we should take it with us
and bring it up at home?
I'll catch it.
Tob chased after the baby wallaby.
As cute as it is, bringing it up
from such a small age is probably impossible.
I suppose.
Don't go any further, Tob!
Come back now.
Tob!
Huh?
Tob! Tob! Tob!
What's wrong, Lucy?
What's wrong?
Tob suddenly disappeared.
Huh? What did you say?
Tob! Tob, where are you?
Tob!
Lucy, you were watching him, right?
I was watching, but...
If so, you were supposed to notice,
exactly where Tob disappeared!
Well, it's was exactly around here!
You've only seen it from afar,
so maybe we should walk a little further?
Tob! Are you hiding somewhere?
Ah!
Kate? Kate!
Kate, where are you?
Here! I'm here! Tob is here too!
Kate! Is it this pit?
Did you fall into this pit?
I can't see you from here.
Don't worry, I can see you from here!
It's because it's so dark in here!
So you two aren't hurt, are you?
Tob, are you okay?
Yes.
Are you really okay?
Stop crying, then.
Kate, what about you?
My butt kinda hurts.
Can you get out?
I'll try now.
I'm going out first!
Why didn't you respond
when we called out to you from above?
I probably fainted.
That must be it.
Huh?
But I came to my senses when you landed on me.
Are you sure it doesn't hurt anywhere?
A little, in my shoulder.
But I'll be fine.
Then, you try to climb out first.
Come out sooner, you two!
Tob is coming right now!
Here you go.
There!
Listen, put your feet on my shoulders.
But I'll soil your dress.
Now's not the time to be saying that!
O-Okay, then...
Climb a little higher!
I'll pull you up from here!
Useless. I can't climb here!
Head, head!
Huh?
Stand on my head!
I can't do that.
It's fine, hurry up!
Just a little more, Tob!
There...
A bit more!
Here, give me your hand, Tob.
You're almost there!
Here, take my hand!
Oh...
You almost did it.
Let's give it another try.
It's pointless. I can't climb that, sister!
Stop saying that and try once more!
Tob! Don't give up!
Come on, I'll push you up with my head again.
The rent is cheap,
so we gotta make do with this much.
But living here for five years would be too much.
Clara and Ben won't be living with us,
and if it's just us and three little children,
this company housing should suffice.
Children grow up fast.
In other words, you're saying
you don't want to live in this company housing?
What I said was not just about the house.
It was about this whole "working in a mine" affair.
Besides, there are no schools around.
You could teach them yourself.
Tell me, honey, do you really feel
that working here is your best option?
I never said it's the best option.
But I thought things through
before opting out for this work.
Can't you think about it for a little more?
No other job around here pays quite as well.
Still, if I could get you to rethink...
Ah. I think I'll go back
to where we left the children now.
Okay.
I'll be waiting there until you finish
your business in the office!
Okay. It won't take long.
Tob! Left! Your left!
Tob, there's a protrusion just above your left foot.
Try to put your foot on that!
Not your right! Left! Left!
Left, I said! Geez!
Can't you tell right from left?
I can't!
Come on, just a little more!
Grab my hand, Tob.
No, other! Give me your other hand.
Right, right!
Tob! Your foot to the right! Quick!
Good. Good! Don't let your guard down. Slowly. Slowly!
Lucy, start pulling yourself back up!
But don't rush! Do it slower!
Good! One last push, keep going!
What are you crying about now, Tob?
Ah! Kate!
Try to climb up, Kate.
Don't be stupid. There's no way I can climb out myself.
That's why I let Tob get out first.
What would we do, then?
Why are you asking me?
I could get out if we had a rope or a ladder.
In other words, go find an adult first!
Got it. I'll go now.
Make it quick!
Okay.
I'll go bring some adult here, okay?
I'll go too.
No way! You want to leave Kate all alone in this pit?
Listen, if you see someone passing through here,
ask for their help, okay?
Yes.
Well, I'll be on my way now.
Okay.
Ouch!
Kate?
What is it?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
If anyone owes me an apology, that's gotta be
the guy who dug this pit out then left it as it is.
This pit was certainly dug out by people.
Could there be something in it?
Ah!
Ouch! Oh, shucks!
Tob! Tob, is Lucy not back yet?
Didn't she just barely left?
I need to get out soon!
There's something in it!
Huh?
There's something in this tunnel!
Dad! Dad, it's serious!
What happened, Lucy?
It's very serious!
Which way?
Over there.
Okay.
Dad, rope! The rope!
Right...
Kate, what's in there?
A snake? A lizard?
I can't see it, I don't know!
You'll be fine, just hang in there!
That's Kate's voice.
What's going on there?
Just a wombat?
Seems like someone didn't bother
to properly bar his trial mine...
That's true.
Did you really shriek that terribly
from seeing an animal so peaceful?
You didn't sound like yourself.
How may times do I have to tell you?
I couldn't see well there.
On top of that, this wombat is still a baby!
Spare for Lucy, who felt elated
on the occasion of finding a wombat she could keep,
on our way back from the mine,
everyone was in pretty low spirits.
Oh my, they returned so soon?
That was really fast.
Welcome ba...
Hello.
Um...
I beg your pardon. I'm Mr. Princeton's wife.
Ah! So, the one who helped Lucy...
And you must be... Ms. Clara, right?
Pleased to meet you.
You've done so much for my little sister...
Ah, please, come in.
Where's everyone today?
To tell you the truth, father would likely
soon start working in a mine,
so he went to look at the mine and the company lodgings
together with my mother and siblings.
Ah, I was just preparing a portion of tea.
Would you like some?
Yes. Thank you.
So, Lucy also went there with them?
Yes.
Which mine did they go to?
If I'm not mistaken, it's the one near Mount Barker.
Ah, could it be our company's mine?
Huh?
Pretty sure my husband told me
he invested into a mine near Mount Barker.
Oh my...
Then, the company my dad
would be working for is Mr. Princeton's company?
Probably.
Oh? What a coincidence!
I'm sure dad had no idea.
I'm just saying he invested in it.
My husband is not exactly the head of that company,
so I can't know for sure.
So that's how it is?
Turns out, it was Mr. Princeton's company? Eh?
Dad went to Mr. Princeton's company.
Eh?
So, at what hour do you expect everyone to be back?
I can't exactly predict
how much time it would take them...
Now, here.
Thank you.
I heard it from Lucy.
You're engaged, aren't you?
My, Lucy talking too much again!
So it's true, isn't it?
Yes.
Are you getting married soon?
Y-Yes.
When you do, be sure to invite me, okay?
Yes.
You're Lucy's big sister, after all.
So I really feel like you're a daughter
of some relative of mine.
When do you think it'll be?
You mean the wedding ceremony?
No.
I mean, when will Lucy return?
I can't believe that mine
belongs to Mr. Princeton's company.
That's true.
That's what Mrs. Princeton told me.
Life is full of interesting coincidences.
What's more interesting, that Mr. Princeton
seems to be awfully rich.
Clara, what did Mrs. Princeton come here for?
I didn't quite understand it myself.
But above all, I believe, she wanted to see Lucy.
Just for that?
Seemed so to me.
If it hadn't been so, why'd she ask me to pass to Lucy
that she absolutely wants Lucy to come visit her?
That's true. Ah, thank you.
Next Sunday, can take Lucy
for a visit to the Princetons house?
I'm morbidly curious
to look at the mansion they're living in.
I'll go.
Huh?
I'll take Lucy there.
Now that you mention it,
when Mr. Princeton came the other day...
He said he wanted to have a talk
with you about farming.
Hm...
Even so, to think that the mine we've been to
belongs to Mr. Princeton too...
Listen Little. You can by no means bully this baby.
If he was still a wild dingo,
he'd totally attack a wombat.
With Little, it'll be alright.
I suppose. He never attacked the sheep, after all.
Now then, how about I make a nest for you?
I'll help too.
We didn't give it a name yet.
You're right.
You sure have a funny little face.
Funny!
What do you think, Kate?
Fine by me.
Kate, you've a very red face.
My head hurts too. For a while now.
Ah! You've a fever!
Going already?
Yes.
I wanted to go too!
To see the Princeton Mansion and all...
Not while you're ill!
I've not been ill even once
ever since we came to Southern Australia.
It's not the last time I'm going to Princetons.
I'm yet to go there time and again after this.
That's what I feel.
Their Missus smelled really nice, didn't she?
That's because she uses a perfume.
Well, I'll be going now.
Have a nice day.
The next day, with Lucy in tow,
dad went to visit to the Princetons.
I'm quite impressed.
With what?
This is the first time
I'm entering a mansion so gorgeous.
I'm glad you could make it, Mr. Popple.
Thank you for inviting us.
Lucy! I'm so glad to see you again.
Mr. Popple, my husband is currently out,
but he'll be back before long.
You could wait for him over there...
Ah! Prospero!
You still remember me, don't you?
It tickles!
You've a beautiful garden.
I've not been able to look after it very well lately.
But isn't it really curious?
Back when Lucy lived here,
she used to go play a lot in this garden.
And I think that was what made the garden
truly bright and beautiful.
Lucy is incredibly fond of animals.
When she played with birds in this garden,
not yet having recovered her memory,
and said to me,
"I seems, I was a very animal-loving girl,"
I was deeply moved by that.
I see.
Ah. Seems like my husband is back.
Hello, welcome.
I came to see you just as you requested.
What do you say if we leave the ladies here
and proceed to over there?
I'd like to talk to you in the library.
Okay.
Well then.
I'll get straight to it, Mr. Popple.
You shouldn't work at a mine.
Huh?
If it's fine with you,
I'd like you to work at my farm instead.
Okay...
I don't ask you to give your answer right now.
Of course, if you'd say you want to work at a mine
no matter what, that's fine too.
However, Mr. Popple, didn't you come to this country
in order to work in agriculture?
That's true...
Well, first of all, I wanted to listen
to your thoughts about agriculture today.
Tell me, Lucy.
Do you like this house?
Yes, it's pretty and big.
You know, I'd be the happiest ever
if you stayed in this house from now on and forever.
I so wanted to go to the Princeton Mansion...
Lucy is probably having lots of fun by now.
Our wombat Funny ran away into the front door.
Just as Mr. Pettywell's carriage was driving by.
Watch out, Funny!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Dad's Decision".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you