South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 21 - The Man Who Designed Adelaide
Looks delicious already.
Ah, and so cold!
I wonder if the goats are also thirsty this morning.
Oh my, what happened to your goatling, Sticky?
I see, you're just as worried as I am?
Oh!
It got out through here, didn't it?
But where could it be now?
Lucy-May, I'll cut the rest of it myself.
You go roll them instead.
I don't know how to roll well...
Ah... You're a clumsy one.
Wouldn't the roll be tighter
if I hold it from this end?
I guess so. Hold it for me, will you?
Ah? What are you up to, you two?
Can't you tell by looking?
We're making bandages.
If you do it without permission,
Dr. Deighton will scold you.
Not if Doctor himself asked us to do it!
That's right.
Ah... Lucy-May, I can't find the goatling anywhere.
Seems like it dug under the fence to fly the coop.
Are you serious, sis?
For how long had it been gone?
No clue. When I checked just now,
it was already missing.
I'll go look for it!
If Mr. Pettywell and his black dog
decide to attack it, it's very bad!
No way! Very bad!
Ah...
I'm coming to look for it, too!
And leaving the bandages half-done, just like that?
We'll do it later.
That's irresponsible, you...
Pansy!
Pansy! Pansy!
Huh?
Ah! Pansy! Don't do that!
Whoa! That was awfully naughty of you to do!
Can you imagine how excited we were
to try a salad made from these radishes?
And where'd Lucy-May go to look for you?
Lucy-May! Lucy-May! I found it right here!
I found this Pansy vermin!
And don't eat the plants
from our field next time, will you?
You understand, Pansy?
Goats don't understand a single word
of what we humans say.
Ouch! Hit it!
Gotta be more attentive, Kate.
We'll have to tell Clara, won't we?
If we keep mum, nobody would have a clue.
"Nobody would have a clue," seriously?
Dad and mom could tell what's what
at the first glance!
But they couldn't tell it was Pansy who ate it all.
You're quite the rogue, you know that?
Come on, let's keep mum!
At least with Clara.
So you found it?
Yes.
You're making me feel like a fool.
I've finished rolling up all the bandages already.
Thank you. And sorry for the trouble, sister.
Did you know? Pansy never went to the field
that's behind our house.
It was actually just hiding in the grass over there,
cross my heart!
Now, now, just put Pansy back into the enclosure.
See? It won't run away again.
Okay.
Sister, could you put this hammer
back into the toolbox for me?
And what will you do?
I'll go look at Mr. Mac's burial.
No! Children can't go there.
We're just going to watch secretly from afar.
Are you coming too, Lucy-May?
Of course I am.
Well, sis, counting on you.
Okay...
Wait for me!
How irresponsible!
Ah! And what is this little thing doing?
Hey!
Hold it!
Ah!
You don't suppose the funeral is already over, sis?
Dad and the others have been gone for a long while.
Funerals aren't supposed to end so soon.
But let's step up anyways.
The funeral of our neighbor Mr. Mac
was held on top of a lonely hill
on the outskirts of Adelaide.
There wasn't yet any cemetery to speak of.
And of course, no pastor either.
So we came a bit late, after all...
And who might that man be?
The one that approached Mrs. Mac?
Yes. And now he's talking to Mr. Bernard.
Well, I'll have my leave now.
And please stay strong.
Lucy-May! Hurry! If dad notices us,
we'll certainly get scolded!
Let's go this way!
Seems like we escaped unnoticed.
Oh, I know!
Eh? What?
The slim man we saw before.
Who was it?
It was Colonel Light!
Colonel William Light.
The man who designed Adelaide.
The Surveyor General of all of Southern Australia!
So that man was Colonel Light?
Probably the busiest man in town,
he still bothered to show up for the funeral.
Shh!
They're here!
I certainly wasn't expecting
even Colonel Light to attend.
You too, sister?
Yes.
He had just returned from the Barossa Valley.
To arrive here at this hour,
he had to get up awfully early in the morning.
Is that the area they're currently surveying?
That area as well.
I just hope that man keep doing his best
to expedite the surveying process.
I'm itching to start cultivating
our own plot as soon as possible.
Some say, that man is currently
the busiest man in all of Southern Australia!
Mapping the backwoods and surveying the land
both are immensely time-consuming.
I never understood that before coming here.
But still...
I must tell you, that man's health
is actually deteriorating.
He's sick?
Apparently, he's been suffering
chest pains for a while now.
But in order to fulfill his duties
he denies himself any sleep or rest.
Now that's just excessive.
Father...
Am I free to go play around for the rest of today?
Yes, of course.
Up to this point, we were constantly
overly reliant on your help.
I'll get back to work tomorrow.
What do you want to do now?
Fishing.
Fishing, then? However, they don't sell
any fishing lines or hooks here.
I brought some with me from England.
Eh? First time I'm hearing of that.
Not just that, but I chose really good ones.
A remarkable preparedness!
Should I try around here?
Certainly, they sprout a lot faster here.
The growth is also fast.
And the season for sowing seeds
is only slightly different from that in England.
Yes. We don't know what winter will be like yet...
But it's clearly going to be warmer than in Yorkshire.
Don't you think the rain is too sparse here?
It's sparse indeed.
But it also could be a seasonal thing
and it's only so sparse this year.
Yes, yes.
Oh?
It's been nibbled on!
What could've nibbled on it?
Maybe Lucy-May's hamster?
No, these footprints...
Father, those are the goat's footprints.
Too small for a goat.
The goatling's.
Goatling's?
Goatling escaped the enclosure earlier today.
I see. That goatling and his mother
are our prime concern when it comes to the field.
Clara, speaking of which,
where are Kate and Lucy-May?
I tried to stop them,
but they went to see the funeral anyway.
Huh? They were there, too?
But when you all have returned home,
I thought they should return soon, too.
Go.
Quickly!
Okay.
Maybe he went downstream?
It's upstream for sure!
I think our brother went downstream.
It was upstream! I'm sure.
Why dontcha go upstream to check, then?
I'm afraid to go alone.
In that case, we're going downstream!
Ah!
Gotcha!
That was very clumsy, bro!
Ah, it's you!
Haven't fished out a single one yet?
And I was hoping I'd finally get to fish
all by myself after all this time...
Well, we're not here to bother you or anything.
Right, Lucy-May?
Yeah! I know the last time you went fishing
was rightly ages ago!
To be precise, about five months ago or so,
when we were still in England.
That's quite the long spell without fishing!
Plus, maybe the fish in England and in Australia
require different techniques to catch them?
How 'bout you call that enough, you two?
Yessir! We'll watch in silence!
Such a big fish living here!
Ben, pull it now!
Quiet! I know!
If you don't pull it out soon,
it'll just run away again!
It's still too soon to pull it out now!
Now!
Keep it up, Ben!
Don't let your guard down!
Ah! The line's gonna snap!
You should relax it a bit, Ben!
Be quiet, you two!
Whoa! It's big!
Pull it harder!
Slower! Do it slowly!
You can do it, bro!
Don't you lose out to it!
Relax it a little!
Right, right! Relax a little!
Huh?
Alright, now's your chance!
Wow! Incredible!
Ah!
Rats!
Your pulling timings are in need of work.
It was thanks to you chiding in
that I've lost my cool!
Oh... Well, my apologies if so,
Ah?
Colonel Light?
Oh?
I've seen you earlier today.
Yes. I was also attending Mr. Mac's funeral.
And who exactly were you to poor Mac?
We were neighbors.
Oh? What about them?
Your sisters, I reckon?
Yes. Kate and Lucy-May.
Ah, and I am Ben Popple.
Well, I see you already know who I am,
so I guess we can skip the part where I introduce myself.
I beg your pardon...
Speaking of which, Ben, it's been a truly long while
since I last had a day off.
On that occasion, I thought I'd go fishing.
Fishing here looks promising,
if you're good at it.
I can't exactly say I'm good at it either.
Rather, I'm on the same level as you.
That said, would you allow me to fish here?
You got any bait?
I thought I'd dig some when I get here.
In that case, feel free to use my bait.
You've not a lot of it left.
I'll be fine.
I need a favor from you two.
Quickly catch some worms in here, will you?
Girls are usually scared of worms.
I don't mind catching some myself.
You don't need to worry for these girls.
I'm sure Lucy-May dreams
of keeping a worm as a pet one day.
Even for someone like me, a worm
doesn't look like the kind of pet you'd wanna keep.
I see. You love all kinds of animals,
but worms are an exception?
But I'm not afraid of them either,
so I can catch some.
So be it. And sorry for the trouble!
See you later!
Please use these worms.
Okay, thank you.
How old are you?
I'm twelve.
Back when I was six,
I was taken away from home.
And when I was twelve, I joined the navy.
At that time, I was convinced
that I'm as much a grown-up as I will ever get...
But now I see - at twelve, one is still largely a child,
however you look at it.
Hm?
Ah... Too bad, too bad.
Say, don't you think this is enough already?
Why don't we gather a bit more just in case?
With this much, those two will be able
to treat all the fish in the river to a feast!
Colonel Light must be someone
terribly important, right?
He was way scarier in my mind,
but it turns out he's actually very kind.
Silence!
Huh?
That way! Look over there. But slowly.
Stop! Do it from here.
Just turn your head casually.
Near the root of that big tree, look.
A rabbit!
Wanna catch it?
Of course!
Then, I'll take these worms now
and go give them to brother and Colonel.
On my way back,
I'll walk to the other side of the tree.
In the meantime, you start approaching the rabbit slowly, while looking as unconcerned as you can.
I see! We'll surround it from both sides?
It's important that the rabbit doesn't get a hunch.
You got that?
Got it.
Here, your worms!
Hey, Kate!
What's going on with those two?
Oh? But that sure is a lot of worms they caught.
Alright, now we both gotta catch at least one.
We'll catch way more.
From an age of six and until I was twelve,
I lived in the village of Theberton, in England.
Until you joined the navy, right?
Yes.
The scenery in these parts
is exactly like that in Theberton.
You went fishing there as well?
Yes, I used to fish a lot.
Are you not feeling quite well?
Yes. It started way before I came to Australia.
But this place has an overwhelmingly good climate,
so who knows if I don't get better soon.
But you could also develop a fever
of unknown nature, just like Mr. Mac.
Hm. The hinterlands here
still harbor all kinds of dangers.
When I'm a bit older, I want to join the exploration team and go on expeditions to hinterlands all the time.
Sure you know what it means?
Last December, we had three folk die
on a mission of mapping the estuary of Murray River.
I didn't know that.
Seems like their boat capsized.
Eh?
Even to this day, some argue
that rather than building Adelaide here,
we should've founded it near Lake Alexandrina,
at the estuary of Murray River.
But this here seems like a great place.
The three that passed away last year
went there to find out whether or not
founding a city there would be viable.
Adelaide is just fine where it is now!
I think so, too.
Starting now, Adelaide's expansion
is bound to be explosive.
But no matter how much it expands,
it will never be a squalid and dirty place.
Have you ever been to London?
No, I haven't.
That city is full of places
that are utterly squalid and dirty.
It had become the focal point for all of Europe.
Our Adelaide, in turn,
is the world's cleanest city.
Its serenity is second to none.
And I'm confident that it'll stay this way, Ben.
Oh?
Ah! I caught one! I caught it! Look, Ben!
Wow!
Did it at last!
Ouch!
Whoa! It's a dingo!
You brute! It was ours! You thief!
We spotted that rabbit first!
Hey! Give it back! Give it back!
Hey! I demand you give it back, you thief!
We were so glad to find that rabbit!
That day, having discussed
a million different things with Colonel Light,
Ben came home with a light heart.
Conversely, the two of us
felt awfully dejected from letting a dingo
snatch away our rabbit.
Ben brings home a dingo puppy!
Although everyone says, "abandon it,
it may be dangerous," I'll keep it.
I'll definitely keep it!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Of Bricks and Dingo Puppies".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you