South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 30 - Birthday Gifts
Finished it! Look, isn't it pretty, Little?
Huh?
Little! Little?
What's the matter, Lucy?
Little suddenly disappeared.
Must be that he chased a butterfly or something.
Still, when I call, usually he'd return at once.
Little! Little!
Little!
At last, a spring was here.
And with it, Little also grew quite big.
Where have you been, Little? When I call for you,
you must return at once, is that clear?
Huh? What's going on, Little?
Seems like he wants you to come along.
I think so, too.
Tell me, Little.
Where exactly do you want me to go?
There are some sheep!
But why is it only two?
You wanted to show up this sheep you found?
Sit, Little.
It'll be alright, Madame Sheep.
Little won't do anything to you.
Must be that Mr. Long is somewhere in the vicinity.
But I don't see any other sheep around.
Then, those must be the lost sheep.
Let's help them find Mr. Long's herd, Kate.
But... Where exactly could Mr. Long be now?
Not too far from here, I think.
You're right. Let's try looking for him.
Ah! Little is going that way!
Let's go, too, Kate.
Yeah.
Come on, come on, come on.
You two need to hurry, too. Go!
Those are Mr. Long's dogs again.
I wonder why are they barking.
Must be that they sensed our smell.
Look!
Little, stick closely to me now. Okay?
Did you forget us, Monocle?
It's us - Lucy and Kate!
It's no use, Little is the cause.
He's barking at Little.
You mustn't growl in response, Little.
Okay, let's keep walking. Slowly, now.
Isn't it strange?
The dogs are making such a fuss over it.
And Mr. Long doesn't seem
to keep them in check at all.
You're right, very strange!
Mr. Long! Mr. Long!
It's as though he left for somewhere,
leaving the sheep unchecked.
Why'd he do something like that?
Well, he isn't anywhere around, is he?
Where are you going, Little?
If he gets in a fight with dogs,
he'll be in dire straights!
Hey!
Hey! Enough already, you two!
You can relax now, Little.
I wonder whose cabin this is.
I'm sure it's Mr. Long's.
Then, do you suppose he could be inside?
But it's very strange. It's been so loud outside here,
but he didn't come out.
Let's try looking inside.
I've a bad feeling about this!
It'll be alright. Let's just enter together.
Okay.
It's Mr. Long indeed...
Is he dead?
I'm not dead.
Ah!
I'm not dead yet, but I'm about to be.
Are you feeling sick?
That's right, very sick. Damn it...
Since when?
Since the day before yesterday.
Sister, let's go and get Dr. Deighton here.
You're right. I'll go find him at once.
Who are you bringing?
A doctor.
Oh, I'd much appreciate it.
And if you see Ben, bring Ben along too.
He'll probably also be around.
You two! Enough shadowing us already,
return to where the sheep are!
Little won't do anything!
I think it's best if you stay here with Lucy.
I'll also me back in no time.
Are you in pain, Mr. Long?
My head spins when I try to get up.
I tried many times to walk,
but would collapse immediately.
But you've nothing to worry about now,
'cause the doctor is on the way!
Thank you, Lucy. I'm so glad you could find me.
I though nobody would ever come here.
It was actually Little who found you!
Little? Ah! The baby dingo?
He'd become quite big already.
So that was what the dogs made all this fuss over?
But Little never had any intention
to hurt the sheep.
I'm really struggling to believe that.
This would be my first doctor's examination in life.
Wow! Really?
Back when I lived in England,
there wasn't any doctor in our village,
and naturally, I've not seen a single doctor
after I came to here.
I can assure you Dr. Deighton is an amazing doctor.
Even if a bit of a drunkard...
I see.
And why did you ask to bring Ben along?
Even if this doctor is as good as you say,
I don't think he'll be able to bring me back to feet
at a moment's notice.
Don't worry. You'll get well in no time.
Thank you.
But more importantly, the sheep need to be herded
to where there's water, that's what I need Ben for.
I wonder if Ben would be able to do that on his own.
He's oughta be.
He helped me with that before.
But I still don't believe in it...
In my brother?
No-no, not that. In a dingo
that's disinterested in sheep.
Oh? Right, right, right.
You're getting quite good with it, Ben.
Here, the bandage is done.
Let me see...
Hm.
Well, I'd say good enough.
Please come again in two or three days.
Okay.
Oh?
Doctor, please come with me right away!
What is it, Kate?
There's a sick person!
The shepherd, Mr. Long fell very ill!
Huh? Did you say Mr. Long?
Ah, right, right. He wanted you to come too.
Eh? Even Mr. Long already knows
I'm helping Doctor Deighton in his practice?
It was for some other reason
that he wanted you to come.
Kate.
So where exactly do we need to go to?
Ah, good, good, thanks.
You no longer feel dizzy?
Seems like I'm fine now.
By the way, where's that guy Little?
Waiting outside the cabin.
I'm curious.
Want me to bring him inside?
No, I'd rather come to the doorway to look at him.
Can you walk?
I can.
Hm?
I see! He even wags his tail like any other dog would.
Also, he's so big now!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Mr. Long! Mr. Long!
Hang on, Mr. Long!
W-wait! Wait a moment, please!
Doctor! One last push, please!
Ah! No, impossible.
Absolutely impossible. Ah, I can't take it.
I'm not Little, remember?
Doctor. Doctor!
Doctor!
Kate, it was because you rushed us too much,
that ever Doctor has foam at the mouth now!
Kate was... spurring me... "Run! Run!"
And I... I'm struggling to even just walk!
Hey, Ben, my bag.
Mr. Long's illness
wasn't that of an easily curable kind.
While he was recovering, Ben had to cover for him
and become a full-time shepherd himself.
A cake?
Mother, are you really making a cake today?
What's so surprising about a cake
when it's someone's birthday?
Because it's the first birthday cake we're having
ever since we came to Australia!
That's 'cause I barely had any free time
for making birthday cakes up until now.
Thank you, mom!
It's so marvelous! A birthday cake!
Still, you'll have to make do
without birthday presents for now.
Our life here is a little hectic as well.
Sure! I don't need no presents.
If we'll have a cake, I won't need anything!
Little! Little!
We'll be eating a cake tonight!
Okay, let's go for a walk!
There!
Ah! It's Lucy.
Let's have her carry half of our bags.
She seems especially exhilarated, somehow.
Remember the scene she made
about going shopping with us?
Judging by that look,
she totally wasn't studying.
Welcome back, girls.
Good job with the shopping.
Hold it, Lucy.
Yes?
Did you solve all the arithmetic problems?
Yes, I did.
Hey, can you carry this for me?
You're telling me to carry it,
after you left me behind while shopping?
It's actually heavier than it looks!
I'm not carrying it.
Well, Little, let's go now.
Something's definitely wrong with her.
Very strange.
Where are you going, Lucy?
Out for a short walk!
Hey!
My, Ben, you're home early today.
Yes. Mr. Long is finally recovering.
So he dismissed me from the shepherd's job today.
What about that sheep?
Mr. Long gave it to me.
Instead of your pay?
Not at all. He gave me the money as well.
He wanted me to give this to Lucy.
What for?
Well, it was Little who found Mr. Long
while he was suffering from illness.
That's kinda true.
Well, he wanted to repay that as well.
Also, he said you don't see a dingo
disinterested in sheep every day.
So if we keep them side by side, dingo and sheep
becoming buddies oughta do for a very amusing sight.
That sounds fun, indeed!
One couldn't think of a better present
for Lucy on her birthday!
Oh, really? It's her birthday today?
Mom had already started making a cake, I think.
I see. So we're finally in a position
where we can afford a proper birthday party again?
Me and Clara both bought presents for her, in secret.
Then, since this sheep is also a birthday present,
I'll try to hide it somewhere until the dinner.
I think... I'll hide it in my room.
Yes! Come in!
Doctor, Mr. Long recovered at a lightning speed.
He said he'd come by sooner or later to thank you.
Is that to say your job as a shepherd is concluded?
Yes. Starting tomorrow, I'll be joining my dad
for the road construction job.
Road construction, huh?
You're not having it easy, I see.
Back in England, all you had to do was going to school.
I think dad deserves more sympathy. He came
to Australia just to end up being a road builder.
I see... It was in the first days of winter, wasn't it?
When Mr. Popple said he might just have a chance
to get his hands on the land.
I was hoping that this spring your whole family
would already be able to move there.
Dad never told anyone where it was.
But it didn't go very well, I imagine.
I, too, hope your father
starts cultivating the land soon.
Here and there, in the fields,
the wheat is growing green already.
I wonder how dad feels about seeing that.
His life is meaningless here,
if he can't farm, isn't that right?
Little, look over there! It's a carriage.
Ah... Dad!
Lucy, what are you doing in a place like this?
We went on a walk, so I figured
I might as well show this place to Little.
What for?
I think it's important that Little
also knows his way through the area.
I also thought I should show him
how many people are living here.
Then, what was Little's reaction?
It doesn't look like he's been one bit surprised.
Say, dad, isn't it about time
we leave the worrying about Little behind?
No, we don't know anything for certain yet.
A wild animal like this
might be perfectly well-behaved at one point,
but at the very next one,
his ferocious dingo blood might call out to him.
Right now, I'm heading straight to home already.
I'm going back too.
Then, let's go together.
Okay.
Dad, you've been to Colonel Light's
surveying office right now, haven't you?
Yeah.
And I thought you'd be building roads all day again.
Hm. Not quite. There was something
I wanted to learn at Colonel's office.
What did you want to learn?
Hm?
I don't understand what "Hm" means!
Hm...
Hmm!
Mr. Popple, it's been a while, hasn't it?
Yes. Good afternoon, Mr. Pettywell.
I finally managed to obtain a carriage.
Looks marvelous.
By the way, have you had any progress
in getting the land?
No, not yet.
Just as I thought. The agricultural land
had been getting increasingly expensive lately.
I'm hearing there's a great many of folk just like you,
who came to Southern Australia,
seeking to cultivate the land,
but couldn't get their hands on any.
Yes, so it would seem.
Still, the surveying continues and the government
will eventually start selling the cheap land as well.
Well, I wonder if they will.
If you keep sincerely believing this kind of thing,
you might end up waiting in the line
to get the land for eternity, I reckon.
Giddy up!
Happy birthday.
Here's a small present from me.
A handkerchief.
Thank you, Kate.
Happy birthday, Lucy-May.
Here's my gift.
I hope you find some little treasure
you'd want to store in that.
Thank you, Clara.
Lucy, my gift today is a lamb.
Mr. Long gave it to me,
in order to see Little and a sheep getting along.
Whoa! Amazing!
Where is that sheep?
I put it in the enclosure with the goats.
You'll see it later.
Thank you, Ben!
Save your thanks for Mr. Long.
Of course I will!
Earlier, I told Lucy-May
that she shouldn't expect to get any gifts today.
And that she'd have to make do with just a cake.
But everyone ended up
giving her such marvelous things!
Yes. I'm extremely delighted!
Well, well, get to eating, everyone!
Thanks for the meal!
My? Do you mean to say you've prepared
some give for Lucy-May too?
Yes. I believe, Lucy-May will like it as well.
But in fact, it's somewhat more of a gift
to our entire family.
What is it about?
It's the land.
You need a vast space of land to run a farm on it...
And I bought just that!
Well, that's marvelous. Marvelous!
At last, we'll be able to start a farm, won't we?
So when will it happen?
We'll sign the official contract in the nearest time.
A certain Mr. Wilson agreed to yield his land to me,
as circumstances warrant his return to England.
Isn't this great news, dad?
The deal was exactly the sum
we were prepared to fork over.
I'm glad. So glad!
Well, to celebrate...
We finally caught the winds of luck.
Nice to meet you, little lamb.
Did you know you have a very beautiful fur?
It's so white!
I've decided on your name - Snowflake!
You're here, Little?
Here.
Allow me to present to you - Snowflake!
You two should get along well, Little.
A dingo and a sheep.
I wonder if it's really possible for them to get along.
After all, it's exactly the same
as if a cat and a mouse were getting along, isn't it?
Today, Lucy turned eight.
As we were returning from our tour
to Mr. Wilson's farm,
Little, who we brought along
seems to be unable to calm down.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Little and the Black Dog".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na