South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 28 - On the Other Side of the River
Little! Little!
After me, Little! We're returning now!
Lucy, are you alright? Not tired or anything?
We could rest for a little if you want.
I'm perfectly fine, why?
Well it's the first hard work you're doing
after you recovered from your illness.
It's fine, I can take this much.
Let's go, then.
Ready!
Lucy had finally broke out
from the grips of her illness.
Today, we went to the forest
to gather firewood for the first time.
In addition, Little's wound
also healed at a lighting speed.
In you go!
I wonder if a roof made of tree bark
would really be a good protection from rain.
The aborigines seem to be making their roofs out of eucalyptus bark all over the place.
Mr Popple! Please bring
some more of that eucalyptus here!
All right!
So we're finally shingling the roof, huh?
That's right.
Look, Lucy! They're almost done with the roof.
Thanks to Billy's dad,
they shingled it in a blink of an eye!
Ben worked pretty hard on it.
Well it's his own house, after all.
If they finish the roof today,
would that mean Ben and Dr. Deighton
can move into it right away?
Not yet. That house is still
completely empty on the inside.
But it'll be good if they at least finish it
before it's too cold outside.
Hey, does Australia have a winter, too?
I suppose it does.
It feels so strange to prepare for winter in July!
Don't tell me, you're still struggling to grasp it?
Australia is located on the southern side of the globe.
So it has seasons opposite to those in England.
I've heard it million times! I got it already.
Why, then, would you find it strange
that winter comes to here in July?
Don't you feel one bit strange about it?
Preparing for winter in July and August...
Well, I...
Actually, it feels kinda odd indeed.
Hey.
That's quite a lot of firewood you gathered.
I'm impressed, you two!
And it's quite heavy, too!
Lucy, sure nothing's wrong with your health?
No, nothing at all.
Today, we'll go fly the kite you made for me!
Think you can launch it all by yourself?
It'll be fine.
I'll be accompanying her.
If you do it right, it can fly real high!
Ben, I forgot to mention it before,
but while I was sleeping, ill,
I dreamed of riding that kite through the sky!
Huh?
I don't think a kite that small
would be good for riding.
Well that's why I said it was a dream!
In it, I even overflew the rainbow arch!
Sounds like you had some wonderful dreams.
It was after I saw that dream
that my fever went sharply down.
The echoes bounce
all around my chest
I want to be a rainbow
in this big sky
that reaches out to the hope
Lucy-May.
Where are you going with that kite?
I wanted to fly it in the grasslands.
You're not feeling in any way unwell, are you?
Yes, I'm alright.
Still, try not to go too far away from home.
Okay.
Good morning!
Hey, Billy!
Hey, Kate!
Good morning, Billy.
We were just about to go try flying a kite.
Coming along?
Huh? Fly a kite?
'Course I am!
Hey, it's Billy.
Good morning, Billy.
Wow, is that the kite you'll be flying?
Exactly!
Hmm? Don't tell me you made it yourself, Lucy?
Of course not.
You really thought I could put it together so nicely?
Nah, never entertained that notion.
Perhaps, give it just 10 more days or so,
and I'll move into a new brick house.
That place seems way more like a proper clinic.
Yeah. A splendid clinic.
Well, then.
Doctor, thank you for everything.
Sure, take care now.
Come on! Hurry! Hurry!
Oh? Lucy-May, how are you feeling?
Ugh, I'm so fed up with it!
Whaddya mean?
I mean, look, Doctor:
even you are worried about my health now!
How can you not find it only natural?
It's precisely because I'm a doctor,
that I'm worried about your health.
You have just barely avoided a pneumonia.
You shouldn't exert yourself.
Actually, come over here for a second.
Doctor, really, nothing's wrong with me!
No excuses! You come here
for a quick medical examination this instant. Hurry!
Geez, this Doctor Deighton is really unbearable!
Finally here?
Alright, sit over here.
Okay.
Good, now open your mouth.
Ah? How interesting...
Yeah...
Oh, I see now!
There, there.
And what about this, this?
What's wrong?
You still haven't figured it out, Lucy-May?
Ah! A lollipop!
Ain't that a rare thing these days?
I got it from a patient that went out earlier.
Delicious! It's so sweet.
Make sure to also treat Kate and Billy.
Okay.
Good.
Here.
Lucy-May, I can already see
you've recovered completely.
Thank you, Doctor.
You wouldn't believe what I got from Dr. Deighton!
Wow!
Huh? A lollipop!
Wow, it's been a truly long time
since we last had lollipops.
Doctor! Thank you very much!
Sure, sure.
We're off now!
Sure, sure, sure, sure, sure!
Yumsee!
Very good indeed!
Absolutely delicious!
The wind blows towards the river, I reckon.
Let's see... It's a southern wind, then?
The cold wind, heralding the winter.
How come the southern wind is actually cold?
Don't tell me, you still haven't understood?
Our Australia is located
on the southern side of the globe...
Enough already, Kate.
Long story short, things here
are the opposite of how they are in England.
That's about it.
That's a good wind. I'm sure it'll fly nicely today.
Right, perfectly centered.
Hey, Lucy, can I try flying it first?
Wait a moment, I'll fly it myself.
Alright, you can have all of it to yourself.
Let's see, if the wind seems
to be blowing in this direction...
We should be able to fly it if we face that direction!
Kate, hold the kite for me, will you?
All right.
Meanwhile, I'll start running to there.
Got it.
Ready now?
Go ahead!
I'm starting!
There!
Kate!
What is it?
If you keep holding the kite all the way through,
it'll never go airborne!
Ain't me! It's your running that is too slow!
That has nothing to do with it!
When I start running and the line is stretched tight,
you go ahead and release it, this time!
Got it!
Here I go!
Now!
Now that's strange.
Kate, grab it!
Ready.
Here I go!
Now!
I wonder what's going on.
It only climbs up once for a short time.
But with a wind this strong,
it's supposed to be flying much further and higher.
Must be something wrong with the way Ben made this kite.
I'll try once more.
Here I go!
Now!
It's hopeless.
This kite just won't climb up, period.
Just as I thought, something wrong
with Ben's way of constructing it.
Tell you this, girls.
The way you're handling it now,
it won't fly no matter how many times you try.
Lemme try my hand at it for a tad bit.
It's the kite's fault that it won't fly!
I don't think that's the case at all.
Then, you're saying it absolutely can fly?
Well, I wouldn't go as far as "absolutely."
Still, flying a kite is a little more
than what you're currently doing.
Hmm, that's a very sturdy-made one.
But pulling it for that long is a no-go!
Ah, 'twas good.
Thanks for the treat.
Ready, Lucy? Look closely!
Naturally, I am looking!
Here I go! Now!
Higher! A bit higher.
Now, that's better!
Higher. Higher!
It's flying!
Wow! It's flying!
This here is actually
an extremely well made kite, Lucy!
How could it not be?
It was brother Ben who made it, after all!
Right, Kate?
Definitely!
Hmm? The wind is on the rise, it seems.
If we don't fix it in place real tight, this eucalyptus bark
may end up getting blown away by the wind.
Let's nail everything tight just in case.
Doctor, we should be able to finish the roof by tonight.
Right...
By the way, about when
will we be able to move in here?
You're also all out of patience, Doc?
Yeah... I can't exactly say
the tent life is giving me the gripes,
but once the weather gets colder,
we can't rely on it for anything.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll begin filling the interiors of the house.
It'll take us maybe a week more to finish.
But that'd be a rather easy task in comparison.
I see you've settled on dividing it into three rooms?
A while ago, didn't you also say
that you'd prefer it this way?
Yes, I did.
But you shouldn't sacrifice
your own comfort for me...
I mean, it doesn't seem to be
exactly convenient for you.
If I have a room, however small,
I'm perfectly fine with it.
But you, doctor, you also need
a consultation room, don't you?
Hey, why are you doing it, Ben?
Huh? What do you mean?
Why is it that your whole family
keeps being so attentive towards me?
Although I'm no relative of yours, not even some friend from old times, you went as far as building me a house!
How did I deserve all this kindness?
Doctor, don't you think you can consider yourself
our sworn friend by now?
Besides, when Lucy got sick,
it was thanks to you staying nearby,
that she managed to overcome such a serious illness.
Lucy-May is, in fact, a very robust child.
While I can barely qualify as a doctor.
She'd have recovered even without me.
I bet, this humbleness
is what our motley crew likes the most about you.
No-no, it's true.
Lucy-May is a child of unlimited vigor.
The kite is getting kinda hard to hold down?
Yeah! It's pulling greatly!
Let me fly it some, too, Lucy.
All right. But hold it tight!
Hey! Wow! It really is pulling me with great force!
Whoa! Amazing, amazing!
Hey, supposing we tie that line around Little's body,
you think it'll have enough pulling force
to send Little flying?
Nonsense! It's not that strong.
You think so?
Only one way to know...!
Drop it!
When it climbed that high already,
I guess we don't need to pull it by hand, do we?
Ah, I forgot! I also brought along some cookies.
Ugh, not a single one is still whole.
Want some?
Yeah, I do.
What about you, Kate?
I'll try one.
Okay, one for you, too.
Ah!
The wind is way too strong today!
I think it's best that we start lowering it soon.
If only we had more string with us,
we could fly it as high as we want. Too bad.
If it's not sturdy enough,
a single gust may tear it away.
Ben brought this line along
all the way from England.
It can't snap so easily...
Ah!
Ah! It snapped.
Think it'll fall into the river?
Looks like it's flying to the other side of the river.
What should we do?
Lucy, let's go pick it up.
But how would we get to the other side of the river?
I think we could cross via the shallows.
It's where Northern Adelaide starts, right?
I suppose.
Hey! Wait for me, you two!
I wonder where it flew off to.
Doesn't seem like it fell into the river.
It couldn't! It was flying way too high.
Dad said we shouldn't ever
wander to Northern Adelaide, didn't he?
Today, we don't have much of a choice,
since we're simply following the kite to there.
At any rate, we gotta go upstream now
to look for some shallows.
We went pretty far upstream.
I wonder if we'll have more luck
finding the kite from the other side of the river.
Let's just cross it and see.
Though I guess we'll now have to walk
a long way downstream again.
Little! Little!
Little!
Little is doing just fine.
More importantly, aren't you cold yourself?
I'm alright.
You just barely recovered from pneumonia,
we'd be in trouble if you catch a cold again.
Here, lemme help you now, okay?
You're right, he's safe.
Thank you, Billy!
We don't want you to catch a cold either, alright?
Eh! Cold!
So cold!
Look, over there!
That's where we started the search.
You're right.
Then, we should continue the search in this area.
But how can we be sure it really flew in this direction?
You were the one who said
it crossed the river, weren't you?
That's what it looked like from where we were.
But if it fell into the river after all,
then the current had already swept it away.
And even if it wasn't swept away,
it got soaked and torn to pieces, I imagine.
One way or another,
we just have to search this area through.
You're right.
Come on, Little.
You're one smart fella, aren't you?
Go and find my kite.
Ah!
Ain't! It ain't here!
Let's go look for it deeper into the woods.
Hey, hey, what do you think those guys are doing?
Ah! Hey, stop, Little!
Ah! The kite!
Eh?
What should we do?
Only got one option - let's ask them to return it.
But will they really return it?
Well, this kite is yours, after all...
But how can we ever get them to understand that?
Hello.
Hey...
Kate, let's forget about the kite and just leave...
Why?
I don't know why, but I'm scared, somehow.
What are you saying?
Those boys are about the same age as us.
Why should you find them scary?
Uhm... Um, you see...
That there is our kite.
Would you please be so kind
as to return it to us?
A-and...
That thing you're holding is a kite.
And well, it's something that belongs to us.
We came here, looking for that kite!
Please give it back!
Hey, I'm serious! Return it please! Our kite.
That kite - our kite, that's what it is!
Brother made it for me! Give it back please!
No! Don't take it away!
Look out, Kate! That's enough!
Let go!
Hey, what are you...
Never I said!
My, is that...
Ah! That's Mr. Heracles.
Thank you so much, Mr. Heracles.
Next time, we'll make more kites like that
and bring them as presents for everyone.
Well, goodbye now.
Goodbye, Mr. Heracles.
Huh?
That is my friend Little.
Oh?
Ah! Dingo!
Huh?
Dingo!
Why exactly did Mr. Heracles start laughing
after saying it's a dingo?
That - we never managed to figure out for sure.
But later, we settled on,
"You did a good job, taming a wild beast like that!"
- this was the meaning behind his laughter.
Hey! Don't tumble this time, Lucy!
Little is visibly worried!
Bleh!
Me and sister started training Little to behave.
The first command is to lie. Lie!
I wonder if Little will be able to learn it.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Little's Training".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you