South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 18 - Tree-Climbing
Okay!
Lucy-May?
Lucy-May!
Got you!
Stop already!
Koala...
Where do you see a koala here?
You've been waving your hands and feet around
for a while now, so I couldn't get any sleep!
I never managed to climb the tree, no matter what...
You were just seeing a dream, dincha?
So it seems.
You can see whatever dreams you want,
but please don't wave your hands and legs around!
Our bed is barely big enough even for sleeping!
I'll start practicing tree-climbing. Definitely!
Did you just say tree-climbing?
Yes. Without knowing how to climb trees,
I'll never be able to capture a koala.
You there! The dead of night
is not the time for chatter!
Okay.
I wonder if our Billy would also become quite
as reliable a prop to his dad when he is of Ben's age.
Without a doubt!
If Billy is about the same age as Kate,
in just two or three more years,
he'll be helping you with work a great deal.
Two or three more years, huh?
Ah!
Sorry for the wait, Billy!
Okay, we can go now.
Kate ain't coming along?
No. I'm the only one determined to catch a koala,
and Kate couldn't care less for it.
I see. Then, how about we try in the woods
that we've been to the other day?
Yeah.
Hey! Where are you two off to, kiddos?
The forest to the west of here.
We're going there to catch the koala!
Oh? You think there are
any koalas in that forest?
I think there are.
Though, for today, it doesn't matter.
Huh?
I'm starting my tree-climbing practice,
with Billy as a coach.
Oh? Tree-climbing, huh?
Because koalas always sit on top of the trees!
I've seen plenty already, but without being able
to climb trees, I couldn't catch any.
Tree-climbing ain't strikin' me
as a very girlish occupation.
Say what you want, but I'm going to become
the star of the tree-climbing world!
My, oh my.
Mr. Popple, almost finished with it, aintcha?
Yes. Thanks to Mr. Jamling's help,
it's being completed way sooner than I thought.
I guess your whole family will finally be able
to sleep comfortably inside now.
Yes.
But as much as I regret saying it, this place
it's still not spacious enough
to place a bed for you anywhere.
No-no-no, I was never counting on that.
Before the winter comes,
we'll build one more hut here.
But until then, I'd have to ask you
to bear with the tent life.
You'll build another hut here?
Yes.
I think we could let Ben try
building it all on his own.
And that's where you'd place me?
Yes. You'll have a proper office
all to yourself, doctor.
Well, I'll be...
I'll be forever indebted, Mr. Popple!
Hey, Billy, I don't see any...
When watching from below,
it's a bit hard to tell.
Ah, that's also true.
Then, let's just search tree by tree,
without rush.
My neck's starting to hurt
from looking upwards so much.
Mine too.
Let's pay attention to our feet for a change.
I'd hate to find myself stepping on a snake
like that we've seen before!
I'm not especially afraid of the snakes.
Rather, it was the snake who looked afraid
and so decided to bite me.
You sure know how to adapt on the fly...
All living beings look universally cute to me.
My neck hurts.
My, it's heavy!
Where could Lucy-May have gone off to?
She always goes wherever she feels like, as soon as she
makes just the amount of candles allocated to her.
Wish I would also have chosen
making candles instead!
I thought one bucket would suffice for our field,
but this soil absorbs water way too quickly!
It really does absorb a lot.
But after we water it that much, the first shoots
might sprout tomorrow already!
This much should be enough, right?
Let's do just one more round!
Eh?
That hurt!
You'll never do it
without being a bit more persistent!
I thought it'd only be that slippery in my dream.
But it's slippery even now,
because I'm just not strong enough!
Ain't no reason for it to be that slippery.
But it is.
Lemme see that hand for a moment.
Here.
True blue. Your hand feels
mighty slick for some reason...
Ah!
What's wrong?
I forgot to wash my hands!
So what of that?
I was making candles before this.
That's why my hands got covered in oil.
And I never washed them before coming here!
No wonder it's so slippery, then!
Right.
I'll go wash my hands somewhere,
and then we'll resume the tree-climbing practice.
Saying "somewhere"
you mean there's any water around?
Of course there is.
You suppose there's some pond
or creek in the area?
Don't know yet.
Let's look for one.
Whoa! Found it, found it! Lucy-May!
Wow! It's super-easy to wash them here!
Rub your hands against the dirt
before you wash them.
Right.
Come on, start washing now!
Okay.
Hey, what's that thing?
Ah?
Look, walking over there.
Oh! Why, that's a platypus.
Eh? A what?
A platypus.
Platypus?
I've only met it once before.
That's strange. Last time, I saw it swimming
in the river, just like a fish.
Eh? It knows how to swim?
Uh-huh!
Ah? You were right! It's swimming!
I guess it's an animal that can live
both on land and in the water.
Wanna catch it?
Sure thing! But not now.
We need to build a proper pond first for it to swim in,
lest it'll just die in the captivity.
That's one bizarre fella for sure...
Now that we know it lives in this river
we can easily come catch it anytime later.
I s'pose.
Say, you gonna wash ya hands or what?
Ah, you're right.
Lucy-May!
Lucy-May! Are you around?
I'm right here!
Ah? Where? Where are you again?
Where are you again?
You hand is almost reaching that branch!
I know.
Then do that one final push!
Have you found a koala?
Not yet. Simply practicing
tree-climbing for now.
Eh? She must be really serious about it,
pushing herself so far.
She's doing that to be able to catch a koala
even when I'm not around.
I'm impressed by her
climbing that high all by herself.
She's been there for a while,
"catching her breath," as she says...
Lucy-May, what's the matter?
Can't you climb any higher?
Of course I can climb higher!
Then keep climbing so that I could see!
I'll do it now, wait just a minute!
From where I stand now,
you look a lot like a koala yourself!
The way you clutch onto that tree
is totally like koala's!
Shut it, you! If you wanna watch, watch silently!
You can do it, Lucy-May!
Extend your hand a bit more!
Just a bit more, girl!
Come on! You can do it!
Like that!
She did it!
Attagirl!
That's the way! A little more now!
Ah!
Oh! Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Are you all right, Lucy-May?
Ouch! My butt hurts so much.
Just your butt, or something else?
Seems like only butt.
Maybe it's best that we show you to Dr. Deighton?
You're right. I think she'll be right, but still...
Exactly! There's no need for me
to see a doctor whatsoever!
Ouch-ouch-ouch.
There, look at yourself!
I see.
In that case, Lucy-May,
show me your behinds.
Never!
No matter what?
No matter what!
Are you sure you didn't hurt anything
except your buttocks?
Yes.
Then I s'pose it's really nothing serious.
Tell me, Lucy-May.
Would you let me examine your behinds,
for good measure?
No!
You sure are a stubborn one!
I understand your embarrassment,
but I'm a doctor, after all.
No! Not even to a doctor!
Ah, then we're done here.
But who knows if it doesn't start to hurt more later.
It'll be fine.
What's with you two?
You can't bother Doctor with trifles!
It's not a trifle at all.
You see, Lucy-May's butt...
Sister! Stop saying thing you don't need to say!
Her butt?
Ugh... I simply hit it with something.
It's just that Kate keeps making a fuss over nothing!
One can never take seriously
whatever you two are saying.
Ben, aren't you supposed
to be helping with building?
We're more or less done already.
Presently, dad is making away with the door,
separating the old house from the new room.
Why don't you two come see it, too?
The construction of the annex
for the house was finally over.
Doubled in size, at last,
it started to resemble a real house.
However, it was yet to be made accessible from inside.
My, my, decided to demolish your backdoor, didja?
Yes. We no longer need this door.
Cutting through it before would've been easier,
but I've decided to keep it until the end
for the sake of this opening ceremony.
Lucy-May, let's see it from the other side.
Yeah.
So? Aren't you two happy?
Yes.
Thanks to your assistance,
it's been finished at a lightning speed!
Glad I could be of any use to you as well.
Yes! With this, starting tonight,
I can sleep soundly, without Lucy-May kicking me!
But I'm the one constantly getting kicked!
Stop telling lies.
It's not a lie!
Oh? Then what about last night?
Are you saying you didn't wave
your hands and feet around while seeing a dream?
Yesterday was special!
Looks the same as always to me.
Because you're a liar.
Look who's talking!
Hm!
Well, come in now.
Well...
We can finally bring the furniture inside.
Uh-huh.
Ah? Going out for somewhere, Doctor?
Ah? Ah... I nearly forgot that have to.
I'm going to Mr. Pettywell's.
My? You still need to go there even now?
Doctors are obliged to bring
the patient's recovery to the completion.
Regardless of what kind of person the patient is.
Alright...
Sister, you shouldn't be so disapproving of Dr. Deighton.
My, was I really disapproving?
"My? You still need to go there even now?"
For us here, it's a moment of delight
because our house finally looks inhabitable.
But when he brought up Mr. Pettywell's name again,
I was reminded that he lives right there,
in our prefabricated home.
I wasn't expecting you to be that hung up on it.
You know that prefabricated home
no longer has anything to do with us.
I know. I know it all too well.
But ever since they completed it yesterday,
I couldn't get my eyes off that house.
That's really one marvelous house
we had to part with.
Ha... Ho-oh?
Come in.
Doctor Deighton is here.
Finally here, that bloody quack?
M-master!
Aye, quack here.
Howdy, Mr. Pettywell.
You're hella late, Doctor... Ouch! Ouch-ouch!
Aye, that's cause your house is so splendid,
I've been looking at it from all sides.
Yes, it was made rather masterfully indeed.
Not just on the outside,
but on the inside as well. Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Still, without any furniture in it,
you can hardly feel at home in this room.
Damn straight.
Today, the furniture is supposed to arrive
from the seashore camp.
We left most of the furniture behind over there.
Oh?
Now, then. How does it look for your waist today?
Not a smidgen better!
The pain is sharp in the morning,
dull in the afternoon.
Pains even when I sleep
and still more when I get up!
Uh, uh.
I gather it troubles you a lot...
Doctor, please.
Do something about it, and quick!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
I'll pay any money you want!
I got important business I need to tend to!
Well, I would accept your money offer, naturally...
Let's see...
Well, for now, I need to examine your condition.
Hurts! Ouch! It hurts so much!
Ouch! Ah! It hurts!
Huh?
This is where it hurts the most, innit?
Ouch! Yes, yes, it hurts!
That's exactly the place! That!
Uh-huh... And what about this one area?
Ahhhh!
Ah. Still hurts, just I thought.
Then, what if I hit here? How is it?
Ah!
Doctor! Doctor, you'll kill me this way! Please stop!
Alright.
Sorry to disappoint, but in all my practice,
I haven't heard of a single case
of someone dying from the waist pain, Mr. Pettywell.
Up we go! Then, how about this?
What are you doing?
If you do that, I'll... Ouch-ouch-ouch! You quack!
You can call me a quack all you want.
But unless you endure a bit of pain now...
Eeeeeh!
Ah! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ah!
I'm being murdered!
Eh? By whom?
Hey! Hey!
Right here would probably do, Mr. Jamling.
No, I think if we dig a well
further in that direction, it'll be way more convenient.
Don't you think it makes more sense
not to distance it from the house?
Good observation.
Let's do it around here.
Hmm.
Dad! Dad!
Dad! Mr. Parker is here!
Mr. Parker?
He's riding an oxcart.
So someone gave him a lift on the oxcart, is that it?
No. Mr. Parker is coming alone.
Holding the reins himself.
Hm? Is it just as hard to believe
for you, Mr. Jamling?
Hey!
Hello!
Okay... Stop! Stop! Good.
Why, Mr. Parker, it's been ages, hasn't it?
Yeah. That there is Mr. Popple's house, right?
Yes. And I was just getting anxious I never got a chance
to thank you for everything you've done for my son.
When he was still on the campgrounds and later...
No need to be so concerned about gratitude.
More importantly, don't you find it ironic?
To have Mr. Pettywell's house standing right there.
Yes.
For sure, if you'd have known it'll come to this,
back when he was begging you for it,
you'd probably refuse to sell
that prefabricated residence to Mr. Pettywell.
That was a bit short-sighted.
No. We no longer hold any offenses against him.
We learned to live with it.
Speaking of which, where might you be heading to?
Well, that happens to be Mr. Pettywell's house.
I came to deliver the rest of the things
he left in my care at the campgrounds.
And where did this oxcart come from?
I happened to obtain it
in an unexpected turn of events.
I figured it might come in handy
for transportation work.
This kind of job happens to be
the most lucrative these days.
Why, it's Mr. Parker!
A-ah! Doctor Deighton!
I owe you a big one
for everything you've done for me at the camp.
It was my pleasure!
By the way, where did you stay?
Right now, I'm still freeloading at Mr. Popple's house.
Why, that's a fine place you chose for freeloading...
Oh!
At any rate, I have to deliver this cargo
to Mr. Pettywell's house now.
I'll stop by later
so we discuss everything without rush.
Alright! Move it now!
We'll probably have a merry party tonight.
Both Mr. Jamling and Mr. Parker
said they'll come have dinner with us.
Mr. Parker will even stay overnight.
I'm so glad we finally have a big house!
Tell me, Lucy-May...
Don't you have this ever-intensifying feeling,
as if we lived in Australia for our whole life?
That's cause we made so many new connections.
I think that pretty much covers it.
My butt still hurts a bit, sis.
Your fault for not letting Dr. Deighton examine you.
It's not that big a deal.
If we spot a koala perched on a tree right now,
just you watch as I climb it with a breeze!
Ah! There it is!
Eh? Where?
Over there.
Doesn't seem to be a koala, though...
This one is much smaller.
Could be a squirrel?
Whoa, sis, there's two of them! No, tree!
You're right.
Whoa! So cute!
Okay, I'll go catch one right now.
Quit it, you. What if you fall to the ground again?
It'll be fine.
I'll make sure to catch this one.
And more!
Hold tight, Lucy-May!
Don't you worry.
I'm not here to do bad things to you.
See? Nothing to worry about. And I'm not
that scary, am I? Now, come closer, little one.
Come on, come here, boy.
Come on, a bit closer. Don't you see
I'm not one bit scary? Come on!
Okay, let's do this: I'll climb to your spot
myself now, so don't be scared.
I won't do anything to you.
Stay calm and easy, will you? Pretty please.
Right, right. Good kids.
That's it, you'll be alright now.
Come here please!
Be a good boy and come here! There! Come!
Ah!
The animal that Lucy-May was trying to capture
turned out to be a sugar glider.
The sugar gliders can fly for up to 40-50 meters.
Tree-climbing proved insufficient,
so unless she also starts practicing flying,
Lucy-May's chances to catch
a sugar glider are less than slim now.
Just flew away...
We went all the way to Adelaide for shopping.
Although she doesn't have the money yet,
Clara makes up her mind to buy a wedding dress there.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Today is the Shopping Day".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you