South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 24 - The Last Day of Summer
Lucy managed to overcome everyone's opposition
towards a baby dingo that Ben found.
So she was allowed to raise it.
I think it got a bit bigger already, Kate.
It's not even been ten days since we found him.
I don't see much change at all.
And I still think it got bigger.
No change at all.
I tell you, he's a little bigger now.
You made this up, dintcha?
Can you spot where exactly
is Little different from a normal dog?
Anyone would tell you it's a dog.
Then Little is a dog!
I'm certain it's no different from a dog.
Even though Ben said it's a dingo pup.
It tickles, Little!
Hey, you two!
Hanging around Little again?
We needed your share of bricks done by yesterday!
Okay!
I've kneaded the clay long ago.
You're supposed to use up
that amount fully, understood?
But my share is just twenty bricks!
I won't do any more than that.
I'll also stop once I've done my fifteen.
Didn't you tell me you can make
as many as we need, be it one or two hundred?
Well I'm just telling you, if the amount of clay
mixed with straw is slightly over the quota,
you make it all into bricks, so that nothing is wasted!
But didn't you just say that you kneaded
a lot of clay already?
I never said that.
There's about thirty five bricks' worth of clay.
But dad said just making
fifteen a day would be enough for me!
I know that.
Are you refusing to work even that little, Lucy?
I never said I'm refusing to work.
Just that I want a bit more time to play!
You don't know, do you?
Don't know what?
The idea that Clara is entertaining right now.
I don't know.
So I thought.
So what is it?
Kate should know, too.
Um. It's about that matter, isn't it?
Um. That matter.
Enough already! Why do you
have to be so nasty, you two?
You wanna know, too?
I don't!
I'll tell you right away, then.
What Clara is considering now...
Right now, sister is working
on an educational course for Lucy.
What's an educational course?
Look, you don't even understand
the meaning of "educational course"!
I do understand! It has something to do
with studying, hasn't it?
Precisely. Because you don't go to school, she's weighing other ways to get you to learn various important things.
That's just evil!
What's evil about it?
It's evil to only make me continue to study!
Well it's the same for Kate.
Then you do it too, Ben!
Do you think I have the time for that?
Ever since we moved here,
all I do is one work after another!
Just go and make some bricks already!
The clay that I kneaded
with so much effort is going dry!
You really are a silly one.
Why so?
Telling Ben to go study, too.
Even if Ben would've liked some education,
he can't get any!
I'd never believe someone that crackers actually exists!
Do you know what Ben wants to become?
Probably a peasant after our father, isn't it?
Not at all.
Oh, I know! He wants to become a carpenter,
just like Billy's dad.
After all, he's such a handy.
Wrong.
Then...
I don't know.
A doctor.
Eh? A doctor?
What's so funny here?
But suppose it... Suppose it...
He - a doctor!
Actually, it's really not one bit funny.
But you can't become a doctor
if you don't go to school, can you?
No, you can't.
Then it's ultimately pointless,
however much he wants it.
Not exactly.
You know of some other way to do it?
Going to study in England.
Eh?!
If he returns to England to study there,
he can become a doctor.
But after we went to all this trouble
to come to Australia,
there's no reason for him
to return to England, is there?
A trip back would cost a fortune. But then,
you'd also need the money to enroll in a school there.
So I thought. It's best that Ben quits dreaming
of something so unattainable, isn't it?
But more importantly...
It's about me - is that true they're going
to make me study again? What do I do?
Don't you feel no hunger
for knowledge whatsoever?
Uh... I don't. What about you?
Eh? No. I don't.
Splendid!
Don't feel it at all!
You've been producing milk at an unabated rate.
I'm really impressed.
What is it, Pansy?
You found something there?
What now, it's just you?
You want to come inside too, Little?
I guess I shouldn't let you in, after all.
Probably nothing would happen, but...
We'll be in trouble, should something extraordinary
happen to Sticky, who's giving us so much milk.
Ah-ah! Look out! I nearly stepped on you!
You're still so thirsty for Sticky's milk?
You're a smart one, aren't you?
Since we're going to make it into a clinic,
maybe it's best that we don't place it
too far from the road?
Sounds reasonable, but...
If it's far from the house,
it doesn't sound very practical either.
Ben, well done.
Have you decided already...
where to build it?
Hm. Well if you ask me,
I'd say we should think of future patients,
coming to Doctor's clinic and build it next to the road.
But before anything else,
it would be Ben's house.
I'm just receiving accommodations there, that's all.
Therefore, you should prioritize
Ben's comfort above mine.
Which implies building it
as close as possible to the existing house.
Ah, so that's how you see it?
Ben, what's your call?
My line of thought aligns with dad's.
This seems like the best place.
What do you say, Doc?
Should we build it here?
Eh? I guess, in that case, I don't mind here either.
But remember, it's the brick house
you're building - a big deal!
It's just bricks dried in the sun.
Almost like a house from mud.
A house of mud?
Works by me as well!
You two helping to make bricks
is becoming a problem...
We've been trying our best
not to stain our clothes.
Maybe you really did,
but that doesn't change the fact
you need to go change now.
Then we'll change!
We've exceeded our quota today.
Isn't that right, Lucy?
Right!
That's 'cause Ben kneaded way too much of clay!
Ah! Wait, wait!
Where do you think you're going?
Where else? Inside the house to change.
While looking like that?
With your hands and feet like that?
Ah, shucks!
Wash them clean over there first.
Let's go wash them in the river.
Yeah.
That's right. Instead of drawing water from the well,
you go there to do the washing.
Kate, see that Lucy-May
washes herself clean, okay?
Okay.
Let's get going, Lucy!
Okay!
Ha! Little!
Let's go!
Come, Little!
These would do, more or less.
Huh? And what are these?
Lucy made these, I imagine.
Ah... Gonna have to remake it.
So irresponsible, jeez!
Little!
Eek! C-c-cold!
The water is so cold!
Like it's supposed to be in autumn!
This place has its own autumn and winter, too?
Of course it does!
And I thought it's going to be warm all year round!
But it's true that we've not seen
any cold days in eternity!
It was summer back in England,
it was also pretty warm aboard the ship.
And by the time we arrived to Australia,
it was summer here.
It's like one long, long summer
has come to an end.
Ah! Oh no! I got my clothes wet, too!
So did I.
Wanna go in?
Going in!
Like that!
If we do this...
We won't have to...
Do laundry...
Separately.
You're right...
B-but it's so c-cold!
We'll be all right, Little.
Wait just a minute more.
Get this!
Ah!
Now you've done it...
There! Have more!
Take this!
Fine! Take this!
A-ah! It's cold!
Take this! And this!
Too weak!
Looks who's speaking!
Ah! Little! You stay there!
We're going out now.
Ah!
You really didn't need to get in the water, too!
Unlike when it-t w-was warm...
M-My c-clothes won't go dry at all!
Th-That's right.
But at least, you won't have
to do the laundry now, would you, sis?
Did you two seriously think
you can make your clothes any cleaner this way?
I'd like you to wash them, after all...
Well, would you look at that.
What about Kate?
I'd like to ask you to wash them, after all...
Now...
Little, you didn't need any cleaning in the first place.
Lucy, how far do you wanna go?
Doesn't have to be far at all.
Just any place where there's plenty of grass.
If we don't bring along a stake,
we won't have anything to tie them to.
But will you be able
to hammer the stake into the ground?
Just leave it to me, will you?
Ben!
Where can I find a stake and a stake hammer?
On the hill, where cockatoos tweet
We'll sit down and spread out our lunch
Hey, hey mother, I'm begging you
After I'm done helping you,
And the Christmas bell will ring far and wide,
Please let me go to the lake with everyone
Wouldn't that be good? Sounds good, doesn't it?
Tell me, mother
Around here should do.
I suppose so.
Okay...
Uh?
Hold it in place!
It was because of soft ground just now.
Guess I can't do it, after all.
Lucy, need you to hold this stake for me.
Um?
Ugh.
Kate, I don't want to die.
What did you say?
That I don't want to die!
Who said you're going to die?
Well if that thing lands on my head...
What's all that nonsense? It'll be alright.
B-but...
Enough already. Just hold the stake steady, Lucy.
Umhm...
Hurry up and do it!
Eh-huh?
That's enough. Can let go of it now.
And... this!
This!
That should do, Lucy.
I drove it pretty deep in.
Who'd think you're actually that strong!
Should be fine now.
But make sure you tie them real tight.
Trust me with this.
I learned it from John back on the ship -
a clove hitch that'll never untie.
John, huh?
He must've already arrived back to England by now...
He said he'll move to Australia as well,
but I wonder if he'll actually come.
Well Clara sure as heck believes he will.
Do you suppose John may also become
our new brother at some point?
Okay, this should do.
Been a while since they've last eaten fresh grass.
Ah! Look how sleepy Little is!
Sister, I'm sure some wild hares are living in this area.
They certainly do.
Let's go catch one!
Wild hares aren't supposed to be
all that fast on the run.
Let's try!
I feel bad for not helping in any way.
It's fine.
We wouldn't want a patient
to see you mud-caked, should one show up.
Mighty commendable of you.
Huh?
You don't ever complain and just do the work done.
In a stark contrast with your
uncontrollable little sisters.
That's because the girls are still too young.
But Kate is just two years
younger than you, isn't she?
Yes.
Commendable.
Doctor.
Uh?
If only that wouldn't bother you too much,
at least at night...
Or even only when you have the free time at night,
wouldn't you mind giving me lessons
every now and then?
Lessons?
For example, I have this textbook on Latin grammar.
But I can't understand a word of it on my own.
Ah, Latin, then?
Doctor, those who study to become doctors
are all made to learn Latin, aren't they?
They do... Learn Latin.
Please teach it to me!
Back when I wasn't boozing so much,
I probably could have taught you a little Latin.
But alas, it's not an option now.
I've forgotten all of it.
Please, try to recollect some of it, Doctor!
If I could recollect it,
I would've done it long ago.
I just don't remember.
Hm?
Doctor?
Ben.
When you have the time, show me
that textbook on Latin grammar, will you?
Who knows if I don't end up recollecting some of it.
Doctor...
We'll split in two to attack from both sides!
You go that way, I go this way. Got it?
But Kate, where exactly is that rabbit?
How could you not see it yet, you dunce?
But that's 'cause you kept...
Hey, that's enough!
If the rabbit spots you, it'll slip away!
Listen! We pounce on it simultaneously,
on my cue. Got it?
Got it.
Charge!
Eck... Ow!
Why, you!
Stop!
It hurt!
Stop, you!
Stop!
That is no rabbit.
Looks like a kangaroo, sis.
That thing is a kangaroo?
So the kangaroos are real, after all?
A very odd fella, isn't it?
And yet, it doesn't seem to mind us one bit.
When I see an animal this bizarre,
I just want to collect as many of them as I can, sis!
I'd suggest you give up on such a plan.
Why is that?
That kangaroo appears so calm simply because it's in the middle of this spacious prairie.
But if you were to confine it inside a tiny enclosure,
that would definitely drive it nuts.
Yeah...
What you mean to say is,
I should consider the kangaroo's happiness?
Yes. That's right.
It's a must for someone
calling herself an animal-lover.
Would it be happier in your keeping, or would it
be happier pounding the earth in the free?
Know what I mean?
Yes.
Ah! Look over there!
Wow! So much of them.
I'll go there to look closer!
Hold it!
Wait a moment, Lucy.
Why?
I think I heard Little just now.
Ah, you're right.
We've strayed rather far from that place.
Let's turn back.
Yeah.
We shouldn't have left Little there untied.
I don't think we need to tie Little down.
Good if so.
Ah! Little had found us!
Now aren't you a bright one?
To figure out we went this way.
Did something happen?
Seems like he's showing us the way to somewhere.
I don't suppose he can actually be that smart.
Oh! This is bad! Sticky is not there!
She took the stake with her!
Must be over there.
Yeah!
My, Sticky!
Eh?
Our baby dingo, Little turned out to be
way smarter than we thought.
While I tried to surprise brother,
he drops his textbook on Latin into the river.
I'm sorry, brother. Will you forgive me?
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"When I'm Out of Luck...".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you