South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 41 -  Strange People in a Strange City
She's fallen asleep.
She's asleep.
Okay.
That girl looks absolutely lovely when she sleeps.
She is a lovely girl, isn't she?
I hope she regains her memory in the morning.
We'll see...
But what will we do if morning comes and she still doesn't remember anything?
Remember what doctor said?
Sooner or later, her memory will return.
One way or another, isn't it awfully curious?
To suddenly forget everything -
her own name, her parents and her home.
But she didn't forget how to speak, did she?
She only forgot things pertaining herself.
Yes, I suppose that's true.
I didn't see the moment
of her getting hit by a carriage myself.
But the impact must've been really strong.
Oh! A runaway horse!
Runaway horse! A runaway horse!
Run away! Run!
Hey! It's heading for the city!
Stop it, someone! It's dangerous!
Madam, did you want to see me?
Yes.
You see, there's a girl sleeping on the second floor.
Yes?
When she fell asleep,
she still hadn't regained her memory.
Yes.
But we believe she might regain it tomorrow.
When morning comes,
please check on her every hour or so.
If she remembers her name
and her parents' name when she wakes up,
please let me know at once.
Um. No matter how early it is?
Yes, that's right.
I understand.
Then, I'm counting on you, okay?
Yes.
The rain almost stopped.
Yes. So it seems.
Where could Lucy have gone?
You don't suppose she could've already
returned home by now?
That'd sure be good.
When it's this late,
I'm sure she had already returned.
What's wrong, mother?
Didn't you hear some noise
coming from the front just now?
I didn't hear anything.
Kate, how is it?
Can you see anything?
Nothing.
But it seems the rain had stopped.
That's really irresponsible of her
to be out till so late.
I'm sure dad and John found her already.
That's what I'd like to hope for.
That's so foolish, when it's this late...
It was Little.
Now we know for sure -
Lucy must've returned already.
You found Lucy, right, Little?
But it's only the two of them returning!
Where's Lucy? Lucy returned, right?
Still not here, is she?
Yes.
John, thank you.
It seems Lucy is not returning tonight.
She must've stayed overnight at some deserted house.
After all, she's ten already.
I'm sure she's well aware of how concerned we are.
Supposing... I'm not saying it'll happen,
but supposing she doesn't return tomorrow either...
Then we'll go look for her once more.
Please let me help you too.
Right, but I know you have job...
I'll take a day off.
No, I can't allow that.
It's fine. She'll come home tomorrow.
Of course, that's what I think as well.
Well then, Mr. Popple, I would leave you for tonight.
I really appreciate it, John.
Thank you very much.
Ah. I'll walk you home for a short while.
Okay. Well, goodnight then.
I'm tired.
You had to walk for so long?
Yes. We went all the way to the northern Adelaide.
Then, all the way to the Adelaide Bridge?
Yes. But if she doesn't return tomorrow,
we'll have to go look for her in Northern Adelaide again.
Could she have gone
to see Dr. Deighton in city of Gawler?
Impossible! It's too far away.
We can never know for sure.
That's true, we can't know...
Ah!
What's the matter?
Back when it suddenly started to rain, Little...
What's the matter with Little barking so much?
I don't know.
John, let's find shelter from rain somewhere.
Okay.
Little! Come, boy!
Hey, Little! What's wrong? Come here!
That's right, it was rain!
Little must've found her trace,
but that heavy rain washed it all away.
Right. I gotta go look around that bridge once more.
Are you going there now?
No, I can do it tomorrow.
As I said, only if Lucy isn't back by then.
You know, I was sure you'd find Lucy
and bring her home tonight.
You get it? I'm counting on you
to find Lucy for me, by all means.
Ah! The moon is out.
The weather is awfully whimsical tonight.
Hey, because the Moon is sitting so high,
it'll know for sure, right?
Please, tell us where Lucy is!
Right.
This is where I went to sleep last night.
But before that...
I don't remember anything before that!
Good morning, Little Miss.
Good morning.
You see, there was something
the madam asked of me last night.
Should you recollect your name
and your parents' names by morning...
I guess you still can't remember
anything about yourself?
Why? Why is it so?
How come I know that there are
five fingers on each of my hands,
but can't recall my own name,
or anything about my father or my mother?
Little Miss, you shouldn't be crying.
That's just a medical condition.
A medical condition
means you can recover from it one day.
Who am I? Oh, who in the world might I be?
Little Miss...
Little Miss, I'll go call the madam now, okay?
Better stop crying, Little Miss!
You're cute. What's your name?
Meow! Here! Over here.
Squeeze!
Too slow, too slow!
Over here now!
Ah! Ouch, ouch! I give up! I give up!
Oh come on!
Good morning.
Good morning, Little Miss.
The cat's name is Prospero.
Prospero? Such an unusual name!
His namesake is Shakespeare's "The Tempest."
Ah. I'm sorry.
You haven't regained your memory yet, have you?
Yes.
Oh my...
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing. I just couldn't stop the tears,
thinking about your plight.
I'll get up now.
You can stay as you are now.
They'll bring your breakfast soon.
But...
You probably never had
breakfast in bed before, have you?
Try to remember.
Look, here it is.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Well, go ahead now.
Thanks for your service.
Bon appetit.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Yes.
What's wrong? You don't like it?
No, it's very delicious.
But I just can't help this odd feeling.
What do you mean by that?
Eating in bed like this is very comforting.
I feel like it's the first time I'm doing this.
I see. But your hand was already halfway to your mouth.
So try to eat it all, will you?
Okay.
It's so delicious!
Here.
I must've inconvenienced you
a great deal with this affair.
When I found her lying on the ground, I brought her here completely on the spur of the moment.
No, it's all right.
I actually think you acted like a hero.
So you don't mind looking after that child?
Yes. I'm glad, in fact.
Good to know.
But what will you do about her now?
We need to give her some strong stimulus.
If we don't do that, her memory might remain
forever obscured in the depths of her mind.
A strong stimulus...
Right. First off, we'll take her to the Adelaide Bridge.
After that...
If we're lucky, she'll regain her memory, right?
Then, we'll take her on a carriage trip around Adelaide.
Chances are, we might drive past that girl's home.
If she sees her own home,
it might serve as a trigger.
Someone from her family
might also see and recognize her.
Yes. We'll seat her next to the window
so that her face can be seen easily.
To the Adelaide Bridge, Max.
Okay.
So, Young Miss?
Does anything around here look familiar to you?
No.
Perhaps, her home is just not in this part of town.
I suppose...
This is where I found you lying on the ground.
Here?
Yes. The runaway horse came from that direction.
When lying on the ground,
how was she oriented?
Let's see. Like this, I think.
That means we can't tell
which side of the bridge she came from.
I suppose. But when I first noticed her,
intuitively, I felt that she came from that side.
Then, she was heading to Northern Adelaide, right?
So it seems.
In that case, it's possible that her home
is in Northern Adelaide.
It happened in the evening,
so she might have been on her way home.
Yes.
So? Anything comes to your mind?
I don't remember anything.
Nothing...
This is the one most lively street of Adelaide.
So? Remember anything now?
Nothing.
What's wrong? You're not looking outside.
It's just...
Yes?
I'm seeing this city for the first time.
It must be that I lived not here,
but in some other city.
That's possible.
But here in Southern Australia,
Adelaide is the only metropolitan city.
Gawler is the only other similar place nearby
that I can think of.
Gawler?
Do you know it?
Pretty sure it was around here
where Little bizarrely started barking.
I don't see anything wrong at all with this place.
Even if there was something,
yesterday's rain washed it all away.
Father.
What is it?
We should go check in Gawler.
Gawler, huh?
Yes. If we take a cart,
it's not that awfully far away, right?
Yes.
I've been having this feeling
that Lucy went to Dr. Deighton for some reason.
Then we gotta think about someone
who'd let us take a carriage to there.
Let's hire one, father.
Yes.
Mom! Mom! It's serious, mom!
What is it?
Lucy was there!
What? Did she come home?
No, she rode a carriage.
A carriage?
Right. She watched at me
from the window of a luxurious carriage.
You shouldn't be saying lies, Tob.
It's true! It's the truest true! It totally was Lucy!
And then? Did Lucy say something to you?
Nothing.
When she saw me, she didn't even smile.
It was as though she's seeing me for the first time!
And then, which way did that carriage go?
Hurry! Hurry after me! Hurry!
It really was her, decisively!
Which way, Tob?
That way!
Looks like it left...
What should we do?
Good question.
For now, let's just turn back to the mansion.
There's some place I'd like to visit first.
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Oh my!
My, how adorable!
It fits her greatly. Don't you think so, dear?
Yes.
It's it inconvenient that we don't know your name?
Until you recall your own name,
I'll be calling you Emily, okay?
Understand, Emily?
H-Hey, Emily was the name of...
Indeed. That Emily was brought back to life.
Okay...
Let's go. I'll give you a tour through the garden, Emily.
What is on your mind, Sylvia?
Come, this way.
The sir and madam treat me kindly
as if I was their own daughter.
But who am I, really?
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A Child Called Emily".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you