South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 49 - Clara's Wedding
Actually, I'm not sure
if I can muster enough courage to say it.
Please don't feel shy and say it, whatever it may be.
If so, let me put it bluntly.
Would you let us adopt Lucy as our daughter?
Adopt her, you say?
Um...
It's only natural that you're surprised.
I understand that you'll need to consult
with your wife on a matter like this.
But we'd really like to bring Lucy up
as if she was our own child.
If possible, we want to adopt Lucy, by all means.
Of course, I also share
a great deal of adoration for Lucy.
But it was my wife Sylvia who came to love Lucy
deeply and hopelessly.
I think I told you about this before,
but several years ago we had a daughter,
who had passed away.
Ever since then, we were never blessed with a child.
Then, a few days ago, Lucy who had lost her memory
came to stay in our house.
My wife started calling Lucy, who couldn't even
remember her own name, Emily.
Emily was the name of our late daughter.
In the time of Lucy's sojourn in our house,
despite me advising her against it,
my wife came to dote on her,
as though she was our own child.
And then, after Lucy's departure,
she feels like a part of her soul had been taken away.
As if we lost our child once again.
She only came to realize it keenly after Lucy left us.
Children are a truly wonderful gift from heavens.
That's what my life finally confessed to me today,
who had since became infirm, as if she was actually ill.
She was wondering if there's a way
we could adopt Lucy.
Eventually, I came to wonder the same thing.
If your adorable Lucy becomes our daughter...
I understand very well how you feel, but...
Ah, just a moment more.
Please let me say just a couple words more.
In fact, if you happen to agree to us adopting Lucy,
I thought I ought to give you something in exchange,
so I'd like to offer you the land in my possession.
The land?
Yes.
Pardon my curiosity,
but the thing you currently covet the most -
isn't it a piece of land that you'd own yourself?
A land?
If you still wish to work on the farm near Gawler,
I was considering transferring a portion of it
to your possession.
When you see it, you'd know right away -
it's a marvelous farm.
You'll have full control over that farm
and would be able to build it according to your vision.
But Mr. Princeton, Lucy is...
Madam, I can guarantee Lucy's happiness.
If only you would allow us to adopt Lucy...
I beg you!
God...
Lucy, we'd never...
Can we make it work, Mr. Popple?
You give me land and I give you Lucy -
is that what you're offering, Mr. Princeton?
Ah...
No-no, that's not how I see it.
I'm only giving you the land as a sign on my goodwill.
In any case, you don't have
to give me the answer right away.
Please take your time to think it over.
There's no need for that.
Then, we can adopt Lucy?
No. I would never even consider Giving Lucy up.
Dear.
Is this fine with you?
Without a doubt!
Mr. Princeton,
no matter how hard the life gets,
parting with our kids
is absolutely unthinkable.
All of our property will be Lucy's.
Please leave, Mr. Princeton.
In the end, you're just another man
who can only think from the position of wealth.
Lucy is our beloved daughter.
There's no way we can let someone else adopt her.
That's right. Exactly right.
Whoa!
Thank you, sir. I had lots of fun.
I'd like to ride it again sometime!
Sure, sure.
Mr. and Mrs. Popple, if I was unfortunate enough
to anger you with what I said, I beg your forgiveness.
But that doesn't change the fact
that my wife adores Lucy.
Therefore, adopting her is the only thing
she can think about.
I understand how you both feel.
Ah, by the way, you didn't mention
any of this to Lucy, did you?
Of course not. I've met the girls on my way here, so I ordered my coachman to circle them around the area.
I see. Then, the carriage hasn't returned yet, right?
Ah! That sure was fun!
We're back!
We're back.
Mr. Princeton, thank you very much.
We've circled all around the place.
Glad you liked it.
Lucy is still outside?
Oh? I thought she'd be back already.
Little following us everywhere,
so she got off the carriage.
She didn't want Little to exhaust himself.
But then... Lucy went home early?
Knowing her, she probably made a side trip somewhere.
My, so you were right here?
Mr. Princeton, thank you.
Huh? What? You mean for the carriage?
Lucy heard everything that happened here.
Hm?
It makes me very happy to know
that you came to love me that much. However...
I understand, Lucy.
There's no way your father and mother
would willingly part with a child as adorable as you.
I should've realized that sooner,
if only I gave it a little thought.
Come to play at our place again.
Well then, everyone, this is where I bid my farewell.
Actually.
I'll still give you a tour through the farm,
just wait for a few more days, please.
There's no need now, Mr. Princeton.
Huh?
I won't be working on your farm.
But why?
Long story short, I refuse to.
Could it be that you're saying so
because my today's proposal offended you in any way?
If so, I can assure you, that's beside the point.
I no longer want to work at your farm.
I understand.
What in the world happened here?
Hey, what's the matter?
This atmosphere is very weird.
Welcome back.
Finally home.
Listen, Sylvia...
It didn't work out, right?
Yes.
Did you also offer the land?
I did...
Yet they refused even so?
Yes.
I wonder if Mr. Popple still wants the land.
I'm sure he wants it so bad it drives him crazy.
But I shouldn't have brought up the question of land.
I made it seem as though
I came to discuss buying Lucy with that land.
That wasn't right.
This would certainly leave a scar on Mr. Popple's heart.
So you believe you should've
talked about the land some other time?
Yes. Because of that, he even revoked
his agreement to work on a farm in Gawler.
It's best if you forget about Lucy now, Sylvia.
I can't forget about her.
I'll say it clearly - that is one unfulfillable wish.
Ah! A shooting star!
So you could become dirty rich, huh?
With a bunch of servants
tending to your every wish too...
You'd have a gorgeous feast every day.
Living like a fabulous princess!
Wouldn't that be really awesome?
Why didn't you ever tell me that you're becoming
Mr. Princeton's adopted daughter?
If you found yourself in my shoes,
what would you do?
Well if I were you, it's obvious...
I wouldn't wanna be adopted
by someone else. Period.
Autumn came. The long summer vacations were over,
so we had to go to school again.
I'm off!
I'm off.
Here, here.
Little, behave and sit still
until I return from school, okay?
I'm also going to school this time.
You understand, Little?
Starting with this new school term,
Tob is a first-grader.
I'll be back soon, Little!
Well, it's time for me to go too.
Have a good day.
Little, I'm leaving.
Having refused the job at Mr. Princeton's farm,
dad now had to work at construction sites,
even though he wasn't used to it.
Mostly laying bricks.
I'm leaving, mother.
Pretty early today.
Yes. That's because I got a day off tomorrow.
Only for tomorrow?
Oh? I should've taken more?
I mean, who goes back to work
on the very next day after her wedding ceremony?
Well, John said he's going to work on the next day too.
My, my, what a hardworking couple.
I'll pick up my wedding gown on my way back.
You'd better. If you forget that,
we can't hold a ceremony tomorrow!
That's right. My sister Clara was finally getting married.
Say, mom.
What is it?
Will I have to go to work too?
And where did that come from?
Well, if Clara leaves to live with John,
we'll become a family of five, right?
So what?
We'll need money, won't we?
Well, of course...
But I'm sure we'll manage somehow.
When Clara becomes John's wife,
she won't be bringing money into our family, right?
The whole family is getting scattered away...
Back when we were leaving England,
we never imagined it'd come to this.
We'll get a marvelous plot of land,
where the whole family would be working.
We'll have plenty of wheat and vegetables.
And the din from the livestock
would never stop on our farm.
I thought that was exactly what dad dreamed of.
Ah!
Imbecile! Don't you know it's dangerous?!
Sorry!
Be careful next time!
Ah!
Clara is back!
Yay!
Welcome back!
And she's carrying a large box too!
That's gotta be a wedding gown!
Finally!
Hey-hey-hey, I wanna carry it too, sister!
Whoa there! Be careful not to drop it.
And... Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho!
Wow!
Ah! Gorgeous!
That sure is pretty!
Well, this should do.
Hey, hey, Clara! Won't you try it on?
Right! To check if they got your measurements right.
Don't worry about that.
I made sure to try it on in the shop.
Please, put it on!
Lucy, you'll Clara putting it on tomorrow anyhow.
I wanna see it today!
What's the big deal, Clara!
Just put it on.
Well, aren't you a stubborn bunch?
Fine, then. It fits me perfectly, you'll see.
Quick! Quick! Quick!
Clara, are you sure?
I'll put it on in my room.
Kate, help me in the kitchen.
Okay.
Maybe I should go look at her wearing it?
I'm going too.
Boys can't go.
Why?
You can't means you can't. Only I can.
You're a meanie, sister!
Tob, how is Lucy being mean to you?
Welcome home, Ben.
I'm back.
Ben, you came to see
the wedding ceremony tomorrow, right?
Yeah, that's right. So where's Clara?
Changing into her wedding gown.
Eh? She's gonna change into it soon?
It's just to see if it fits her.
Oh, is that so?
Okay, where's mom, then?
In the kitchen, I assume?
Yes.
Mom! I'm back.
Oh. Welcome back, Ben.
Someone's at the door. Go meet them.
Me?
Yes, you.
I'll go.
Clara sure is taking her time with it.
Isn't wearing a wedding gown awfully difficult?
Well, perhaps it's that she can't fit into it at all?
Clara gained a little weight lately.
Hey. How is it going?
Ah! This is bad!
Huh? It's bad that I come now?
I thought we needed to meet
to settle things for tomorrow.
Say, John, you wouldn't wanna see
the bride in her wedding gown today, right?
Well... I wouldn't mind seeing her, to be honest.
But I heard that it only okay for you
to see the bride after the ceremony had begun.
As for seeing her the day before - I'm not so sure...
I suppose. Yeah, you're probably right.
I don't wanna see her today.
Lucy, go tell Clara
that she can't leave her room just yet. Quick!
Okay. Plus, I'll get to look at her myself!
I wanna look too!
I see. Guess I can call you "brother," starting tomorrow.
Yes. I can too.
I... I suppose.
I guess that'll make sense.
No... I feel a little embarrassed.
If you call me that.
So pretty, sis!
Pretty, alright...
Thank you.
Lucy, I never forgot.
You also contributed your five shillings
into this wedding gown.
Ah, that's right.
I'll say my thanks once again.
Lucy, I appreciate it.
On the next day, Clara and John got married.
Those two looked very happy.
The reception party was held in our very own backyard.
With foods and drinks and dances,
it became very lively.
John's little brother Paul.
The bride looks gorgeous.
Mrs. Mac and Mr. Bernard.
Congratulations, Mr. Popple.
Thank you.
Mr. Jamling and Mr. Parker.
Cheers!
As well as Billy.
And some of John's colleagues.
Our backyard became crowded
with folk from the neighborhood.
When the guests left,
Ben returned to the port,
and John went home together with Clara,
our house has suddenly become very lonely.
And dad just kept drinking in silence.
Both me and Lucy were thoroughly worn out
and didn't even have the energy to speak out loud.
So our house became quieter than ever.
Hm?
Then it started raining outside.
It's wrong, you hear me?! Lucy-May Popple,
be more attentive. And now, redo it once more!
The egg came first, I'm tellin' ya!
I know it was the chicken!
Wouldn't it be nice if dad got some land
where the whole family could work together?
I suppose.
I wonder if it'll ever happen.
You think it will, Kate?
Doesn't look like it. So far,
things have only been changing from bad to worse.
From bad to worse?
What are you doing, Lucy?
You go ahead without me, Tob.
What's the matter?
I need to stop by at one place.
What about the school?
Tell the teacher I'm taking a day off!
I'm glad to see you here, Lucy.
Are you having this whole day to yourself?
Yes.
Well, that's just great.
My wife would be happy to know.
Is everyone at home doing well?
Mr. Princeton.
What is it?
Please...
Please make me your child.
Huh?
Please make me the daughter of your family!
If I... If I could become your daughter...
Ah, Lucy...
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow - final episode:
Towards the Rainbow
Don't miss it!
Final episode:
"Towards the Rainbow".
Don't miss it!
The Alps Story: My Annette
Next show - The Alps Story: My Annette.
It starts in the new year.
Don't miss it, okay?
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you