South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 33 - A Lost Dream
Three long years have passed
since we arrived to Southern Australia.
In that time, from a small settlement with measly 300 inhabitants, Adelaide transformed into a bustling city.
Now, also with a splendid bridge.
October 1840.
And I thought that we could see it from here...
What do you mean?
Our house.
Huh?
The house where we used to live before.
No way you could see it from here.
The river meanders a lot, plus tons of trees.
But... It's that way, right, Kate?
Right. That way.
It's been a while...
Say, you wanna go look at that house?
I suppose.
We've also haven't seen Doctor Deighton in ages.
Yes.
Okay, Little. Enough waiting. Let's go now!
About year or so ago,
we left our old house upstream the river
and moved into this house on Angas Street.
Where are you going, Tob?
To go play look for the sisters.
Kate and Lucy should return soon enough.
So you'd also better not to stray too far.
I won't go far.
Look out for the carriages!
Okay.
Hey, you two! Been a while.
Mr. Bernard!
But I thought you guys no longer live in this area.
We went to see the opening ceremony
of the Adelaide bridge.
When we looked this way while standing on the bridge,
we became so, oh, so nostalgic!
I see.
Fancy a ride?
Yay!
Ah!
Ah... You have Little with you?
We can't take Little along...
It's fine. Little would be running after us.
Alright, get in, then.
Although it's a little tight up here...
Okay
May I add, you two have sure grown quite big.
Is this your carriage, Mr. Bernard?
Impossible! I'm nowhere near rich enough
for such purchases.
This is the carriage,
allocated to the Surveyor General.
Ah, so it's Colonel Light's carriage?
Well aren't you a dunce?
Why so?
Colonel Light passed away last year.
Is that so?
Yes. Right now, Charles Sturt is the Surveyor General.
And I serve as his personal secretary.
Oh, so that's how it is?
Admirable growth, Mr. Bernard!
I wouldn't exactly say a secretary job
is all that admirable.
Huh?
Oh? Looks like Mr. Pettywell
is moving out of his house.
Ugh, it's heavy... Hey, watch where you step!
I'll just quickly grab some things,
then return to the office at once.
What about you?
Then, you'll be able to take us
to King William Street, right?
Sure thing.
But remember, I'll be leaving again
in 20 minutes or so.
Okay. We only came to say hello to Doctor Deighton.
Little, what are you doing?
What's the matter with Little?
I don't know.
Huh?
So Mr. Pettywell now keeps a bulldog?
Looks strong!
I bet, he went to the trouble
of bringing it all the way from England.
Hey, that's a no-go! You can't be
making enemies with that dog as well, Little.
Let's go now.
And where is Mr. Pettywell's new residence?
Hm? That's be on Angas Street.
Angas Street?
Eh... Thanks for telling me...
Lucy! Lucy!
You wouldn't believe it!
Mr. Pettywell is moving to a house on Angas Street!
Really?!
But how in the world...
I can't believe he's moving to a house next to us again!
Jeez, that Mr. Pettywell...
It ain't gonna be pretty.
Doesn't seem like anyone lives there,
Pretty sure we sold it to some Mr. Watson.
Still, no one lives here.
Look how dilapidated it is!
Yes, exactly so.
For the last three months, not a soul lived here.
Doctor Deighton!
Hey, hey, I'll suffocate if you keep pushing so much.
Good morning! It's been a truly long time!
Well, I wasn't looking for a split second,
but you two have grown so big already!
Huh?
Hey, Little, I see you're doing fine as well.
But why isn't anyone living here?
Because Mr. Watson sold the house and the plot
and went to live in the city of Gawler.
But why doesn't the buyer live here either?
Mr. Pettywell bought up this whole stretch of land.
Mr. Pettywell bought it?
I hear his plan is to subdivide the land
into smaller lots, build houses on them, and sell.
Did you know the land is rapidly growing in value?
We know. That's why our dad
had already given up on buying any farmland.
Exactly.
Both the farmlands
and the residential areas grew in price.
Mr. Pettywell also operates
under the assumption the price will keep rising.
Doctor, but then...
What's wrong?
If all the land here now belongs to Mr. Pettywell,
what'll become of that house of yours?
Huh?
Doctor, doesn't you house
now technically stand on Mr. Pettywell's estate?
Yeah, he demands that I move out these days.
You're getting evicted, Doctor?
No, I'm not goin' anywhere.
I came to really like this house your dad built.
Come fire and brimstone,
I'm not goin' anywhere.
You heard me right!
Ain't no way I'm moving out!
That's right. In these past two years,
Adelaide underwent a brilliant transformation.
But that also means
there's more nasty stuff happening.
That's what dad told us -
bad people became numerous.
But the police cells became even more numerous.
Yeah, we keep hiring new policemen,
and it's getting troublesome.
There are folk like Mr. Pettywell,
still enjoying hefty profits,
but there's much more of those
who came all the way to Southern Australia
just to have their dreams smashed
and end up living hand-to-mouth.
Hey, that's not what's gonna happen
to our family, right, sis?
Who knows. We aren't exactly wealthy.
It's very different from your case!
Look, you have such a splendid house, don't you?
Also with a small field and orchard in the back.
But it's not nearly enough
to be selling vegetables and fruits to others.
Well, doesn't your family have
Clara and Ben who are also working?
Even so, dad can barely find any work.
Hmm...
That's 'cause your father
had been a farmer for all his life.
His experience at cultivating fields
and keeping livestock
cannot be converted into some useful skill
for quarrying or building roads.
If only Mr. Pettywell didn't snatch it from us,
we'd have ourselves a marvelous farm by now.
So? How about on this corner?
Thank you for everything.
Give my greetings to your dad and mom.
Okay.
Are careful on your way home, okay?
We're going to stop at Mrs. Mac's store
on the way to buy some bread.
Want us to tell something to her?
Let's see...
Tell her that I'll also stop by soon.
Okay.
Oh, and also, say hello to Clara. Go!
Are you alright? Not tired or anything?
You never question Little's infinite energy.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Sister.
Give me just a moment.
Ah! Lucy! Leave the dog outside, please!
Where's Mrs. Mac?
In the back.
Hm?
Hello!
Hello, Kate.
We saw Mr. Bernard just now.
Interesting. Where?
Near our previous house.
What were you doing all the way out there?
Remembering the old times.
I was also feeling lonely there,
now that you're gone.
It smells wonderful.
Do you need something else from me?
Mr. Bernard said he'd pay you a visit before long.
Bernard's "before long" could mean anything.
Ah, but thanks for telling me either way.
You can get your usual bread from Clara.
Okay.
Sorry for the delay.
Thank you for your purchase!
I'd like to have our usual bread, please.
Sure.
We've been to the opening ceremony
of the Adelaide Bridge.
Was it very crowded?
Yes.
Tell me, what do you think?
About what?
Me and John are going to see the play tonight.
What play?
Romeo and Juliet.
The Liverpool Theater troupe
came from England to stage it.
I wanna see it too!
You're still a child, so it's out of question.
The problem I have is...
What do you think dad will say?
He'll probably forbid you.
"Watching plays is highly depraved of a maiden..."
Dad has such a stuffy predisposition.
But that's such a backward thinking.
You're right.
Besides, dad had been so insusceptible lately.
Sister! John's here!
Huh? What was he thinking?
It's still too soon!
He's also dressed to the nines!
Wow! He looks very determined too, our John!
Welcome!
Hey-hey, that's quite the welcome.
John, you've finished the work already?
Yes.
But I'm still far from being done.
Got it.
Well, in any case, I'm ready and waiting,
so I thought I'd stop by to let you know.
Looking sharp, John.
Thanks.
Working as a carpenter means
you have plenty of free time, I imagine.
It was a special kind of work today.
It almost feels unreal.
What is?
They've built a theater in Adelaide
and are now staging plays there.
Romeo and Juliet.
What kind of play
do you think Romeo and Juliet is?
I'm at a loss for words...
You don't even know the story of Romeo and Juliet?
I don't.
A famous playwright Shake...
Shakes... No, wait, not Shakepear either.
Shake sounds right. Shake...
It's Shakespeare.
Ben!
I was actually about to say "Shakespeare" myself.
Sorry about that, if so.
Romeo and Juliet is a famous play by Shakespeare.
Do you understand now, Lucy?
I understood really well!
Speaking of which,
what are you two doing here?
Just made a detour on our way home.
What about you?
Going home from the port.
I have a day off tomorrow.
Did you walk all the way from the port?
Nope, not at all.
I took a diligence.
It's very convenient. Not so long ago,
you'd either have to walk all the way,
or hope that someone
would let you ride their cart.
But now, anyone can ride it for just three shillings.
Look, that's the one that brought me here.
Eh?
Hey!
Hello.
Had a plenty of passengers today.
My horse is worn to a frazzle.
Sure, sure, gimme a moment.
I'll release you right away.
Well, if it isn't Tob over there!
You're right! Whenever he has a free minute,
he comes to see the blacksmith work.
Tob!
What are you doing?
Let's go home now!
Sister!
That's what he said.
Mr. Pettywell is moving to Angas Street.
Hmm...
I wonder if there's a house on Angas Street
big enough for Mr. Pettywell to move in.
Remember, one house away from us...
One house away?
Yeah.
Ah! That house!
That's right, gotta be that house.
That's a very cruel irony.
Seeing that Pettywell
invade our neighborhood again.
You think it's a coincidence?
Gotta be one...
Good, that's it.
Hold it from your side!
Okay.
And now, heave-ho...
Okay, give it to me now.
There you go.
Alright...
Damn thing's heavy.
So it was exactly as you said.
What's worse, Mr. Pettywell keeps a bulldog now!
Huh?
Thought it's still in the other house,
I'm sure it'll try to get Little's back up.
A carriage is coming.
Little, calm down now!
Huh? Is that true?
Children say they've seen it with their own eyes.
So we'll have to put up
with being around Mr. Pettywell again...
In the end, this city of Adelaide is really a tiny one.
So it seems.
And... Clara actually wanted to ask you for a favor.
What is it?
John also came to ask for it.
I told them before.
The time is not ripe for that yet.
That's my final ruling.
It's not that.
Huh?
They didn't come to talk about marriage.
Really? What, then...
Why don't you hear it from them?
Why can't I go see a play?
Theater is where they teach children
all the wrong things.
But Clara is no longer a child.
To me, she's a child.
I shouldn't think a play such as Romeo and Juliet
could teach Clara any wrong thing, dad.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I really didn't want to ever say this,
but your way of thinking
is about several centuries too old!
Old ways are best ways.
Dad.
You know that to succeed in farming,
one ought to embrace the progressive thinking.
Hm?
When you decided to go to Southern Australia,
it was because of that progressive farming
that you wanted to put into practice here, remember?
You're right.
I... I wanted to try out a whole kit and caboodle
of my progressive ideas on a plot vast enough.
Because the government promised
that it would be possible here, in Southern Australia.
But without any land on my hands,
all this progressive farming ain't worth a zilch.
With all my heart, I pray that you get to implement your progressive farming, if even just a day sooner.
But... Right now, well, about that theater play...
Huh? What did you say?
Dad, for a man employed in inventing
a new ways of progressive farming,
staying always stuffy and old-fashioned
toward a theater play is strange, to say the least.
That... That's...
He's right! Exactly so!
What?
Father... You've always kept proving yourself
a progressively-thinking man!
As far as farming is concerned, there's no other man
with thinking quite as progressive as yours.
So why shouldn't you think progressively
towards theater too?
Ben, that was a very compelling argument!
Don't worry, Clara.
Dad will quickly come to see the reason,
because he's a very understanding man.
Go before I changed my mind.
Huh?
If you so much wanna see that play,
then go and see it right now!
Wow!
Thank you, dad!
Hey! That was unbecoming, Clara.
John, let's go now!
Mr. Popple, thank you very much.
John, what time is it?
Ah... Don't worry. We still have
plenty of time until the play.
I'll go change, then.
OK, I'll be waiting.
Honey, are you happy with this?
Those two sure looked delighted.
Now that I think of it,
Clara is already nineteen, isn't she?
Soppy! Soppy!
If eventually, Soppy also turns out
to be a milk-producing goat, that'd be great!
Sticky and Pansy are already producing plenty.
And we add to that Soppy...
Mother could make enough cheese
to start selling it!
If we get a cow, I'll look after it.
That's right. Getting a cow wouldn't be half-bad.
Should we ask dad for it?
No way, it'll put dad into a fix.
The family budget is running low right now.
Hey, mom asked you to finish sooner here.
We're almost done.
What about Clara?
Did she go to see the play, after all?
Yeah. In a feat of persuasion,
I made dad change his mind.
Who'd think I have all the makings of a lawyer?
What's with becoming a doctor?
I gave up on that one.
I've turned 15 already. It's too late to start now.
So you're becoming a lawyer?
Who knows. That seems to be just as difficult.
And what's wrong with becoming a farmer?
It'd be great if you could succeed dad!
Right. Being a farmer is alright.
But right now, our family has but a zilch of land.
Just some tiny orchard in the backyard.
I'm sure we'll get a vast plot one day!
First obstacle - money.
That, we haven't for now.
Second - need the government to deliver
on their promise and stand handing out cheap land.
Doesn't seem to be happening any time soon.
Only if we all work hard as best we can...
Then again, even if I start saving up my pay
from the port customs, it would still be measly amount.
Alright, I'm all done here.
I'm done with mine too.
Little! Little!
Please herd Snowflake to here!
It's time to get inside now. Hurry up!
One day, I'm certain,
we'll get out vast plot.
And then, we'll build a marvelous farm there.
That's what our family
chooses to believe in to this day.
When Little follows me to school, the teachers
gets the wrong idea and scolds me bad.
And when we get home,
a tragic news await there.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Little and the School".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you