South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 47 - Dad's Decision
It doesn't hurt anywhere?
Yes...
Try to get some sleep.
The fever will subside this way.
Okay.
Even I, who is knows to be so rarely ill,
suddenly developed a fever.
At that time,
I made up my mind to go see the Princeton Mansion.
But only dad and Lucy could accept the invitation.
They must be serving some marvelous dishes there.
Now I'm hungry too.
Seems like the fever subsided.
Thank you for your hospitality.
No, no. More importantly,
please consider what I proposed before.
Okay.
My farm is in a dire need of a man such as you.
To be perfectly frank, if I leave that farm as it is now,
I would eventually have to give it up.
But if you lend us your strength,
it'll be put back in order.
In any case, please let me think about it first.
I'm looking forward to receiving your reply.
Lucy, come visit us again.
Okay.
I'm serious, come soon.
Even if your dad is busy,
you can come on your own, can't you?
Yes. Um...
What is it?
Can't I bring along someone else?
Huh?
My big sister Kate really wanted to come.
But she's ill today...
Ah... Of course.
Next time, be sure to bring Kate along.
Okay.
Well, then.
Be careful, taking them home, Max.
Okay.
Hm? Did you say something?
Yes. You changed your mind
about working at the mine, didn't you, dad?
No.
Then, you're going to go work at the mine, after all?
No...
But Mr. Princeton said he'd like you
to lend him your strength, didn't he?
Yes. That'd mean I have to work on his farm.
Isn't it great, dad?
You think so?
Yes! I think it's way better than working at the mine.
Right? Isn't that right, did?
Give me a minute of silence.
I need to think about many things at once.
We're crossing the Adelaide Bridge.
Returned, huh?
What's that? I thought you'd be asleep.
I've just woken up.
So? How are you feeling?
I had a meal a little while ago
and the fever is not very strong anymore.
Thank goodness.
So hey, what were you doing at the Princeton's place?
Dad was talking to Mr. Princeton.
And I was talking to Mrs. Princeton.
Just talking?
We also had lunch with them.
Knew it!
Right, right. Their cat Prospero still remembered me!
And what were you talking about
with that gorgeous Madam?
All sorts of things.
About me, about things that happened
since our arrival to Southern Australia, about family.
Come to think of it, during my time
in their house, I didn't have my memory with me.
So we couldn't discuss that kinda thing back then.
I suppose.
Mrs. Princeton was very delighted,
no matter what we were talking about.
Did you talk about me?
Of course.
I told her that though we argue a lot,
you're the best big sister one could wish for.
Ah, good to know. I thought you'd just
shower me with slander.
She said I should come play around
together with you next time.
Really?
Yes.
If I'm going to play around in their house,
I'd also rather go there with you.
Why?
I'm a little scared.
What are you saying?
What's there to be afraid of?
That Madam.
Huh?
She's a very kind and a amiable person,
but I'm a little scared of her when we're alone.
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
Tell me, Lucy, do you like this house?
Yes. It's so beautiful and big.
You know, if you stayed in this house
from now on and forever, I'd be the
And how is that scary? Didn't you know
Mrs. Princeton dotes on you a great deal before?
Yes. I did know, but it goes beyond that now.
Truly, you're such an adorable girl.
I don't want to let you go.
I want you to become my child.
Bring me back my Emily.
Hey, what are you doing there?
We've done talking.
We'll join you in no time!
Was it a little too tight?
N-No...
I'm sorry, Lucy.
I couldn't help suddenly feeling
like you're Emily who lost memory again.
This girl called Emily was Mrs. Princeton's daughter,
isn't that what you said?
Yes. And then, she also called me that for three days.
So the one Mrs. Princeton loved
was not Lucy, but Emily?
Considering you didn't have your memory back then,
you were lucky to get even that.
I guess you're feeling a bit lost
now that you've returned to being Lucy.
"A bit" doesn't make it justice...
In that case, why don't you just become
Princetons' daughter and be done with it?
You might as well change your name to Emily too.
K...
Kate!
Just kidding! Just kidding.
You don't joke about that kind of thing!
My home is here!
No matter what happens,
I'm Lucy-May Popple!
Seems like Mr. Princeton is really, really rich.
Yeah. One look at his mansion
is enough to understand.
After all, he's one of the co-owners
of the mine I'm to work at.
Tell me, honey. In the end, you elected
to work at a farm, rather than at a mine, didn't you?
I know how reluctant you are to take that offer...
I want a farm of my own.
I've had my share of working at others' farms.
But this time you won't be working
under someone else's order.
You'll be free to decide for yourself what to do.
Mr. Princeton holds in great respect
my drive to build a farm in this country.
However, there's still another man
in charge of the farm.
And there's no telling whether or not
he'd listen to my advice.
Is it because of that man
that things aren't going great on Princeton's Farm?
I suppose.
If so, why won't you make that farm manager stop?
That's something for Mr. Princeton to decide.
I can't have a hand in it.
But say, let's suppose that man
ends up listening to your advice, after all.
Would you still rather work in a mine even then?
If I reject the farm offer,
I won't be able to work in the mine either.
Don't you think?
Then, farm it is.
We should start preparing to move.
Wait a minute there.
I've considered things thoroughly.
So?
I'm not working on another's farm. Period.
Darling...
One way or another,
I'll have to raise money with some other job.
You've been quite stubborn recently, you know that?
Don't do that, Little!
Funny is sleeping. You'll wake him up.
Ah! He woke up.
You must be awfully bored inside this box.
So, how about we take you outside, Funny?
Don't do that too, Little!
You're scaring the life out of Funny.
There, take a look!
He's running away scared now.
Funny! Funny, come here!
Hey! You can't walk on the field! Get out now!
You can't go there either! Little, come!
Funny is heading to the front!
Please catch him!
Funny!
Whoa! Whoa, whoa.
What is it? What happened?
A wombat, huh?
Sir, we've ran over a wombat.
A wombat? I see. But there's nothing wrong
with the carriage, right?
Nothing, sir.
Good, then hurry up.
Okay.
It's dead?
Poor thing...
Maybe we shouldn't have rescued him from that hole.
Either way, to get ran over by a carriage...
Hey, Lucy. I know how much you love animals.
But from now on, try to leave the wildlife
alone as much as you can, okay?
Not all animals are happy with being kept by people.
Thank you very much, Mr. Popple.
What's this about, John? So suddenly...
Clara just told me.
You gave your permission to us getting married.
Yes.
Then... Then, I think, it's best that we decide
on the day of the wedding ceremony as soon as possible.
Why?
Soon, your whole family
is moving to live near the mine, right?
Therefore, we should get married before that.
We're not moving.
Huh?
We've changed our mind about moving.
Ah. Then, you're going to the mine alone?
No. For various reasons, I changed my mind
on the whole "working in a mine" thing.
Huh?
Is that so?
Therefore, you don't have to hurry so much
with the wedding ceremony.
Oh. Is that so?
I see now. So you've decided against the mine?
Yes.
But regardless, thank you very much
for approving our marriage!
I'm home.
What's wrong, Lucy?
Funny died.
Funny?
The wombat we caught yesterday.
Oh my, it died?
He ran out to the street
and got ran over by Mr. Pettywell's carriage.
Well, that's a very unfortunate thing.
Ah, did John come already?
I don't know.
Then, father,
if you're going to work on Princeton's Farm
you'd have to move anyway, won't you?
Mr. Popple, so we need to hurry
with settling on a date for the ceremony, after all?
Don't worry about that. For the nearest time,
I'm not planning to work at Princeton's Farm either.
But why? It really felt like
he made you some great offer!
That's what I said too.
I also don't understand
why you can't work at his farm.
I don't want to work on a farm
ran by someone else.
I want to run my own farm, on my own land,
no matter how small.
Either way, you have the last word, darling.
Yes. I think I'll go see Mr. Princeton
to give him my refusal tomorrow.
Then, let's go have dinner now.
John, I've prepared a portion for you as well.
Thank you.
Good night, Clara.
Good night, John.
Kate, are you sleeping?
I've spend this whole day sleeping,
so I don't feel one bit sleepy now.
The atmosphere was somehow strange.
What do you mean?
At the dinner tonight.
What atmosphere?
Everyone ate in silence.
And what did they decide
on Clara and John's wedding ceremony?
They didn't discuss that.
How strange.
Seems like everyone is displeased with dad.
With dad?
Yes. Myself included.
Mr. Princeton put great faith in dad.
But dad said he would only work on his own farm.
So it seems like dad is turning it down.
But it totally looks like a great offer!
Don't you think so too, Kate?
I suppose.
But dad has a mind of his own.
Lucy, because you're still a child,
you don't understand grown-ups well.
If dad made up his mind to turn it down,
we can't have a say in that.
Good night.
I wonder what'll happen to us now.
If Clara and John get married,
they'll be happy, at least.
What about us?
Good night, Lucy.
Good night.
Now, come. This way, please.
Okay...
Now then, you'd give me your answer today, won't you?
Yes... No, I mean...
What's the matter?
Unfortunately, I cannot accept it.
Does that mean...
you don't want to work on the farm?
Yes. After a long consideration,
I concluded that I'll have to refuse, after all.
If so, are you saying you'd like to work at the mine?
No.
Well, now I really can't understand.
As far as I'm aware,
you're currently looking for a job, right?
Yes.
Did you find some better job, then?
No.
What's the matter then?
I believe that by working at another's farm
I wouldn't be able to govern my own decisions.
Well, that's not 100% true.
In order to put the farm straight, we would heed strongly to your advice - that's what I'm offering.
I made up my mind already.
Is that so?
Really, I'm sorry to say this.
I appreciate deeply your kindness.
You were my best bet, Mr. Popple.
But in this case, I have no choice,
but to sell that farm away.
Well then, I hope you excuse me now.
Come in.
Mr. Pettywell has arrived.
He says he needs to meet you by all means, sir.
Pettywell, huh?
It's almost as though Mr. Pettywell was waiting for you to refuse, to come and grab the farm for himself.
Pettywell?
Do you know that man?
I do.
He's about as apt in business
as he is nasty in personality.
He got wind of that farm not doing well somewhere
and had been doggedly pestering me
to sell it to him for a while now.
Pettywell, then?
Up to now, I've been flatly refusing his persistence.
But today, finally...
What is Mr. Pettywell doing now?
Presently, I told him master
is still conversing with his previous visitor.
So he's waiting for the latter's departure.
In that case, tell him Mr. Popple is leaving
and bring Mr. Pettywell here.
Okay.
Um...
Yes?
I changed my mind, Mr. Princeton.
Then...
Will you work at that farm, Mr. Popple?
Yes. Though I can't if I'd be able to do much...
No. I'm sure, with your help, we'll manage, Mr. Popple.
That's what I believe in,
as long as we heed to your advice.
Tell Mr. Pettywell to leave.
I'll be busy with my current visitor for a while now.
Will do.
Now, please be seated, Mr. Popple.
I'd like to explain to you
the situation on my farm in more detail now.
Ah, but before that, let's have a toast!
Dammit! I'll remember this!
And I'll make him pay for it, I swear!
Ah! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Father.
Ah, welcome back, Clara.
My, you stink of alcohol!
You've drunk quite a lot, haven't you?
Yes. I did.
I also noticed your unsteady gait
when I saw you from behind.
Say, didn't you promise not to drink anymore?
I sure did.
Why, then?
Because I was too happy.
Happy?
Right.
Hey, Clara, don't you think we gotta invite John soon
to make arrangements on your wedding ceremony?
Oh come on, father.
Listen closely, everyone.
Dad wants to tell us all something.
Today, I accepted the offer
of working at Princeton's Farm.
Huh?
To tell you the truth,
I was actually planning to turn it down.
But in unexpected turn of events,
I suddenly had a change of heart.
Up until now, I always dreamed
about owning my own farm.
But now I've come to think
that as long as they follow my advice in managing
the agriculture, working on another's farm is fine too.
We'll all be moving to live on the farm.
And the day after tomorrow, Mr. Princeton
will show us around the farm. That's all.
Now, let's eat.
Thank you for the meal!
Is there a school at Princeton's Farm?
Not at the farm itself,
but in the nearby city of Gawler.
Though it's a little far to go to.
I see, so there is a school...
Though Lucy is noticeably disappointed,
I really feel that tonight's dinner
is the first happy one in a long time.
Next time: "Becoming a Well-Off Child..."
Don't miss it!
The Alps Story: My Annette
Next show - The Alps Story: My Annette.
It starts in the new year.
Don't miss it, okay?
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you