South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 12 - The Night in Adelaide
Stop resisting, Sticky!
Ah! It's dangerous, Lucy-May!
No! Sticky!
She fell down!
Ah! Lucy-May!
Kate! Help me!
Hang on!
Grab on to me, here!
I can't, Kate! Ah!
Ah! Lucy-May!
Kate! Help me!
Someone! Someone, please come here!
Someone, we need you
to come immediately here!
I think I just heard someone's voice.
Certainly, I heard it, too.
Could it be the girls?
It was in the direction of river.
Someone!
I'll go check it out.
Someone! Someone, please hurry!
Kate!
Lucy-May! I'm coming to you right now!
Ah! Let go! I need to go save Lucy-May!
What's going on?
A... A native!
What's he doing?
Kidnapping Lucy!
Oh my!
Hey! Let that child go now!
You! What were you planning to do with her?!
If you don't let her go this instant,
you'll regret it!
You don't understand what I'm saying?
That child is my child!
Let her go now or else!
It's not what it seems, dad!
This man was actually saving Lucy-May.
Both me and our Sticky!
What did you say?
Thank you, sir.
Thank you so much!
Burigan barina.
Huh?
Oh, I know! This goat will have a baby very soon.
Lucy-May, how in the world
did you end up in this situation?
Sticky and me were about to drown.
Which means, what that man did...
Sir! Thank you!
We were quick to misjudge him.
Hm.
But that's quite the complexion he has.
He was like Heracles, this guy.
Hey, who is Heracles?
Oh, you don't know?
I don't. A famous Englishman?
What a nonsense.
It's the name of a Greek God.
Ah!
I never asked that man his name.
That's right. After all,
you kinda owe him your life now.
It's alright.
Until I find out what his real name is,
I'll just call him Mr. Heracles.
Lucy-May, you're soaking wet!
You need to change clothes quickly...
It's fine, they'll go dry in no time.
Oh? This goat seems to be shivering a bit.
My, you poor thing.
Sticky, are you cold?
Lucy-May, instead of worrying for the goat,
you should be more worried for yourself.
You'll catch a cold this way.
Go and change quickly.
Ah!
What's wrong?
Ah! I left Tob behind.
What did you say?
Huh?
I left Tob all alone at home.
That's not good.
I'll look after the rest with those two,
so you'd better go, too.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Well you two just gave us a handful more
of unnecessary trouble.
But I didn't do a thing.
It was Lucy-May who nearly got herself drowned.
But that was because Sticky nearly drowned.
So I was just trying to save her.
In any case, I'm glad neither you
nor the goat drowned.
Now, let's return quickly,
with that goat in tow.
I'm sure Tob hasn't gone anywhere.
Good if so.
Tob! Tob!
Sorry to trouble you, but I'm gonna
have to ask you to look on that side.
Okay.
Tob! Tob!
Haven't you drunk enough water by now?!
Kate, we're going ahead.
I'm still worried about Tob,
and Lucy needs to quickly change clothes.
All right.
Now.
You'll need to give birth to a baby soon!
Falling into a river
is not very responsible of you!
Tob! Tob!
Tob was here, right?
Well, about that...
Maybe in the shack...
I mean... have you looked in the house?
Of course I did.
What about Bernard?
Have you tried looking together?
Yeah, I asked him to check
if the kid didn't go to your house, by any chance.
Ah, there he is.
Have you found him, Bernard?
Haven't found anything!
You don't suppose
he went to the river past us?
It can't be. In that case, we or someone
would've noticed him on the way.
Then, I'll go try looking that way.
And I'll go over there.
Truly, I'm so sorry for all the trouble, ma'am.
No, it's nothing!
Ah? Found him! Found!
He's here!
My!
Thank goodness.
Really, thank goodness.
Taking an afternoon nap in a place like this?
What about Tob?
He was here all the time?
No. It seems, he embarked
on an expedition to Mrs. Mac's house.
Tob must've thought
Mrs. Mac's house was ours.
Hardly. He's a kind of child you can't take your eyes off,
lest he'll wander wherever.
If I were Tob I probably also wouldn't believe
that such a run-down shack could be ours.
Clara, I feel like I've heard
more than enough of that grumbling.
For sure. Let's call it enough, Clara.
You're right.
Mother, where is Lucy-May's change of clothes?
Ah? They're still there.
But in which of the crates?
This one.
Lucy-May! Come here!
But I really don't need to change
from these clothes.
Enough.
And I'm not one bit cold!
But I like these clothes especially!
Enough.
Hey, can't you walk even a bit faster?
What now? We're almost home!
Come on, let's keep going, Sticky!
Sticky, are you...
Sticky, you don't mean to tell me
you're about to have a baby, do you?
Ah! Then it must really be so.
But you can't do it here!
Try to walk a little more. At least to the house.
Come on, getting to the tent would be enough.
There, feel free to have your baby, okay?
Ah! It's too soon!
You can't have a baby yet!
We'll be in trouble.
Come on, get up!
Please believe me,
you can't have a baby in a place like this!
Do you understand, Sticky?
Come on, just a little more.
A few more steps.
Ah! N-no way! No!
You can't have baby yet! Ah!
Ugh. Come on, get up!
Someone!
Ah! Ah! No! Wait! You can't! No-no-no-no-no!
Right, sorry for all the trouble.
Say, sis. Kids sure look sweet when sleeping.
You should hurry up
with having your own kid, too.
That is my own wish as well. But as you know,
such things are only for our good Lord to decide.
That must be so. Now, if you excuse me,
I'll go get this child to bed.
Let me help you with that, too.
Thanks, but I can handle the rest of it myself.
It's having a baby!
What's going on, Kate?
Sticky is about to have a baby!
She just lies there on the grass
and won't budge!
But I feel sorry for the baby if it gets born right there.
Kate! Sticky's is having a baby?
So I think.
But I also hadn't seen a goat
giving birth ever before.
Lucy-May, mind you manners a bit.
Now go back inside
and put this on properly.
My, Lucy-May, you're in nothing but your underwear!
Don't you have any shame?
Mrs. Mac will laugh at you.
No!
Kate, you're telling us you can't move the goat?
Yes.
All right, I'll go with you.
But our Sticky is heavy.
That guy previously lifted her with just one hand.
Which means I can, too.
Are you really just as strong, Mr. Bernard?
I suppose so.
Kate! Wait for me!
So the goat is finally in labor?
So it seems.
At such a haphazard time, we'll have
an additional trouble of looking after the baby goat now.
That's something you could task Lucy-May with.
Instead, let's get to carrying our things
inside this tent and the house.
That's right. Clara, will you lend us a hand?
Of course.
May I help, too?
Out of question, ma'am!
It's something we should do ourselves.
You've helped us with so many things already.
It's nothing.
Well, then, I'm going home now,
please tell my brother so.
Thanks a lot, Mrs. Mac.
We hope your husband recovers soon.
We really do.
Thank you.
If we had a good doctor here to show my husband to,
he'd get better in no time.
Agreed.
See you.
Father, Mr. Pettywell is here.
Hm. Took him quite a while.
That's because he kept fighting
the oxcart owners.
I wonder which plot are they going to settle.
Who knows. As long as it's somewhere
away from here, I'm not complaining.
Mr. Popple!
Huh? Is something wrong, Mrs. Jane?
We have another addition
to our neighborhood today.
Ma'am, you know these people?
I mean, Pettywells.
Look, they bought the plot
right in front of our house.
Our neighborhood gets filled one after another,
and I'm so happy!
This can't be!
Why do you need to shout it like that?
Because right there, on that spot, Mr. Pettywell
will be assembling our prefabricated home!
Well it's no longer ours, is it?
We've decided on letting Mr. Pettywell have it.
Ironic, isn't it?
They ended up living so close to us.
We'll have to watch him assemble a house there,
while we live in this...
But I already gave you a promise
not to speak out about that house anymore.
Just as I was so delighted
to have neighbors such as Macs...
Mr. Pettywell settles over there.
Adelaide is supposed to be spacious...
Even Adelaide is not spacious enough, Clara.
Mr. Bernard, hold her real tight.
You can't afford to drop her.
She's heavier than I thought,
that's for sure.
Of course she does,
she's carrying a baby inside.
I think she has no less than five of them in there.
I'd say it's two.
With this weight, she might as well
have all 10 in there!
Now, where do I lay it down?
Dad, can we use one of this tent's corners for it?
Well, if it'll happen today, or tomorrow at latest,
I guess we've no choice.
Mr. Bernard, careful.
You can do it!
Down you go.
Oh?
Let's see.
I see. It really is about to give birth.
And how many babies will it have?
Hm. We won't know until she's out of labor,
which is probably will take until tomorrow.
I see, tomorrow?
Sticky, you can do it, girl!
Right, this here is a very
valuable thing, so be careful.
Oh? And that looks like our
new neighbors right there.
Dad, is Mr. Pettywell living there?
Seems to be so.
Oh-huh?
You seem to have something
against that man, you little ladies.
I hate him!
Kate!
Do you know them?
Mr. Pettywell owns a large chunk
of Southern Australian land.
Together with a mine on it.
Yes, we managed to put it together
that he is wealthy.
Oh.
Mr. Pettywell seems to be coming this way.
And I shouldn't think
he's coming to say anything good.
Well, is this your house here?
That's right.
I didn't realize it back when you passed by me
on the way, but a servant told me just now.
It must be fate that you and me ended up living so close,
you could even say we're neighbors.
I think it was a coincidence.
But more importantly,
that's one shabby house you have.
Yes. But we never expected it
to be a palace in the first place.
You seem to lament selling away
your chance to live in a prefabricated home.
I never had that kind of thoughts.
Oh?! Well, that's a great relief to hear.
After all, seeing it assembled right before your eyes
would probably deliver you a great heartache.
While we're at it, although I understand
it may sound a bit presumptuous,
Would you be so kind as to assemble
that prefabricated home over there?
What did you say?
Aren't you supposed to know
how to assemble it better than anyone else?
Look - before, you said you'd assemble it
in two weeks, didn't you?
Yes. But I'll have to refuse.
For the moment, I have more things to sort out
about my own house than you can shake a stick at.
I absolutely cannot afford helping you
build your house as well.
I never said you'll do it for free.
I cannot agree to this,
regardless of the pay.
Obviously enough, assembling it
with my stupid servants spells disaster.
Maybe you should find a carpenter.
There can't be any skilled carpenters here in Adelaide!
It's the same as with doctors - there are none.
One way or another, I refuse.
Eh?
As you can see, I haven't even started
sorting things our on this end yet.
Please try to accept it somehow.
But I will pay exactly as much as you ask for...
Please leave.
It's starting to rain, Mr. Pettywell.
People! Hurry up to carry our things
to inside the house and the tent!
Eh? How can one be so arrogant?
Ah! It's wet!
To over there.
If I'm getting drenched again,
I really didn't have to change, after all.
Lucy-May, hurry!
Right, that's one fine rain.
Doctor, make a bit of room please.
Hey, I'll spill my drink this way.
Doctor, it's been decided
that I'm going to Adelaide tomorrow.
Didn't you say you'll have to hang around here
for two or three days?
Mr. Parker managed to find
another oxcart for us.
Big enough to take on all this luggage.
Oh? Which means, I'll have to ride it, too?
I'm not sure if you'll be able to ride it.
Since we're going to Adelaide,
you'd better be prepared for a walk.
You think I can walk for ten kilometers?
I think you're drinking way too much alcohol.
Aren't you a doctor?
You should take better care of your own health.
Alcohol is the only thing
keeping my spirits high, Ben.
I feel terrible disappointment from seeing that.
You do? From just seeing me do that?
Not exactly from that.
I haven't told anyone about it yet,
but I hope to become a doctor myself, in the future.
Well, well. That's a surprise.
You a doctor, huh? Hm...
It's only natural that you're surprised.
Without any way to learn it,
wanting to become a doctor...
You're still young.
There'll be plenty of ways for you to learn soon.
But how come you decided
that you want to be a doctor?
I wanted to help people who are in pain.
But now I'm not sure whether or not
I feel like becoming a doctor anymore.
How come?
After meeting you, I'm starting to think
a doctor's work is terribly tedious.
And I just help it.
Doctor, when we get to Adelaide,
stop drinking that much.
And give your undivided attention
to people suffering from illnesses!
Ben.
I'm sorry. I let slip something arrogant.
Listen, Ben...
About that... I don't think
I'll be able to quit drinking at once.
But I could vow here
that I'll be examining my patients seriously.
No!
I definitely vow to do just that, Ben.
Ah! It's stopped raining.
You hear it?
I do.
The natives are chanting songs.
You think Mr. Heracles is there, too?
Such a man should definitely be the natives' leader.
That's how I felt.
The one I owe my life to.
He sure was a big guy.
He probably didn't understand a word of it,
when we were saying our thanks.
We could try to memorize the words
that his people use, instead.
True...
Are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy. Good night.
Good night.
After some time, our first night in Adelaide
had become soundless again.
Even if today was by all means
a very turbulent day.
Dad made a house for our goat.
At that moment, we hear our names
called out from afar...
Just who might it be?
Next time:
"Ben Has Arrived!"
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you