South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 23 - Your Name is Little
Doctor. Doctor!
Did Lucy stop by here, by any chance?
Doctor Deighton!
Where did Lucy go?
Uh? Ah, Ben went out, alright.
Forget about Ben, where is Lucy?
Huh?
Lucy-May came a little while ago.
And then went out.
Together with Ben?
Eh... Ben left way before she did.
Also took with him the puppy that was sleeping there.
Ah, sorry I woke you up, Doctor.
No, no.
Seeing how you're still awake,
it's probably not that late into the night yet.
Yes...
I suppose our brick-making venture didn't succeed...
Just as I thought, a complete failure.
But it's strange that dad isn't here either.
Lucy!
Where are you?
Father!
Lucy! Father!
Well, let's turn back, Lucy-May.
Ben isn't here either.
But I wanna search more in this direction.
You can't, Lucy-May.
A lady can't be wandering alone in the night.
But if we stop, Ben might abandon that baby dog
somewhere and we won't know!
That is not a baby dog, but a baby dingo.
I told you from the very beginning
we should abandon it.
No! I'll never forgive myself for abandoning it!
I wanna keep that baby dog!
Father!
See? We need to return.
Kate came here to look for us.
Ben, don't abandon the pup.
I beg you with all my heart not to abandon it!
Huh?
Maybe the aborigines congregated somewhere nearby?
At that, little one, I'm leaving you
to live around here, so take care.
Still just a baby, aren't you?
But if I were to bring you home now,
we'd be in even bigger trouble.
Because you're a baby dingo, when you grow up,
your ferocity may wake up again.
And then, even you would start wanting to butcher the sheep and poultry, which we people are keeping.
When that happens,
we won't be able to keep you anyway.
Not just that, we'll have no choice
but to kill you with our own hands.
And that's not something I would be able to handle.
Goodbye now. Feel free to stay in the woods,
or to run off to the prairies of faraway.
Just make sure you get as far from people as you can.
What's wrong? Leave now!
Hurry up and leave!
Fine. Then I'll have my leave first.
Damn it...
Why does he have to be so damn cute?
Ah!
Look at who's the timid little guy.
You're a baby dingo, remember?
A baby of the dog that's nurtured in the wild!
Like it or not, I'll have to leave you behind.
Alright, let's look for a better place elsewhere.
Doctor! Doctor! Need you to wake up right now, Doctor!
Yeah...
Doctor, where exactly did Ben go?
Lucy-May, eh? Didn't you ask me
the same thing a bit earlier?
But you only said that Ben went out with the puppy!
Didn't Ben tell you exactly where he's going?
Let's see, where did he go...
Please, try to recall it, Dr. Deighton!
Yeah... Sure.
Ah! I know.
It was as though he muttered,
"Probably best in the forest".
The forest?
I knew it! Ben left to dispose
of that baby dingo somewhere.
What happened, Lucy-May?
Does your tummy hurt somewhere?
It's not that.
Lucy wanted to bring up that puppy herself.
That's why...
Oh, but alas...
That was a baby wolf, wasn't it?
Not at all! It was a baby dingo!
Nothing to do with wolves!
Hey, I see, I see, I get it.
But it's nothing irreparable.
Although it may not be the same dog,
we'll find and catch another one.
I would also set my mind to it.
A normal dog would do just as well.
No! I wanna keep that one puppy and none other!
Ah, geez.
Ah. Lucy-May, I never suspected
you could be that uncooperative.
I want that puppy! That puppy!
Just as I thought, I need a kiln with temperatures
way higher than that for firing bricks well.
In the end, making your own bricks
and firing them at home is a fool's errand.
But then, the house for Ben and Dr. Deighton to live in
would also have to be built from timber?
No. Right now, I'm considering simple dried bricks.
Dried bricks?
Yes. In other words, a house from dirt.
Even that would be an improvement over the tent.
When the winter comes,
one would simply freeze in that tent.
Tob is finally asleep.
Thank you.
My, but it's that late already?
What are Kate and Lucy-May doing?
Probably waiting for Ben to return.
Ben is supposed to return?
Yes. Seemingly, Ben went
to release the baby dingo into the wild.
But they should be long asleep by now.
Clara, go see what's what.
Okay.
What's the matter, Lucy-May?
Crying from learning
that we'll have to abandon the baby dingo.
Nothing serious.
My, we should be proud of that boy.
Hm...
We didn't even have to ask Ben for anything.
He heeded closely to my sentiment
and left to get rid of that dangerous puppy himself.
Eh?
Stop crying and go to sleep already.
What's that? Asleep already?
Oh? Back at last?
I see. So you didn't go out to dispose of him, after all?
I went to dispose of him.
But you couldn't bring yourself?
Yes.
Well, at the very least,
you'll make Lucy-May delighted.
Doctor, what's the matter with you?
Doing that at so late an hour?
I like to sleep at night just like everyone else.
But tonight, as soon as I'm asleep, I'm roused,
as soon as I fall asleep - roused again.
So now I cannot even shut my eyes.
Ben, it was actually all your fault.
Because you took that din...
What now, fell asleep already?
Well aintcha a lucky fella?
Ah, and I don't want to sleep at all!
Going to pee?
Yes.
Hm...
Ben is here...
I'm so glad! So he didn't get rid of you.
Isn't it too early yet?
But I'm awake!
Ah, right. You woke up in the middle of the night, too...
I did not.
I see... I hope Ben returned while we were asleep.
He did return.
How would you know that?
Ah!
So you did wake up in the middle of the night!
You're right! The puppy is sleeping right here!
I think Doctor is about to fall, Kate.
Let's wake him up.
Doctor, you'll fall from the bed this way!
No, I can't have the breakfast yet.
I couldn't get any rest last night.
You just leave me to sleep like this...
Don't lie! Whenever I came here,
you were fast asleep, snoring loudly!
Sure, sure, sure, sure...
Hey. Good morning, you two.
Good morning.
Even though I spent the whole evening crying,
thinking you'd done away with the puppy!
Yeah...
I actually went to do away with it...
Knew it!
I thought doing away with it
is the best thing to do...
But I just couldn't.
And I ain't letting anyone
do away with it from now on!
But dad and mom said,
the sooner we do away with it - the better, Lucy.
I'll ask them to rethink!
Say, Lucy.
Do you actually intend to take seriously
the bringing up of this baby dingo?
'Course I am!
And you do realize it may be dangerous?
Yes.
It's not just about you.
You'll also have to take action
if it starts troubling others.
I know that.
I believe that I can become best friends
with this wild dog!
And if we become true friends,
this dog won't have any reason to turn against me.
Ah! You're awake, boy?
Little one!
One more thing, Lucy.
This fella has one side that I'm finding a little odd.
Oh?
Which is him being a scaredy-cat.
Scaredy-cat?
Must be mighty hungry, aren't you?
I'll go get some milk for you now.
Wait here just one moment!
Oh my.
So he never abandoned the puppy?
That's right.
Clara, can I have some of it?
Did you tell mom already?
Was planning to, after this.
Careful.
Here.
Thank God. I guess you can consider Sticky
your wet nurse now.
I'll go introduce him to Marsh now.
It's still thirsty.
Can you pour a bit more?
It really doesn't look one bit dangerous!
He seems to be an awful scaredy-cat, in fact.
Eh?
Here you go now.
You're right, he's an awful poltroon!
If he remains this way even when he's big,
he won't cause us any trouble.
That makes sense, I suppose...
But I'm still not entirely happy with it.
Better that than becoming feral.
Hm...
Even a normal dog would've been
a bit more daring than that.
Ben, Lucy-May. Come inside,
we need to have a talk.
Come on. Hurry up inside.
Listen closely, then.
I'll allow you to keep that baby dingo
under a set of conditions.
Promise me to adhere to these at all times.
First condition:
should that dog attack a person
or hurt someone,
we'll put it down then and there.
Got it?
Yes.
Did you understand, Lucy-May?
Secondly, be it the sheep or the poultry,
in other words, if he attacks or hurts
any kind of livestock,
we'll also have to kill him, or else set him free in the wilderness, away from any livestock.
Okay.
Understood.
The third condition.
If that dog ends up
only listening to Lucy-May's orders,
ignoring whatever others tell him,
we'll have to banish him to the woods.
But...
No "buts".
Listen.
If you put your every effort into petting him,
any ferocious beast would become attached to you.
But even then, it still remains the very same
ferocious beast towards everyone else.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
It is essential that the dog becomes friendly
towards other people as well, not just you.
And if it can't get friendly,
at least that it's not hostile.
That's the kind of upbringing I want you to give it.
Think you could do it, you two?
Yes. I'll try my best.
Good.
Honey, is that fine by you?
I suppose so.
Though I still think it's best
that we don't try to raise it.
It'll be all right, mom!
Just don't forget that I opposed it
from the very beginning.
Okay.
Now, then. It seems, I'm starving, honey.
How about we hurry up to eat?
We need to give him a name.
What do you think about "Little", Lucy?
Little?
This way, even when he grows big,
we'll still call him by this name,
filled with hopes of him remaining forever
cute and innocent, the way he is now.
Little, then?
Little.
That settles it.
That settles him as Little.
Little!
I'm sure he'll grow up to be a good boy, our Little.
That's what I thought.
Ben.
My mind was so set on the dog matter,
I kept forgetting to tell you something up until now.
What is it?
Firing of bricks didn't go as planned.
Yeah...
That's why...
For now, we'll have to build a new house
for you and Dr. Deighton from simple dried bricks.
And I was already starting wonder, "wouldn't it be nice
to live in a house from fired bricks?"
Hm. Sorry to disappoint,
but for now, that's not happening.
Starting tomorrow, I'll try to get help with making dried bricks from anyone who's not too preoccupied.
You say "starting tomorrow",
but you've not done any preparations yet, have you?
That's why we'll divide the labor
between us two from now.
I'll take it upon myself
to prepare a wooden form.
Meanwhile, you go buy some straw
and start chopping it up.
We'll need to mix it with the clay.
Did you hear? Starting tomorrow,
we'll be helping making bricks!
And with no time to play around?
Seems so to me.
Lucy-May, this dog doesn't bite now, does it?
Don't worry.
Ah...
Very well if so.
Ah, I'm still sleepy.
He actually ran away,
afraid that Doctor might bite him, instead!
Now that's surprisingly yellow of that guy.
Hey, sis!
If our playtime ends tomorrow,
why don't we play to our heart's content today?
Good idea.
Let's take Little along and go to the hill!
Let's hurry, while we've no errands to run yet!
Yeah, let's hurry! Little, come!
Come on, after us, Little!
Wait, Little!
Hurry up!
Little!
Lucy became completely obsessed
with the baby dingo we got.
Say, Little, when you become a full-grown dog,
you won't turn against Lucy, right?
Because Lucy is your friend, isn't she?
Because we stained our clothes
while making the bricks,
we went to the river to do the laundry.
To make them as clean as possible,
we've decided to wash ourselves altogether.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:"The Last Day of Summer".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you