South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 16 - The Boozed Doctor
Me and Lucy-May went to the forest
a bit further away from our home
to gather some dead twigs
that we'll make into firewood.
Oh my? Isn't it a koala?
Uh. It's no use. Climbing somewhere
that high is out of my reach.
I wonder if Lucy-May even remembers
she's supposed to be gathering branches.
Please climb down, little koala!
Wait, you're not koala!
Something like a fox!
Lucy-May.
Don't tell me you wanna climb up there
to break the branches from the tree?
Look over there, sister.
What is it?
Ah!
When I first saw it, I thought
it was a koala. But it's not!
It's looking at us, isn't it?
It has a pretty little face, too!
What kind of animal could it be?
I wanna catch it, sis.
Well feel free to catch it,
if you can climb this tree.
Of course, I can't climb it!
Ain't nothing we can do, then.
You go catch it, instead!
Are you not right in the head, or what?
You're right. There's no way
you can climb up there either.
Now that you know, just give up
and gather some firewood.
Ah! Sis!
Ah! Did you see? Sis, did you see?
I saw it...
It's a baby! A baby is clinging onto her back!
Wow! Wow! I so wanna
have it as a pet! It's adorable!
Australia sure is full
of tree-perching creatures, isn't it?
I've decided to start learning
tree-climbing starting today.
The animal we saw
resembled a possum.
As we would learn later, it was a species
called common brushtail possum.
That thing is heavy!
We overloaded it a little bit.
Maybe dump it?
No way! Dad said to get enough
to sustain an open fire for a long while.
Why so?
They're charring the tips of the wood that'd they make into the pillars, though I don't know why.
Ah! That's Billy over there!
Billy!
Thank goodness, we can have him pull this for us.
Or even have him capture that animal
we saw perched on the tree for us!
No, not that!
What are you saying?
We gotta take this firewood
to father quickly, or else...
But it shouldn't take all that long.
Not now, alright?
Ya finished gathering it already?
'Twas fast, y'know?
But it still weighs a ton.
Care to help?
Sure. 'Course. That's why I came here.
Because I'm the one strong here, innit?
You'd help us a great deal.
Just leave it to me, alright?
Huh?
Told you it's heavy.
Lucy-May, let's push too.
Ah! Lucy-May,
that's not necessary at all!
I haven't really been
putting my spine into pulling now.
Let's go!
Huh?
Oh, come on!
Doesn't seem like you're really
all that strong, Billy.
Lucy-May, let's both push from behind.
Uh-huh.
Billy, we're pushing!
Okay...
That's it!
If ya ever need to carry something even heavier,
ain't no way it budges without a cart underneath.
Say, Billy, what brings you here, actually?
I was at your house,
cause my dad also went there.
My! Does that mean your old man is gonna
lend us a hand with rebuilding our shack?
Certainly! He already refused to go
to Mr. Pettywell's site.
I bet Mr. Pettywell was fuming!
Was so mad his face went all red!
Well, well, everyone.
Good job, good job.
I'm off to find a replacement for Mr. Jamling.
In the meantime, please continue with the construction
in accordance with this blueprint.
I'm counting on you.
Huh?
Tsk.
By sawing all the pieces in advance like this,
we expedite the final assembly, isn't that right?
That's correct.
The prefabricated home that we sold to Mr. Pettywell
was also made with that consideration in mind, right?
All the parts of the house are sawed
in advance and mapped on the blueprint.
Exactly so.
Mr. Jamling, even though you've left, they still can
construct that prefabricated house somehow, right?
They definitely can,
if they take their time.
But truth be told, none of them except me
seems to know what he's doing.
I can imagine Mr. Pettiwell's angry face now.
Ben, let's continue.
Okay.
Aight. The tea was delicious.
Thanks a bunch.
I couldn't help noticing
you don't drink any alcohol these days.
Alas, there ain't none within reach,
'sides, I've been somewhat broke lately anyway.
If only you had plenty of patients to examine...
Huh?
Ah, I know! You should put out a signboard.
Signboard, eh?
Aight. I'll go get a fitting piece of wood, then.
Doc, you need something?
Uh? Ah, no-no.
Mr. Jamling, has your leg healed?
Yes, thanks to you, it's fine,
with just a slight limp.
Ain't that dandy?
By the way, you plan to use
that plank for somethin'?
This one? Yes, we'll use it.
Huh? I see.
Mr. Popple, about this plank...
Certainly, we're using that as well.
Doctor, why do you require a piece of wood?
Oh, it's nothin'. Was jus' thinking
of making a little signboard.
Uh...
Please, Billy! Come to those woods with me
once we're done with this, will you?
I don't see why I should.
It's 'cause Billy is such an unparalleled
tree-climbing pro!
Coaxing ain't gonna get you anywhere.
Fine. As long as you agree
to go there with me, it's okay.
Say, why is it that the lumber
won't rot if we char it?
What did you say?
How come the lumber doesn't rot
if we treat it with fire?
Dunno.
Ugh... It's been this way for eternity.
Oh?
Aight, let's see.
Should be ready by now.
Aye, this would do.
Doctor, what are you doing with it?
Well, look here to know.
Oh my. That's your signboard, Doctor?
Aye.
Where will you post it?
How about on the tent?
No way!
It'll be too far away from the road
for anyone to read it.
Methinks you oughta post it
somewhere near the road.
Isn't that right, Lucy-May?
Uh-huh.
Ah! How about you nail it to the tree over there?
Oh?
Oh, good call.
Wait a minute, though.
It would need this to hang there.
Now, then. Time for a doctor's visit
to our neighbor.
Kate!
Weren't you told
not to get your eyes off the fire?
Ah! Oh no! It slipped my mind completely!
Hey, Lucy-May.
What is it?
Never mind, c'mere.
So big now, ain't they?
And cute, too.
That's cute, but three baby goats
will make the milk run low.
That's not the case!
Everyone of us gets to drink
a cup of milk every morning.
But suppose she only had one baby,
she would produce more milk.
Huh?
Billy, what are you trying to say?
Well, you wanted me to follow you
into those woods, dincha?
That's correct. It's to catch
the animal we saw there.
Besides, I feel there are plenty more
of different animals over there, somehow.
Meaning, I'd need to climb a tree?
Naturally! You can't catch it any other way.
Well, I wanna have a goat.
Huh?
You don't need all tree baby goats, do you?
Oh! I see, so that's what it all was about?
Think about it, Lucy-May: you found this goat,
so you're also the one to let it go.
Well, that's true, but...
Think I need to ask grown-ups in the house
if we can give it to someone else or not.
Then you don't mind me having it?
I suppose.
As long as you manage
to catch that creature we saw.
Alright, I will definitely catch it!
I also feel like there should be koalas there.
Alright! Gonna catch 'em all!
When you do, I'll give you
the second baby goat, too!
Uh? Are you serious?
Yes.
Let's go, then.
Right now?
'Course.
But it's almost my turn
to watch the fire instead of Kate.
But you've not been commanded
to do anything yet, innit?
Let's go then, but quietly.
Nobody has got a clue!
It's a success!
A great success!
On which tree did you see it, exactly?
I think it was around here.
Ah! There's that tree!
Huh?
Can you still see that animal?
I don't see it.
And the greenery sure is thick.
I first saw it sitting low,
but then it climbed higher.
That's one tall tree, y'know.
Climb it, then.
Eh? Want me to climb it
without even knowing for sure it's there?
It definitely was there before.
Well a lot of time had passed since then.
Couldn't it have left by now?
You climb to check it out.
Hmm... Hm. Sure is a tall one...
You can do it, Billy!
Hmm?
Kate, where's Lucy-May?
She was around here up until a while ago.
Lucy-May! Lucy-May?
Mom, there's no helping it.
Let's just bring him along.
But the riverbank is full of dangers.
Then, we could probably ask Kate to do it.
You're probably right. Kate!
What is it?
Look after Tob. Me and mom
are going to the river to do the laundry.
But it's my turn to watch the fire...
We know that.
But there's no way we can
bring Tob along to the riverside.
When we're doing the laundry,
we won't be able to keep an eye on Tob.
I got it, alright.
I'll look after him.
Now, Tob, go play some with your sister Kate.
But I can't really play with him.
Oh, sorry. Then, you just keep each other company.
And let's hope Lucy-May returns some time soon.
Then, feel free to entrust Tob to her, Kate.
Okay.
Like that!
And here...
It's not here, Lucy-May!
Where do you think did it go?
It could have moved
to any other tree around here!
I'm going down!
So? D'you notice it on any other tree?
Oh...
Ah!
Look out! Stop there, Lucy-May!
What's wrong, Billy?
There's a snake! Right behind you! Whoa!
Ah!
It might be a poisonous species!
Run, Lucy-May!
Dashing away is also dangerous!
It may then spring at me in a flash!
Then just stay where you are,
while I climb down to try to kill it!
Ah! Lucy-May! Wah!
That's one incredible bird.
What kind of bird could it be?
Let's go back, shall we?
Yeah.
Mom, you go home first
with what's already in that basket.
I'll do the rest of it.
I'll probably do just that.
Sorting out the dinner is also on me.
Counting on you, then.
Sure.
My, our esteemed neighbor is also here.
Ah.
Good morning, it's a perfect day for laundry, isn't it?
Good morning.
Good morning!
Good morning, Clara.
Is your husband feeling any better?
Thank you for asking.
It seems the fever had subsided
and he's finally regaining his strength.
Doctor Deighton saw him just now.
He said there's no longer anything to worry about.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
When I first saw him,
he didn't seem all that reliable...
But Doctor Deighton has proven himself
an excellent physician.
Well, if you say so...
Oh? Am I mistaken?
Ah? No, that's not what I meant to say...
Just that the Doctor is a terrible drunkard.
But he had to refrain from it
for the last two or three days.
Oh my.
My husband is recovering at a lightning speed,
and I felt like celebrating it...
So I encouraged the Doctor
to have some of our whiskey.
Then the Doctor...
He drank several glasses
because it was so delicious.
Several glasses?
Darling!
Come here! Quickly!
Ah... So it was here, after all.
Doctor Deighton's home.
Ah, thank goodness. The rumors of a doctor
starting a practice in the area were true.
The sign points over there.
Hmm?
G'day!
May I help you with something?
Ah... Young miss, is there any doctor around here?
Yes, there is one.
But inside here...
Ah! This boy is sick, isn't he?
Indeed he is. That's why we need the doctor...
Right now, he went to our neighbor's, Mrs. Mac's house.
He has a patient there.
Which means he'll be back in no time, right?
I suppose...
Hm?
I'll go invite him here for you.
Good. You'd help us a great deal if you do.
I can do it, no problem.
Feel free to rest here while you wait, sir.
Sorry to trouble you...
I'm gonna go to Mrs. Mac's for a minute.
And you stay here
without roaming around, will you?
I'm going now!
Darling, he'll be alright, won't he?
Consider him safe already.
The doctor will see him in no time.
Oh dear, but this fever is terrible.
My bag! Bag!
I have it here, doctor.
Eh? Hic... Aye, much obliged, lil' miss...
The patient is a little boy
about the same age as our Tob.
His dad and mom seem morbidly worried.
Please hurry up to examine him.
I got it, I got it.
Let's rush there if so!
Eh? Hey, I can't run.
Nah... Out of question. Look! I'm trying.
There, there, there...
Ouch!
Doctor Deighton,
are you all right?
Yeah... My bad, my bad.
I just tripped over a tree root.
I'll do alright this time.
Oh...
Ah! Doctor!
Nah... I'm good, I'm good.
Yeah, can go now. Let's race!
Like this! Like this. Like like like this...
Doctor, let's just walk slowly for now.
Ah? Eh?
Ah, guess you're right.
If we walk, it shouldn't take that long.
Why did you need to get so drunk, Doc?
Well I never thought I may have another patient
coming to me as soon as today.
Ah!
What's wrong?
I forgot.
What?
The bag.
Didn't I tell you just now that I have it?
Oh?
My, that's good. Good, good, very good.
G'day, ma'am.
Where's that poor fellow feeling unwell?
Doctor...
Hm?
Whoops. Howdy.
Where's the sick man?
Doctor, it's this child.
Aye, aye, you go lay him right there.
Let's see. Need you to step aside a bit.
Ah... Of course.
Right. I can't cure him by just looking.
I beg your pardon.
Hmm.
Oh? That looks pretty constipated to me.
Gotta give him an enema now.
Glycerin, glycerin...
Doctor, your bag is over here.
Huh? Yes, I know.
Let's see, here we got...
What's this thing?
Uh...
Doctor, can you come out for a moment?
Sure, but right now I'm examining this kid, you see.
I know you do! That's exactly why
I want you to come here for a moment.
Eh? My, my, what could be the meaning of this?
So what in the world was it
that you wanted, ma'am?
Please shut your eyes for a moment.
I'll try to alleviate your intoxication now.
Eh? No, I appreciate the offer, but what're you...
Shut your eyes, please.
Okay.
Whoa! That's cold!
Ma'am, what was that for?
If that didn't help, I can do one more.
No-no-no! I'm sober enough already. Really sober!
That kid is about the same age as our Tob.
Doctor, please do whatever it takes to help him.
Okay. Got it, I'll make every effort. That's a promise.
Doctor...
Yeah, nothing to worry about.
I'm no longer drunk.
Now, first things first.
Yes, this constipation in the bowels
is unmistakable.
I'll start with an enema.
Is Doctor Deighton managing it well?
Yes, it's all well.
Mom really surprised us when she doused
Doctor Deighton with water.
But if she hadn't done it,
Doctor would probably still be dead drunk.
Very soon, the sick boy also got better.
Mr. Pettywell's black dog
got one of our baby goats.
You can't die! No way you die!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A Tragic Incident".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you