South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 35 - Showdown
What? They're detonating it so close to here?
Yeah.
Hm?
It's a landslide.
Huh? What?
Hey! Get out of there, everyone!
There's a landslide!
Everyone escape!
A wall of rock is coming your way!
Ah! Run!
A word came out that a major landslide occurred
at the Mount Lofty quarry.
That's where our dad was working.
Mom, you should calm down a bit.
I am calm enough as it is.
You wouldn't be pacing back and forth
if that was so.
You're right. I just can't help
roaming through the room without realizing it.
I'm sure dad is fine.
When John returns with more news,
we'll know for sure where dad is.
Oh dear Lord, I just beg you
to keep that man safe.
Little also can't stop pacing through the garden.
Usually, he'd be sleeping in his doghouse by now.
He must also be worried.
Huh?
Well, everyone in the house
is restless because of dad, you know.
So you think Little can feel that, too?
Don't forget how smart Little is.
I hope dad is alright.
Of course he is!
I can't even fathom
something bad happening to dad.
So he's safe, right?
Yes. Must be safe.
Aren't you sleepy, Kate?
I'll stay awake for a little longer.
But you have a school tomorrow,
so better go to sleep.
I don't feel like sleeping at all.
Ah!
What's the matter?
Little dashed towards the street!
Oh? Little, what is it?
I see. You're also worried about Mr. Popple?
So, you couldn't find out if dad is alright or not?
Yeah. They had to evacuate
five or six men with the most serious injuries.
But thankfully, Mr. Popple wasn't among them.
Then, there were seemingly multiple people
with light injuries still on the site.
But I couldn't determine
exactly how severe their injuries were.
And why didn't they evacuate the rest of them?
It's not like they can do any quarrying this way.
Unfortunately, they only have three carriages there,
so they can't evacuate everyone.
In that case, I want to find a carriage
and go to the quarry myself right now!
I can't wait to know if dad is alright.
Me too.
And me!
Wait a moment, you all.
The road to the quarry is narrow.
There wouldn't be enough space for carriages heading there and returning carriages to pass by each other.
The road is still closed?
Yeah, probably. But I think
they'll let you pass in the morning.
Then, I'm going to the quarry
first thing in the morning tomorrow.
At a time like this, I can't wait even a second more!
Excuse me, but do you have a carriage?
Maybe a wagon or an oxcart?
Obviously, we'll have to borrow one...
Whom from?
Let's see... Who could lend their cart to us now...
The closest one is Mr. Pettywell's.
Moreover, he has a fleet-footed carriage.
Did you say Mr. Pettywell?
Mr. Pettywell...
At a time like this, should it come from Mr. Pettywell or whoever else, I wouldn't look down on any carriage!
But him, of all people...
Then, you've got anyone else on your mind,
willing to lend it to us?!
Mr. Parker has a cart as well.
But that man is living at the port.
Then, Ben could borrow
one of the carriage from the port customs!
You silly, Ben is also at the port.
So we've no choice, huh?
In that case, I'll go try
to implore with Mr. Pettywell.
But will he really be willing to lend it to you?
If I explain our circumstances,
I'm sure he'll be cooperative.
Then, would you please go with mom
to the quarry tomorrow?
Okay.
That was rude of you.
John has work tomorrow, you know.
Ah, but isn't it your day off?
About that...
I've driven a horse-drawn carriage
many times before.
John, please.
Okay. Got it.
I'll go with your mother.
I still feel bad, doing that...
Don't. It's like I'm almost a member
of the Popple family already anyway.
Therefore, Mr. Popple's... No, father's condition
concerns me just as much as everyone else.
I'll go.
Thank you, John.
And you two should long be in bed!
Okay.
Mom, I'll skip the school tomorrow.
Why?
When I'm that much worried about dad,
I can't do any studying!
Not happening.
But come on...
Leave it to me to take care about father.
Instead, better put your mind
to studying as hard as you can.
But...
Come on, go to bed now.
You're going to school as usual.
I'm off!
I'm going to school, Little.
Wait here, okay?
I'll try to return as soon as I can.
Good morning, Little.
Lucy went to school, didn't she?
Good morning.
Good morning. Glad to see you're here.
How did it go?
Did Mr. Pettywell let you borrow his cart?
We were just about to go there now.
In that case, I'm coming along.
It doesn't bite, right?
We should be fine if we stand still.
Yes. If we stand still.
But man, for how long will he keep us waiting?
Really, that's very rude.
Thank you for your patience.
I apologize for the inconvenience, but Master is still resting, therefore he cannot receive you right now.
We could come a little later, if so.
Ah... No, that really wouldn't be necessary.
Why?
Well... You see...
It's quite possible that Master
would still be resting even then, therefore...
Are you sure you explained
exhaustively to Mr. Pettywell
why Mrs. Popple desperately needs
that carriage right now?
Yes, that too...
Ah... I mean, no.
As I said, Master is still sleeping.
Ah, so that's what it's all about?
We get it. You don't want to lie to us.
Mother, let's return.
Right...
Hey! Can't you do something about that dog?
No. It doesn't listen to me either.
He looks inclined to bite!
Hey, Silver!
Move out of the way!
Okay, please go now.
You're one troublesome guy.
Damn that Mr. Pettywell.
What do we do now, mom?
There must be a cart we could lend somewhere.
But where could it be?
I'll try asking from everyone I know.
Ah! I'm coming along.
Sorry for the trouble, John.
Sister.
Hm?
Did dad die?
What are you saying?
Why'd you possibly ask if he is dead or not?
Well, because nobody wants to tell me openly...
Ah, that's true.
You see, there's been an accident
on a quarry where dad works.
And so, everyone's worried
about whether or not dad had been injured.
So he's injured?
No. We can't know for sure yet.
That's why mom prepares to go to the quarry herself
to check on dad's health.
Ah, I see.
Then, dad is well, after all?
You can't properly understand
even one bit of it.
How did it go? Did you manage
to borrow a carriage, mom?
When we came to ask for it,
Mr. Pettywell's servant told us he is still sleeping.
I knew it.
But then, where are Clara and John?
Maybe if we'd come to Mr. Bernard's office,
he could give us some advise?
Yeah...
A well-connected man such as him
would definitely know someone.
But... What if he went out
on a surveying mission in the hinterland again?
I hope he's in the office.
And now, does anyone here
have an answer to this question?
Yes!
Lucy-May.
Yes?
Answer the question I just asked.
What's wrong, Lucy-May Popple?
I don't know it.
What?
What was the question you just asked -
I don't know it.
So you weren't listening again?!
Yes...
Idiot! Stand by the wall!
Okay.
Is that clear? Everyone else
needs to stay concentrated, too.
During the class, you always listen carefully
to what teacher says.
Looking to the sides, or thinking about other things,
as well as talking to the others is unacceptable!
Is that clear?
Yes.
Lucy, you understand too?
Then, answer this new question, Lucy!
Okay.
Uhm... Well...
Uhm... So...
What's wrong, teacher?
I digressed to tell you off
and forgot what it was about!
Tell me, everyone, what was I
asking you just a moment ago?
Is there anyone else we could ask?
Not that I know of...
If only Mr. Bernard was here,
he'd think of something!
At any rate, let's be on our way.
Sorry for bothering you.
How did it go?
Not happening. They need it for work.
I see.
But I know of one more person with an oxcart!
Let's head there at once.
Okay. It's a little far, though. This way.
You don't suppose
they'll let us borrow that carriage?
Your mom is probably beside herself back at home.
I suppose.
We'll find where to borrow it.
Right. Let's hurry up with it.
Hey! Clara!
Someone called you.
Huh?
Clara!
Hey! Here! I'm here!
What are you doing all the way out here?
Are you two going somewhere?
Father!
Dad, leg hurts?
Yes. Just a bit, though.
You know I was worried?
Oh really? Seemed to me like you
didn't even understand what's happening.
Thanks, Tob.
Alright, let's have some tea.
Mother, I'm going to the store.
All right. Make sure to apologize to Mrs. Mac!
Well then, I'll have my leave too.
Ah, John. I'm really sorry
for all the trouble you had to go through.
No need.
What's more important, Mr. Popple, don't you think
you should see a doctor about your leg?
What for? It's nothing serious.
I just twisted my ankle
while helping to carry the wounded.
But it hurts, right?
Well, when I sit like that, it's perfectly fine.
John, you want to go together?
Yes. Well, Mr. Popple, take care.
Thank you for everything, John.
It's nothing.
John is exaggerating.
It's really nothing more than a twisted ankle.
Ouch!
See? Maybe the bone is fractured, after all?
I was naturally shocked when you
entered this room limping so much.
Nonsense! It'll heal in no time.
I'm not supposed to worry
since it's not even my leg, but still...
Hey, dad, you won't go to work
at the quarry ever again, right?
I will go. But that quarry
will be shut down for some while.
They're afraid there'd be another landslide.
I don't want you to go to the quarry anymore!
Well if there was any other good job for me,
I wouldn't be going to the quarry.
I guess no other job
fits you quite like farming. Right, dad?
Honey, I'll go get a bit of sleep now.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night,
having to look after the injured.
You're right. It's best that you go to sleep now.
Okay.
Ouch!
Darling!
Now that's mighty strange.
I'm back, Little.
Were you behaving well?
Lucy, did I make you worry?
How could you tell it's me with your eyes closed?
That's easy to tell. Although the school
ended pretty early today, it seems.
The teacher wasn't feeling too well.
That's worrying.
What about your leg?
I was worried.
Hm. Hurts a little, but that's it.
I'll take Kate along
and we'll go fetch Dr. Deighton for you.
Sorry for the trouble, Lucy.
I'm glad it's just a leg.
Still, he wasn't in the way of falling stones,
but hurt his leg later, while helping transport
the wounded, which strikes me as careless, somehow.
Can't say it's the same for me.
If anything, it's proof dad was working
like mad for people he barely knew.
Right, Little? Don't you agree?
Ah!
We can't rest now!
Sister, look over there!
A smoke!
You think there's a fire?
It can't be...
And it's coming exactly
from where Doctor Deighton lives!
Doctor Deighton lives in a brick house,
which can't catch fire.
But our former house is made of wood!
No way! You think it's that cabin that's burning?
Let me go! Let go or you'll regret it!
Stop resisting, Doctor.
Enough already, let him go now.
This Doctor can't hope to put out that fire on his own.
That's also true. There!
Damn you...
Doctor!
Oh? It's you two!
Doctor, what has happened?
These bandits set fire to the shack!
So it's an arson?
Young ladies, do we look like arsonists to you?
But Doctor said...
The owner of this building gave us
an explicit order to burn the shack down.
This is not the same as arson! No, sir!
The owner of this building...
It's Pettywell, Kate.
Yeah, I know!
Next, they'll put fire to my house as well!
No, no, Doctor. That house
would be a pain to set ablaze.
For that house, we'll bring a huge hammer
to tear it down nice and easy!
So you already have plans
to come for my house too?
Those were the direct orders
we've received from Mr. Pettywell.
Well, it'd be better if you moved out
of that house by then, Doctor.
I'm not going anywhere!
This house was built with blood and sweat
of those girls' father and brother!
And it's the best one I've ever lived in!
Too bad the land now belongs to Mr. Pettywell!
But the building is mine!
The shack is collapsing!
Ah, beautiful!
What the... What are you saying, Lucy-May?
I'm sorry.
This house holds countless memories from the first two years we spent in it after coming to Southern Australia!
So it's heartbreaking
to see it turned into ashes like that!
And yet, you seem to enjoy it,
saying "how beautiful!"
I'm sorry.
By the way, what brings you two here today?
Ah... Doctor, we need you to come with us.
Father injured his leg.
Oh? Really? That's a no-go?
So, is the injury very bad?
We don't know.
But the pain is evidently so bad,
even our enduring dad agreed to us fetching you.
Alright, I'll go there right away.
Just let me grab my bag.
What's wrong, Little?
That's Mr. Pettywell's carriage.
I really don't want to see him now!
Let's tell him all we think
about him letting the house ablaze!
All right'o...
Right, good job, gentlemen.
You can see for yourself.
Oh, it burns really well.
Huh? What's wrong, Silver?
Well, well, if it isn't daughters of that Popple?
You went to the trouble
of coming here to watch the house burn?
Wait, that doesn't seem right. You weren't
supposed to know I'm going to burn this shack.
Hey, Silver!
If need be, feel free to bite him to death, will you?
Lucy, you're not gonna tell Little to stop?
Now, that bulldog too...
No way! You have to stop him.
Hey.
Yeah, we're in for quite a show!
Oh?
Mr. Pettywell, a man like you...
To be perfectly frank, back then,
even I myself wanted to order him to do just that -
tear that bulldog to shreds there and then!
Back off, Little!
Inside a bird nest I spotted by chance,
I found some money!
Though it was just five shillings,
they came in really handy.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Five Shillings in the Nest".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you