South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 09 - The Road to Adelaide
Go! Go! Down!
Here you go. Behave yourself!
Uh... Hey! Hey!
Need your help!
Got it!
Well done!
He's got it!
And down!
All right, good.
I wonder how many more people have come
on that ship that arrived yesterday.
It's a very big ship, so it can probably carry
up to 100 passengers on board.
Someone else would probably be living here,
on our spot, in no time.
I think so too.
Anyone needs help over there?
No, all is good here.
Besides, Ben is apparently coming late.
I suppose the cart's owner
hadn't quite sobered up yet.
Last night, you could say he was blind drunk.
Do we really have to trust someone so unreliable
with transporting our precious furniture?
Well, we're not trusting Mr. Bard to do it all by himself.
The three of us will be accompanying him.
Mr. Bard, this way.
Like that! Keep walking, you slacker!
We're almost there.
Much obliged for what you did.
After all, the soil here is sandy and soft,
so my cart's wheels are prone to sinking.
I thought so.
Ah! Good morning, Mr. Jamling!
Good morning, Ben. Aren't you glad
you'll be going to Adelaide under a fine weather?
Yes. Is your leg doing better today?
Thank you for asking.
It's the same as yesterday, still hurts.
Please take care, then.
Bye.
Yeah.
I hope that ox would still be able to move,
once all their luggage is loaded.
Dad, what are you mumbling about?
Oh... You know the Popples
are moving to Adelaide today, don't you?
I hope you don't feel too lonely without them.
Well, ain't we also going to Adelaide soon?
Yes. As soon as this bloody leg recovers, we do.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
We were wrong! On that raft,
it's not people they're bringing. It's sheep! Sheep.
Wow! So many sheep,
and they all came from England?
Now that we can keep sheep in Australia,
it's bound to become a mighty fancy place!
You think that ship could've
brought here oxen and horses, too?
There's no way I would know that.
If we'd have enough oxen and horses here,
transporting our luggage would be a cakewalk!
And dad could live in our prefabricated home,
instead of selling it.
But isn't it nice that instead of a prefabricated home,
he bought us another house in Adelaide?
Didn't you hear what Ben said?
He wouldn't exactly call it a house, even.
"Shack" seems like way more fitting a word.
So we'll be sleeping in a shack
when we get to Adelaide?
There's no telling if we'll even be able to sleep in it.
Why so?
Apparently, that shack has no more than two rooms.
Only two?
Which means, the two of us
will keep sleeping in a barrel, right?
I hope it would at least be a decent barrel.
Heave-ho!
Kate! Whatcha people doin' all the way out here?
We wanted to watch them
unload the sheep from the ship!
Oh, that's right. Folks from your family
have been looking for you.
Oh?
It seems, they're done
loading the luggage onto the cart.
Lucy-May, we need to return quickly! Quickly!
Ah! Sister, wait!
And like this! Looks good.
Ben stays behind for now.
We don't want to leave our things unattended.
I see. Well, I have to travel
back and forth a lot, you see.
so there's no way I could look after your furniture all day long.
You understand?
Once we hire another cart in Adelaide,
we'll come back for this furniture.
Okay.
We'll try to find a cart as soon as possible,
however, I can't tell if it won't take us up to a week.
It ain't easy to find a cart these days!
Even I myself will have to switch
to working without day-offs, starting tomorrow.
Ah, I'm so fed up with it!
Maybe you'll be able to find a wagon around here.
Like, if they decide to send something here
from Adelaide, and the cart would be returning empty.
In that case, Mr. Parker, I'd like to ask you
to help Ben with loading this.
I'll be sure to compensate you
for all the trouble.
Sure, will do just that.
Which reminds me, Ben,
where are you going to sleep?
In this barrel, I suppose.
I don't mind you coming to my tent to sleep.
That tent is obviously too spacious for me alone.
Thank you. Although I feel bad,
asking you for so much.
It's nothing. These new lands necessitate
increased responsiveness towards one another.
That's what I thought.
In any case, I entrust Ben
and this luggage into your care.
Sure.
But now, it's time to hit the road.
Yes.
Where's Kate and Lucy-May?
Ah. They've just returned!
Oh, that's right. The ship that brought us all here
will be returning to England today.
I thought so. Probably, only to return here
some half a year later, carrying even more immigrants.
So it would seem.
That's why John didn't come to see us off?
Yes.
And I was already considering
leaving you two here.
No way!
Come on! Keep walking, you slacker!
The ship that came yesterday
brought over a whole lotta sheep!
The shore was filled completely with just sheep!
You're exaggerating.
It's the truth! Right, Lucy-May?
I felt so bad for the sheep that fell into the sea.
Its fur was soaking up the water rapidly
and I thought it'd drown.
Now that I think of it, wasn't there a shepherd with sheep near Adelaide, too, dad?
Yes. Ah, Ben, you should return now.
If we walk together just a little more...
No, up to here is enough.
Mr. Bard! A quick stop, please!
Whoa!
Well, I'm counting on you.
Okay.
We'll try to come pick up
the rest of our stuff as soon as we can.
Okay.
Mrs. Jamling promised
to share their bread with you.
I remember.
Good, but we have to go now.
Mr. Bard!
Got it.
That's it! We're leaving, you slacker!
Go!
Take care, Ben.
Goodbye, brother.
And you two, walk straight all the way to Adelaide.
We'll be fine.
Make sure to go to the shore
to see the sheep, brother!
I'll go see them!
And you walk straight, remember?
I will!
Good! Keep going, you slacker! There!
Go!
Now...
John's ship is still here, it seems.
Yes.
Clara! Do what I told you last night
and go ahead, with those two in tow.
Okay.
It's a shame you didn't get to see John once more.
I saw him yesterday.
Now, Kate and Lucy-May,
we three need to go ahead.
Okay!
Oh, wait for me, you two!
Lucy-May, you need to walk faster.
If you can't keep up,
we'll have to leave you behind.
You're mean.
Lucy-May! Walk faster!
Lucy-May!
What's wrong, Lucy-May?
Kate, did you notice?
A mighty strange lizard right here!
A lizard? I'm not very fond of lizards, you know.
But this one is nothing like what I've seen before!
You should come see it too!
Oh my. And which way is his head?
We'll know when it moves.
Really strange!
Told you! A mighty funny thing!
You're right, it's very funny.
Grrr...
Ah.
Sorry, Kate.
Well, let's go now.
Okay.
Let's not make any more detours than that, Lucy-may.
I don't know about that.
Hmm?
All right, doctor, we've here.
Ah?
Oh, yes.
Well.
Down I go.
John.
Hey, Ben. Glad to see you.
This means your family hadn't left yet, had it?
No, I'm the only one left behind.
Everyone else left for Adelaide.
Eh? Had it been long already?
No, not particularly long...
Hey, John, I'm going on ahead
to Mr. Jamling's place.
Sure. Just one thing, doctor.
Make sure to come back in an hour, alright?
If you do it leisurely, in your usual manner,
the ship will leave without you!
He-he. Examining Mr. Jamling's leg
cannot possibly take an hour.
Oh... Speaking of which,
which way is Mr. Jamling's tent here, kids?
He's hopeless.
Oh, I know. Ben, could you
accompany doctor while you're at it?
Sure. But doctor seems mighty drunk.
Yeah, like always.
Well, I'm counting on you.
What about you?
I'll go see Clara.
O-ooops.
My goodness...
Like that! Don't stop walking, you slacker.
Move it!
Clara's group must already be far ahead, right?
Yes, however, she is with the little ones,
so I doubt they can walk very fast.
Probably.
Hmm?
Someone called you just now.
Huh?
Mr. Popple!
It's John!
His ship hadn't set sail yet?
I caught up with you sooner than I expected.
I heard your ship is about to depart.
Yes.
It is.
But I still have a little more time until then.
And... Where is Clara?
Clara went ahead.
Huh? Ahead?
Yes. With Kate and Lucy-May in tow,
we sent her ahead.
The cart cannot go faster than that.
Sorry, but... was it long ago?
I don't remember for certain,
but I don't think they're that terribly far yet.
I'll go, too.
Eh? But do you really have the time for that?
I still have about 40 minutes.
Just 40 minutes, huh?
In either case, I'll try to catch up. Excuse me!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch.
Hurts terribly there, doctor.
Hmm.
The recovery is slower than I anticipated.
Could it be that there's a bone fracture, after all?
It can't be, doc!
Didn't you tell me it's a mere sprain the other day?
But in that case, the swelling
would've receded already.
Does it hurt here?
Ouch! Doctor! Have you decided to kill me today?
W-wait, what's that?
Whiskey, sir. Helps numb the pain.
Unacceptable! Totally unacceptable!
What do you mean?
Drinking things like whiskey
would only do more harm to your leg.
Is that so?
But when drinking this,
I can at least forget about the throbbing pain.
No way! It would only hurt more from drinking whiskey.
Let me have that for a moment. Come on.
Huh?
I said lend me this booze bottle!
But doctor...
Now, don't say more. Don't.
I see now.
Huh?
You can't drink that. It's a bit too tasty!
Eh... This stuff is good.
No way you can drink something like that.
Those guys sure have loaded
a ton and a little extra onto their cart.
They're lucky to have managed
to hire two oxcarts at once.
Must be someone with very deep pockets.
Isn't it Mr. Pettywell over there?
Huh?
Oh, and that looks like Mr. Pettywell's wife,
always in her ritzy feather hat.
And it's their servants,
who are pushing the carts from behind.
But then, sis, in this mountain of stuff, loaded onto two carts, there must be our prefabricated home, too?
It's not exactly "ours" anymore.
After all, dad couldn't help
but to sell it to Mr. Pettywell.
I bet the prefabricated home is loaded
onto the right cart.
It's loaded onto the left one as well.
One cart can't hold all of it.
They stopped!
Didn't you hear what I said? You!
They're quarreling over something.
Let's get closer to find out!
You shouldn't be running!
I won't tolerate any back talk
from just some handymen for hire!
But sir, you're asking for impossible!
Going any faster than that
is totally, decisively, impossible!
I just want to get to Adelaide sooner! That's exactly
why I paid you more than double the usual fee!
Hey, you two! You'd better do as master says, now!
We can't do that.
Especially when we're so ridiculously overburdened!
If we speed up any more than that,
the ox would drop dead!
I couldn't care less if the ox dies.
Oh my! How cruel!
If the ox dies, who'll be transporting your things?
Why am I supposed to think of that?
All I want is just for you rascals to transport
my prefabricated home and furniture already!
And we're doing just that!
Do it faster!
He's being a lunatic again. Let's go now.
If you rascals don't start going faster than that,
I'll have you return half of the money to me!
Right! You'll return half of it!
Want half of it back?
How are you better than a simple thief, then?
What? Thief? When did I ever do any thievery?!
Mr. Pettywell sure is capricious, isn't he?
That, too, but...
He just thinks the power of money
can get him anything.
He sure does!
Like he got our prefabricated home!
I told you, it's not "ours" anymore.
They're throwing fists now!
Apologize, I said!
When did I do any thievery?
Apologize to the master, you!
Let go of me!
Damn it!
My, to think they call themselves grown-ups...
Mr. Pettywell just punched him!
Ah! Now he's been punched back!
He's overwhelmed!
Just what's gotten into those people?
Well, let's go now.
Take this!
Sure, sure!
Swindler!
How dare you punch me?
I'm not letting is slide now!
I'm hungry.
It's too soon for that.
Hey, sis, why don't we just eat our lunch?
We're still not even halfway there.
But I'm very hungry already!
For a moment, hush, you two.
What's wrong, sis?
It's as though somebody
was calling out my name just now.
In the middle of this forest?
Perhaps I just imagined it.
Must be it.
Let's go now.
Huh?
They're calling.
Right? You heard it too?
Was it John?
Huh? What's wrong, sister?
John is calling me.
To where?
The ship's supposed to set sail today.
He came to see me before leaving.
John!
Clara!
It really was John all along, sis!
Oh my! John!
Clara!
Why don't we leave them alone for a bit?
Looks like a sound thing to do.
Let's go.
John!
Made it...
And I thought we'd never meet again.
We did...
Do you still have time?
No!
But...
No time at all!
It can't be...
I just wanted to see you one last time...
I'm so glad I got to see you.
And on that, goodbye!
John...
Goodbye, and wait for me.
I will definitely come again!
I'll be waiting!
Bye, John!
Did you get to see her, John?
I saw her!
And take care, you two!
You take care, too!
He took the trouble to come,
even knowing he's out of time.
So it would seem.
Dr. Deighton!
Hmm?
If you're looking for Dr. Deighton,
he returned a while ago.
With my whiskey under his arm.
Thank you.
Dr. Deighton!
Sister was glowing with happiness
from that unexpected encounter with John.
Actually, it even charged me and Lucy-May with delight,
making our gait much lighter.
Once we're out of the woods, we're in Adelaide.
By mistake, we walked the wrong road
on our way to Adelaide.
Some animal was chasing us three
all the way through the forest.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The City of Greenery".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you