South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep 40 - Who Am I?
A runaway horse!
A runaway horse here!
Hmm?
A runaway horse!
Run away! Run!
Whoa!
Dodge it to the right! Right!
Hey! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What is it? Something happened?
A runaway horse!
A runaway horse is coming this way!
A runaway horse?
Hey! It's heading towards the city!
Someone, stop it! It's dangerous!
Ah, that was dangerous.
Master, I apologize for the inconvenience.
No, it'd be more of a trouble if it hit us.
Ah, that's true. Oh!
What is it, Max?
A child lying on the ground, Master!
Huh?
Where?
Look, over there.
Did runaway horse do it to her?
That... I don't know.
Little miss.
Oh! Blood!
Now...
Sir, it wasn't my carriage that hit her.
She's unconscious.
We gotta let the doctor see her quick.
Hurry!
Um... Which way?
Return to the mansion. I know a doctor near there.
Now hurry up! What are you doing?
Y-Yes.
Giddyup!
Little miss...
Look, Snowflake is no longer here. We sold her!
Can't you understand what I say?
Ah, but he'd probably understand if Lucy said it.
Snowflake is no longer here,
can't you understand that?
Right. Did you finally understand?
Mom, I feel sorry for Little. He can't get
a peace of mind, constantly looking for Snowflake.
Wasn't it adorable how Little and Snowflake,
a dingo and a sheep were getting along so well?
Lucy hadn't yet returned either?
She dashed out in tears, hoping to stop Arthur
from selling Snowflake.
Even though she knows it's a lost cause...
It was a really bad thing we did to Lucy.
No matter how destitute we are,
we shouldn't have sold that sheep.
I'm home!
Dad returned.
Welcome back.
Welcome back!
Hey, don't be too startled.
That sheep went for three pounds at the auction!
Oh my, three pounds?
Yes, I was surprised too. It seemed as though
they'd stop at two pounds, but here I am with three!
Aren't you glad?
With this, we can make ends meet for now.
Ah, I also got 12 shillings for the old clothes.
Um... Haven't you seen Lucy, dad?
Lucy?
Seems like she went to the auction grounds.
No, I haven't seen her.
Only found Tob in front of the blacksmith's shop.
She hadn't returned yet? Lucy-May.
Sorry for the wait.
It's okay.
Is your family really in such a tight spot money-wise?
I think we'll stay afloat for the time being
after we sell the sheep and the clothing.
Plus, if dad starts working again,
we'll pull through somehow.
Oh, by the way...
What is it?
Today, I've been to Northern Adelaide for work.
So on my way back,
I saw Lucy there, a little while ago.
Oh?
I think it wasn't that far from the Adelaide Bridge.
Seeing her walk to Northern Adelaide,
the opposite way from home, I called to her.
Lucy was there alone?
Yes. And it seems she ignored me completely.
Though she turned her face to me,
it was as though she was looking at a complete stranger.
I wonder why Lucy was heading to Northern Adelaide?
I'm quite certain it was Lucy, alright.
This sounds very strange, somehow.
Sylvia, Doctor Jones is finally here.
Doctor, please examine this child sooner.
She's been unconscious for a while now.
She's still breathing, right?
Yes.
Hmm...
Yes, she'll be alright.
Just lost consciousness upon impact.
First, I'll tend to her hand.
Why are you pacing the room back and forth?
Hm?
Just feel like walking a bit.
Are you hungry, Tob?
No.
Back at it...
Hey, Clara hasn't returned yet?
Oh my. Did you forget, Darling?
Eh?
Clara went to a dance party with John.
A dance party?
At the commerce chamber.
But aren't you worried
more about Lucy, than about Clara?
Lucy?
By Jove, where does that girl
loiter around until so late?
Who knows...
I bet, her pride just won't let her come home.
She's probably hanging around nearby.
You still didn't give up hope, Little?
But that's true.
Snowflake is no longer here.
Lucy is also yet to return.
I wonder what she's up to?
Okay...
Here.
Doctor, isn't it about time
she regained consciousness already?
You're right.
Isn't there any way to help her wake up sooner?
No, I can't do the impossible.
But she should come to her senses before long.
Doctor, would you please stay until then?
Yes, sure thing.
In that case, Doctor,
may I offer you some tea downstairs?
Sure.
I'll stay here.
Good. I'll arrange some tea to here too.
Such a cute girl...
Here.
Thanks.
Bring some tea for my wife too.
Will do.
If you excuse me this remark,
your wife allots so much of her concern to the girl,
it's almost as if it was her own child.
Yes.
Yes, it's not an easy thing to do,
especially for a child you're seeing for the first time.
We had...
A baby before, but we lost her.
Oh...
It was a girl.
After that, we've never been blessed
with any more children.
If that child was still alive, she'd be exactly
the same age as that girl sleeping upstairs.
I see. So that's what happened?
My wife always wanted to have a child.
Emily...
Emily.
Ah!
Are you awake?
Ah, dear God, please...
The parents must've already started looking
for that girl, don't you think?
I suppose.
Since it's past the nightfall,
they must certainly be worried.
Once she regains consciousness,
we'll be able to contact her parents.
Yes. As soon as she tells us her name
and where she lives,
I'll send a servant there at once to let them know.
Now then, how about I check
on her condition once more?
She's supposed to already be awake by now.
I suppose.
Two hours have passed since the accident.
Huh? That much time already?
Do you think we shouldn't have brought her here?
No, I certainly can't say that.
Come in.
How is she?
Hasn't opened her eyes yet.
Let's see...
Nothing seems to be out of ordinary.
If she doesn't recover her consciousness soon...
Doctor?
What's the matter?
Her eyes just moved.
Is that so?
Look, again!
Oh! They moved indeed.
Thank goodness.
The face color is also healthy again.
Yes. She'll be fine now.
Little miss, do you understand what we're saying?
You don't have to worry about a single thing.
I saw you lying on the ground,
so I carried you to our house.
She seem scared, somehow.
Her new circumstances need a bit more time to sink in.
Listen, this place is our house.
Of course, we ought to introduce ourselves first.
I'm Frank Princeton.
And this here is my wife Sylvia.
And this gentleman is a doctor, Mr. Jones.
A doctor?
Nice to meet you.
That's right, a doctor.
Look, he applied a bandage to your left arm.
It must be that you got injured
while falling after getting hit by a carriage.
Do you remember?
How he tended to your left arm.
Little miss.
Did you understand what Madam just said?
Are you able to hear what I say?
Good. If you don't feel like talking, feel free not to.
Just answer to me by nodding.
Surely, you can see with your eyes right now?
Then, why don't you try to talk,
instead of just nodding?
You can talk, right?
Then, you don't know how to talk?
Come on, which one is it?
I just want to know your name
and where you live as soon as possible.
I'm sure, you father and mother can't are also
worried sick and keep looking for you all over the place.
Don't you want to bring them a relief sooner?
What's wrong?
Does it hurt somewhere?
So? Is this position more comfortable?
Yes.
Oh! Well now, you can talk, after all.
Then, what are your name and address?
That's troublesome...
If you just tell us your name and address,
that'd be enough.
I...
Yes?
I... Don't know.
Don't know... You mean, what, your address?
My... My name.
Huh?
Little miss, did you forget your own name?
I wonder... I wonder who I am, even.
I don't know anything about who I am.
The place where I usually live...
I don't know that either!
What about your father's name?
Or mother's?
I don't know. I don't know!
Oh my, poor child.
Do you remember when you came to Adelaide?
Adelaide?
Adelaide is the name of this city.
It seems, she'd forgotten everything that happened up to this point due to being unconscious for so long.
But don't despair, you'll get
your memory back in some while.
Who... Who in the world am I?
Oh my.
I don't know. I don't know...
I'll go look for Lucy.
Where will you look for her?
I'll start with the vicinity of the auction grounds.
Any other places Lucy would be likely to go to?
I don't know. But just sitting home
doing nothing is too unsettling.
Kate, it's already pitch dark outside.
I can do just fine even at night.
You should stay home.
But...
I'll go.
You'll go look for her, right?
Yes.
You selling Snowflake
must've come as a terrible shock to Lucy.
I know.
I'm sorry for selling your friend.
But we really couldn't help it.
So how about we go look for Lucy now?
I'm taking you with me.
Dad! Clara and John returned!
And John said he saw Lucy
walking in the direction of Northern Adelaide.
What did you say?
So... The place where I spotted Lucy
is a bit further ahead.
Hm.
Explain to me once again
what did Lucy look like at that time.
Let's see...
I was on the other side of the road, so I couldn't
exactly grasp what her expression was like.
Though I can tell for sure it wasn't cheerful.
She didn't even try to avoid other pedestrians
and bumped into everyone. That's what she was like.
And when I called to her,
you could say she ignored me entirely.
So she looked deep in thought?
Yes. But surely, it can't be that she was considering
taking her own life in such an age...
John!
Ah, I'm sorry. I let slip something horrible.
I suppose she came to the Adelaide Bridge.
Perhaps Lucy crossed this bridge
and went to Northern Adelaide?
Ah! It seems, Little just found some trace himself.
Yes.
Mr. Popple.
Lucy must've passed through here.
So it seems.
Oh?
It's raining.
Now this is troublesome.
I wonder why is Little barking so much here?
I don't know.
John, let's find a shelter somewhere.
Yes.
Little! Come!
Hey, Little! What's the matter? Come!
Terrible rain, isn't it?
Yes.
Is it delicious?
Very delicious!
I've never eaten something so delicious in my life.
Does that mean you remembered
what food you've eaten before?
It's hopeless. I still can't remember a thing!
Not a thing!
It's alright. Just eat and don't think about anything.
I'm sorry for talking so rashly.
Trying to restore my memory,
we circled the town in Mr. Princeton's carriage.
But I don't recognize anything I see.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Strange People in a Strange City".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you