South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 50 - Towards the Rainbow
Glad to see you here, Lucy.
You're having this day to yourself?
Yes.
Well, that's just great.
My wife would be delighted.
Is everyone doing well at home?
Mr. Princeton.
What is it?
Please...
Please make me your child!
Huh?
Please make me the daughter of your family!
Ah?
Make me... Make me your family's daughter!
Lucy?
Did Lucy come?
Where are you?
Oh my! Lucy, it's so good you came! Oh my!
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
Did something hurt you, Lucy?
The matter with Lucy...
Lucy came to tell us
that she wants to become our daughter.
Ah!
Is that true?
Is that true, Lucy?
Of course, Lucy.
You're welcome to live with us.
My! What's wrong, Lucy?
Come live with us, really!
Wait a moment, Sylvia.
What's the matter, dear?
Lucy came to tell us that she wants to become
the daughter of our family.
So?
I don't believe it.
I think Lucy is lying to us.
Huh?
It's not really a desire to become our children
that is driving Lucy.
No way...
Isn't that right, Lucy?
While having such wonderful
father and mother of her own,
There's no reason why she would
sincerely want to become our child.
But I sincerely...
Enough already, Lucy.
Don't force yourself to say that.
But tell me, why?
Why would Lucy say such a thing?
I don't understand it at all.
Right.
Tell me, I'm a little curious.
Your father and mother at home probably
don't know about you coming here, do they?
Yes. It was... It was my own idea.
Oh my, Lucy, don't cry.
I know there was some special reason for that.
Here, blow your nose.
Good, one more time.
Look, Lucy. Both me and Sylvia would be infinitely
happy to have you as our own child.
But, please understand, Lucy.
We gave up on that hope.
Darling, can you please explain,
why is Lucy saying that?
Well, you see...
When I visited the Popples' house the other day
to put forward an offer of us adopting Lucy
Lucy happened to be in the next room
and overheard everything.
As a matter of fact,
if you agree to us adopting Lucy,
I thought I should give you something in return,
like a piece of land in my possession.
Land?
That's right.
If I may, Mr. Popple, what is it
you currently covet the most?
Isn't it owning your own piece of land?
A land?
I thought you'd appreciate it if I hand over a part of the farm near Gawler that you agreed to work at.
Lucy, isn't that right?
Isn't it because only by becoming our daughter
you could fulfill your father's dream
of owning his own land?
Thoughts like that were what brought you here.
Oh my...
Please, Mr. Princeton! I'd really
rather stay here with you. In exchange...
Lucy.
I feel... I feel so sorry for my dad!
He had lost all hope.
He's no longer the dad he used to be.
Now he just drinks all the time.
Honey?
It took a while, didn't it?
Yes.
Sorry, I took one too much.
Mom's face screams exasperation.
What should we do, Kate?
Dad is no longer the dad he used to be.
Why can't he return to how he used to be?
You should understand that much yourself.
It's the land, right?
A vast, vast wheat field,
where dad, mom, and Ben, as well as John and Clara -
everyone is working together to harvest it.
We've had a bumper crop this year.
You, me, and even Tob are bundling
the harvested wheat together.
Everyone is working themselves into a sweat.
The work is hard, but also fun!
A grasshopper stops in front of Little's nose.
Little is awfully scared
and starts running around and howling!
Everyone laughs heartily at him!
But it's just a dream.
That's how we imagined things would be one day.
But we gave up on it now.
So I take refuge in seeing happy dreams, at least.
I understand exactly how you feel, Lucy.
I'm sorry for all the trouble...
You have nothing to apologize for.
It's us two who are at fault for even wanting
to separate you from such a loving family.
No matter how much we adore you, going there
and saying we want to adopt you was unacceptable.
Sylvia...
Darling, please escort Lucy home, will you?
Sure.
Remember, Lucy. You can't lose your hope.
No matter how hard it gets.
Okay.
Something good will happen to you.
It won't take too long.
Right? Isn't that right?
Hm?
Y-Yes...
Perhaps, it'll happen today already, dear?
Hm? Hm.
Well. Goodbye, Lucy.
I'm sure something good will happen to you, Lucy.
Ah!
What is it?
I'll get scolded if I come home now.
You'll be fine, since you didn't tell anyone
you were going to see me.
I'll explain well all the reasons.
That's not what I mean.
I'll be scolded for not going to school today.
Huh?
On my way to school, I split with my brother Tob
and went to see you.
Then we're in trouble.
Well, for today, you've no choice
but to let mom scold you.
Actually, I needed to have an important discussion with them, so it was fortunate that you showed up.
Seriously, what were you thinking?
Skipping the school and going to play around
at Mr. Princeton's house again!
Actually, Madam, Lucy didn't come to play around.
But then, what for?
As a matter of fact, she came to say
that she wants me to adopt her.
Ack!
Lucy, are you out of your mind?
Madam, I beg you not to scold Lucy for this one matter.
Still, joking about such things...
No, she meant it.
My. But then...
She tried to make it seem as if she meant it,
but deep inside, she knew it was a lie.
What I mean is, she wasn't sincere when saying she wants to become the daughter of our family,
but for some other reason.
Which is out of consideration
for the happiness of her family.
Honestly, I don't quite understand...
Ah! I know! So that's what this all is about.
What is it about, Kate?
Lucy wanted to present our family with the land.
Right. Exactly so.
That's what I deducted too.
After all, it was all too unbelievable that Lucy
would sincerely want to become our daughter.
Oh my, so that's what happened?
Really, I am so, so sorry.
We just keep giving you more trouble.
No, it was no trouble at all.
On the contrary, both me and my wife
were deeply moved by Lucy's dedication.
She wished for the collective happiness of the family
even at the cost of her own comfort.
Madam, I'd like you
to pass a certain message to your husband.
What is it?
There's a farm I own near the city of Gawler.
We know that.
Part of that farm's land is still waiting to be developed.
There's not much of it, but still.
That's what I'd like you to pass to your husband.
I'm determined to sell that land to Mr. Popple.
Because I want to see it with my own eyes -
him making a fresh start in life on his wonderful farm.
Well, Mr. Princeton...
I mean, I'm infinitely grateful for the offer.
And I'm sure my husband
would also be most delighted.
But well... Unfortunately, our family
is currently struggling with money.
So... We can't really afford also buying that land.
And so, um...
Madam, this land near Gawler also comes with a house.
If your whole family moves there,
you will no longer need this house, right?
Y-Yes, I suppose...
Sell this house to me. And then,
we'll call this house a down payment for the land.
As for the rest, it'd be all fine with me
if your husband helped out on my farm in his free time
and thus gradually worked off the cost of the land.
Mr. Princeton...
I hope to hear your husband's response tomorrow.
Go there! Marsh, go there!
Ah? He's back!
He's back! Dad is here!
Dad returned already?
He returned, alright!
Maybe he didn't stop by the bar today?
He's back early, so he probably didn't.
Can you imagine how dad will react?
Will be the happiest ever!
You dunce, saying it out loud is no fun!
Think he'll laugh?
I suppose. He'll probably laugh.
Lately, I don't ever hear
dad laughing sincerely and heartily.
I wanna be the one who tells him.
No way! Mom said she'll do it, remember?
But I can't wait to see dad's delighted face!
Welcome back!
Well now, dad looks mighty surprised already.
I'm home.
What's the matter?
All three went out to meet me.
You're back early today, dad.
Ah? Yes...
Then, something good will probably happen to you.
Something very good!
What could it be?
Did your mom prepare some delicious dinner today?
No, no! It's not food.
What else could it be?
Oh? Little, you know it too?
I see. So you do know?
Now, then... I really wonder what it is.
Dad!
Mr. Princeton said he's determined to sell it to you.
What is it? He knows perfectly well I'm penniless,
and still tries to sell me something?
It's the land, honey.
What did you say?
He wants you to buy some of his land in Gawler.
Come on. Can't you put two and two together?
We're as poor as a church mouse.
We have the money for that.
Where?
We can sell this house. And then use this money
as a down payment for the land and the house there.
But what's next?
How am I supposed to pay out the rest.
By working on Mr. Princeton's farm.
Of course, work on our own farm comes first,
but in the spare time you could help out on his farm.
And he'll count that money towards your debt.
We'll have plenty of helping hands.
John and Clara, Ben too -
he'll quit his job at the customs office
to live and work with us.
I'm not dreaming, right?
It's not a dream.
Will I finally get to own my own piece of land?
That's right. This time, nothing will stand in the way.
Mr. Princeton is the man you can put your trust in.
You guys all knew that, but kept silent?
See? Didn't we tell you
something very good will happen?
Yes. You were right.
All of this is happening to us thanks to Lucy.
Thank you, Lucy-May.
Don't you think Mr. Princeton
is the one you should be thanking?
Certainly. I'll do it tomorrow.
But really, aren't you glad, dad?
I'm glad.
And I'm so happy!
Happy...
I'm happy, with all my heart.
It feels really strange. Tears are coming out!
Dad.
Dad!
Thank you, Lucy-May.
Ah!
Dad, Little is following us again.
Why are you following us?
Didn't I tell you not to follow us
because it's such a long way to the Gawler farm?
Lucy, you can let him in. I don't mind.
Thank you.
You've grown increasingly disobedient these days!
Mr. Princeton took dad on a tour
through the land that's about to become his own.
He'll have to go on several more trips
before the whole family could move there.
But for the first one, only Lucy could accompany him.
Can you see three eucalyptus trees
all the way out there in the distance?
Your plot starts from this fence
and only ends there, Mr. Popple.
My plot...
That's right.
I look forward to seeing you make a fresh start here,
on wonderful farm of your own.
I can promise to you, it'll be gorgeous.
I see two small houses over there.
Is that where we'll be living?
That's right.
We could probably let John and Clara
live in the one that's smaller.
Yeah.
You wait for me here.
I'll go introduce myself to the others.
Okay.
So many sheep they're keeping here!
Little, what's wrong?
Ah!
You're not thinking of attacking these sheep, are you?
Little!
Wait!
Wait I said, Little!
Snowflake! You're Snowflake, right?
I see. So Snowflake was there?
I'll do what I can to buy her back for you, Little.
We finished packing the bags and were finally
about to depart, when it suddenly started raining.
Don't worry. It'll stop soon enough.
I'm sure it's a passing rain, honey.
Yeah. Even so, that's pretty unfortunate.
Our things would get all sodden.
Okay, setting out!
Setting out!
...To not let this flame die
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
We set out towards the land of hope.
On one autumn day, some four and a half years
after our arrival to Southern Australia.
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Mom, look, a rainbow!
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
You're right. It sure is pretty!
Seems like our destination
is exactly where that rainbow bridge starts!
The echoes bounce around in my chest
I suppose. One day, we'll cross
that rainbow bridge for sure.
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
The End
The Alps Story: My Annette
Because John stole the paper knife
that Lucien had made,
Annette gets into a big fight with the boys.
The new show: "The Alps Story: My Annette".
Episode one: "Annette and Lucien."
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you