South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 17 - A Tragic Incident
Like this!
Lucy-May, didn't I tell you before
that you can't leave Marsh's basket here?
But why?
Just now, some soil that I've plowed
flew this way and hit Marsh!
Oh my, poor thing.
Marsh, please get back inside the basket.
If you keep hanging around here,
my dear sister might plow you next!
Lucy-May, thanks for the initiative.
But this way of shoveling won't get you anywhere.
It'll be fine.
Look at how much we've plowed
while you were away over there!
It's still useless. We can't make it into a garden
unless you dig a bit deeper.
Now, let's switch.
You go look after Tob, instead.
Oh, I hate it when I have to babysit Tob.
Marsh! Marsh.
Lucy-May, this is no game.
I'm doing it because I want our field
to be ready sooner.
I understand that much...
Tob, I won't accept you bullying Marsh!
Marsh...
Kate, try to dig a bit deeper, will you?
Okay.
Because fresh vegetables
are so difficult to get in these parts,
we've decided to plant
a vegetable garden behind our house.
But because dad was so busy expanding the house,
me and mom ended up fulfilling the duty
of planting the garden.
Mr. Jamling, wouldn't you like to rest for a bit?
No. While we're at it, I'd rather finish this sooner
so as to lay the roof sooner.
I almost feel guilty...
You're barely taking any breaks.
That's because I want to be done with it
before they finish assembling Mr. Pettywell's house.
I appreciate your determination,
but that's a bit unrealistic.
After all, what they have there is a prefabricated home,
with a crowd of hired workers.
You think the competition is too uneven?
Ah, Ben. Please give me that plank.
Sure. This one?
Yeah, yeah.
Darn, they seem to be mostly done indeed.
While everyone is working with all their might,
I'm just spending my days away with a cup of tea here.
I'm truly sorry for being such a burden.
There's about one cup more of tea left.
Eh? Oh, thanks but no.
Maybe there's at least one thing I could go help with?
As a carpenter, I'm probably good for nothing.
But as for planting the garden...
A doctor doesn't really need
to do anything of that.
Yeah, but the thing is, I'm currently a doctor
without a single patient.
Moreover, I keep relying on this family's hospitality...
It starts to rip my heart apart.
My, "ripping your heart apart?"
You must've been brooding over it quite a lot.
But actually, both my parents were greatly pleased
by you staying at our place.
Naturally, I was glad as well.
How couldn't I? When living so close to a doctor,
you don't have to worry about anything.
Even so, I was sure this place
would have at least some folk who are sick.
It has.
It's just that those ill people don't know yet
that a doctor is waiting for them right here.
I put out a signboard.
Our neighbor Mr. Bernard
also posted a notice at the governor's office,
which is supposed to be telling
the town folk about me living here.
But it's been just three days, hasn't it?
Soon, you'll see a deluge of patients
on your doorstep.
I hope so. I really do.
You will, definitely!
The inflow of immigrants will only get stronger.
It's summer now, but once the winter comes,
I'm sure those with weak health would fall ill in droves.
Huh? Southern Australia has winter, too?
Ah... Well, if it has summer,
it must have winter, too.
Maybe you're right... I've never even entertained
the thought of winter coming to here.
That's normal. After all, you never even
considered staying here in Australia.
Yeah...
What was it that made you change your mind
and settle in Australia?
If you really had a mind to return to England,
you could board any other ship.
You're right.
I can't quite understand it myself,
why did I decide to settle here.
But at any rate, Australia
had grown on me since then.
This is good soil.
I'm sure it'll produce superb vegetables.
What are we sowing here?
Who knows.
I need to confer with your father first.
He'll know which plant
would be the fastest to grow to edible.
We're lucky it's summertime.
The radish that we can eat raw
would probably grow nicely.
Whoa! And we'll be able to eat salad, right?
I suppose so. In just forty or fifty days from now.
My, that long?
Australia is a land of mystery.
I really wouldn't mind it growing big enough for eating
the very next day after we sow the seeds.
I sure hope it does just that!
Hm?
It's coming from that direction.
I don't suppose they're laughing at you, are they?
By Jove, that'd be mighty rude!
Who could it be?
That's a remarkable vigor.
Ah, madam.
There was someone laughing at us just now.
Didn't you hear anything?
Yes. Must've been a laughing kookaburra.
A laughing kookaburra?
Oh, you didn't know?
It's a very odd bird that cries
in the morning and the evening.
It was really alike to a human laughter.
Agreed.
When I just moved here,
I was mighty spooked.
But really, that laughing kookaburra
only eats snakes, lizards and frogs.
And especially because it also eats poisonous snakes,
we grew to rely heavily on that kind of bird.
Now that you mention it,
Lucy-May told us this the other day.
When a snake was just about to bite her,
a bird appeared and had that snake for dinner.
And I even called her a liar back then...
Look after Tob for a moment, sis!
Lucy-May, sorry for what I said the other day.
The other day?
Remember when a snake was about to bite you...
I don't know what you're saying,
but let's postpone it!
Marsh has disappeared!
Look after Tob, will you?
Marsh!
Marsh! Marsh, come out, please!
Marsh! Marsh!
Marsh!
Marsh, where did you go? Marsh!
Huh?
Marsh!
Marsh.
It's crying again.
Australia is rich in some
of the most bizarre creatures ever.
Have you already seen a platypus, dear?
Platypus? What is that thing?
They live by that river.
I only know about it from my brother's witness,
but I'm yet to see one myself.
Does that platypus thing
has this very long kind of beak?
And it also swims in the river
using those very short legs it has?
Yes, sounds very much like it.
You've seen it, too?
I saw it near that river.
Me and Lucy-May did together.
So that was a platypus, huh?
Say, you're pretty well informed
about the animals' names, aren't you, madam?
To tell you the truth, it's not me.
My husband is the one who knows them all,
I'm merely parroting him.
I was really glad to learn
that your husband is getting better.
Thank you for your concern.
Yesterday, he set out northwards
on a surveying expedition again.
It's all thanks to Doctor Deighton, by Jove!
That man can be a truly terrific doctor
whenever he is not dead drunk.
It wouldn't hurt to have just a mouthful today.
Once we're done with the house,
you'll have to dig a water well next, Mr. Popple.
Yeah.
Speaking of which,
I don't suppose you know anyone
who can help us dig a well?
I know one such man.
Please tell me who it is. I can dig it myself for sure,
but it'll take a while if I'm doing it alone.
It's me.
Huh?
Please let me also dig the well for you.
I guess... I guess it'll be an excellent well
if we trust you to dig it for us.
But I'm also somehow embarrassed to ask you...
Even now, you're working for half
of what Mr. Pettywell was offering you.
Then, as long as you don't mind doing it...
I accept the request.
But in exchange, I've one favor to ask.
What is it?
Your goat. I'd like to ask you
to give us one of the goatlings.
Ah, those that Lucy-May is keeping?
Yes. My son would like to have one, too.
I suppose, since three of them were born,
even Lucy-May would agree
that yielding just one to your son
is not a big deal at all.
In that case, I'll try to talk
with Lucy-May about it.
Thanks a bunch.
Oh no. I got so engrossed in talking,
I completely forgot about the work.
If this keeps up, we'll end up
letting Mr. Pettywell open up a lead.
How do you like this? Give it just a week more
and we'll be living in a real house.
It'd better be the fanciest house
in the neighborhood.
But of course!
To build a house fancier than this, one would have
to desperately scramble for only the best materials.
And even then, it'll take them no less
than four or five months to assemble it. No, ma'am!
Are you quite sure it'll be ready in a week?
Oh... That's what the workmen told me.
Well, I'm asking you, not them!
I ain't building it myself, y'know.
I am decisively fed up with living in a tent!
I need you to promise me
that this house would be completed
in just a week more!
Got it. I promise, alright?
In that case, I'm going on a promenade
through the area.
Sure, sure.
No need to answer me twice!
Sure...
Have a nice walk.
Darling.
Is there anything else?
What are you going to do
about the water well?
The well is usually being dug
after the house is completed.
For the time being,
we should prioritize assembling the house.
The water that they draw
from the river is all mucky!
I know that...
Then build a well to solve it please!
I told you, give it just a week more...
We need it right now!
How can you say that,
when we've no workers to spare...
Workers?
And what about you?
Uh? What are you saying?
What is your role in this?
Eh? You're asking what my role is,
well, that's quite...
Let's just settle on you digging the well yourself.
You can't ask me to do that!
Damn you!
How can you be so cruel?!
Why is it me who has to do this?
Huh? Hey, tell me why!
Huh? They're not here.
Ah!
Oh? You guys chose to hang around here?
Don’t you know it's rude to bother Dr. Deighton
during his afternoon nap?
You're a cute thing, you know?
Billy!
Yo!
What are you doing?
Look, your goats wandered all the way to here.
Ah, got! Got!
Ah! Hey, Sticky!
That must've been how they got out.
Come on, in you go.
Yes. You too, 'cos you're good kids, aintcha?
Billy, I'll give you one.
Huh?
You said you wanted a goatling.
I'll give you one.
Remember I said I'll give you one
if you catch for me that animal sitting on top of the tree?
But I never caught any.
But you'll catch one for me one day, won't you?
Yeah! I'll break my neck to catch it!
That's why I'm letting you
have one of baby goats now already.
Really?
Yes.
But I think it'd be better if we let them
drink Sticky's milk for a bit longer.
That's true, alright.
But... Are you really letting me have it?
Yes. Consider one of them yours already.
T-thank you, Lucy-May!
Now... Which one should I choose?
Huh? Isn't there supposed to be one more?
Huh?
It's probably still in the tent.
The goatling doesn't seem to be in here.
Billy! There's Mr. Pettywell's black dog!
Billy! Hurry up!
It's about to grab the goatling!
You jerk!
Damn you!
Billy, what happened to the goatling?
Hey! Please tell me the goatling is alright!
It's dead.
I can't hear!
It's dead!
Oh, screw you!
How about this?
I can do something useful, too!
You can even dig a well alright
if you set your mind to it.
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Huh?
Hey, Happy!
Don't tell me you've done
something stupid again!
I'll know right away if you have!
You can bet this fellow
will always be good-for-nothing!
Whoa!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
It hurts! Damn it!
Man, my back hurts so much!
Hey, Happy! Don't be such a bloody eyesore!
Screw you! Ouch! Ouch-ouch...
I see.
Look, they ain't having it good
when bitten in this part of the neck.
The viciousness of this dog knows no bounds.
I'll go and tell Mr. Pettywell
everything I think about him!
Even giving him a mouthful
won't bring this goatling back to life.
Besides, it's not like Mr. Pettywell
deliberately ordered it to slaughter the goatling.
That black dog is getting my hardest kick
next time we meet!
The problem is in Mr. Pettywell himself!
Dogs always take after their owners!
That dog is Mr. Pettywell's spitting image!
Only ever being violent and mean...
Stop with that talk, Lucy.
But come on!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Master is in big trouble!
What are you talking about?
He fell into the pit.
Into the pit?
What in the world has happened?
He said he can't get out of the pit.
What do you mean?
From a hole that tiny?
Well. I suppose it's impressive
for something you've dug all by yourself.
But what is it with you being unable to exit that?
It's my back. My back hurts so much
I can't move at all.
Your back?
Right. Whenever I move even a little,
it hurts so much I think I could die! Ouch! Ouch, ouch.
How should we handle this, then?
Do you intend to live in this hole
for the rest of your life?
What's this nonsense... Ouch! Ouch-ouch...
Doctor, I beg you. We need you
to come see him in that hole.
He's a mole now, huh?
Does it really hurt that much?
Yes. He won't allow anyone to come near him
and just keeps shouting, "Hurts! It hurts!"
Oh? Well, I guess the divine punishment
caught up with him.
Huh?
Oh, no, don't mind me.
Now, let's start with the examination.
I'm goin' out, folk!
I bet you, it's a strained back. Strained back!
I think it'd be perfectly fine for him
to refuse to see Mr. Pettywell.
It definitely would!
He is bound by the doctor's oath.
Which means even if it's the most spiteful
enemy of our parents,
the doctor is obliged to examine him
whenever he is in pain.
I don't think I'd ever be fit
to become a doctor.
We climbed the hill
to bury the poor goatling there.
This was our first tragic incident
since we had crossed over to Southern Australia.
In order to catch a koala,
I started my tree-climbing practice.
I'll become really good at that soon enough!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Tree-Climbing".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you