South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 14 - A Stout Man
Say, Marsh,
aren't baby goats cute?
Hey, Marsh. I got to keep a handful of animals again,
just like back in England!
Careful, Marsh!
Baby goat may step on you.
Lucy-May! It's so awfully early,
but you're already up?
That's 'cause I can't ever get any sleep
in a place so cramped.
Even if you say so, it's where we two
will always have to sleep, starting now.
But it's too cramped!
Well isn't it why dad promised
to rebuild it bigger with time?
But you can't do that on a whim.
Well, of course it won't happen tomorrow
or the day after that.
I don't want to sleep in a tent.
I feel better in spacious places.
Well, that might be so.
But Dr. Deighton and Ben
also need some place to sleep at now.
We can't help that.
And those two are still just sleeping peacefully!
Because our brother and Mr. Deighton, the doctor,
suddenly needed a place to sleep at,
me and Lucy-May
had to relinquish our tent.
Baby goats look healthy.
Why wouldn't they?
Ah, Marsh! You're still there?
Come here now, boy. It's dangerous there.
Oh! Marsh is acting big.
I'm sure Marsh wants to examine
the baby goats from all possible sides.
Marsh? Are you alright, Marsh?
What's he saying?
Who knows.
But I'm sure he feels mighty embarrassed
for being squashed by a baby goat.
The weather looks perfect today as well.
Yeah, the sea was calm last night,
so I slept well without any rolling.
Doctor, you've disembarked the ship already.
Hm? Eh?
Huh?
Right, right!
I have come to live in Adelaide now.
Exactly. And you spent a night in our tent.
Well then.
I gotta go see the neighbor
who's been ill now.
Would it be serious if the fever didn't subside?
Uh? Yeah...
So I really hope it did subside.
Good morning, Doctor.
Good morning.
Ben, sorry to trouble you,
but can't you go fetch some water?
Sure, no problem.
Wait, brother!
I'm going too!
Me too!
You two should go gather some firewood instead!
You think there's any
fallen firewood near the river?
I don't know.
You're not awfully attentive, are you?
Well, whatever.
We'll go there anyway.
I'm sure there is some!
Are you going to visit the Macs again, Doctor?
Uh? Aye... Thought I should check
on the patient's condition. Now...
Bero-bero-bero-baa!
Hoity-toity-oity-baa!
Oh... Ah!
Could someone please bring Tob outside?
Ah, Tob...
Do you want me
to help with something?
Not for the present.
I'll call you if there's something
I absolutely can't do without your help.
Well, feel free to call me, then.
Bye, bye!
Without any profound repairs done,
there is still barely any smoke outflow!
Ah!
Hm?
Eh?
Kate! Lucy-May!
C'mere for a moment!
There's a strange animal!
Where? Where?
It's in the river.
Oh, so it's a fish?
I don't think so, it got four limbs.
Listen, I saw it in the water over there.
Come slowly to look.
Yeah.
I don't see anything, Ben.
Look closely, it's here.
There, found it.
Ah! It's there! There!
It got a beak.
Maybe a waterfowl?
I've not seen a bird
with four feet ever before.
It got a tail, too!
Ah! It went over there!
What in the world is that?
A strange thing, that's for sure.
Australia has some of the most
peculiar animals, doesn't it?
Hold up.
Surely, you're not thinking of keeping
this animal as a pet, too?
I'll keep it, if it ever returns.
Eh? That thing?
I'll dig a pond in front of our house
for keeping it.
Oh, I can't believe it.
I'll go home now.
Lucy-May, make sure
you don't fall into the river again!
Last time you nearly drowned, remember?
That was because I was trying to save Sticky!
Well, just be careful now.
Also, hurry up with gathering the firewood!
I wonder if it'll come out again.
Since then, we didn't get to see
that bizarre animal there ever again.
It wasn't until a much much later point that we learned this animal was actually called platypus.
You think we could capture it alive?
Hey, Lucy-May,
I was a little curious, do you plan to keep
things like snakes and lizards, too?
Yeah, I do.
Surely, you can't be serious when saying that?
I am serious.
Even those disgusting snakes and lizards?
I wanna build a whole zoo of my own!
Forget about the snakes and lizards. That animal from before is about as much as I can tolerate.
If you look closely,
snakes and lizards are cute, too.
Didn't you hear what dad said?
Around here, some snakes and lizards are poisonous.
But such things are not common.
Please, just forget about snakes and lizards, okay?
If you so insist, I will give
snakes and lizards the least priority.
Only when I would have collected all the other animals,
I'll go after snakes and lizards.
Oh, just do what you want!
What's wrong, Kate?
Wait for me!
You got problems to solve
even so early in the morning, Doctor?
The only problem is the patient.
The fever still won't subside.
That is distressing.
Once I'm done eating my breakfast,
I'll go to the city center to look for the medicine.
You think they have any medicine there?
According to Bernard, they have
all kinds of medications at the governor's office.
Well, for emergency situations and such.
Since we can't get them in a proper store, I guess we've no choice but to ask the governor to share.
Doctor, while we're at it,
what exactly is Mr. Mac's illness?
Eh. That's something I don't know myself.
Eh?
He seems to have contracted it after going
deep into the hinterland for the surveying work.
Meaning he may have been stung there by some insect,
carrying a pathogen that we don't know a thing about.
That kind of disease
is problematic, I imagine.
Ah, good job.
Just leave it over there.
What about Lucy-May?
Coming later.
Listen, Kate.
When going out to the wilderness,
you two ought to stick together.
Around here, you might find yourself
in great peril any minute.
At such times, your only option to make it through
may be through sticking together.
Yes, I know that.
But sometimes I absolutely can't stand
sticking with her!
Huh?
Almost there...
Oh no, no, no... Ugh.
Huh?
Ah!
Mr. Heracles!
Doctor, why don't you
have breakfast inside, with us?
Thank you, I was just getting real hungry.
Oh, and doctor...
Yes?
What do you actually plan to do
from now on?
Huh?
Last night, you slept here,
but what about tonight?
Ah, I see. Guess I'm homeless now, innit?
Well, if that would suit you,
you're welcome to stay here for some while.
Guess that's what I'll do. I can't think
of a single other place I could stay at...
If only it's not too big an inconvenience to you...
It's no inconvenience at all.
Rather, I feel ashamed somehow
for making you sleep in a shabby tent...
Life in a tent ain't half bad either.
Huh? What's wrong, Mr. Popple?
There...
Huh?
Ah! That's...
Dad, you recognize him? Remember,
the man that saved me the other day.
Ah, uh-huh...
Oh, you can put that firewood down right here.
Dad, we gotta pay our gratitude somehow.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
What do you think we should do?
Hm, anything would do, I reckon...
Darling, breakfast is going cold...
What's going on, darling?
There, this is the man.
The one who saved Lucy-May
the day before yesterday.
Oh...
And so I wanted to thank him somehow.
Right. I think it's a good idea, Annie.
Probably, yes.
But what is it we could present him with
to make him really happy?
Hm. Some edible might do.
Hmm... What about clothes?
That's gotta be something to drink, if ya ask me.
Well? Ain't that right, mate?
Something to drink?
Like what, for instance?
Oh, let's say, could be whiskey.
We don't have any whiskey.
Then beer, maybe wine?
And we've neither again.
Meaning you've not a bit of alcohol here with you?
I'm afraid no.
None, then?
Oh, I know.
How about some of yesterday's bread?
Ah, it should totally do.
That one was very delicious.
Right, then I'll go get some.
Ah!
Hmm?
This here is my entire family.
Hey, what's the matter?
Wait a minute!
Mom will now bring the bread
that we wanted to present you with.
In just a moment.
This is the bread that I baked.
Please try it.
It's yummy stuff!
Come on, taste it.
Am.
Um, mm, mm.
Smells just as good, don't you see?
How are you finding my bread?
Hm.
I'm so glad!
Goodbye!
I'd say we made him mighty happy with that!
Seems so.
His people don't know
how to bake bread, right?
Yeah.
They grew up in the wild,
where they've only ever eaten plants and animals.
Maybe they drink alcohol, too?
I doubt they can brew it all on their own.
Eh? So not drinking alcohol either?
Truly, some odd fellas they are.
There we go! Right! There!
Listen!
The man who owned this prefabricated home before
said he could try to assemble it in two weeks.
Two weeks? Impossible! It's three weeks,
even if we rush it to the utmost!
I'm sick of living in a tent so much
that I can't take it anymore!
And my wife feels the same way.
At any rate, I want that house built, and fast!
As soon as possible!
We're off!
Be careful, will you?
Alright, move it!
Heave-ho! And... there!
Oh... There it goes!
Now move it, move!
I've seen that man's face somewhere.
It's Mr. Pettywell, who came on the same ship as us.
Oh, oh-oh! It's that man, alright.
What do you know, he's quite a taskmaster.
Just a consequence of being dirty rich, it seems.
Ha. So that's what money does to people?
But the economy here is booming,
so the houses would soon mushroom anyway.
Damn him!
What's wrong, Ben?
Isn't it considered polite
not to say such things?
That house used to be ours.
Huh? And what's that supposed to mean?
That prefabricated home
was the house that we brought along from England!
Ben, that's enough.
Petty complains won't change anything.
See ya.
I hope Doctor finds the medicine he needs.
Yeah.
Dad, you think they have their own cart at the sawmill,
for moving the lumber?
They gotta have it.
Without it, their clients won't be able to transport
the timber they bought.
Further ahead?
Yes.
Must be an oxcart they have.
Kate! Lucy-May!
Where are you?
I need you back home!
My... Where could they have gone to?
This is strange. I definitely heard those two
talking here a moment ago.
Now, let's hurry.
Yeah.
Not so fast, you two!
Ah!
We just wanted to make a little trip
to the Adelaide city center.
Not today.
If we start here, we're immediately on the road,
so there's no way we get lost.
Besides, there aren't many buildings yet,
so you can see us anywhere.
Not happening!
But we won't even go all that terribly far...
We'll only take a stroll to Colonel Light's office.
As soon as we look at Mr. Bernard's working place,
we'll turn back.
There is something else
I need you two to do today.
Work?
That's right, just some simple job.
Something even Lucy-May can do?
Maybe.
But I was hoping Kate would do that.
Then, I'll go play around some.
No way!
The oil is viscous enough already.
In that case, you can stop stirring.
Ah! I was already feeling stiff in the chest.
It smells so bad!
Not something we can help, is it?
After all, it's just some oil leftovers
that we scrambled together.
There's no longer anything for me to do, is there?
Not at all! You now need to watch closely
to what I'm doing.
Next time, you'll also be doing it.
I don't wanna.
This place is no England for you!
If there's something we can do ourselves,
we do it ourselves!
But there's plenty of candles for sale!
There is.
But those are expensive.
Now watch how it's done.
We do it like this, making sure the yarn
is thoroughly soaked in oil.
About this should be enough.
Now we leave it to dry up in the shade.
That's be one mighty long and narrow candle.
Don't be silly, we'll yet have to repeat
this process many times over.
Once it congeals, we dip it in oil,
then drying it up again.
Once it congeals, dip in oil.
And so, it gradually thickens.
Takes quite a while to finish, I imagine.
True.
Might take several days, or even weeks
until it finally starts to resemble a candle.
You try it too.
Okay.
Here.
Ah! I got some oil on my hand.
You can wash it away later!
Ah! Now I got the oil on my clothes, too...
Once it's done,
we'll have to pull the cart by ourselves?
Ain't got much choice.
No oxen or horses around.
No way we carry it all in one run.
You'll manage if you hire someone extra.
After all, you've got the cart already.
It's fine. We'll try to get it done by ourselves.
Whatever suits you, mate...
Ben, this kind of job
requires a great deal of effort.
Ben, put your back into it!
Doctor, I'm glad they let you have
the medicine needed.
Aye. The office folk were mighty understanding
towards our unforeseen plight.
They agreed to divert some medicine
from their own stocks.
Starting tomorrow, you could run
a private practice in that tent.
Yeah.
I hope everyone in our neighbors' house
is well and healthy soon.
I expect the fever to subside come morning.
I'm sure it will subside.
It sure is taking dad and Ben
ridiculously long.
Ben, let's rest a tad bit.
Huh?
Hey! Mr. Popple, s'that you?
That's right! Popple here!
Ah! Your dad and brother are back!
Eh?
Ah! Thank goodness!
Dad!
Welcome back! Yay!
Welcome back, dear.
Yeah...
Welcome back, dad.
Welcome back, Ben.
Welcome back!
All right, Ben, let's move on.
Uh-huh.
There!
Like that!
Dad and Ben brought along
a whole lot of lumber.
With this, we can finally start expanding the house.
And when we do, our sleep will be
way more sound than now.
We've never seen our neighbor Mr. Mac,
so we were starting to wonder if he's even real.
Oh, I just can't take it anymore!
We'll have to peek inside.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Two Homes".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you