South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 15 - Two Homes
Oh my, it's raining.
It's raining, dad.
Started so suddenly.
We're out of luck...
Sticky and her babies
will get wet!
Ugh, ain't no helping it.
Why don't we rest a spell?
Hey! Come get inside here.
You're sodden wet, ain't ya?
Only together with the goat, Doctor!
The goat?
Probly just a rain shower.
Yes, might be.
Work goin' smoothly?
The wood is harder than I thought,
so it'll take a while.
As much I woulda liked to help,
I ain't cut out for doin' carpenter's work.
No, it's all right.
We were never counting on you
to prop us here as well.
'Sides, if a bungler such as myself woulda helped you,
we'd only arrive to a house that goes "wobble-wobble"!
Ah... Eh? Huh?
Ah! The goat - alright, can't be helped.
But you two must definitely go hide in the house!
Wah!
But we're already in here, aren't we?
You're being mean!
But there's no reason
for you two to be in here.
You were on your way home.
We're just as fine here.
Right, Lucy-May?
Yeah, yeah.
Now, now, now.
Quite a fuss over nothing, you two.
But it's Ben who's saying we should go out.
You're not someone to tell us do that, Ben.
This tent belongs to me and Dr. Deighton.
But it was our sleeping place before you came!
Right, Lucy-May?
Yeah, yeah!
But now you have
the house over there for yourselves.
We can't stand that godforsaken house!
It's all cramped and dirty.
Yeah, yeah!
Kate!
What is it?
You can't be saying such things.
You know both dad and mom
don't consider that house marvelous either.
Even Clara is just bearing with it.
Don't you know what dad and me
are currently working for?
We know that, alright. You're working
on making this house bigger, isn't it?
But there's no way of knowing
just how long will it take.
I don't think it'll take that long, Kate.
It's true that I'm not a carpenter by trade,
and Ben cannot yet stand on his own either.
Still, we keep doing everything in our power
to make this house
much bigger and comfortable for living
as soon as we can.
So I'm asking you both, Kate and Lucy-May,
for a bit more of patience.
Okay!
Okay.
Good, good.
Oh no! Mother, another leak over there!
Ah... It seems this roof is thoroughly tattered.
Tob! Don't do that!
Ah...
Your father and the others
probably chose the tent.
Seems so.
I'd really love to start living
in a proper house soon...
Dad may not have admitted it,
but that was probably one big mistake, after all.
What was?
Selling away our prefabricated home.
Oh...
Dad said he had to sell it
because he couldn't move it to Adelaide anyhow.
But Mr. Pettywell was apparently able
to move it no problem.
Well that was because Mr. Pettywell is so wealthy.
Even so, that was an obvious miscalculation
on dad's part.
Clara.
Yes, I know. It's no use lamenting something
that's already done.
Your father promised to make it
into a way less objectionable place very soon.
But it's really getting on my nerves.
Eh?
At Mr. Pettywell's plot,
they've finished the foundation already.
My, already?
And it's no wonder.
That's what prefabricated homes are for.
Mr. Pettywell.
What is it?
The rain is too strong.
We should give everyone a rest.
Well, I guess we've no choice.
Then, I'll go tell them to rest.
Hey! Everyone!
Let's take a break!
Once a professional carpenter joins the team,
the rate of their advance becomes a whole other thing.
Yes, yes.
Doesn't seem to be stopping at all.
Doctor, have you been to the Macs today?
Aye, I was just thinking of going there,
when suddenly, this rain...
That sir next door is still unwell?
Well, he ain't too well, that's for sure.
Just as I felt relieved by his fever finally subsiding,
it went right back up!
Dad, we've prepared some tea.
Doctor is welcome, too.
Aye, much obliged.
Well, if you don't mind me going ahead.
What about us, sis?
The children will have to stay here until later.
That's unfair!
The roof is leaking terribly.
If you two come inside, you'll end up soaked
as there's nowhere to hide from the rain.
Ah... I sure hope it stops raining soon.
Hm? Got me.
Ah, another leak formed there as well?
Doctor, sorry to trouble,
but if you could move just a bit...
Sure.
Mr. Popple, if I were you,
I'd also try to repair this house as soon as I can.
If it's that bad, Annie,
shouldn't I ask for someone else's help?
And where will you find anyone willing to help?
Hmm. If only Mr. Jamling was here...
But he's still on the beach, isn't he?
Nope, his leg should have healed by now.
Right, Doctor?
Let's see... How long ago was it, again?
Aye, gotta be able to walk by now.
Then he might've left for Adelaide as well.
If he comes through here,
I wonder if he'll stop by to say hello.
You told him how to find us, right?
No. Ah, I suppose he's still stuck
in the seaside camp, after all.
Even supposing his leg had healed, I doubt he could
find a cart to carry his things at a moment's notice.
If only we could ask for Mr. Jamling's help, I'm sure,
repairing this house wouldn't take nearly as long.
Oh? Isn't it supposed to be over by now?
Hey! Back to work! To work!
The rain had nearly stopped already!
Hm.
What does he mean?
It's still raining.
What do you think, Mr. Jamling?
If it's fine with you, we can renew the work.
This rain is nothing special at this point.
"Because he's paying us
more than double the usual wage", isn't it?
Well, it may have played its part.
Look, here he comes.
Now, now, Mr. Jamling, I hope to see the favor
of letting you have a rain break returned now.
But the rain hasn't stopped yet.
My, is that so? And to me it seems
like there's barely any precipitation.
Alright, alright, we get it.
We'll work one more shift until the evening.
Right, good.
Now, put off dillydallying
and do your best for some more!
Well, let's try our best, Ben.
But we'll only be able
to saw a few until the evening.
We'll saw what we can saw.
Oh?
Hey! Away! Away!
You can't go around eating my stock-in-trade!
Look, the rain is finally over.
Go out an chew some grass now. Grass!
Oh my, my. I sure wouldn't want
to spend a night in one tent with you three.
Doctor Deighton is visiting our neighbors.
Let's go and check them out, too!
What for?
Cause we need to know our neighbors well.
Whaddya mean by "know well"?
Means seeing what their rooms are like inside,
what's in them and such.
Let's go peek inside through the window!
Lucy-May, do you quite realize
just what are you saying?
But that's just cause I'm so curious about it!
Don't you know what you can do
and what you can't?
Oh, I do know, for sure.
But you have to agree that we haven't seen
Mrs. Mac's husband not even once yet.
Ah, good day to you, ma'am.
Well that's cause he's ill.
It's only natural we can't see him
as he has to sleep inside all day.
And that's why I want to know -
what does he look like and such.
Sis?
What is it?
Do you really mean to say
you don't wanna find out at all ?
I... Well, of course, I do wanna know!
Sis!
Let's use this window to peek inside.
What's wrong, sis?
I guess it's a no-go, after all.
What is?
You know exactly what!
I came to realize
that peeking into other's homes is very rude!
Meaning you won't do it with me?
Ah, fair! It's an ugly business -
that much I could tell myself.
But also... I can't help wondering
what Mrs. Mac's husband is like.
Don't startle me like that, sis.
So, you seen it?
Seen what?
What do you mean "What"? You wanted to see
the house inside, didn't you? What did you see?
Here is their living room.
Mrs. Mac and Doctor went into another room.
So, that must be where they have
the sick room, don't you think?
I suppose so.
Tell me, was that door closer
to that side of the house or to this one?
That side.
Eh? Which one do you mean?
You'll know at once when you see it.
Just take a look yourself.
No way! I can't look in there.
You're acting kinda kooky, sis.
Hey, just tell me which one it is!
It's right there, the door in the back!
Okay, so it's the one in the back.
Then, the window to the sick room
is on the other side of the house.
Hurry up after me, Lucy-May!
Look, must be this window.
You do the peeking this time, sis.
Surely enough, that must be you!
Didn't I tell you I won't look?
Come on, just take a peek through this window.
I'm sure you'll see everything well.
This is just getting ridiculous now.
Ah?
So, how is it?
How's what?
What you're looking at, of course!
Just tell me already.
Can you see the patient?
Come on, you see him or not?
Come on! Tell me now, you meanie!
I can't see a thing.
Huh?
This here looks like Mr. Bernard's bedroom.
Oh geez...
The patient is in another room.
But hey, what's Mr. Bernard's bedroom like?
Just peek in yourself, you...
Hush!
So, another window
for the sick room, isn't that right?
After me, Lucy-May!
I'm not doing any more peeking!
Not very logical of you to say that.
You've done peeking two times already.
And so I refuse now!
I mean, look: you already misbehaved twice anyhow.
So just adding one more to the stack
won't make any difference, don't you agree?
I don't wanna do any more peeking.
And that window is way too high
for my stature anyway.
You're right, it's too far even for me.
Maybe if we find some platform to climb on?
Good idea.
Go ahead, Lucy-May.
"No" means "No"!
You're a selfish one...
Why won't you go ahead and peek in?
Very well. Let's peek in together, then.
Together?
Right. By doing something together,
we can halve the guilt for misbehaving.
You see?
Now get on and let's peek in together, deal?
Aye, Kate, Lucy-May!
Ah! Billy!
You brute, brute, brute!
Oh, this Billy is unbearable!
Ah! Ouch! Ouch, ouch, ouch! It hurts, aye!
Hey, what's the matter with you two?
At least tell me what's...
Billy, you've finally made it to Adelaide, too?
Yeah. We arrived here two days ago in the evening.
Our house is a bit difficult to see from here,
but it's really close!
Whoa! Thank goodness we're
in the same neighborhood. Right, Lucy-May?
But don't slap people on the butt
like you just did, Billy!
My bad, alright. But I also wasn't expecting you two
to be so startled by it.
It was real rude on my part though, sorry.
It's fine already, you're forgiven.
Appreciate it.
Still, though, I'm kinda jealous.
Why so?
In this place, that's one impressive house you got.
Mine is still nothing more than a tent.
You're wrong, that one is Mrs. Mac's house.
Mrs. Mac?
Correct. As for our house, look -
the pitiful cabin over there.
Oh, I see then.
Which means you two were peeking
into other people's house?
You could say so...
But we still had a pretty solid reason to do that.
That being Dr. Deighton...
Eh? You got Dr. Deighton here with you?
In this neighborhood?
Exactly. He lives in a tent by our house.
Eh? So that's how it is?
Thanks to Dr. Deighton, my dad's leg
got much better and in no time at all!
He even returned to work already.
Mighty glad to hear that.
He owes your daddy and Ben a big one
for saving his skin in the forest.
Dad even said he won't ever forget
the kindness of those two in his life.
Our dad merely did what
anyone else would've done.
Ah, actually... Dad probably hasn't a clue!
While working so close, he never even stopped
by your place to say hello.
And where is he working?
Right there, see?
Over there, meaning at Mr. Pettywell's place?
Yep. He's working for that moneybag Mr. Pettywell.
Mr. Pettywell's messenger came all the way
to the beach camp, bowing and begging my dad to do it.
Wow...
They even took care of an oxcart
to bring along our stuff.
Is it true Mr. Jamling
is now working on Mr. Pettywell's site?
We've seen it ourselves, very closely.
Right, Lucy-May?
Yes. Mr. Jamling was assembling
the prefabricated house there, that's for certain.
Damn it!
Hey, Ben. In case you're directing those words
at Mr. Jamling, you're making a mistake.
Why so, dad?
Mr. Jamling is free to work at anyone's site,
that is his basic right.
Even if it happens to be Mr. Pettywell's site!
Back when we saved Mr. Jamling in the woods,
he was crying with gratitude, mind you!
Listen, Ben, you're forgetting
the most important thing here.
Which one?
It may stand true that Mr. Pettywell
is infinitely intolerable,
but that doesn't make him
our sworn enemy or adversary.
Back when Clara was in agony
due to her deteriorating condition,
he broke the line and proceeded to disembark first!
Then the fresh meat we got from Mr. Parker
got snatched away by Mr. Pettywell's dog!
My, my. You're still hung up
even on such petty things?
Then there was also the oxcart intended for us,
but Mr. Pettywell managed to take that away as well!
Don't you remember how we had to walk our feet off
to find a replacement oxcart?
Hm.
Because the transportation here is such a bust,
we figured transporting
our prefabricated home is a non-starter.
And so, you made a decision to sell it.
Didn't you, dad?!
I think... I think that was indeed
a mistake on my part.
And that's why Mr. Pettywell
was the last person you'd want to sell it to.
But as cruel irony would have it,
that house landed right into Mr. Pettywell's hands!
That was a pure coincidence.
Even so, all the Jamlings
were perfectly aware of how it actually is!
Ben! That's enough.
Listen, Mr. Jamling will work wherever he pleases.
Nobody can stop Mr. Jamling from that!
Come now, Ben!
There you go!
Good! Nail that down real tight, gentlemen.
Um... Next, we're setting up that pillar.
Dad.
Yes, Billy?
What's the matter?
I noticed you've been watching us for a while.
I was hanging out with Mr. Popple's daughters
Kate and Lucy-May.
Ah...
Right! Right there.
Now nail it hard.
This house is the house Mr. Popple
brought along from England, innit?
Uh? Uh, uh-huh.
But listen here boy,
this house now belongs to me.
Dad, if you look over there,
it's Mr. Popple's house.
Yeah...
You already knew, dad?
Who'd think Mr. Popple would buy a house
right across the street from my plot, huh?
Apparently, Mr. Popple
is planning to rebuild this seedy shack.
Oh, actually. Dad, Dr. Deighton
also ended up staying at Mr. Popple's place.
It's dangerous to keep working when it's so dark.
Let's continue tomorrow.
So I thought.
Are you tired, Ben?
What about you?
I've gotten quite used to it.
Ah, I'm starving.
Someone's coming here, dad.
It's Mr. Jamling.
Mr. Jamling!
Good evening, Mr. Popple.
Yes. Good evening to you, Mr. Jamling.
Is your leg doing better now?
Yes. Through your care,
it's just as you said.
Glad to know that.
Mr. Popple...
Ah?
Isn't there something I could help you with?
Ah... I know how it sounds from my own lips,
but I'm actually a master carpenter.
I know that very well, Mr. Jamling.
If you'd like to use my services,
I'll gladly start as soon tomorrow morning!
No, even starting tonight is fine.
Mr. Jamling...
A child who suddenly fell sick
is brought to Dr. Deighton's office.
But because Doctor is so drunk,
he can't even walk straight.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Boozed Doctor".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you