South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 45 - Tob Disappeared
I'm at home again.
There. Come out, you guys.
I really wish you'd lay way more eggs than that.
Good morning, Sticky, Pansy, Soppy!
Maybe I got up way too early?
It seems even Little,
the usual early bird, is not awake yet.
I wonder why.
Kate! Good morning.
Seems like I got up awfully early,
since I haven't slept at home for such a long while!
It's not particularly early.
Huh?
Rather, it was me who overslept.
Oh?
Seems like mom and the others are still sleeping.
What's the matter with everyone?
This is all your fault.
My fault?
Of course! Because you've been missing
for three days straight,
everyone lost their sleep to the worrying!
So we turned into a sleepless family.
Hm...
We were that much worried!
Sorry to bother you, but but could you please
milk the goat this morning?
But...
No "Buts!" I'm counting on you.
Then, could you bring these to the kitchen for me?
Ah, okay.
Is mom really still asleep?
Ah!
I overslept so badly.
So you've been losing sleep
for these three nights too, haven't you?
Yes. Thinking about Lucy,
I couldn't get any sleep.
I guess I gotta go wake Clara up before it's too late.
Oh my, Clara is still asleep too?
Yes.
Then do go wake her up
and then hurry up to milk the goats, please.
Lucy is on that already.
Oh my? She is up so soon?
Well, Lucy's the only one who hasn't been losing sleep.
Rather, she led a somewhat queen-like life
in Mr. Princeton's house.
As soon as I return home,
I'm made to do some chores.
Your turn is later!
Better go wake Clara up if you've nothing better to do.
Hey, stop it! What are you doing?
Be a good girl and wait for your turn.
But say, everyone has sure been
worried about me a great deal.
That's right. We were all deprived of sleep
by worries about Lucy who wouldn't come home.
But upon seeing Lucy return safely,
the whole family felt a great relief.
And so, every single one of us overslept that morning.
I'm very hungry!
I'm sorry. Wait just a moment, it's almost ready.
I'm really hungry. I am hungry!
Mom, I also gotta leave now.
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear that.
But you could still probably fit in some time for breakfast?
I don't have that luxury.
I wanted to catch the first stagecoach of the day.
I also overslept dreadfully.
I wonder if Lucy's awake.
In the garden, tending to goats.
Lucy, I'm returning to the harbor.
And you won't be back until next Saturday again?
Probably.
Don't you give everyone so much worry anymore, Lucy.
Okay.
Clara, I'm going now.
Have nice week!
I'm finished with mine already, Clara.
Then, why don't you hurry up to bring it to mom?
Okay.
Ah, so heavy!
What are you saying? It's the same as always.
Father, are you awake?
Huh? Yes.
I'm returning to the harbor.
Huh? It's that late already?
Yes.
Father.
Yes?
I think I'd better quit the customs job.
Why do you think so?
The salaries there aren't anything spectacular.
If I stumble upon any other place that pays better,
I think should rather transfer to there.
You don't like your current job?
No. This is a good job.
Then you shouldn't quit.
But the salary...
Ben, I'll start working again.
Once I do, we'll have enough money.
I appreciate you concern, but...
It'll be fine. We'll work it out somehow.
Have you already found a good job, father?
Yes. Though I still haven't decided on it for certain.
But I found it.
You hear me, right?
Mr. Popple's House.
Yes. I understand, sir.
You wanna go to the meadows
for the first time in a while, Little?
Is that... Oh, right.
It's Mr. Princeton's carriage.
Good morning.
Hello, Lucy. Here, this is for you.
This...
No need to be shy about it.
I bought it for you, after all.
But...
My wife insisted on me bringing it along. Now...
Unload the rest of the luggage, will you?
Will do, sir.
Is there anyone else at home?
Mom is.
How did it feel last night
to finally return to your own home?
I slept like a baby.
So it's true what they say - no place like home?
Yes.
Which means your husband
is currently looking for a job?
Yes. But he said he had come up
with some promising plan when he left today.
You'd not have this problem if you had the land, right?
Well, that's true. But the way things stand now,
our every attempt to get a plot came to naught...
I see.
Um. If that wouldn't trouble you too much,
please give my best regards to your missus too.
I really feel like I'll never be able to repay
everything you've done for us...
There's no need to thank me.
When you have some free time,
please be sure to visit us at our place at least once.
As I stated last night, I'm interested in discussing some agricultural matters with your husband.
Of course. I'll pass it to my husband.
In that case, I'll have my leave now.
Are you sure you'd like us to keep
such a wonderful doll and dress?
This doesn't feel right, somehow.
Oh, please do! There are no children in our house.
We've no need for a doll or for a girl's dress.
You even wore such a lovely dress!
And walked in these shoes!
My, you really was living like a queen!
I appreciate the gift, of course,
but they don't really fit with this house.
I wouldn't say so.
How is it bad to have a queen in our house too?
Being a queen and all... Is embarrassing!
Ah! That's a pretty dress!
Didn't I tell you to knock before entering a lady's room?
Ah, right.
Lucy, our guest is leaving already.
We couldn't help like something was very off this morning,
as if our own daughter
had suddenly disappeared yesterday.
My wife. I mean, Sylvia,
seems particularly saddened by this fact.
She absolutely wants you to come play around more.
Okay.
Your siblings are welcome to tag along too.
Okay!
Well, then.
Truly, we are so grateful!
Goodbye!
Goodbye.
Lucy! He said I can come visit them too!
Yes.
So, when are we going, Lucy?
How should I know?
It seems, that gentleman wants
to discuss something thoroughly with your dad.
Lucy, bring dad along when you go there.
Okay.
I want to go too, mother.
Sure, sure.
Really? I can really go?
What did you want to talk about?
Hm. Well, I figured I should let everyone know.
So I was waiting until everyone gets together.
But Ben is not here.
I'll tell him later.
Thing is, I've met with the mining company man
to inquire into their job opportunities.
Did you say "mine?"
Yes.
Like, coal digging job?
To be precise, the iron ore digging job.
But that's a dangerous job, isn't it?
Maybe it's a little dangerous,
but the wage is accordingly high.
But I'd rather you not do such a dangerous job.
That's right, father.
There's a certain degree of risk to any job.
Father, couldn't you apply for job at some big farm?
Wouldn't that be the one most fitting job for you?
I've had my share of working thanklessly
at another's farm.
If I'd go to work on a farm,
it won't be another's farm, but my own.
Even so, why mine, of all places?
Hm. Actually, what I wanted
to talk to everyone about is this house.
Thing is, if I want to work at a mine,
I'd also have to live close to it.
Does that mean we'll have to move too?
The company offers cheap housing for its workers.
We'll sell this house.
And then, if we put aside as much money as we can,
in five years, we'll have enough to buy our own plot.
In other words, you're going to work at a mine
so as to buy the plot in the future?
That's right.
Where is that mine?
It's near Mount Barker.
Mount Barker?
That's a long way from here.
That's why I want everyone to be ready for a long trip.
Um...
What is it?
I won't be able to work at Mrs. Mac's store, right?
Probably...
"Probably?" Commuting to here
from Mount Barker would be totally impossible!
I suppose...
So I'll have to quit, won't I?
Try asking John for advice.
Eh?
Weren't you two planning to get married soon?
Oh...
Dear...
That's how I see it.
I'm also by no means opposed
to Clara and John getting married.
You two could stay to live in Adelaide.
Father...
Is that fine by you, Clara?
Yes.
What about Ben?
He can keep working
at the customs office as he does now.
But it'll be awfully difficult for him to go home all the way to the Mount Barker every Saturday.
It can't be helped.
Seems to me like everyone is getting scattered
all over the place, somehow.
There's no certainty to any of this yet.
Tomorrow or the day after that,
we'll hire a cart and go check out the mine.
I would definitely like you all to see the place
that I myself have not yet been to.
Giddyup! Giddyup! Giddyup!
We went to see the mine
where dad was going to work.
Coincidentally, we went there to look at the company lodgings that we'll soon be occupying.
The scenery is becoming so deserted...
That there is the Mount Barker, probably.
They won't have a school
at a place like that. Right, mom?
Who knows.
How many people are working on the mine, dad?
Maybe about 80 workers or so.
Then it's settled!
There won't be any school in a place like that!
You can never know that for certain.
I actually wanted to go to school!
Too bad for you, but you won't be getting any school!
I don't like it!
I'd rather not move here.
Well I'm all for it!
When you said "mine," I thought more of a big hole,
which you enter to dig out coal and such.
All the mines in this area are open-pit type.
Which means there are many ores
that are close to the surface.
This seems way less dangerous
than descending into a hole.
Yes.
Where would be the place that we'll live in?
Look. See an arrangement of houses over there?
Ah, you're right!
But those are pretty small houses.
They only seem small when you look at them from afar.
I don't think so. Even if we get closer,
they won't get much bigger.
Well, maybe you're right.
Now, I need to meet someone in the office.
Are you coming along?
We probably don't have to come, do we?
Of course. You could get off here
and I'd pick you up on the way back.
Ah!
What is it?
They're here!
Who?
Kangaroos!
Why would there be kangaroos
where the grass is so sparse?
Well, "sparse" doesn't mean there's none at all.
Look, over there!
You're right! There are kangaroos.
On the second thought, those are probably
not kangaroos, but wallabies.
They're a little smaller.
Couldn't they just be babies?
They're not! Look, look.
They even have actual babies in their pouches.
You're right!
I'll go catch a kangaroo.
It's not a kangaroo.
It's a wallaby, Tob.
Be sure to stay around here, will you?
Okay.
I'm going with your father.
I also need to check out the company lodgings anyhow.
Okay!
Okay.
Be careful around the cliffs over there!
Can we go now, honey?
Kate! You're the oldest one, so look after everyone.
I know, I know!
Not like that, Tob!
They'll run away if you rush so much.
But those kangaroos aren't moving.
Those are wallabies!
Let's try getting a little closer.
Yeah.
Oh?
Mr. Popple, isn't it?
Yes, that's right.
I take it you haven't signed the official contract yet?
Yes. I wanted to see the actual place first,
with my own eyes.
Oh, if so, feel free to look around.
Excuse me...
Yes?
May I also go look at the company lodgings?
Yes, without a doubt.
I'll show you around.
Let's see. I take it you don't have any kids, do you?
We do. We'll bring along three of them.
Oh...
Are you using gunpowder too?
No. That's just someone hunting kangaroos, probably.
Kangaroos?
They've a delicious mean
and a hide that can be used in more ways than one.
And there just happens to be a lot of them around here.
Stop! Stop shooting!
Why are you shooting them! Aren't they cute?
Stop your shooting!
You're so evil, uncle!
I wonder if he managed to shoot any wallabies.
I didn't see any fall on the ground.
Thank goodness! I really wonder
why'd they wanna kill such cute animals?
Ah! Over there!
Huh?
I'll catch it!
Can you really catch something like that?
I'll catch it I said!
Be careful, okay, Tob?
The bullet hit the parent wallaby!
And what'll happen to the baby now?
I guess we'll have to take it home and raise it ourselves.
I'll catch it.
Hey! Wait!
Though it's cute, we probably won't be able
to raise it from such little age.
I suppose.
Enough already! Come back now!
Tob!
Tob?
What's wrong, Lucy?
Tob! Answer me! Tob!
What's going on?
Tob suddenly disappeared.
What did you say?
Tob! Tob! Come out now!
Tob! Where are you?
In a mysterious way, we suddenly lost sight of Tob.
Tob and Kate fell into a pit.
Tob managed to climb up,
but we had to leave Kate waiting in the pit.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Wombat in the Pit".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you