South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 05 - After the Rain
It's dangerous, Lucy-May!
Please come back!
In her animal-loving daze, Lucy-May was approaching a pack of sea lions,
unable to hear me begging her to stop.
Oh no!
It's okay. Keep calm
and I won't do anything to you.
Because I know you won't do anything to me either.
Quiet!
Lucy-May! Flee! Flee that place, quick!
Lucy-May! Are you okay?
They all hid in the sea...
What were you thinking standing idly,
surrounded by a pack of sea lions?
I thought about how sea lions
are absolutely cute when you look closely.
Were you really not one bit scared?
Not at all.
What is wrong with you?
I though they could eat you any moment...
Of course not!
Wow! It sure is raining hard!
Let's find a shelter somewhere!
Under those rocks should do. Let's go!
Turns out, the sea lions
hate thunderstorms just as much.
There, we're home.
Oh! You're not as wet as I thought.
Yes.
We took shelter at Mrs. Jamling's text.
But it seemed like it won't stop any time soon.
Did Mr. Jamling finally return?
No, not yet.
I just heard that he left for Adelaide yesterday.
Also that he wasn't planning to stay there overnight.
Mrs. Jamling seems to grow really worried.
Now it's also blowing hard.
This rain really is here to stay.
Your dad and Ben are probably
exploring Adelaide sodden wet.
The wind picked up, Mr. Jamling.
We'd better get home sooner.
But if we head out now,
we'll get soaked at once.
My wife is probably pulling her hair out...
It's not so far from the tents now.
But with that leg...
I'm sure there is no fracture.
Just a small sprain,
not something that'd prevent me from walking.
When we get back to the tents,
we should show you to a physician.
Physician?
I thought there are no physicians around here.
Right. There are none ashore,
but not on the ship.
Ah, the naval surgeon.
That man who never gets sober.
He's the only physician we have.
Mr. Popple, we should head out.
I don't mind getting sodden wet.
I'm sorry to trouble you, but could you
find a branch for me to use as a walking stick?
You want to return on your own?
Yes.
Careful.
You saved my life, truly,
by carrying me all the way to here.
I have to take over from here on somehow.
If I had a walking stick, I could...
Mr. Jamling, we'll go with you.
But you'll get wet.
Here. Please get on my back.
Mr. Popple.
This rain isn't gonna stop.
How do you know?
That's just the feeling I've got.
I think it'll be stopping soon enough.
Why so?
That's just the feeling I've got.
Don't copy after me, Lucy-May.
But that's how I really feel!
You could wait all day,
but the sea lions won't come back.
We're getting soaked here anyhow.
Let's head out.
You're right. Mom is probably worried too.
Exactly.
Me and mom had our share of worrying
when dad didn't return from Adelaide last night.
At a time like this, the sooner we return - the better.
Lucy-May, don't fall behind!
Kate, do you remember where you tossed shoes?
Probably.
You don't sound terribly confident to me.
Yes, I'm not confident.
You'll help us look for it, won't you, Billy?
Guess I gotta!
Mr. Popple.
Yes?
Will your tent be able to weather this?
Yes.
If the wind gets any stronger,
there will probably be some flying tents.
I'd like to think that our tent can handle this.
I believe, mine is not at risk either.
That's because you're a carpenter,
aren't you, Mr. Jamling?
But my dad is a farmer,
and thanks to that he's also very dexterous.
That's why our tent is stretched tight.
I helped set it up too.
Oh, I see.
I hope Billy makes just as helpful
an assistant to me when he's your age.
Billy is ten, right?
He's the same age as our Kate.
If so, you can't blame him now.
For example, Kate is good-for-nothing, compared to me.
Caught a cold already?
It's not a cold,
simply something in my nose.
Just as Clara finally got better,
my another big sister comes down ill!
I'm not ill, you hear me?
Ah!
It's it behind that rock?
The place where you tossed your shoes.
You think so too?
Yeah. It's here, alright.
Ah! It's here, alright.
This way, I think...
That's odd. They should totally be around here.
Don't just stare idly! Help me look for it!
Eck!
What is it?
I stepped on...
On what?
I don't know yet.
But it's so slimy to the touch...
Can you move your foot away?
Ah... I suppose.
What was it?
It went that way!
Eh?
Where, where?
Ah!
What is this thing?
I don't think it's a snake.
Where have you seen snakes like that?
It has proper legs.
Then it's a lizard.
I suppose. Must be a lizard.
But it has two heads.
That's true...
What a curious fellow.
I hope it comes out again.
I wanna check if it really has two heads.
I hope it doesn't bite...
Did it bite you, Kate?
No.
See? Didn't bite even after being stepped on.
It's gotta be alright.
Guess I should've heeded to mom's advice, after all...
What advice?
There are dangerous insects in the grass,
so she told me to wear shoes at all times,
lest I'll get stung.
The head must be on the side that it walked with.
This one certainly was no insect.
It looked like a lizard, albeit an odd-shaped one.
It being a lizard only makes matters worse!
I'm not taking my shoes off ever again!
Lucy-May! Start looking for my shoes!
I'm not setting a bare foot in that grass again!
Shoes?
Your shoes were right here.
Eh? You found them in a place like that?
Pretty sure I tossed them that way...
Someone must've brought them here, then.
Right! That's gotta be it!
But who would do such a thing?
No reason any of the immigrants would come to here.
But who'd ever be interested
in fooling around with some shoes?
Shh.
I figured it out!
I know who fooled around with the shoes.
Who?
Just don't look at him.
Hiding in the shadow from the rock
to the side behind me.
Could it be him, who...
That's right, gotta be him.
The kid that owns that cute baby bear.
I got some questions.
Like where does one find an animal like that.
Hey, I've got something I want to ask you.
Will you please tell me?
That cute animal you're keeping...
Why did he run off?
He probably thinks we're scary.
No, it's not about us.
They probably think all the white people
who arrived to this land are scary.
Really? So you didn't make it to Adelaide?
Well, we judged that we should carry
injured Mr. Jamling home first.
Certainly! You two did a great thing.
When we just got there,
Mrs. Jamling couldn't stop thanking dad in tears.
What about Arthur?
Hurried to row into the open sea
to bring the doctor from the ship.
When it's raining and blowing so hard,
rowing the boat all the way to the ship must be hard!
Did he go there alone?
Yeah.
I can't see the ship that brought us here!
You think it sailed back to England already?
It was supposed to stay anchored
at this bay for three or four days more.
That's right. That ship still has
our prefabricated home on board.
It's probably still anchored in the usual place,
but we can't see it for the haze.
Oh? What could that be?
Seems like a boat. Someone's riding it.
You're right. Three people are riding it.
Who'd wanna ride such a small boat
amidst such high waves?
Totally not me!
Look, the waves are rocking it so hard.
I wouldn't wanna ride it either at a time like this.
Those must be very courageous people.
Oh? Isn't it your very own dad?
There, the one who looks this way.
It can't be! Our dad is in Adelaide today.
I suppose. Just someone alike, then.
No, it's dad for sure!
He's waving to us!
Then it must certainly be someone we know!
So, your dad's brother or something?
No, that's gotta be dad himself!
Yes, that's dad. No two ways about it.
Dad!
Hey! Dad!
Well, this way, Doctor.
Jump on the ground.
Right... I'm... now...
Good, good.
Get yourself together, Doctor.
Ah... I can't take it. I can't take it anymore,
now I'm both booze-drunk and seasick-drunk.
W-What's that? Now even the earth is shaking!
Ah, can't take it. I can't take it!
You guys. Why are you playing on the shore
during such a terrible weather?
Hey, dad! Did you ride this boat
all the way from Adelaide?{/came from ... on the ship
Ouch!
Doctor, that hurt like hell!
Ah, I see... How about here? Here.
Ouch! Doctor!
Does that mean the bone is broken?
I see. Seems to me like the bone is intact.
Yes. You'll be fine. It'll heal up in a week or so.
You'll need to keep it chilled with some cold water.
Doctor, in two or three days,
we'll need to move to Adelaide.
What was that?
Do you have a wagon or something?
Of course not!
Will you go there on foot?
I hired an oxcart for our things. As for me...
You can't walk.
Forget about those "two or three days."
Forget about it while you still have a chance.
But there's plenty of work for me in Adelaide.
Ah... Doctor! I'm a carpenter,
and they're erecting a whole new city over there.
Carpenters are in mad demand...
One week!
Well, if possible,
ten days of rest would be even better.
And remember, it's not just for the good of your leg,
but for your own good as well!
Ten days...
Change the compress frequently enough.
Okay.
Then, I'll have my leave now.
Thanks a lot, Doctor.
By the way, the sailor that rowed the boat for us
is waiting on the shore, right?
No, I think John went to my tent.
Oh? Why so?
That's because John is on good terms with my daughter.
Oh? I see. Right, right, right!
Mr. Popple, I'm grateful for everything.
While you're here, there was something
I wanted to talk to you about.
Okay, Doctor. I'm sorry for making you wait.
This way, please.
You don't happen to have any whiskey?
Yes, but not much of it.
Could you treat me to just a cup?
Sure, no problem.
If the weather is that hellish,
I need it simply to endure another trip on a boat.
Seems like it stopped raining.
But this wind is still raging!
I'm seriously worried about going back on a boat.
Good afternoon, Mr. Pettywell.
Hello.
The hell! The damnation!
Darling. What are saying?
Sorry.
I'll have to ferry that boozed Doctor
back to the ship soon.
But I didn't think I'd get to see you today.
Neither did I.
What about tomorrow?
I don't know yet.
Ah! Welcome back, dad.
Hey there.
Doctor, you're done with the checkup already?
A date inside an empty barrel?
Well, ain't that romantic?
W-We're just taking a shelter from the rain!
No-no, it's no use hiding it.
Someone here just told me about what's going on.
O-Okay...
But what a pity - in less than a week,
you two will have to part for good.
Even if...
Even if there'd be oceans between us,
our hearts will always stay together.
My, oh my. Now you even got me envious!
Doctor, we don't have much...
Yes, appreciate it.
Well, John, we're leaving!
Tomorrow I'm going to Adelaide for sure
to find a place where we'll assemble
the prefabricated home.
Everyone is fed up with this cramped tent, right?
And so, I ended up tending to Mr. Jamling
all day long instead.
But Mr. Jamling also offered me something
as a token of his gratitude.
Thing is, there are barely any horses or oxen
fit for transporting luggage in this area.
Yesterday, Mr. Jamling scouted a fantastic ox
and signed a contract with its owner.
But now he won't be able to walk
on the day they settled on.
So he passed to me his right to use that oxcart.
Then, we'll be able to transport
all our belongings in one run?
I hope so.
Even the big sofa I got from Mary
that's still on the ship?
Certainly! According to Mr. Jamling,
the transportation of big items is currently
the one most difficult task around these places.
Really, I'm so glad, honey!
That makes getting the land our only remaining concern.
By night, the rain had stopped.
The wind had settled down too.
Of course, I'd be way happier,
sleeping in a proper house in the city of Adelaide.
But tonight, I wouldn't trade
this barrel house for anything.
I think, Lucy-May might also
feel this way about it.
Dad and Ben went to Adelaide again
to look for a good plot.
But they couldn't obtain
neither the land, nor the oxcart.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A City Called Adelaide".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you