South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 04 - First Explorations
This is our third morning in Southern Australia.
Good morning, Mr. Popple.
Good morning, Mr. Parker.
How is your tent looking?
Better than ever, thanks to you.
I'm no longer anxious.
Let's see.
I slept like a log last nigh.
It'll stand firm even if a storm comes.
Are you going to Adelaide?
Yes. We need to be quick
about finding a good spot for our future house.
I'm sure you'll find a fine site.
Thank you. Still...
Eh? What is it?
No, nothing at all.
Since we left England, a whole bunch
of unexpected trouble found us.
We can't really afford being picky now...
That's what I though! Let's all do our best!
Well then.
Come, Ben.
Okay.
Don't get lost on your way to Adelaide.
Thank you!
Lucy-May! Let's get it over with quickly,
without playing around!
I wonder if dad and Ben made it to Adelaide.
Don't say nonsense.
To get to Adelaide you'd have to walk through the forest
for over ten kilometers.
No way they'd do it so soon.
How much is ten kilometers?
Well, it's like going from our home in England
to the city of Burton.
Then it's not really too far.
But there aren't any paved roads yet,
so it's easy to get lost in that forest.
Our dad would never get lost in the woods!
I suppose.
You'd better!
I thought this road would be a little harder to make out.
For the moment, this is the only option.
There are no other roads,
connecting the coast to Adelaide.
Hey, dad.
Why didn't they found Adelaide right next to the sea?
Aren't cities normally placed close to the harbor?
Hm... That's true.
Even I don't know all the details.
A major argument is being fought over whether the city
should be distanced from the ocean or not.
Transporting various goods to and from the ship
seems awfully inconvenient this way.
When the city is away from the harbor, I mean.
The local surveyor-general Colonel Light
seems to be a very obstinate man.
Following the Colonel's lead, the city was founded
about ten kilometers inland from the sea.
Colonel Light?
Yes. The Colonel strives to build Adelaide
into a model colonial capital.
They say the city is being built
in strict accordance with his plan.
Eh? I wonder what his vision for Adelaide is.
Ben, don't set your hopes too high.
They've just barely started building it.
It's still nothing more than a few scattered houses
among forests and fields.
There's not many people living in it?
Yes. The city's populace is mere 300 residents.
However, the immigrants will keep following
in our footsteps at an ever-increasing rate.
In a blink of an eye, 300 will turn into 600.
600 will turn into 1200.
1200 will turn...
That'd be...
Into 2400.
Right, right. It'll be growing steadily now.
Clara, seems like we won't have to do any more trips.
Yes.
Can we go play around, then?
Ask mom first.
Where did she go?
Mrs. Jamling's invited her for some tea.
Inviting people for tea while you're living in a tent?
Sugar?
Yes, one spoon.
Delicious.
I knew you'd be able to appreciate
the sophisticated taste of this black tea.
Another cup?
Thank you. Maybe just a half.
You shouldn't hold back.
See? I still have a full tin can more.
Mom!
Mom...
Clara said we don't need to go fetch any more water!
Can we go play now?
Where are your manners?
You didn't even greet Mrs. Jamling properly!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Good morning. Billy should be somewhere around here.
Want to play together?
Yes!
Can we, mom?
Let's see. Ever since we disembarked here,
you two have been of great help to me...
Fine then.
You can be free for the rest of the day.
Yay!
Then, I'll be playing with Billy!
Wait for me, Kate!
Can't you play by yourself for once?
I can't!
Your family is moving to Adelaide soon?
I think it may very well be so.
I'm sure Arthur will find a good plot there.
My husband left yesterday
and still hasn't returned from Adelaide.
My, do you mean to say
he didn't even come home to sleep?
Yes. Although he said he'd be back by night...
I'm sure, whatever he does,
it takes him more time than expected.
It must be that.
It can be awfully tricky to make it through the forest
and return home after dark.
That's what I thought too...
That's right!
There's nothing to worry about.
Yes...
Ah!
How about another cup?
Dad, are we halfway there or so?
Why? Are you tired of walking?
Just a bit.
We can take a rest.
It's alright.
Let's hurry to get out of the woods.
This is probably the right road, I believe...
Eh? Dad, what did you just say?
Just saying that we probably didn't take the wrong road.
Are you sure it's all alright?
Probably, yes.
But it's the first time I'm going through here.
Come to think of it,
we haven't met anyone in a while.
Yes.
Let's take a rest after all.
Okay.
All right...
Will you drink?
Yeah.
Hm? What's wrong?
It was like I've just heard someone's voice.
Someone's voice?
I didn't hear anything.
Really?
Dad!
Now I heard something too.
It was kinda like a growl.
Maybe there are some aborigines nearby?
Aborigines?
Seems to me like the sound came from that direction.
Aborigines are living in these woods,
so it could be them.
Dad!
Yes.
Someone is definitely calling for help.
Let's check it out, dad.
Agreed.
What now, just a rabbit?
Ah, it startled me.
Oh!
That voice again.
That way!
You can go play there,
but promise me that you'll listen to Billy.
Oh? But Billy is just five months older than me!
A difference of five months is still a difference.
One way or another, do go too far away, okay?
And be sure to look after Lucy-May.
I can't take that much responsibility, mom!
How come? Why are you saying
you can't look after your little sister?
That child is not like all the other kids!
Once she lays an eye on a peculiar animal,
you can't drag her away from it with a horse.
It's especially irritating when we're in a hurry.
You're only going towards the shore today, right?
Should she spot a peculiar animal,
just let her watch it all she wants.
If she sees a cute one, I can put up with that.
But with Lucy-May,
be it a centipede, a lizard, or a caterpillar -
she's fascinated with their peculiarities all the same!
Gosh, I hate the caterpillars.
Lucy-May, be so kind as to only adore cute things.
But caterpillars are cute!
There, see?
Ah!
You're bringing this along too?
I wanna let Marsh play on the shore!
He'd be a nuisance.
I'll be carrying him myself, it's fine!
Ah! Billy is here.
Sorry for the wait.
I entrust them to your care, then.
Okay!
Then, we'll be on our way, mom.
On our way!
On our way.
Billy!
Your dad still hasn't returned from Adelaide?
Yes. Still hasn't returned.
Take care!
Okay!
Help me! Is someone there?
Mr. Jamling!
How did I ever manage to stray away from the road?
When it's pitch black, it's nothing special.
I should've stayed overnight in Adelaide.
I probably made my wife sick worried
when I didn't come home last night.
I'm so indebted to you, Mr. Popple...
No, no. We're finally on the road again.
Right you are.
Ah! Put me down somewhere around here, please.
Okay, putting you down.
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
I hope you didn't break your leg there.
No. It'll probably be alright.
Just a sprain, I believe.
Now then, how do we bring you back to your tent?
Oh, there's no need!
Weren't you on your way to Adelaide?
Please don't give me no mind.
I'll do it, somehow...
Right! I'll crawl back home.
I can see the road clearly now,
so I cause you any more trouble.
With that leg, you're in no position
to return on your own.
We can go to Adelaide any other day.
Still...
Either way, we're not leaving you here.
Mr. Jamling, please hold on to my shoulder,
so that we walk you back on just one leg.
Ben, don't forget Mr. Jamling's belongings.
Okay!
Now, let's try to stand up, Mr. Jamling.
Thank you, Mr. Popple.
Never mind it.
Walking on the sand sure is tiring.
You're right.
My legs are sore already.
We didn't even walk all that far yet.
But I'm sure no other kid ever went this far.
Lucy-May!
Stop falling behind! You promised!
I remember, alright?
What's in there?
A cute bug!
A bug?
Look!
My! What a disgusting bug!
Toss it away somewhere!
Never!
Hey.
Probably no one has ever been to the other side of that cape.
Right. Let's hurry up, then.
My feet hurt terribly now! I'll go barefoot!
Mom said we shouldn't be walking
around here barefoot!
Yes. Of course she did.
But unless you spill it, mom won't find out.
Oh! It feels so much better!
This way, I can walk all day!
There!
Did you throw away your shoes?
Of course not. Just deposited.
We'll be passing through here on the way back.
I still don't understand.
It'll be fine if you memorize the look of these rocks.
I'll take my off too.
But I'd rather bring them with me.
Now, let's hurry to the other side of that cape!
The exploration finally starts!
Wait for me, Kate!
Okay...
Really, I did something embarrassing.
And now you're also having to waste
your whole day because of me.
You should stop saying that.
More importantly, I see you tired your leg.
I ought to carry you on my back again. Here, get on.
I'm sorry for being so heavy...
Back in England, we'd catch a carriage by now.
But here, not a single person passed by yet.
Ah, right!
Is something wrong?
No, it's not about that. I believe, you plan to eventually transport all your belongings to Adelaide, right?
Certainly. The reason I wanted to go
to Adelaide today was to hire a wagon.
Well... There aren't many wagons in Adelaide now.
Eh? There are no wagons?
But then, how in the world do I transport our things?
No, I didn't say there are none at all.
It's just that they are very scarce.
After all, the population increased sharply.
If not a wagon, a bull would do as well.
I'll hire an oxcart.
There aren't many oxcarts either.
Then, do you mean to say that even if I go to Adelaide
to hire a wagon tomorrow, I won't find any?
That is very likely.
But that'd mean we have to live
in that seaside tent encampment indefinitely.
Well, eventually, you'll probably find a cart...
I went to all the trouble of bringing
a prefabricated home here from England.
But in the end, I can't even
transport it to Adelaide from the coast?
Rome wasn't built in a day either.
The surveying is falling behind,
not in the city alone.
The farmland surveying is delayed as well.
None of the applicants can get their plots.
Farmland surveying is delayed?!
That's right.
My new farm here, in Southern Australia...
I came here thinking I'd be able
to build a farm of my dreams.
But if I won't even be able to get any farmland,
what in the world was it that we came all the way to the Southern Australia for?
What did we come here for?
Oh!
Dad!
Huh?
Ah, thank you.
It's here! Look, it's here!
Be quiet, Kate!
Can you do it, Lucy-May?
Leave this to me!
Jeez, you're clumsy.
This time I'll do it for sure.
No ships ever pass through here.
Well, it's a pretty big gulf, isn't it?
That's true. It was first discovered by Captain Flinders.
They called it Gulf St Vincent.
I know that much myself.
After that, Colonel Light sailed around the bay
and charted it, right?
Yeah.
Colonel Light is also the one responsible
for planning Adelaide.
Isn't he a man of great merit?
You bet! When I grow up,
I'll be going on expeditions too.
And then, it'll be searching for places that Captain Flinders and Colonel Light never set their eyes on.
I'll join the expedition party too.
A girl can't do that!
Well, I will.
Impossible!
No it isn't!
It is!
It's not!
Ah! I saw something!
What could it be? It looked like a person.
Don't say nonsense!
No people ever visit this place.
But it's true. A head just showed up
from behind that rock!
Your eyes must've played a trick on you.
I swear, I saw it!
Look! Something peeks out over here.
I felt it too, but I couldn't get a good look.
Hey, Billy, can you go take a look?
Me? But there aren't supposed to be any people around here!
Didn't you wanna become an explorer
when you grow up?
Let's go together, then...
All three of us will go!
They're saying something...
Doesn't sound like English.
What kind of animal is that?
Must be sea lions.
They don't look like seals to me.
Sea lions?
They sure look cute enough. Surprisingly.
It looked over here!
I hope they don't bite...
It'll be fine! If we don't do anything to them,
they won't do anything to us either.
But they're scary!
They aren't scary.
I'll go take a closer look!
Don't! There, didn't you see what great teeth is has?
Lucy-May, it's best that we don't go any closer.
I'm going there alone.
Cut it! It's too dangerous!
I'll just quickly look and touch them.
Don't!
Lucy-May!
We all knew how much
an animal aficionado Lucy-May is.
But when she decided to approach those bizarre animals,
the sea lions, things got really scary.
Look out!
Lucy-May...
To bring the naval surgeon Dr. Deighton ashore
to examine Mr. Jamling's leg,
dad had to row the boat out in the storming sea.
Next time on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"After the Rain".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you