South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 22 - Of Bricks and Dingo Puppies
Have you forgotten us, Monocle? It's us!
Monocle, where is Mr. Long?
Ah! He's over there.
Huh?
Good morning, Mr. Long!
Good morning!
Right, good morning.
Sorry we interrupted your afternoon nap!
Uh? It's nuffin, nuffin.
I can return to my nap anytime I want,
but it's not all that often that I have someone to talk to.
Glad to know, if so.
By the way, are you sure you can afford
a detour to come see me?
Yes, we'll be fine.
We told mom we'd go here, alright.
Now that's delighting.
That said, I don't suppose you've come here
to have a chat with me, have you?
You got any business here?
Yes. We were hoping to learn
a little something from you.
Oh? What is it?
That thing from three days ago.
You know, the wolf-like one...
Oh, dingo, innit?
So we've seen that dingo
in the grassland near the river.
It snatched away the rabbit
that we two were chasing.
It's a dingo!
You brute, it was ours!
I felt so sorry for that poor rabbit.
And if it attacks any of the sheep
in the same fashion...
The place where we saw dingo
is not too far away from here.
So we figured it's best that we inform you,
since we always see you surrounded by sheep.
Hm... Why, thanks a bunch!
It's a good thing you decided to tell me.
If I don't keep a vigilant lookout for a dingo
coming here at night, my sheep would be done for!
But we've seen it during the day!
Yeah, I figured as much.
But that's what I got Monocle here for.
As long as he keeps his watch,
no dingo would dare to come near.
But it's a different story at night.
You don't suppose the dingos
are copious in this area?
Hm. I can't know for sure either,
but I think it's one or two at best.
But the word is, dingos prefer to flock together
on the vast prairies further inland, rather than here.
If some random dingo strays to here, it was likely
exiled from the pack for one reason or another.
Exiled from the pack?
But of course, that's just me speculating.
Nobody can know for sure.
Even though it looks
not one bit different from a dog!
Ah!
Look out!
Away!
You rogue! You!
Get this! And this!
Away! Away! Away!
That's true. But they're different in character.
I don't really think so.
How can you say that after we've seen a dingo
pouncing on both the sheep and the rabbit?
But it doesn't try to pounce on humans, does it?
My, you forgot already?
On the way from the seashore to Adelaide...
It was just following after us,
and eventually, it never attempted to attack us.
It's true that dingos
don't seem very interested in humans.
So I figured, if you raise a dingo
from very little age,
maybe it can make just as good a friend
for humans as the usual dogs do?
It appears that among the aborigines
there are some who succeeded in taming a dingo.
Maybe that's also thanks
to adopting it from the little age.
So adopting a dingo is the way to go!
Hold it, hold it! You'd best drop it right away.
That kind of a wild beast might stay tame most
of the time, but then fly into a rage all of a sudden!
And then, you couldn't keep it at bay.
Still... One day, I'll do it!
Better give up, Lucy-May.
Mr. Popple!
Oh!
Good morning, Mr. Bernard.
Good morning. That sack sure looks heavy.
I've got some clay in there.
Clay?
Yes. I was thinking of making some bricks.
If you do this, clay and sand
would mix together nicely.
Maybe you should've gathered a bit more sand?
No. For now, this should be enough.
If we switch to a full-blown production,
we can always get more.
Wah!
And here!
Ow!
Ah! Looks like something interesting they're doing!
Lemme try it, too!
Lemme try!
You dunces!
Dad is mixing the clay and the sand
in order to make some good bricks.
Ah! So we'll build a new house with bricks?
Well then, this much should do.
I'd prefer to put them into an actual mold,
but we don't have that now.
You two feel free to use up the remaining clay
for whatever you like.
Can we mold an animal from it?
Sure, go ahead.
Just remember that it has to be something small.
Yay!
What will you do with them now?
Wait until they dry up,
then burn them in a kiln.
That's how the bricks gain their reddish-brown hue.
I think I'll make a dog.
I'll make a plate.
And what should I make from it?
Hey, you two. The meal is ready.
We were just about to go ourselves.
What did you make with it, Kate?
A toy ball.
And you, Lucy-May?
What could this be?
It's a dog.
Eh? I thought it was pig at first.
Molding small things is hard!
Hm...
Well, whatever. Hurry up inside.
Not happening! Absolutely unacceptable!
But I just want to see
if we can fire them there at all!
This kiln is where we bake our bread!
Trying to fire bricks at a place like that
is straight-up madness!
You can only fire bricks at a very high temperature.
And this kiln is currently the place
with highest temperature in the house.
Then please think of another way of producing them.
I'm sure it's nothing you can't do.
Well, I... could build another kiln for firing the bricks.
But that would take time!
And that's why using the kiln
in which we bake bread is unacceptable!
But honey...
Not happening. Absolutely not happening!
Dad was hoping he'd be allowed a quick test
to see if he can fire bricks
in the kiln that we use for baking bread.
But mom was ultimately deaf to his pleas.
Left with no choice, dad had to devise
another method for doing it.
Dad, I brought it.
Good, leave them there.
That felt very hot. Perhaps, we could
do just as fine with this method.
Alright, now it's your toys' turn.
Okay!
Dad, about how long will it take?
I can't say for sure...
At most, it may take up to four or five hours.
Oh? It takes that long?
Building a brick house is a big deal, I imagine.
Hm.
Ah, you three, I need you to go gather some firewood.
We'll need way more of it, by the looks of things.
Okay! I'll go to those woods in the east.
So will I, surely enough.
And I'll go to the riverside.
Maybe I should also go there instead?
Sis, are you that quick to betray me?
Well I never promised
that I'd go to the woods with you, did I?
That's true, alright.
But you considered going with me first, did you not?
Guess it's riverside, after all.
Do as you please!
Lucy-May! Wait for me, hey!
Hm?
Hey, boy!
A wild dog just smelled these rabbits
and tried to sneak on me.
So I shot the bastard down!
A wild dog?
So he shot your mom?
Ah, Mr. Bernard, please put them in softly.
We don't want the bricks to deform.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Let's hope it comes out nicely.
Agreed. It'd be amazing if you manage
to build a brick house all on your own.
We got the firewood, dad.
Good job.
And you've also split quite a lot of firewood here.
Yeah.
Say, Mr. Bernard, haven't you heard
a gunshot some while ago?
Yeah, I heard it.
I knew it!
It came from the river's direction.
Ben hadn't returned yet?
Ah... That's right.
Strange to see it taking more time for Ben
than for you two.
No, no, no, no, no!
You're burning a bonfire when it's that hot?
Welcome back, doctor.
Doctor, you've been on a house visit today?
Yeah. Had to go a bit too far this time.
You must be tired then, aren't you?
Yeah... But on the bright side,
I got this as a souvenir.
Look.
First-class booze!
If you'd like it, I'll pour a bit for you as well.
Well, well, I'd be greatly obliged.
Eh, but for now, as you'd expect,
I need water even more than booze.
And... Here...
Got it.
Doctor Deighton!
Huh?
Doctor!
Good thing you're back already.
Eh? Someone needs help somewhere?
Why are you that flustered?
What happened, Ben?
Didn't you go there to gather firewood?
Ah... I forgot it there.
You met the man who fired the gun, didn't you?
Yes, that's right.
Doctor, could I ask you to follow me for a bit?
Did someone get hurt, then?
It's not exactly a human...
Not a human, that is to say...
Why, then, was it some animal, Ben?
Yes, sorta.
Well I ain't no vet doctor, Ben.
I know that. But I thought maybe you could still help it.
It's a dog who's been shot at.
My! Poor thing!
And a small baby...
What? A human?
The dog's baby.
Ah...
The dog's baby is shot, too?
No, just yowling by mom's side.
How sad! Where was that, Ben?
There! It's where I went fishing the other day.
You know, with Colonel Light!
Got it!
Hey! Wait a minute, you!
You won't find it without me coming along!
Doctor, is it a lost cause?
Well, I can't go as far as to say that.
At any rate, I'll go take a look.
Hurry up! Hurry, doctor!
Ah...
It's a kaput.
As I thought...
Ben, this doesn't look to me like a stray dog.
It must be a dingo, I think.
Poor thing. You're all alone
to fend for yourself now, aren't you?
I don't think we should leave
the mama dog here like this.
I suppose not.
Then you just bury her yonder and be done with it.
Doctor, I owe you a big one.
Aye. Too bad I came late.
Lucy-May, how about we take this puppy home?
Of course we will!
Were you really going to leave it here, Ben?
On the opposite.
I will look after it myself.
Eh? You will?
You got any problem with me looking after it?
I'll look after it!
You're already having to look after
both a goat and a hamster!
And I want a dog, too!
But this is no ordinary dog!
A dingo is closer to the wolves than to dogs!
Even so, I wanna keep it!
Come on, Ben!
Please let me have this puppy!
Not happening. That one is mine.
Brother, pretty please!
That's just insolent, Lucy-May!
I was the one who found it.
I get to keep it!
You're a stinger, Ben! I refuse!
I guess Lucy-May just never changes.
Kate, you go tell her that I get to keep that fella.
I doubt she'll let go of that pup now.
Mr. Bernard.
Would you help me bury this dog?
Sure. But we'll need some shovels first.
In the end, we'll just have
to return home once more, won't we?
Mom, I need a bit of goat milk.
You go milk it yourself.
I got my hands full already.
My, you found a puppy somewhere?
You don't mind me keeping it, do you, mom?
As long as you look after it responsibly.
Sure thing!
Recently, I myself came to think
that having a dog in this house could be beneficial.
I'm so happy!
But my hands are also full for the moment,
so you'll have to milk the goat yourself.
Okay!
You stay here and behave, little puppy.
Ah? Lucy-May, what are you doing?
Pouring a goat milk for...
Ah! Kate, it's running away!
Huh?
Kate, hurry up! Hurry up after it!
And so, I came to ask for a shovel.
Which means you left Mr. Bernard over there?
Lucy-May, this way!
Ah! Kate, you go over there!
Ouch!
It ran away?
Hey, little one, why are you trying
to run off already?
It headed for the hills
as I was about to give it some goat milk.
That must mean it's not really hungry.
Is it really?
Could it be trying to return to mother?
Uh-huh. That must be it.
I'm going to bury the mama dog now.
Until then, I'm letting you look after it, temporarily.
Ben...
Hm. I know, Lucy-May.
Why don't we look after it together?
Deal!
I think it's best that you drop that notion, Ben.
What do you mean?
This whole thing about keeping a dingo pup.
On the outside, it certainly resembles a dog.
But you shouldn't let it trick you,
as it's still majorly feral on the inside.
That little puppy doesn't really strike me as feral.
Well it's 'cause it's still a child, isn't it?
Strangely, I feel like that puppy
would remain like this even when it gets big.
Ben, it wouldn't be wrong to say
I'm no dingo connoisseur either.
But hear this -
supposing that puppy grows big, once its dangerous nature, different from that of dogs, resurfaces...
You understand, right? When that happens,
it's going to get killed just like its parent.
It can't be...
No - if you won't have the courage to put it down,
better not to adopt it in the first place.
Just dispose of it somewhere now,
while you still can.
If you do that, the kid probably won't be able to forage for food himself and would die from natural reasons.
I can't! Just not to abandon it!
In that case, hear this: make sure you remember
at all times what I just said.
Dingo is not a dog.
Dingo is a dingo, down to the last hair.
A wild, vicious beast, remember?
Lucy-May is probably still too young
to understand any of that.
But you're supposed to be old enough
to comprehend what I say.
Well, let's hurry up burying it.
Good night to everyone.
Ah?
Oh!
Ah, that's a funny sleeping face.
Hey.
Hm... Well, this thing is still closer to a wolf.
Is that to say it's just as dangerous, darling?
Hm.
My...
Lucy-May, forget about keeping that puppy.
But it's so awfully cute!
Not happening!
It's going to be a disaster if it bites Tob!
And when it grows big, Tob wouldn't be alone in this.
Everyone of us will be in danger.
My! I never had any idea
it was that kind of dog!
Lucy-May, it's out of question!
I thought any creature can become sociable
if it grows up with humans from very little age!
Isn't that right, dad?
Yes. That might just as well stand true.
Exactly! And I'm sure that dog
would become a great friend for us...
But hear this -
dingos are apparently prone to attacking sheep.
It could become sociable,
but still wanting to attack your goat Sticky.
The shepherd Mr. Long
also said it's best not to try to tame them.
He's right.
I want you to think twice
about keeping that puppy, Lucy-May.
Now then, the bricks
should be thoroughly fired by now.
Lucy-May, in two or three days,
we'll have to abandon that puppy.
Lucy-May!
Ben?
Ah!
Doctor! Doctor!
Huh?
Oh? Lucy-May, what is it?
Do you know where Ben went?
Now, I remember him going out...
But to where?
Who knows.
Let's see.
Hm?
Hm.
Ah!
Bungled it? Goddammit.
Dad, Ben is not in the tent!
He took the puppy and went somewhere!
Hm.
Oh? My clay dog is done?
Ah!
It broke.
I really don't wanna kill you, buddy.
We brought the baby dingo back home.
And we also gave him a name of Little.
Tell me, Little, we'll be friends until the end of times, won't we?
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Your Name is Little"
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you