South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 03 - The Replacement
Well, you're quite a cute-looking fella.
Listen, please don't bite me.
What's wrong, Billy?
What are you doing? Hey, hey!
Can you be quiet for just a minute, please?
This fellow just won't budge!
I'm definitely keeping you!
My little sister Lucy-May was immediately
head over heels for the cute animal from the tree top.
She decided to keep him no matter what.
But on our way home, an aboriginal family
appeared out of nowhere in front of us.
No!
Oh?
Lucy-May, chin up!
We'll find another animal like that.
Kate, Kate! Did you see it?
The way he was clinging to that boy.
I saw it.
That was really darn cute!
I'll find him.
And then keep him, no matter what anyone says!
I'd wanna keep that fella too.
Now, it's best that we hurry back to mom.
It already took us unbelievably long.
That's right. Let's hurry.
Lucy-May!
Huh?
You're carrying your bucket yourself!
Ah! My bad, my bad!
Even though you finally brought the water,
I can't really thank you since it's taken you this long!
We ran into aboriginals.
Aboriginals?
Yes. The one was carrying a spear.
A spear?
But they didn't do anything to you, right?
The aboriginal child plucked off me
the cute animal we've caught earlier.
But it it belonged to that boy, seems like.
He had a solid proof,
so we couldn't object much.
What kind of animal was it?
I don't know what it is called, but it had a large nose,
a fluffy fur and it was the cutest ever!
What were you planning to use
such an animal for, even if you caught it?
I thought I'd keep it.
Didn't we already bring along from England
your hamster Marsh?
Even though father and me pleased you not to!
But Marsh is a dear friend of mine.
And that's why Marsh alone is enough.
Adopting yet another new animal now is unthinkable!
I told her so too,
but she just wouldn't give an ear!
Forget it.
It's out of question, Lucy-May!
That's a pretty loud argument you got here.
How is your fever?
Decreased already?
Yes. Seems like it decreased.
I suppose. It's less severe than before.
But it's best that you don't move too much yet.
But everyone else is working hard.
I'm the only one napping.
That's totally excusable for someone ill.
But can't I be helpful in any way whatsoever?
One way or another,
you should get a good rest today.
This is a mother's order.
Okay.
Marsh!
I wonder what that animal even feeds on.
Nuts, probably.
Why else would it climb a tree?
That must be the case.
I'll catch a creature so cute whatever it takes.
When that happens, get along nicely, okay?
My little sister Lucy-May
is really into extraordinary animals.
That's why she often happens to know
the names of animals she had never seen.
However, we didn't yet get a chance
to learn about koalas, who only live in Australia.
As it turned out later, koala's menu
consists exclusively of eucalyptus leaves.
My, my, this tablecloth is permeated with mold.
After three months in a damp
ship's underbelly, it's not a wonder.
Is that the trunk dad brought from the ship?
It is.
Then, dad and Ben went to Adelaide already?
No.
And where are they?
Mr. Parker's tent kept collapsing
and he just couldn't do anything about it,
so Ben and your dad are setting it up anew.
Now, Ben. Let's do it!
Okay!
Heave-ho!
Good. That should do it.
Alright, now the other side.
Okay!
Um... Are you sure you don't want me to help?
We can handle it, so please stop loitering about
and get seated over there.
I-If you say so...
Alright! Pull now, Ben!
Then, I'll take your word for it.
Now then...
Good, good. Right, that's the way.
Here...
Temporarily secure it on your end!
If you think about it,
I'm rather an urbanite type of person.
So it's only natural I wasn't
particularly good at setting up tents.
I suppose.
Last night, when I had to prop up the poles myself,
out of fear of the tent collapsing, I couldn't get any sleep!
You should've asked me sooner.
Good grief. I disembarked in Australia just to spend the first night awake, propping up the tent poles!
That'll make a good memory for the future you.
For when you'll be living in a marvelous house.
Marvelous house?
You'll probably build one in Adelaide, won't you?
No, I'm not going to Adelaide.
I'll be doing business right here!
Here?
Exactly. The flow of immigrants will only be growing stronger.
Before long, they'll build a proper wharf.
When that happens,
we'll need a trading post.
I'm sure my business will rise and prosper here!
It may, or it may not.
No, it definitely will!
Hey, Ben! I'll stretch the rope from my end once more,
so hold it over there too!
Okay.
And then, tie another knot, but a tight one this time.
If we don't secure it tightly now, Mr. Parker
will have to spend another night propping up the poles.
That's right, Ben!
Please secure it tightly!
Ah! They're here, here!
Looks like they're almost done!
Ben! Is it finished already?
Yes. Did you want something here?
We came to check how you're doing.
How attentive of you.
It's true! Mr. Pettywell is also having a hard time
trying to fix his tent now!
When Mr. Pettywell's tent collapsed on him yesterday,
we couldn't help bursting into laughter!
But Mr. Pettywell got real mad!
Of course he did!
But Mr. Pettywell had such an important look on his face
while the tent was slowly descending on him...
Hey, Ben! Stretch it harder!
Okay!
Well...
Can I ask young ladies for a small favor?
What is it?
Here is some lamb meat.
I only bought it the other day, so it's a fresh meat.
See?
As a payment for your father fixing my tent today,
I'd like to give you this meat.
Wow!
That meat hadn't been salted yet, right?
Of course! It's fresh meat!
Wow! I hate salted meat most of all!
It always has that weird smell.
This meat is not oozing any weird smells at all.
Now, would you take it to your mother?
Okay, sir.
Goodbye!
My... I can't remember the last time
when we had some fresh meat!
All the meat they served on the ship was salted.
So it must've been over a hundred days ago!
I thought so.
I sure hope you two said a lot of thanks to Mr. Parker.
Did you say it?
I said it.
No, all you've said was "Goodbye", and nothing else!
Lies! I said "Thank you!"
It was you who clearly didn't say anything!
I think I probably said my thanks.
It's a natural thing to do
when receiving goods from other people.
But I'm sure you never said any thanks!
I swear to God, it was you who said nothing!
Enough of that, both of you!
Mom, I'll leave it here.
When your dad and Ben return, I'll start cooking.
Could you go check on Tob, Clara?
Okay.
Now, now. It's alright, Tob.
What's the matter?
I wanna back home!
This is our home now, Tob.
Wanna home!
We'll have to be patient for the time being.
Once we get to Adelaide,
we'll assemble a wonderful prefabricated home
we brought from England for us to live in.
Ah! Somebody... Somebody catch this dog!
Kate!
Hey!
Oh no!
Somebody get that dog!
Stop!
Catch it!
Mom! Hurry! Hurry up and catch that dog!
What's going on, Clara?
There! See that dog?
That dog stole your payment, the meat!
Dammit!
Catch that thief dog!
Hold it!
Wait! Wait!
Catch it!
Catch that damn dog!
Here, here!
You're not getting away! Take this!
Hey, what's the matter, Happy?
Something happened to you?
I say, what's this all about?
Why is everyone collectively bullying my dog?
That dog of yours is a thief!
He is a thief?
I'd never believe that baloney.
Pardon my bluntness,
but this dog is better fed than you are.
Right, Happy?
Here! You can see for yourself!
Your dog did this to our hard-earned meat...
My, my, Happy,
you feel like playing pranks today, do you?
This is by no means a prank, Mr. Pettywell!
What is it you're trying to say, then?
Are you implying I have to pay to you
the price of that meat?
How much do you want for it, boy?
Well...
Uh...
Hold it, Annie.
Dad...
Now, return home, you three.
Mr. Pettywell, that meat was priceless to us.
That's why I said I'd reimburse it.
I'm not afraid to assume responsibility
for my dog's tricks.
It's not about compensating us with money!
I don't understand one bit of what you're saying!
Are you oblivious of the very concept of apology?
What is the logic behind me
apologizing for the dog's pranks?
Mr. Pettywell!
A man such as you...
Honey...
Let's go home, honey.
We can no longer eat it, can we?
After such a long time, everyone hoped
to taste some fresh meat again.
Is it really inedible now?
Let's throw it away, mom.
No.
But what will we do with it, mom?
We'll wash it then eat it.
This fresh meat is too precious.
But to wash it...
The sea is great for washing it.
After that, we can eat it.
I can wash it!
I'll go too!
I can do just fine without you!
I said I'll go, so I'll go!
You'll only get in the way if you come!
You're a meanie, Kate!
Be careful now.
Ben, can you come along?
Okay.
It's fine, I can do it alone.
Kate, that much washing should be enough.
It's so much smaller now...
Back when we received it from Mr. Parker,
it was actually this big!
Liar.
Who is?
You, of course!
What makes me a liar?
When we received it from Mr. Parker,
it was no bigger than this.
It was about this big!
Right, Ben?
It was never that big!
It was really about this size!
It was this size, I said!
No! It was like this!
Give it a rest, you two!
You're still a terrible liar!
You're the only liar here.
No you!
You!
Just how I remember it.
The unsalted meat is delicious!
Actually, the slice was so small,
I barely tasted anything.
I think it was totally delicious!
I wonder when will we get to stuff ourselves
with some fresh meat next, if ever?
Well, I shouldn't think it'll be too long before that.
This country has ample land and favorable climate.
It's perfect for keeping livestock.
At the moment, I'm focusing
on building us a new farm.
Though we might eventually end up running a ranch.
And my first step towards it
would be going to Adelaide tomorrow.
I'll pay a visit to Colonel Light in the surveying office
to decide on our own plot as soon as possible.
Dad, are you going there alone?
No, you're coming with me. If you memorize
the road to Adelaide, it'll come in handy later.
I wanna go too!
Me too!
Not happening.
This time it's just Ben.
Our whole family is going to Adelaide soon anyhow.
Until then, you have to be patient.
Can't we at least see you off?
You want to get on my misbehaving children list?
Then, after you come back from Adelaide,
you'll unload the prefabricated home
and the rest of our things from the ship?
Hm. The ship will stay anchored for five more days...
Well, you already know that better than anyone.
John must've told you about it plenty of times.
Well...
What is it, Lucy-May?
Nothing.
Get back to sleep.
Okay.
I'll certainly catch it!
When Billy grows up,
he dreams of becoming an explorer.
To further that drive, we embarked on an expedition
to the other side of the cape.
Next time on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"First Explorations".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you