South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 29 - Little's Training
While the girls are busy studying,
I wanted to bake a cake for them.
I hope you have a lot of milk for us today.
That's be 43...
43 minus 12 is...
Can't subtract 12 from 3,
which means we do it from 40...
And answer would be 75.
Yes, this one is correct.
The next one...
Ah, this one is also correct.
Kate, you've nailed all and every one of them today!
That's 'cause your problems are way too easy, sis.
I wouldn't say so. You just did really well.
You should be proud of your wits.
Ahh! You're so noisy! Stop babbling already!
But we're not babbling here.
You just did!
What are you saying?
I was merely praising Kate
for doing such a good job.
One way or another, just keep silent!
I'm still not done here!
Gosh... You still can't find your way
around such simple problems?
One more problem to go,
but I can't concentrate.
Let's see, if we subtract 26 from 48...
God knows why,
but I'm actually an arithmetic genius.
At the same time, Got knows why,
Lucy is a real bungler at arithmetic.
Did it! Did it!
We can finally go play outside now, can't we?
Can we, sis?
Give me a moment while I look at your answers.
They gotta be all correct!
15 minus 6 is 9. This one is correct.
I'm telling you, the rest is alright as well!
...Makes 12. That's good.
49... 23?
How come you wrote 23 here?
Where?
The one where you subtracted 26 from 48.
How did you come to think it's 23?
Do it again.
Once the brick house was finished,
Dr. Deighton and Ben moved in it from their old tent.
After that, the flow of patients flocking
to Dr. Deighton's clinic was growing ever-stronger.
Did you hear the doctor? There's nothing
to worry about. You'll be well and dandy from now on.
Aren't you glad, Christopher?
Huh? You're still here?
Ah, we just can't believe our happiness!
Doctor, thank you so much for everything.
No, no. It was all thanks to your
timely decision to bring him for examination.
So, if you ever think something's wrong with him from now on, just bring him here without thinking twice.
I'll examine him anytime.
Thank you so much.
Bow-wow. Bow-wow!
Christopher! Christopher! We're going home.
Bow-wow.
Bow-wow!
That dog's not going to bite him, right?
Yeah... Oughta be alright.
Bow-wow. Come. Come!
Christopher!
L-Little...
Ah!
Little! Little!
Come here! I'll pour some goat milk for you!
Bow-wow. Bow-wow!
Sure, sure. Some other time.
Well, let's go home now, okay?
Even I still don't have full confidence in Little.
Ah? Still a little too fast.
Bow-wow. Bow-wow! Bow-wow!
Look, Little, I was worried sick
that you might bite that kid who just left.
I'd like to think you're no dingo pup,
but really, just a dog. Huh? Right? You're just a dog?
Okay, let's go!
We're done! Done!
Kate, let's go visit Ben at work now!
Sure. Are we bringing Little along?
Of course!
You sure it's alright to bring Little along
to where there are sheep?
I think it'll be perfectly alright.
Dingos are known for attacking the sheep.
But there are also respectable dingos that don't.
And I'm sure Little won't ever have a go on a sheep!
Doctor, do you place your trust in Little?
Well, about that, I was actually
very distrustful of Little just a moment ago.
What could have caused that, Doctor?
Um, well, there was a little boy
who extended his hand to Little.
At this hand, he'd go "GAWR!"
- in some far corner of my mind, I was seriously
pondering whether or not it could be possible.
But he didn't do anything like that, right, Doc?
Yeah. All he did was lick the boy's hand,
and I was oh, so relieved!
Because Little was born a very special,
kinder than any other dingo.
Well, let's go, Little. We're off!
We're off!
Yeah, see you 'round.
Hm, I guess, it should be alright.
No, it'll totally be fine.
Little! Keep it up! After me!
Whoa! Hey, that's cheating, Little! Get off!
Ugh! No!
What are you two doing?
Little is trying to cheat!
Whoa! No I said!
Recently, Ben started helping out
Mr. Long with shepherding.
Mr. Long's job is to move the sheep
from here to there and so on.
Right now, they've arrived to a nearby grassland.
Mr. Long!
We've checked the woods,
but couldn't find any lost sheep there, Mr. Long.
Are you sure?
Monocle had been running
all over the place, looking for it.
I see. We can trust his nose with certainty,
if I do say so myself.
I guess it fell prey to a dingo, after all.
Dingo, after all? Thought so.
I can't think of anything else. You wouldn't expect
such a fat ship to just disappear into thin air.
I'll try searching for it once more.
Enough already. Dingo did it, no two ways about it.
Oh? What's wrong?
Hm? You sense someone there?
Ah, that's my sisters coming.
Oh? Really?
But this is mighty strange.
The dogs aren't usually that nervous.
It's because of Little.
What?
My sisters brought along a baby dingo we're keeping.
Eh? What did you say?
Calm down! Little, you calm down, too!
Back! Monocle, back!
Lie, boys! Lie!
Quiet now. Calm down already!
Sorry if my friends scared you, young ladies.
But it should be all right now.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh? Isn't this a dingo pup?
Yes, that's right.
Now that's unusual.
I'm used to seeing them attacking my sheep.
Hmm, you guys can leave now. Go!
Monocle, you too.
Come on! Go back!
You've managed to train them really well, sir!
Dogs are intelligent creatures.
With just a bit of discipline,
you can make them obey your every command.
But let me tell you, that's one unbelievable thing.
Seeing one so obedient...
Back when I just found him, he was clinging
desperately to his mother's body, crying and whining.
That's how it was.
That sounds believable for sure...
But look how cute he is now!
Very cute, isn't he?
Oh? He wants to take a closer look at the sheep?
He won't do anything.
You'll have no trouble with our Little.
Maybe that's 'cause he's still too small?
Even when he grows up,
I'm sure he'll remain the way he is now.
Do you think so?
As someone who had lost several ships to dingo,
I find it extremely hard to believe.
Listen, Lucy.
The time has come for you to also start
teaching Little discipline, bit by bit.
Perhaps. He's no longer a baby, after all.
To me, it still seems like
he only sees the sheep as a prey.
Sister, don't you think we did well, after all?
What do you mean?
Bringing Little along to where the sheep are.
Perhaps...
We can have no doubt now -
Little is the most ordinary dog.
Yeah, about that...
Means he needs to be trained like other dogs.
Say, Lucy, don't you think Little
is an extraordinarily clever fellow?
Ah! You came to think so, too?
To tell you the truth,
I'm kinda afraid of something.
Afraid?
Yes.
What if, thanks to being so clever,
Little even managed to hide his true self?
"Hide his true self" - what's this about?
Right now, while Little is still little and has to rely on humans for survival, he has to behave and be obedient.
But soon, when he grows big and strong
and would no longer need to pretend...
Eh?
I mean... When that time comes,
he'll be able to live in the free, all by himself...
Suddenly, he lets his true ferocious nature take over...
Stop it! Stop it, Kate!
That's very cruel of you, Kate!
I'm also praying that it never actually comes to that...
But...
Shut it, Kate!
I don't want to hear any more of that!
Let's go, Little.
Lucy... I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Kate?
Dad?
Lucy looked somewhat vexed just now.
Yes...
Quarreling is bad. Start getting along again soon.
Okay...
Ah! I completely forgot to say welcome back!
I appreciate it!
You're returning from work
at a stone quarry, right, dad?
Hm.
Is quarrying hard?
Hm?
Are you tired?
Hm...
Dad, when do you think
will they finally give you the land?
I don't know.
I hope you get to grow wheat soon enough.
Grow vegetables, too!
And we'll definitely keep a cow!
I really didn't have to say this out loud...
Currently, I'm doing my best
to find the most suitable plot.
But due to government's backward approach,
the surveying is delayed.
Therefore, they can't start distributing
the agricultural land.
It's not just about me,
A great many of people who came to Southern Australia,
seeking to start a farm are facing the same problem.
Then, we've no chance to get the land any time soon?
I didn't say that.
Even if it won't be the government plot,
I shouldn't think it'll be impossible
to buy land from those who already own it.
So, if you find someone
selling their plot, you'll buy it?
If only it won't be too expensive.
Then, when do you think will you buy it?
Let me think...
Until the spring of the coming year,
whatever it takes, I'll get a plot.
Wow! Amazing!
Hey, it's in our best interest
to get the plot as soon as possible, right?
Hm.
Oh? Welcome back.
We're home.
So what do you rate it?
Are you finding that new brick house comfortable?
It's perfect. Perfect!
Well, I'm awfully happy to hear that,
even if it's just a courtesy.
It's no mere courtesy. I've been walking around like that for a while, looking at the house here and there.
To think that me getting left behind in Australia would result in me finally opening up a proper hospital...
Yes, that's one unbelievable turn of events.
Doctor, before the coming spring,
dad would also buy a plot for farming!
Oh? That'd be rightly marvelous.
But have you found a fitting lot already, Mr. Popple?
Kate just doesn't know when to stop, I must add.
Yes. To tell you the truth, though I've not yet
entered the talks about it, I found a lot.
Oh? Is that so?
Well, ain't it a fitting occasion
to raise a glass for as soon as tonight?
Doctor, as I said, we've not yet started
to even negotiate it properly.
Huh? Then, we can't celebrate it?
No, let's go for it. Tonight.
Splendid.
Then, I'm looking forward to drinking with you tonight.
But until then, I'll go do some more work.
Work, work, work!
How is Little doing, Lucy-May?
What's wrong?
Have you been crying, Lucy?
It's 'cause... 'Cause Kate said something
terrible about Little!
Breaking into tears over that...
Seems strange to me.
Besides...
Hmm?
Besides, I also came to think about it
in the same way as Kate.
I see.
It's the dilemma of keeping a wild animal, isn't it?
No matter how much you domesticate it, there's no telling if it won't suddenly revert to being wild one day.
But I can't stand putting him down!
Huh?
Wasn't that what you said?
A condition under which I'm allowed to keep Little.
Ah, you mean that thing?
Yes, if Little attacks or hurts a human,
we'll put him down then and there.
That was the condition.
But I don't want Little to be put down!
Hey, Little. Do you have any idea
how much Lucy-May dotes on you?
Make sure you don't disappoint Lucy-May, will you?
Mom, you wanna hear it?
Sure, go ahead.
"Although it's technically an autumn now,
we barely see any yellow or red leaves down here.
Everything remains as verdant as it ever was.
Therefore, it doesn't feel like Autumn at all.
Not to mention that the Autumn ends in June...
Still, we can already feel the winter crawling closer."
Ms. Clara, who're you writin' that letter to?
'Bout the June autumn, the red and green...
It's to my grandmother back in England.
Oh, I see. You're mighty good at composing letters!
Doctor, awfully sorry,
but can I please have a moment of silence?
Ah? Ah... Right, my bad!
Okay... Where was I?
"We can already feel the winter crawling closer..."
Ah! Right, right. "Crawling closer," here.
"The new brick house is finally completed.
Ben and Dr. Deighton have already moved there."
"Doctor?" You also writin' 'bout me there?
Well, I already wrote in the previous letter
that you're living with us.
Well... I'm flattered!
By the way, are you also writing
about the land situation in those letters?
No.
After all, we've not yet received any to speak of.
Right, dad?
Yeah.
Doctor Deighton, would you like another glass?
No-no! Though, if you say it's just one glass, I might...
Now, what I was reading next...
"Presently, Lucy-May is head over heels
for her pet dingo, an animal akin to the dog.
His name is Little."
Are you... still mad at me?
No.
I went too far with what I said there.
My bad. Sorry.
No need...
After all, you were just saying openly what you think.
Little will be fine,
and he won't turn against you.
I'd like to think so too...
At any rate, come tomorrow,
we'll start training him for various things.
Sit!
Sit! Little, sit!
Um, no, no! Not that! Sit!
Not that! I didn't say "jump!"
Sit!
Sit! Little, sit!
Good!
Ready! Kate, watch this!
Sit!
Good.
Up!
Wow! Little is amazing!
Lie!
Lie! Little, lie!
I'm telling you to lie, understand?
Little, lie! Lie!
Lie!
Lie! Little, Lie!
Little, come on! Lie!
Lie!
Good, good!
Stop!
Good, run!
Go!
Stop!
Good! Go!
Go!
No! You can't move now.
Yes, like that.
Sit, Little! Sit.
Good! Now stay like this!
Don't you move!
Can't move, remember? Don't move!
Like that, like that!
No! You can't move!
Don't move! Just don't!
Not yet! You can't move yet!
Don't move! Not yet! No!
Alright, come here, Little!
It tickles, Little!
Wait!
Good!
Lucy, I'm going now.
Come back soon, dad!
I'm going out.
Sure is getting cold!
We've been continuing the training
all the way throughout the winter.
To ensure that Little becomes a good friend to humans,
Lucy was putting her every effort into it.
Little, go!
Keep going, Little!
Go!
Stop!
Okay! Lie!
Pick it up. Pick it up! Little, pick it up!
Let go. Let go!
Great, great!
And then, the spring came.
Everyone is giving me their amazing gifts.
And brother even presents me with a lamb.
I'm so moved!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Birthday Gifts".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you