South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 26 - I Fell Ill!
Sister! Sister. Sister!
Clara! Wake up, please, Clara!
What is it? What do you want, Lucy-May?
You're wrong, it's me, Kate!
Kate?
What's the matter? It's not even morning yet.
Lucy looks a bit strange. Can you come and see?
Eh? Looks strange? What do you mean?
She has a fever and seems to be in pain.
And even talking through delirium!
Delirium?
Lucy-May. Lucy-May, what's wrong?
Ah, that's a terrible fever.
I'm sorry, forgive me.
Kate, light a candle. And wake mom up.
Okay.
I'm sorry, forgive me.
In the middle of the night,
Lucy developed a terrible fever.
She was even talking in her sleep.
For some reason, she kept begging for forgiveness.
Doctor. Doctor!
Wake up please, Doctor Deighton.
Doctor! Doctor, please!
We need you to wake up, doctor.
What's wrong, sister?
Ah, sorry. I didn't mean to wake you as well...
Lucy is very sick.
Eh? So suddenly?
She was all well when she went to sleep.
Doctor Deighton!
Wake up, please!
Lucy suddenly fell ill!
Huh?
Where? Where the sudden illness?
How is she, doctor?
Hm... There are certainly some crackles in the lungs...
And what does that mean for her?
Uh...
Her condition is anything but normal.
Need to bring the fever down first.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
Ah, speaking through delirium again.
Right, right. Yes.
This oughta knock the fever down fast.
I brought more cold water.
Let me change that water now.
How is Lucy?
Sleeping now. Seems like she's still in pain.
If fever subsides by morning, she'll be all right.
Well, you can be free now.
Return to sleep in the other room.
She still speaks in her sleep?
No. Well, go back to sleep now.
Okay.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I wonder who is she apologizing to.
I'm sure it's me.
Yesterday,
Lucy took it to heart when I dropped my textbook on Latin grammar into the river because of her.
Ah! My book!
I succeeded! You should've seen your face!
Idiot!
Huh?
You can trust me and your mother
to look after Lucy-May.
The two of you go back to sleep.
Okay.
She's on the verge of pneumonia.
Why did she suddenly develop such a fever, Doctor?
I can only surmise it's because of a physical weakness.
She was so full of life during the day.
But now that I think of it, in the evening...
She barely touched her dinner...
Whatever the case, we'll be in trouble
if her fever doesn't subside.
Isn't there some special way?
A way to knock down the fever?
I hope the fever medicine
that I gave her before takes effect.
After that, we just need to keep cooling her down.
I understand.
Doctor, thanks a lot for your work.
We'll call upon you again if there's any development.
But until then, please feel free to have your rest.
Some development happening is my only wish.
I think, she'll probably be fine.
After all, it's the energetic girl Lucy-May we all know.
Yes. It was always unthinkable to me
that Lucy-May could ever fall ill.
Still, there are no people who never fall ill.
I'll go catch a shuteye now.
Thank you for everything.
When you also grow big, this box
will probably become too cramped for you.
We need to build you a proper house soon
for you to dwell in once you grow up.
Nothing serious happened to Lucy, right?
Once the fever subsides,
she'll be her usual self again, right?
It's unthinkable for a girl that lively
to end up dying, isn't it?
Yes. Normally, you'd think it's impossible.
Doctor, is that to say
Lucy's illness is not "normal"?
That talking in delirium worries me.
But normally, anyone would speak in his sleep
when he develops a high-grade fever.
What's odd is her repeating
the very same words.
"I'm sorry" - nothing more!
But I told her long ago - I forgave her already,
for the book and everything.
Hm?
Did you know, Ben?
Sick people who don't strive
to get better end up dying.
Doctor, you don't mean to say... Lucy, too...
Usually, in children,
a desire to get better soon prevails.
But in Lucy-May's case,
if her heart is besieged by worries,
it takes a toll on her body as well,
resulting in a high-grade fever and such.
But I... But I... forgave Lucy already. It's the truth!
Did you forgive her from your heart?
The hard fact that she caused the loss of a book so dear to you is the only thing that Lucy-May remembers.
What I mean is,
after you said you'd forgiven her,
could something in your behavior
have betrayed your true feelings?
Ah...
Doctor...
Something came to your mind?
Doctor, I...
You shouldn't equate Lucy-May's usual cheerfulness and frivolousness with insensitiveness.
She saw it right through that you weren't sincere
with yourself when you said you forgave her.
She may have perked up on the outside,
but deep in her heart, she kept brooding
over the depth of her guilt before you.
It's true that after that happened, I feel like I couldn't help treating Lucy in a colder manner than usual.
Forgive me!
Brother!
Please, brother!
I'm sorry!
Forgive me, please!
I see, so that's what happened?
Which means I'm the reason
for Lucy's current illness?
Ben, don't be jumping to conclusions like that.
Lucy-May's illness was caused by a common cold.
Still, among the reasons
why she almost developed a pneumonia
was this heavy burden of responsibility
she has to carry in her heart.
Well, that's about all you need to know about it.
So to make thinks better I just need to relieve
her heart of this heavy burden, Doctor?
Yes. Yes.
If only you can, do just that.
Well then, I wanted to go get some more sleep.
Lucy, are you really that...
Good night.
You're one kind kid, you know that?
I'm sorry... Forgive me, brother...
Come on, you have to eat, Little.
Lucy won't come. She's ill!
She still has a high-grade fever,
so she can't show up outside for the time being.
Well, eat now, Little.
Hey, what would be the thing
Lucy wants the most now?
That'd be a koala.
She already has Little as her pet.
Isn't that quite enough?
I don't think Lucy thinks this way.
But maybe there's something outside animals?
Let's see... What in the world
could that girl be wanting to get?
You want to eat something, Lucy-May?
Uh-uh.
But Doctor Deighton advised for you
to eat at least something.
I don't feel like eating anything.
Good morning, Mr. Popple!
Hey. Good morning.
I have some business with Doctor Deighton today.
Huh?
So? How about I nap for a little more?
Good morning.
Hey, good morning.
Thing is, my master insisted
on you coming to see him today.
A thousand pardons,
but who might your master be?
My, you have a rather poor memory
for your age, Doc!
I'm Adam. And my master is Mr. Pettywell.
Uh... Ah, right, right, I remember now!
So, will you be so kind as to follow me?
Eh... Explain to me Mr. Pettywell's complaints first.
Of course. He's been in great pain since last night,
and couldn't eat anything in the morning.
Oh? Got a naughty stomach, then?
No.
Is it in his head?
Then, is it his waist again?
No!
Enough of your riddles!
Just tell me where!
It's his tooth.
Huh? Tooth?
Here. His tooth hurts since last night.
Go home, you dunce.
Just as I thought...
What's that supposed to mean?
I was telling my Master the same thing:
"Doctor Deighton is by no means a dentist."
But Master replied, instead:
"If you summon that quack to my place,
he'll come this instant, wiggling his tail!"
I ain't got no tail.
Now, 'bout time you left, boy.
I see. In that case, excuse me.
Ugh... After all I've done, calling me a quack!
Damn this jerk Pettywell.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Come in!
Enter!
He'll come right away, right?
About that, you see...
You told him I'd compensate
him generously, didn't you?
Doctor Deighton said, because he is no dentist,
he can't provide you with a proper treatment, sir...
What? Why?!
Eh?! Master, I can't breathe!
Eh, damn!
I'm fed up with Deighton's insolence!
Fine. I'm not counting on him for anything, ever again.
Will find someone else!
Ah, ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
How is she? The fever is still there?
Still pretty hot.
If only we could knock the fever down...
I'm sorry, forgive me...
Ah... I can't listen
to this delirious murmur any longer!
Sister!
So? How is Lucy looking?
I see... Still that bad?
Started talking in her sleep again.
I see...
Mom even said she's fed up.
She doesn't want to hear it ever again.
I wish I could say that, too...
Pansy. Pansy!
Come here!
Brother.
Hm?
I want some water.
Ah, water?
Wait, I'll help you drink in a moment.
There.
The water is tasty. Thank you.
Lucy, since I'm already here,
would you mind listening to me for a bit?
I don't.
In the end of the day,
I wasn't acting like a man should.
While you had a high fever,
you were talking in your sleep...
I know.
Eh?
I heard it from Kate. I kept saying
"I'm sorry" and "forgive me," didn't I?
Yes. You were probably still recalling that time,
when my textbook on Latin grammar...
But you've already forgiven me for it, didn't you?
Yes. I really intended to.
But somewhere inside, I still had that sentiment,
screaming "can't forgive."
But I can swear now. I really forgave you.
I no longer hold any grudges.
Thank you, brother.
Get well soon, will you?
Okay.
I just recalled that there was something
I promised to make for you when we were in England.
Do you remember?
A kite?
Yes, a kite.
I'll go and fulfill that promise right now.
I'm glad.
Get well soon, so we can fly that kite together.
Okay.
Ah, my bad! My bad, Lucy.
I shouldn't have tired you with talking.
Brother.
Hm?
Thank you.
Then, I'll get to making it right away.
You don't need to be in such a hurry.
I want to make it sooner.
This way, you'll also get better sooner.
Okay, I'll get well.
I'll be going then, Lucy.
Okay.
Oh my! What's wrong, Lucy-May?
Does it hurt somewhere?
It's nothing.
If so, you'd better return to sleeping quietly.
Let's see now...
Doctor.
Ah... Yes?
Doctor, I need a favor.
Please help Lucy get better
as soon as you seem possible!
Ah, of course I will. However, for that,
the fever has to subside first.
It subsided a bit, I think.
Oh?
Then, I'll go check on her real quick!
Really? Subsided?
Doctor! Doctor!
Help me, please! It hurts so much,
I feel I could die! Ouch! Ouch!
You can't die from a caries.
At least try to look at it!
Imagine I looked at it:
"Oh? This looks like a cavity in the tooth.
Must be a caries. Hurts bad, I imagine!"
That said, I can't treat it anyhow.
Oh, whatever, just look at it, whatever comes!
Eh? This one?
Waah!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! It hurts!
Looks like it hurts, alright.
Do something to stop this pain!
Ain't something I can do.
I'll pay any money!
But please, do something about it!
Whatever problem you encounter,
you start putting out money.
Ah! Ouch! It hurts! It hurts!
I don't know the first thing about dentistry.
But back when I was a kid,
mom used to yank out any hurting teeth we had.
Do you suggest yanking it out?
I will never agree to that!
Well, that was about the only thing I could do for you.
Huh?
Well then, I need to see my patient now.
Ah, a moment. Moment, Doctor!
Damn it!
Ah! It hurts! Hurts!
Damn that Deighton quack!
Ah! Ouch-ouch!
Ah? Hey! You're in the way, you rogue!
Who'd ever think this is a good place to sleep at?!
It hurts!
Okay, Sticky. Let's go get some fresh grass.
Pansy, you come, too!
These are the last for today.
Oh, I see.
Dad.
If you don't have any more special errands for me
to run today, I'd like some free time now.
Yeah, I don't mind. What will you do with it?
I want to build a kite,
so I'll go fetch some bamboo.
A kite?
I need to give it to Lucy.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Doctor! Doctor Deighton!
Ah! Doctor! Yank it out!
I can't stand this pain no more.
Alright, in that case, I'll need a pair of pincers.
Pretty sure Ben had one.
Hurry up! Hurry, Doctor!
Now, now, don't rush me.
I'm getting the pincers.
Ah... Oh, found it!
Huh?
Come on, open your mouth wide.
Doctor, I count on you to be gentle...
Yeah, I know, I know.
Oh God...
Open wider now!
Aah.
Doctor!
Ah?
Lucy-May is acting strange.
Please. Please come quickly!
Eh? That sounds urgent.
You, hold this for now.
Okay, let's go.
Ah? Doctor!
Damn it! It hurts so much! Ouch!
Little?
Carried away by thoughts of Lucy's illness,
I was already dozing off, when suddenly
I heard Little's distressed shrieking.
Little!
I was awfully startled, so I dashed towards
where his shrieking was coming from.
Little!
I don't remember for how long exactly
I had been asleep,
but I remember riding a kite through the sky!
I'm sure it wasn't just a dream.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Riding the Kite".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you