South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 32 - At the Foot of the Rainbow Bridge
Good Morning, Little.
Ah! Ah!
Stop, Little! You're tickling me!
Stop it already!
It tickles!
Well, start with your morning breakfast now.
Hey, Little, did you know we're moving
to a new house soon?
We'll be living on a vast farm.
And when I say vast, I mean it!
And then, it seems,
we'll get a handful of sheep to keep.
Which means you'll be looking after them!
Oh my, you weren't listening
to what I said, were you?
Ah, really? So you were listening?
Good morning, Lucy.
Good morning, Ben.
Little, good morning.
Having breakfast already?
Hey, how is Doctor Deighton's leg?
Last night, it hurt awfully, it seems.
I don't think he could get any sleep.
My...
Mr. Pettywell's black dog
was probably sick with something.
So Doctor contracted it too, when the dog bit him?
We can't tell if he contracted anything yet.
But it sure does pain him a lot.
By the way, how is sheep doing?
Snowflake got bitten too, didn't it?
Yes. Nothing seemed wrong with it yesterday.
Okay, come here now, Snowflake.
Ah! You two can't go yet!
Hm...
Seems alright.
The would is barely visible already.
Huh? Although both were bitten by the same dog,
Dr. Deighton seems to be taking it much worse.
I feel guilty before Dr. Deighton...
Doctor! Doctor Deighton!
Huh? Ouch!
Your meal is ready, doctor.
I ain't hungry. Sorry but I ain't slept a wink last night,
so I'll go back to sleep now. Ow! Ouch!
Doctor, your wound hurts that bad?
That damned black dog...
If it hurts too much,
I could bring you a doctor...
Ah!
You're a doctor yourself, right.
Ben, come with us.
The other day, you were the only one
who didn't get to see Mr. Wilson's farm.
Yes. But starting today, it's no longer
Wilson's farm, but a Popple's farm instead, right?
We're signing the contract of sale today,
but until the exchange is registered,
the farm cannot be officially considered ours.
With the contract of sale signed,
you'll pay Mr. Wilson his due, right?
Yes.
Then, the farm becomes ours today,
however you look at it.
Agreed.
All the formalities aside,
that farm is ours, starting today.
That's it!
So you'll sign the contract right there, at the farm?
Yes. I'll borrow the oxcart again.
Anything to conclude it sooner.
Then, we're going now.
You'll be back before evening, right?
Of course.
Come back soon!
Ah, doctor! You're finally feeling better?
No... Alas, alas, the wound festered.
But I think I'll pull it through somehow.
How about a breakfast?
No, I'm good.
I see Arthur and Ben are going somewhere?
Yes. To conclude the contract
for the purchase of the farm.
Oh? At long last?
So that's how it is? It's today already?
My heartfelt congratulations
on finding such a fine farm!
Thank you very much.
It's been exactly one year, isn't that right?
Huh?
Exactly one year after we came to Southern Australia,
we could finally acquire a piece of land.
Right. By the time we were leaving England, I was sure
we'd buy a vast plot of land as soon as we arrive here.
I thought we'd start an ideal, vast farm,
of the kind that'd be impossible to realize in England.
Right. We're doing it one year late.
But even a year later, we can still make it work,
if the whole family starts doing their best now.
Yes. If everyone does their best at earnest,
we could recoup this lost year.
We'll build a marvelous home, right, dad?
Yes.
What do we need to buy next, Clara?
Hm...
Hey, where are we going next?
To the post office.
Post office?
Ah, I know! We'll check if there's no letter for us
from our grandma back in England?
Can't believe you're such an idiot.
Why are you saying I'm an idiot?
The reason Clara wants to stop by at the post office
is not for grandma's letter.
We've just barely received
the previous grandma's letter.
Ah, you're right! I understand now.
We want to check if Aunt Mary
hadn't sent us another package.
Idiot.
Kate! I'd appreciate it if you called me
something that's not "idiot!"
That's true, Kate. You should learn
to never call other idiots, ever.
That's right, right!
Heard that, Kate?
Your own fault for being so obtuse!
How am I obtuse?
You're too obtuse to even understand you're obtuse!
That's it! You're not getting a word more from me!
Wait for me here, you two.
Good morning.
Huh?
Well, I've heard a ship had arrived from England
the day before yesterday.
Yes...
So? Did the latest mail arrive on it too?
Yes.
Uhm... In that case, if there's something for Popple...
I mean, perhaps there is some mail for Clara Popple?
Huh?
Do you happen to be Clara Popple?
Yes.
Hm...
Yes. Pretty sure there was a letter for Clara Popple.
Give me just a moment.
Ah.
Aren't you glad?
A letter from John is here!
Didn't I tell you two to wait outside?
Found it, found it!
It was right here.
Uh... To Miss Clara Popple.
Okay, here you go.
I can see you're glad, sis!
Let's read it right away.
Don't say nonsense, you.
Rereading it for the second time.
Wrong, it's the third time.
Though it's only natural for a letter from John!
To tell you the truth,
I no longer really remember John's face.
That's right, since the day John left,
almost a whole year had passed.
Still, I remember that one time when John
followed Clara all the way to the forest to say goodbye.
Oh, that one I remember too!
Clara!
He came to see me off...
John!
Clara!
Ah, you were right, it's John, sis!
Ah! John!
John...
So glad I caught up with you!
Well, goodbye now.
He wrote something good, didn't he?
I can tell right away from that look of yours.
He's coming here!
John?
Just as promised, he's coming to live
in southern Australia together with his brother.
And when will he be here?
He writes that he'll try to arrive as soon as he can.
And that he'll board a ship
one week after writing this.
Then, it'll be in a week from today?
Perhaps.
If John's ship had a smoother sailing
than this one, it might arrive much sooner!
Say, Clara.
Couldn't John have boarded the same ship
as the one that delivered the letter?
Don't say nonsense.
Ah... I'm sorry. But to think
something like that could've happened...
That'd mean...
That'd mean John is already there,
in the shore camp!
Imagine, what if he's walking
that road through the forest as we speak?
Well, let's head home now.
We've done all the shopping.
Ah! Wait!
Wait!
Mr. Wilson's farm starts
immediately after that hilltop.
What would be Popple's farm
starting tomorrow, right?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Some carriage is catching up.
A carriage?
I think it might be Mr. Pettywell's...
Huh?
It's Mr. Pettywell, alright.
He's in a terrible hurry.
I wonder where he's going.
Is it not too tight?
It's fine.
So it turns out we're finally moving
to a farm soon enough.
I would've liked to stay with you,
but the place is rather far...
Guess I'll have to stay
and continue receiving patients here.
Operating a clinic from there
would be inconvenient indeed.
All right, this should do.
Right. Much obliged, much obliged.
Should you really go out
on house calls like this?
Yeah. That wound won't be giving me any more trouble.
Look!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
God damn that black dog!
Such a dog really deserved to die.
Dad, Mr. Wilson's house is also somewhere near?
I wonder where Mr. Pettywell was going.
See you some other time, then.
Good afternoon, Mr. Pettywell.
Yeah... Good afternoon.
Weather's nice today, isn't it?
No, doesn't seem so.
I see clouds appearing here and there.
Well then, I'd best return soon.
We're home, Little.
Ah! No! No! Later, later! Sit!
Huh?
We're home!
We're home.
My, that was interesting!
Good job with that.
Back... Back... I'm back!
No I said! We'll play later.
Later.
Hey, mom, John didn't happen to drop by?
John?
Not here, after all?
That John being John the sailor?
Yes, we've just collected a letter he wrote.
He's finally coming here with his brother.
My, oh my!
He's close already, I can feel that.
Well, well.
By the way, I was about to start
with the dinner. Will you help?
Sure.
I'll help too! Making the dinner.
Aren't you glad? John stuck
with his promise all the way through.
Yes.
Mr. Wilson, I'd still like you to rethink.
That's the only thing I ask for.
It's too late to change my mind now.
Look, according to this contract of sale,
the exchange is concluded already.
That is not what we agreed upon!
Pretty sure we've agreed on you selling the land to me!
Mr. Pettywell agreed to fork out 500 pounds extra.
Money is what I need the most now!
I've got a trip back to England ahead of me, therefore...
But does our promise mean nothing to you?!
I'm sorry, Mr. Popple, but I don't suppose
you got 500 pounds extra?
That's... Finding 500 pounds extra
is impossible now.
In that case, I suppose,
I have no choice but to sell it to him...
I despise a person like you!
He offered 500 pounds extra...
Let's go, Ben.
Forgive me if you can, Mr. Popple...
But I could by no means turn down those 500 pounds.
Mom, how many eggs do we need?
Three. You only need the egg yolk,
but make sure to stir it well.
Okay.
Kate, help me here, will you?
Why should I?
Because I can't do it myself!
I'm still not done here.
Kate, that's my job,
you go help Clara instead.
If you keep nibbling on it like that,
there won't be anything left by the time it's ready!
But I wasn't nibbling anything,
just tasting to see if it comes out good. And now I now.
Pour some of that oil into here, will you?
Careful. Be careful.
Just a smidgen. Slowly, slowly.
Look, you can't pour that much all at once.
Why didn't you do it yourself, then?
Look, it tastes good now.
Don't spill that!
I know!
Ah, it smells great.
Come on, Kate.
Sister.
What is it?
Isn't there a faster way to make mayonnaise?
Why do you ask?
I wanna go help mom sooner.
You're just as helpful here.
Hey, hey, do it slower!
Good, good.
This time, I'm throwing it even farther, okay?
Fetch!
Doctor.
Mr. Pettywell? G'day.
Going on a house call?
Yes.
Oh, by the way, I had a sleepless night because that
wound from your black dog's bite pains so horribly!
But if you were able to walk even so,
it probably wasn't that bad, Doctor.
That's 'cause I'm walking through pain.
Numerous patient await a visit from me.
How can you say that, Doctor?
My dog was bitten to death by Popple's dingo!
And that was your black dog's fault as well!
You two were much alike, I swear on me mum!
It became so dark so fast...
Dad and Ben will probably get soaked to the bone.
I hope they come back soon.
After all, we've everything ready
to celebrate this day.
I'll go meet them down the road!
No need, you'll get soaked too!
Oh, wow! Dad has already returned.
They look completely soaked.
Huh? They stopped in front of Mr. Pettywell's house.
I'll try to talk to Mr. Pettywell, come what may.
I'm sure it's pointless.
It may be pointless indeed.
But I'll still try to ask him to yield that land to us.
Dad...
Ever since we came to Southern Australia,
there wasn't any other day
filled with quite as much sad thoughts as this one.
We've arrived to Mr. Pettywell snatching
that marvelous plot away from right under our noses.
Yes.
I think that's exactly what happened.
In this wicked fashion, our family was hit
by Mr. Pettywell payback, sworn earlier.
I haven't seen a rainbow that beautiful
ever in my life!
Beautiful indeed...
Hey, everyone, stop looking so glum, will you?
One of these days, I'm sure,
we'll also arrive to the foot of that rainbow bridge.
But until then, we should all
join the efforts and keep doing our best!
"Foot of the rainbow bridge..."
I want to walk that bridge to the other side!
Yes, certainly. One day, we'll get to cross it.
Now then, why don't we have a dinner, everyone?
Good idea, 'cause I'm starving.
It's John!
Well, this is here.
It's been a while, friends,
but me and brother finally made it here.
This here is my little brother Paul.
John, but when...
The day before yesterday.
I took that voyage easy thanks to being used to sailing.
I can start working tomorrow already.
I came here to ask
if I could possibly work on Popples' farm.
There is no farm.
Huh?
Even thought a whole year had passed,
we were never allocated any farmland.
John...
Clara...
Bridge across River Torrens -
its opening ceremony in Adelaide was held
in two more years from then.
In that two years' span,
Adelaide has transformed into a bustling city.
Lucy turned ten, and I turned thirteen.
We've moved to live in the city!
The house we have in the city is big, but even now, three years later, we never managed to get any farmland.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"A Lost Dream".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you