South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 44 - Little! Little!
Ah...
The moon is out.
Is that Kate's dress?
No.
Lucy's?
Yes. A button came off it.
It's a lovely dress.
It's getting a little tight for her, though.
She probably couldn't wear it in the coming year...
Moon, you know where Lucy is, don't you?
Please tell me.
Honey, why won't you go to sleep already?
I'm not sleepy.
Makes sense.
How else can we go about looking for Lucy?
Worried about Lucy who wouldn't come home,
we all grew completely unable to get any sleep.
Lucy, where are you?
Wow, you can even swim underwater?
Ah! Stop, Prospero!
You're tickling me! Stop!
Prospero, so you were actually a dog?
Just a dream, huh?
You had a dream, Emily?
I was chasing after a girl I felt like I know very well.
But when I caught up to her,
she didn't have a face.
My, how uncanny.
But I'm sure I know that girl.
I felt like I was about to call her by the name
back when I was chasing her.
Was that the only thing you saw?
No, it continued after that too.
Did you meet some more people that you know?
I dreamt that I was drowning in the pond
and crying for help, but nobody came to help me.
None of the people standing on the shore
even turned to look at me.
My, poor thing!
It's just a dream, isn't it?
Still, having nobody to come save you...
I think I lost my voice back then.
There, see? A common happening in any dream.
More importantly, weren't there any clues in your dream that could help you remember your past?
The cat turned into a dog.
What do you mean?
Prospero...
That's right. What happened is you turned into a dog.
Cat turned into a dog, huh?
So it didn't bring back any particular memory?
I wonder if I used to keep that dog as a pet.
That's possible.
Since you love animals,
you'd be likely to keep a dog too.
Well, let's call it enough of talking about dreams, Emily.
Today we'll be coming with a visit
to the Duchess of York, remember?
Yes. But I...
The Duchess is a very amiable lady.
After hearing your story,
she'd become very sympathetic.
She's dying to hear more about yourself.
I have nothing to tell about myself.
I only remember things that happened
after my arrival to this house. Before that - nothing...
Now that I think about it, you're right.
But I'm sure the Duchess would be contented
with just being able to meet you, Emily.
I was never particularly religious.
But that Sunday, I prayed to God earnestly
that we find Lucy soon.
Honey, are you going to look for Lucy today as well?
There's no telling if we'd ever find her
if we just keep walking around haphazardly.
But it's still better than doing nothing.
I think so too.
Father, let's go look for her either way.
I'm going too.
When that notice in Adelaide Times is published,
someone might try to reach out to us.
But there's no newspaper on Sunday,
so we might as well go walk around again.
Yes.
I'm going too.
There's no need for you to come too.
I'd rather you help me with housework.
Even Little must now be searching for her somewhere.
Ah! It's Little!
It really did look like Little.
He must've come home to see if Lucy returned or not.
What a smart dog.
He's not a dog, but a dingo.
Indeed, this dress looks
very becoming on you, Little Miss.
I almost feel like I'm a queen herself!
If you become the Little Miss of the Princeton family,
you will actually be as happy as the queen herself.
But I'm not the daughter of this family.
With my hand on my heart, the madam does seem
to think of you as of her real child.
As evident by her naming you Emily.
Emily was the madam's daughter,
who died when she was just two.
I know that, but...
And when you call her mother,
she literally starts beaming with happiness!
I have another mother out there somewhere.
But I don't think you'll find a mother as kind and beautiful as our madam anywhere else in the world.
You can't remember anything about you past, right?
Just leave things as they are now and strap in
for a life of happiness as the new Emily in this house.
I'm not supposed to be bearing this name.
You look gorgeous, Emily.
That dress looks great on you.
Thank you, mother.
The Duchess is waiting for us.
Let's set out now.
We're approaching the Adelaide Bridge.
It's where I was hit by a carriage?
Yes.
Here is the mansion of the Duke of York, acting
as an emissary of Her Majesty in Southern Australia.
No wonder it's so magnificent.
But it's unthinkable that Lucy
would come anywhere near this part of the town.
I suppose.
So, it's only been three days
since she's lost her memory?
Yes.
Isn't it rightly curious?
You're probably feeling befuddled,
not even knowing who might you be.
Yes, very much so.
I understand.
When grown-ups don't know who they are,
they simply cannot stop worrying.
But you're handling it remarkably well,
even though you're still so small.
It's thanks to my mother's kind support.
Mother's?
I asked her to call me that.
I've also come to think of her as of my own child.
I know you've been yearning to have a child
since long ago, Sylvia.
Yes.
Then I'm sure those three days
were the happiest time of your life.
Yes. Very much so.
My wife is getting unreasonably obsessed with this child,
even making me ever so slightly worried.
So I thought.
Her memory should return one of these days.
Sylvia, the very moment that happens,
your newly acquired motherhood will be over.
Yes...
Besides, I've arranged for a notice regarding this child
to be posted in tomorrow's Monday newspaper.
Perhaps, upon seeing that notice,
her real parents would make themselves known.
But I'm sure Emily would never forget you two.
Isn't that right, Emily?
Yes. Most certainly.
It's remarkable how compassionate the Duchess is.
Hm.
Ah, dear, I'd like to stop by at a shoemaker's.
Do you want to buy shoes for yourself?
No, for Emily!
I found a good pair the other day, but I didn't like
the ribbon on them so I ordered it replaced.
When I saw those shoes, I knew at once
they'd fit perfectly with this dress.
Hey, Max. Stop at the shoemaker's shop
on King William Street.
Those shoes would fit perfectly
with your wedding gown.
Yes. But they're so expensive!
That's true.
I can't possibly afford them.
I'll be working harder than ever
and before long, we'll buy them!
Such expensive shoes are a money thrown away!
Ah...
But before that comes Lucy-May.
Right. Gotta find Lucy first.
So? They're not too tight?
Not at all!
Those are wonderfully cute shoes!
And they fit the dress perfectly.
You can go home in those shoes, Emily.
Tell me, Emily, is there anything else you want?
No, nothing.
You don't need to be shy.
Well...
What is it?
Well, I'd like to stop the carriage for a moment.
Eh? Where? We can stop at whatever shop you'd like.
It's not that. I just thought
we'll be approaching Adelaide Bridge soon.
That's right.
I'd like to stop at the bridge.
What for?
I want to inspect once more this spot where I was lying.
Does that mean you remembered something?
No, I don't remember anything.
That's why I want to walk over bridge again.
Very well. We'll stop the carriage
at the Adelaide Bridge.
Do you think she remembered something?
No, I didn't get that kind of impression.
How is it? Anything comes to your mind?
I don't remember anything.
Nothing... I remember nothing.
Now, you can't help it with crying.
Don't worry.
You'll definitely regain your memory one day.
Let's go home for today.
I'm sorry. I'll return to the carriage soon.
Can you please let me stay here for a little longer?
Sure. I don't see why I shouldn't.
What can we do?
Only what she just said -
give her some time alone.
Dear, it charges at Emily.
Is that...
Dear, Emily needs help...
No. Wait a moment, Sylvia.
Stop it already!
I said stop! You're tickling me, Little!
Little?
Little...
Ah! Little!
Little! Little! So it was you, Little!
I think Emily is no more, Sylvia.
Yes. I suppose.
Mom, I'm hungry!
Don't you know, Tob?
We'll have dinner once your dad and brother are back.
I wonder if they'll bring Lucy along.
It's Little!
That's it! That was Little's barking!
Did he find her?
What's the matter with you?
Did you find Lucy? Tell me, Little!
Mom...
Mom.
Mom!
Lucy! It really is you, Lucy!
Dad, is that a carriage parked in front of our house?
So it seems.
I wonder who came in it.
That's a pretty extravagant carriage.
Little is here...
That means...
That's it! Lucy had returned!
I'm sorry, but we'll have to leave soon.
Of course.
I can't stress it enough
how grateful we are for everything.
No, we only did what anyone would've done.
Ah, but I hope I'll get a chance to discuss things
more thoroughly with you one of these days.
Huh?
You came to Southern Australia
aiming to build a new farm, right?
Yes, that's true.
Lucy explained everything to me.
I also operate several farms and ranches.
So I'd love to hear all about it next time we meet.
Of course...
Let us go, Sylvia.
Emily...
Bye-bye!
That's exactly why I've been so worried.
You came to love that child deeply, didn't you?
Right! You need to sit still, Little. Like that!
Hey, Lucy.
Tell me in more about Mr. Princeton's mansion.
I want details!
How many bedrooms does it have?
Eight? Nine? Maybe all ten?
They had a room filled right up to the top with books.
Ah! You can't move yet!
It's your fault for gathering so much dirt!
Where in the world have you been rambling
while I was away?
How about food?
Hey, was it good?
What kind of dishes did they serve?
All kinds!
"All kinds" means nothing to me!
That's because all the food they served
was something I never tried before.
But everything was delicious!
Ah! You can't go, Little!
Ah! Stop, Little!
Hey, Lucy!
What kind of stuff did they have for the tea break?
Hey! Stop I said!
Hey! What snacks did they have?
All sorts of them!
"All sorts" means nothing!
Biscuits with raisins, soft and delicate muffins,
pancakes fully covered in honey!
Sweet fresh cream and spongecake
with strawberry jam in-between!
Also some of the best chocolate ever,
sent directly from France!
We found a wallaby,
which is like a kangaroo, and is very cute!
But while we chased the wallaby,
Tob suddenly disappeared.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Tob Disappeared".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you