South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 43 - Passed By
My sister Lucy hadn't been home for two nights now.
We looked for her as best we could,
but couldn't trace where she went.
And then, when I woke up the morning,
Little was gone too.
Do you think he went to look for Lucy?
I'm sure of it.
Little is an intelligent dog,
so he might actually pull it off.
That's be good...
More importantly, why won't Lucy come home?
Dad shouldn't have done that!
Hey, Kate.
Dad shouldn't have sold our sheep, Snowflake.
But you know he didn't have a choice.
If dad would've kept her, we'd go completely broke.
Dad could solve it by working more!
Not with an injured leg!
It already healed by then.
You don't understand
because you've not been home in a while,
but dad is being an awful layabout lately.
All he does is drinking all day long!
All day long?
Yes, precisely. Even after his leg healed,
he didn't go out to work.
That's how we became so poor!
Before, dad used to barely drink any alcohol at all.
Lucy running away from home and all is dad's fault!
I feel sorry for dad.
You pity him?
Dad was robbed of the last fractions of hope.
He came to believe
that he won't ever get to own a farm in his life.
The reason we came all the way to the faraway Southern Australia was to build a marvelous farm here.
Right now, that prospect seems to be as distant as ever.
But one should never give up on hoping, Ben.
Yes. Without a doubt.
I know! You go say that to dad.
That things are only starting now.
And we'll definitely get our chance to own a plot.
That's what I believe in.
I won't criticize dad anymore.
Good. Dad repents it himself more than anyone else.
Ah! Ouch!
I hit it again just as it healed up.
Well, if only a cup...
Where's dad?
In the next room.
Father.
Are you drinking from the very morning?
Ah, no... It's that I just hit my leg.
No. I'll stop. I won't drink.
Is Little still away?
Yes.
So Little disappeared as well?
He's probably searching for Lucy.
We also have to go look for her.
Yes.
Even so, you wanted to drink instead?
I'm told you've been spending your days drinking lately.
Not really...
I've been saving a little of my salary,
but even that won't be enough
to buy Snowflake back, right?
I doubt it. I got good money for Snowflake.
But thinking about it now,
I probably shouldn't have sold her.
Father, even if you didn't have a single chance
to get a plot up to now,
I still think it's way too soon to throw away the hope.
Father, one day you'll get your land
and build a marvelous farm on it.
I'll also put my every effort into it
and even Clara is going to do her best...
Yes, I'll do my best.
Ah, Clara? You're going out?
Yes. Ben, I'm reassured now.
You've become such a responsible man!
Not really...
Ben, Clara.
It seems I've been causing you
a lot of unnecessary worry, haven't I?
I've always put my unwavering trust in you.
It's just that if you keep drinking...
I know.
Ben gave me quite a scolding for that just now.
I couldn't scold you, father.
After meeting nothing but disappointment and worry in these lands, I ended up developing a drinking habit.
I see now. Ben put it in no uncertain terms for me.
I threw away every trace of hope.
The hope of building a marvelous farm.
Saying things so faint-hearted is not like you at all!
I also said that we'll still have a chance
to acquire as much land as we need.
Certainly! Father, don't let the flame of hope die out.
For family and for everyone!
Right. I'm lucky to have such a wonderful family.
Even if it's missing one of its members now.
Right. Lucy-May...
Where could she be by now?
Why won't she return?
This...
This remorse from selling Snowflake is unbearable!
Mom, why are you crying?
Back when your dad was taking Snowflake away,
I should've stopped him,
then nothing of this would've happened...
Mom.
Hey. Good morning.
Good morning.
Your father is still home, right?
Yes. They're awaiting your arrival.
This is something haunting me since yesterday.
We don't have a single clue
about how we should look for Lucy.
Combing through the city of Adelaide
from one edge to another is our only option.
That'd be totally impossible with just three of us.
Either way, we just gotta find some leads.
Why is it happening?
Why is Lucy nowhere to be seen?
Oh. Mr. Pettywell is going out.
Ah!
What's wrong?
Everyone forgot about it,
but little Tob actually said he saw Lucy.
Ah, is that so?
Because it's just something Tob said,
we didn't make much of it and soon forgot about it.
But if what Tob said was true...
About Lucy looking at him from the carriage window?
Without saying anything, not even smiling at him?
That's a bizarre story for sure.
But if it was true after all,
that's the only lead on Lucy we currently have.
Tell me, Tob.
Hm?
You know Mr. Pettywell's carriage, right?
Was it that kind of carriage?
The one Lucy rode.
It was even bigger.
Even bigger? How much bigger?
This big!
Listen, did that carriage have any paintwork on it?
I forgot.
Say, Tob. Are you sure the girl in carriage was Lucy?
That was Lucy for sure. I'm certain!
Then, why did she pretend not to know you
when she saw you?
I don't know.
You don't suppose it could've been someone else?
No way! It was our Lucy, I know that!
Why would Lucy pretend she doesn't know you?
Because... Because that's what happened!
Tob, no need to cry.
I'm sure that girl just resembled Lucy a lot.
In a place such as Adelaide, there should be
at least one girl resembling her.
And what if she suddenly fell ill, developed
a high fever and became inert to everything?
Fell ill, huh?
When examining her from the outside,
I can't seem to find anything out of the ordinary.
That said, she's still unable to regain her memory...
I suppose she is...
After all, it's the first such case in my practice.
Do you feel unwell somehow, Emily?
I don't.
Doctor.
Hm?
Am I going to stay forever like this,
unable to regain my memory?
No, I wouldn't consider that as a possibility.
Doctor, I want to find out who I am.
That's why...
Yes, I know, I know. It'll be fine.
Your memory will totally return one of these days!
It'd better.
Hey, Emily.
I understand how you feel,
but you shouldn't rush yourself so much.
You're not at all troubled
by your current position, are you?
Y-Yes.
In any case, you can think of this place
as of your own home for now.
And of me as of your own mother.
Okay.
You seem to have taken matters pretty far, madam.
What do you mean?
You don't get it?
Letting her call you mother and all...
Yes, I don't mind it.
I really think she's an adorable girl.
Is that so?
By the way, her parents haven't showed up yet?
We can't count on that.
How would they know she's here?
Ah, is that so?
But then, her parents are probably desperately looking for her now.
Yes, I suppose so.
But then, what should we possibly do about it?
Come in.
Prospero! Come here.
How does she look, doctor?
I see. Still no progress?
Ah, Sylvia, I'm going out now.
What for?
To visit the Duke of York in his mansion.
He returned from England yesterday.
Ah, I see.
Please give my regards to Duke and his wife.
Sure.
Well, you can be free now, Emily.
How about you go play in the garden?
Okay.
Hey! Stop near that carriage.
Hey, Mr. Princeton!
Are you going out?
Mr. Pettywell.
It seems I'm in luck today.
If I'd had come just a little later,
I wouldn't be able to meet you.
Do you need something from me?
Certainly! I've been meaning to resume yesterday's talks.
Resume yesterday's talks?
Yes.
So how about it?
Will you please sell your farm near Gawler to me?
Pretty sure I already gave you
my unambiguous refusal yesterday.
And I said that I'm not giving up that easily!
My answer remains the same today.
I'm not selling that farm.
Now or later, I have no such intention.
Please take your leave now.
I've prepared a whole 2000 pounds!
You just can't understand, can you?
It's not a matter of money.
Huh?
Mr. Pettywell.
I was about to leave.
Mr. Princeton!
Okay, we can depart now!
I'm not giving up!
I'll be waiting here. Mr. Princeton!
Adelaide Bridge...
Oh shoot! I've forgotten something.
Hey, Max! I'm sorry, but could you
turn back to the mansion?
Oh? He's back!
I probably overdid it, offering 2000 pounds.
Well so be it. I can definitely resell
a farm like that to another with a way bigger tag.
Well now, it seems you finally came
to see the reason, Mr. Princeton?
Are you still here?
Please rest assured. You didn't mishear it
when I offered you a whopping 2000 pounds for it...
You'd better leave at once, Mr. Pettywell.
I returned for another reason.
But...
No pecking! It hurts. No means no!
Oh, come on!
You can't peck me. I don't like it.
Ah? What's wrong, guys?
Ah! So it was you, Prospero?
I see. She's a girl with an adoration for animals?
She said it's something she realized about herself.
It's curious how she can't even remember her name,
but managed to realize her animal-loving nature.
What a good child she is!
Didn't I tell you not to come near, you naughty child?
It appears you've come to dote sincerely on this child.
Yes!
Ah, dear.
Well, you see, there was something
I needed to talk to you about.
Ah, doctor, it's okay.
I'd like you to hear it too.
What is it about?
It's about her.
What about Emily?
We absolutely can't let her stay here indefinitely.
But she has a medical condition.
Isn't that right?
Amnesia is a medical condition, right?
Indeed it is.
However, her real parents have no way of knowing that
and are probably desperate to find her.
Therefore, the sooner we let her meet her parents,
the sooner they'll be relieved.
But how do we get in touch with those
who might be looking for her?
With this. We'll put a notice in the newspaper.
Here, they have advertisement section.
This is the one more conspicuous spot,
where we could put a notification
of us keeping her in custody.
I wonder if her parents will really see it.
We can't know for sure. But perhaps,
it's not just her parents who are looking for her.
Be it a relative or just someone close...
Right. Someone will definitely see that.
What do you think about this plan?
Yes, it's good I suppose.
Sylvia, listen.
It's true that she's adorable.
But she's not our daughter.
I know.
Now, come back, you guy! Come now.
Now, come over here.
Now!
After all, my wife dotes on that child so much...
So it would seem.
I beg your pardon.
Is someone in the office?
Yes!
Excuse me. You see, I need to ask for a favor.
I'll be there in a moment!
How may I help you?
I'd like to post this notice in the advertisement section.
It's ten shillings per word.
Very well.
Then, please post it in the tomorrow's issue.
Hm.
I can't.
Huh?
Is tomorrow's advertisement section filled up already?
No-no, it's just that tomorrow is Sunday
so we won't have an issue.
Ah... That's right, it's Saturday today.
Too bad. Then, the Monday's issue, please.
Without a doubt.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
Now we're finally going to Duke of York's mansion.
Duke of York, huh?
He totally wouldn't know anything about Lucy.
A newspaper?
They wouldn't know anything about Lucy either.
No, not necessarily!
Good morning!
Good morning.
I'd like to know something.
How much does it cost to post an ad in your paper?
What would you like to post?
A missing person notice.
That'd be ten shillings per character.
Ten Shillings?
Thank you.
Hey, hold it!
Huh?
You want to post a notice
about a missing person, right?
Yes.
But I have to consult my family first.
You'd better apply for it as soon as possible.
The advertisement section tends to fill up in no time.
Okay.
A girl of about ten years of age,
who lost her memory, huh?
This goes in the "missing person" section.
Wow, so lovely!
Are you... Are you giving this to me?
Certainly, it's yours!
Do you like it?
Yes, very much so!
I'm seeing a doll this lovely
for the first time in my life!
Look, you did it again!
Huh?
You need to remember your life up to this point
to be saying things like that.
Ah, you're right.
But I'm sure it's true. Even if I can't remember
anything about my past,
I know it's the first time I'm seeing a doll so wonderful!
I'm so glad to see that I made you happy, Emily.
It caught my eye in a store I've been to.
Thank you, mother.
I'm delighted.
Oh my, how curious.
Prospero seems awfully jealous of this doll.
I'm sorry, Prospero.
Look, it's my sister. Isn't she cute?
You shouldn't be mad at her.
Right, right! Do you understand it now?
She's my sister and her name is...
What name will you give her, Emily?
What's wrong, Emily?
Just now, in my mind,
a certain name suddenly popped up.
What name?
I don't remember. But it's a very nostalgic name,
the one I know very well.
I'm sure... I'm sure it used to be my own name.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Sylvia, the Duke of York's wife
said she absolutely wants to meet Emily.
Oh my dear.
You already told her about Emily?
Yes. And the incident piqued her interest a great deal.
I told her she's an adorable child
and promised to bring her with me tomorrow.
My!
Hey, Emily, have you ever met the duchess?
Ah. It was foolish of me to ask that.
You don't remember a thing from your past, right?
Each word costs ten shillings
so be sure to make it as short as possible, okay?
I know that.
When you're done writing that,
have some tea before going to the publisher.
You've enough time for that, right?
Well, this should do, I reckon.
Lucy-May, ten, missing - Popple.
This goes in the missing persons section, right?
Lucy didn't return that day either.
I manage to regain my memory
thanks to a reunion with Little.
Now I can return safely to my family.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Little! Little!"
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you