South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 39 - Two Partings
Hey, Snowflake. If the goats are giving us milk,
why aren't you giving any?
Answer me! Hey! Hey!
Ouch!
That hurt!
Little... So Lucy returned already, huh?
Where have you been to?
I giving Little some exercise.
Kate was looking for you a little while ago.
I bet she wants to make me study again or something?
Finally on my summer vacation,
studying is the last thing I want.
It's not about studying.
She said it's something about Snowflake.
About Snowflake?
Yeah.
What about Snowflake?
How should I know?
Makes sense. I guess I won't be able
to learn anything from you.
When autumn comes, I'll go to school too.
Ah! Pure thing!
I'm actually happy!
You're an odd fellow, Tob.
Hey, can I ride this hammock too?
Sure.
I'm pretty tired from all this
running around with Little.
Ah, sister, be careful.
Huh?
Ah!
Ouch!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Did I tell you? Be careful.
Ah, it hurts.
What's with this hammock?
You propped it up, didn't you?
Yes.
When you do that, at least prop it tightly!
If you climb it slowly, it'll be alright.
Alright...
Ah, feels good!
Cooking is nowhere near as exciting
when you're doing it without any meat.
Did meat really become that expensive?
Yes. The meat-yielding animals
such as cows, pigs, and sheep are very sparse here.
After all, the population
of Southern Australia increased greatly.
Even though we see a lot of sheep around...
That's true. But they only
keep the sheep for their wool.
Ah, I sure would love to stuff myself
with some delectable meat.
It seems, we might soon be able to do that.
But for now, just try to bear with it.
Still, unless we have the money,
we can't buy any expensive meat, can we?
Yes...
And dad can't go to work yet,
even if his leg healed up already?
It hadn't fully recovered yet.
But the other day, I heard Doctor Deighton
telling dad it's already fine.
If dad starts working again,
we can buy meat and whatever, right?
Kate!
Didn't I tell you already?
Dad's leg hadn't fully recovered yet.
One way or another, he drinks too much.
Look, I'm almost out of alcohol.
Please don't harm your health
furthermore by drinking so much.
Well, I'm not drinking that much.
Still, you start even such
a bright morning from drinking...
Before long, it'll be evening again, wouldn't it?
It's true that dad was drinking too much as of late.
There was something deeply frustrating about this.
Dad was now drinking even more
than Dr. Deighton, an inveterate drunkard.
Doctor! Doctor Deighton!
Hey. Well met, Clara.
Good afternoon, doctor.
You've finished working already, John?
Yes.
Going on a date tonight?
We've met you at a perfect time.
Huh?
Actually, Clara was awfully worried lately,
so she even came to ask for my advice.
Advice? What in the world is this about?
It's about my father.
My father won't stop drinking these days.
Ah, so that's how it is?
I understand how father feels
and why that makes him want to drink more.
But by drinking so much,
he'll ruin his health for sure.
He still can't get any land,
add to that his leg injury.
Because nothing ever goes according to plan,
Mr. Popple resorted to drinking alcohol, I think.
That must definitely be so.
If as Clara says, he'll ruin his health,
that'd be a disaster.
Well, drinking that much
won't be enough to ruin his health.
Just look at me, who's been drinking for most of my life,
yet my health is still more or less excellent.
That doesn't sound like something
a doctor should say!
Yes. But well, I was just telling the truth.
You're still in favor of drinking, after all?
No, I didn't say that...
Yes. I suppose, Mr. Popple is drinking too much.
It'll be better for him to hold back a little.
Besides, doctor...
We no longer have any money at all in the house.
Oh my.
It's been two months since father last worked.
On top of that, I've begun
freeloading at your place again.
My and Ben's salaries are totally not enough
to keep our family going.
I also thought I'd go talk to Mr. Popple,
ask him to stop drinking and start working again.
Doctor, if only you can,
please help us persuade him. I beg you!
Because I'm such a drunkard myself,
if I'd tell another to cut back on drinking,
my words won't have any weight to them.
Well, I'll try to hint it anyway.
Ah! I would really appreciate it!
Yes. By the way, in two or three days,
my stay in your house will be over.
Huh?
But then, where are you going next, Doctor?
I've settled on going to a medical office
in the newly built city of Gawler.
City of Gawler?
Adelaide is pretty well-supplied with doctors now.
But in Gawler, they've not a single Doctor yet.
Which means we won't get to see you
for a long while, doesn't it?
So it seems.
And when are you leaving?
In three days.
Well, that's very sudden news.
Yes. We agreed on them
sending over a carriage for me.
Well... Having to part with you sure is sad.
Here, have a drink, please.
No.
Huh?
I'm not drinking today.
Why is that?
Somehow, I'm just not in the mood for drinking.
You don't sound like your usual self.
To tell you the truth, I'm cutting back
on drinking from now on.
Huh?
For my health's sake.
John, will you drink with me?
No.
Don't want a drink?
Yes.
Come on, join me!
No, I'll pass.
What's with you two?
That's very strange.
Father!
Huh?
I beg you, please, stop drinking.
However you look at it,
this much is too much!
I understand your feelings,
the frustration that's tormenting you!
My feelings, huh?
Even if she doesn't say anything,
mom is very worried too!
I understand.
Huh?
Father...
Drinking alcohol didn't make me
much happier anyhow.
Honey...
I'm sorry for causing you so much worry.
Huh? They're going to eat Snowflake?
I said it's probably a joke, alright?
It's horrible even as a joke!
The only thing we don't have to worry about is the goat's milk. It's coming out really nicely.
Say, Kate, is our family actually that destitute?
So it seems. We've completely ran out of money.
What'll become of us now?
If dad starts working again,
we'll pull through, somehow.
Hello, Little.
As always, sticking close to Snowflake, huh?
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Doctor.
Right, I came back with Clara and John.
Oh?
Hm?
What is it?
Doctor, you've not drank anything today?
Yeah.
Now isn't that unusual?
Dad didn't drink either?
He did.
Oh...
Doctor, are you unwell?
Me? No, no.
Why, then?
I have my reasons. Right.
For the next three days, I'm not drinking anything.
Why three days, exactly?
I'm going to the city of Gawler
to work at the doctor's office there.
Of course, it comes with a free dwelling.
Then, we'll have to part?
Gawler is pretty far, isn't it?
I wouldn't say so.
Then, we may come visit you there?
Of course.
You don't me lying here?
I'm getting pretty exhausted.
Sure.
Ah! Doctor, be careful.
Right, right.
Ah!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Doctor, didn't I tell you to be careful?
Yes, but I didn't expect that.
There.
You gotta climb on it slowly.
Right, got it.
Yes. Slowly, right?
Ah, it sure is comfortable.
Take care.
Thank you.
Please give my regard to Ben as well.
Will do.
Well, farewell, then.
We'll come visit you!
I'll be waiting.
Well, we may go now.
Alright.
Giddyup!
Doctor! Doctor! Farewell!
Farewell!
Since our arrival to Southern Australia,
Dr. Deighton became part of the family for us.
And now he left for the city of Gawler.
What a truly tragic parting.
I protest! I decisively protest!
I brought Snowflake up myself!
Besides, her and Little made great friends!
We knew you'd probably say just that.
But dear, please hear me out.
We no longer have any money whatsoever in the house.
So, because we don't have any urgent need in her,
we wanted to put her out on the next town auction.
Anything but Snowflake!
Listen, Lucy. I want you to think of it:
there's no point in keeping just one sheep.
Even if we shear her, one sheep's wool
isn't enough for anything.
So you're saying Snowflake is of no use to us?
No, on the contrary.
It can be of great use to us.
Above all, we could use her for meat that we can eat.
Dad!
Ah, sorry, sorry.
Because we've known Snowflake ever since
she was a baby, we can't do that, right?
Please! Just let Snowflake stay in our house
the way she lives here now.
The goats are good for milking them. But that sheep...
Snowflake has a very soft wool.
Just touching her wool
is greatly pleasing to the senses!
Well, we can't put that to any use.
Little... Little will feel very lonely!
We kept Snowflake so as to get Little used to being
around sheep without attacking them, didn't we?
We got it from Mr. Long, the shepherd!
Little is now perfectly used to being around sheep.
Seemingly, not one bit interested in attacking them.
Which means Snowflake
already fulfilled her role, didn't she?
No! I don't want to part with Snowflake!
Please come to see the reason, Lucy-May.
It's you who is being unreasonable here!
Honey, isn't there anything else suitable for selling,
other than that sheep? Let's think about it.
Thank you, mom.
Good night.
Father and the others are having a hard time, Lucy.
What do you mean?
We really don't have any more money.
It seems, starting this Monday,
dad starts working at road construction again.
Then, we no longer need to sell Snowflake off, do we?
That's not what I meant.
Say, Lucy, what if we swallow the bitter pill
and sell Snowflake?
Even you say we have to do that?
I just think that for the good of our family,
we'd better sell her.
You can't only think about yourself here.
Hey, kid, do you happen to know
where Mr. Popple's house is?
Right here.
Oh, here? Much obliged.
Hello, Mr. Popple! Hello!
Is anyone home?
They should be in the backyard.
Backyard?
Sir, what did you come here for?
You live in this house, kid?
Yes.
I came here to take a look at the sheep.
If I like it, I might buy it.
Uh? It's in the backyard too...
Show me the way, kid, will you?
Okay. This way.
They came to buy the sheep!
I called from the doorway,
but you couldn't hear me, it seems.
Oh? It's that sheep?
This one doesn't look half-bad.
Ah, Madam. Good morning.
Good morning.
Excuse me, but who was it
who told you about this ship?
Why, it was your husband, of course.
I met him at the town market,
where he asked if I would like to buy a sheep.
Mother, we've decided not to sell Snowflake, right?
Right... Instead of selling Snowflake,
we decided to raise money by selling my clothes
and the clothes that you girls outgrew.
I'm prepared to fork out two pounds for this sheep.
Two pounds?
By selling clothes, you could raise
ten shillings at best, Madam.
But this sheep...
Sir, we can by no means sell Snowflake!
Dad also said we don't need to sell it!
I see. There's probably been
a conflict of opinions somewhere.
I'm so sorry for turning you away.
Ah, it's a shame.
This one is an actually good sheep.
With two pounds, we'd probably be
well off for some while.
But if you've returned to working,
we don't need those two pounds, do we?
No, it doesn't necessarily imply
there will always be job.
But that sheep...
If we explain it really well to Lucy,
she'll probably also come to see the reason.
So we're not selling these clothes for now?
They'd probably only be one fifth or one sixth
of what a sheep would yield.
How should we bring it to Lucy...
Pretty sure it's tomorrow
when they're holding the auction.
Ah! Don't you startle me like that, Little!
Hey!
Get back here!
Really!
Go play with Snowflake in the backyard.
I'm home!
Oh? Where are the clothes that were here before?
Arthur took them to the auction grounds.
I hope he gets good deals for them.
So do I.
Listen, Lucy.
What is it?
What's going on there?
What's wrong, Little? That was pretty loud.
Mother, where did Snowflake go?
Hey! Snowflake is not in the backyard, mom!
Arthur took her to the auction.
No way... No way!
Look, I'm sorry. But that was
the only option we had left!
How cruel! Awfully cruel!
Where are you going?
To bring her back from the auction grounds!
Lucy-May!
Cruel. So cruel!
Well, everyone, a splendid sheep we got here!
Good both for shearing and for butchering!
A remarkable sheep, however you look at it!
Let's start the bidding at one pound!
Right! One pound!
One pound! One pound! One pound!
Pound and a half!
At once, we hear a bid of a pound and a half!
Pound and a half! Alright, it's a pound and a half!
One pound and a half!
Two pounds!
Good! Two pounds! Two pounds!
Any more bids? Two pounds for this amazing sheep!
Now, will we hear one more bid?
Fine! Two pounds and a half!
Good! Two and a half! Two and a half!
A two and a half pounds bid was made!
Whoa!
Hey! Watch where you're going!
Huh?
Hey, Lucy! Where are you going?
A runaway horse!
A runaway horse! A runaway horse, people!
Run for your life!
Dodge it to the right! To the right!
Hey! It's heading towards the city center!
Stop it, someone! It's dangerous!
When I came to my senses, I found myself
in an unfamiliar luxurious mansion.
Unable to remember where I used to live before
or even what my name was.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Who am I?"
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you