South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 07 - Ben's Bad Luck
Ah! This was green wood, it makes too much smoke!
We don't burn it because it burns cold!
And this fire's supposed to be bright!
How can you not know even that?
I know that.
We burn it so that dad and brother
can spot it even from afar, right?
And that's why you don't throw green wood
into the fire, understood?
Wah! So smoky!
But won't they be able
to also use smoke as a landmark?
That's only in daytime!
Ah! That's a terrible smoke you got.
Don't you know how to burn it better?
Lucy-May just threw in some green wood.
Dad and brother returned already?
I also tried looking for them on the coast,
but still nothing.
I was hoping we'd just missed each other on the road
and they're back home already...
Do you think dad and brother may have gotten lost?
I just hope they're fine and well, that's all.
Remember Mr. Jamling injured his leg,
when he got lost on his way home from Adelaide?
Are you really sure they're fine?
Well, the ones who rescued Mr. Jamling back then
were dad and Ben, right?
It's unlikely they'd make the same mistake.
Probably right. I'm sure you're right.
Still nothing, even now?
Yes...
Is Tob asleep already?
He's asleep, and it's also time
for you two to go to bed.
It's way past your bedtime.
But it's just...
There's no reason for you to worry
about dad and Ben, is there?
Back in England, he used to go out
for a night stroll all the time.
But we're in Australia now.
And what difference does it make, Kate?
At night, all places are the same.
At least, the moon may come out soon.
Let's hope it does.
Be careful where you walk, Ben.
Okay.
Let's speed up a bit.
Ah! You two are still awake?
This won't do! Go to bed now.
Hurry up now!
Are you sleeping?
No.
How about you?
There's no way I can fall asleep.
God, please protect our dad and brother, please.
Dad.
What is it?
I have this feeling we've been walking in circles for a while.
It can't be, we've been walking towards the shore all this time.
Are you sure?
Just trust me.
Okay.
It's about time the moon comes out.
The moon?
With just the lamp's light,
we can't really see all that far.
Dad, does that mean we're lost after all?
No, I think we were probably
on the correct path up until now.
But we should already be
out of the woods by now.
Yes, that's also true.
Let's not walk further
until the moon comes out. Please, dad.
However, everyone is likely worried about us.
It's best that we return as soon as possible.
But we might get lost!
Ah! Huh?
What happened, Ben?
I just bumped into a strange animal.
A strange animal?
Look at that!
Doesn't seem to be a dog.
Looks like a wild boar.
The animals living around here
are nothing like what we've seen in England.
Ben, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Good, let's keep going.
Okay.
Oh?
The moon is out, dad.
Thank goodness, mom.
I believe in your father.
Moonrise or no moonrise,
he is not the kind to get lost.
In that case, there's no need to worry
about dad and Ben, right, mom?
Correct.
What's so funny, Clara?
It's just that a single glance at your face would be enough for anyone to tell how worried you are.
Oh my.
I am glad.
Huh?
I'm really glad the moon decided to come out.
Wow!
You can already hear the waves clearly from here!
Which means, we're almost at the shore.
I think we may have strayed
a little to the south from the road.
We can now return safely
by going north along the coast.
If we made it to here, that means our tents
are already near, right?
Yes.
And she said she was worried
and couldn't get no sleep!
Dad had returned?
You were awake?
Of course I am!
I'm so worried I can't get no sleep...
You're a skilled liar!
Hey, look.
What is that?
It must be some animal
that only exists in Australia.
That's a peculiar one...
Hey! We don't have the time for detours!
Yeah, I know!
Ah...
Huh?
Sure are peculiar guys. Both of them.
Go to sleep, Clara.
I'll be all right.
Why don't you go take a rest yourself?
I can't stop thinking that they should return soon.
I have a feeling they won't return today either.
I wonder if something unexpected
happened to them in Adelaide.
And if they haven't returned even this late,
it must be that nothing particularly good happened.
It's not the time to succumb to brooding.
We'll know for sure when dad returns, right?
You're probably right. No reason to worry
about something ahead of time.
Mother.
Hmm?
We've all come to Australia,
hoping that we'll be many times happier here
than we were in England, right?
Yes.
Do you really believe this will come true?
You don't sound very convinced, mom.
No, I'm convinced in it.
We will become happy...
no matter what happens.
Had dad returned yet?
Oh, I'm sorry I woke you up.
Daddy isn't here yet.
Now, don't you worry and go back to sleep.
Ah! They're back!
Huh?
Lucy-May, you're still half-asleep.
Mom just said, "not yet," remember?
But they are back! Can't you hear?
Huh? Hear what?
There! He's whistling.
Whistling?
It's our brother's whistling.
I can't hear anything.
Clara, Lucy-May says she can hear Ben whistling...
Ah, the bonfire crackling is too loud here.
You lied, didn't you?
Who? Me?
Just admit it that you didn't hear no whistle!
But I heard it before!
Nobody likes the liars.
I never tell lies!
Ah! Looks like they're back!
Ah!
It's Ben right there!
Yay!
Hey!
Welcome back!
We're back, mom.
Welcome home. But is sure is a little late.
Yes. A lot of things happened.
And what were those things?
Dad will tell you later.
And why are you two still awake?
Oh, come on!
Say, brother, were you whistling while on the way here?
Yes, but as we got closer, I stopped.
There, heard it?
I wasn't telling you no lies!
But still...
What do you mean "But still"?
I demand an apology!
Okay...
What's going on, Lucy-May?
Apologize, sister.
I'm sorry.
Ah! Welcome back!
I'm sorry for giving you all that worry.
Did something happen?
Yes, more or less.
What was it?
I'll tell you later.
I'm sorry for making you all worry,
but as you can see, we've returned safe and sound.
Now, it's late, so everyone goes to bed.
Good night, dad!
Good night, mom.
Good night.
Good night, brother.
I was trying my utmost to stay awake
and listen to dad's story with others.
But due to feeling so relieved,
as soon as I was in the bed, I ended up falling asleep.
Say, honey,
what do you say if we sell the prefabricated home
we brought over from England?
Huh?
You're thinking of selling it?
How come?
It's as though I clearly heard dad
saying he wants to sell the prefabricated home.
Sounds ridiculous.
No... it must have been a dream. Just a dream.
Good! We're done!
On the next day,
dad and Ben went to retrieve
the rest of our things from the ship.
Tomorrow, we're all setting out for Adelaide.
Good, put it on top of the rest.
Now, Ben, I need you to stay here.
See that our things
don't get mixed with someone else's.
Got it.
Meanwhile, I'll make one more trip to the ship.
No heavy stuff among our remaining things,
so I should be able to manage by myself.
Besides, an oxcart might arrive soon
to carry our things.
From Mr. Bard, right?
Yes. The precious oxcart
that we barely managed to locate yesterday.
If not for that oxcart contract
we concluded with with Mr. Bart,
moving to Adelaide tomorrow
would've been impossible for us.
So, when Mr. Bart's oxcart arrives,
we start loading our things onto it?
Yes. I'm counting on you.
Here we go!
Mom, what's wrong?
You keep sighing so deeply.
Ah!
Oh, thanks.
I just feel disappointed, somehow.
Still hung up on that prefabricated home?
I used to dream about how we come here
and live in that house ourselves.
But it can't be helped since we can't take it to Adelaide.
It's not like there's absolutely no way
for us to take it there...
It would take several days and a small fortune
to transport, isn't it what dad said?
Yes. That's why, I guess,
I have no choice but to give up on it.
Ah?
And where's Lucy-May?
Walk!
Come on, Sticky, start walking.
Are you taking that goat back to its owner?
Not at all.
Her owner hadn't appeared yet, Billy.
Then, you'll have two goats soon, you know that?
Yes, that's right. They'll be our goats.
Both she and her baby goat!
It'll be born soon already!
That's what Mr. Parker told us.
And where are you taking her now?
Isn't it obvious? We're taking her
to where there's grass for eating.
Now, Sticky, start walking.
You even gave her a name already!
There we go!
Yes, that's the way.
Move it!
Yes.
That's the way.
Come on! Keep going, you lazy thing!
Let's go!
This much should be enough for her.
No way! If she doesn't eat enough,
she can't give birth to a healthy baby.
Positively horrible!
What is?
That mister has been whipping
the poor ox for a while now.
Come on! Come on!
Take that!
You wretch! Slacker!
Looks like the cart is completely stuck.
Should we help pushing it?
Probably.
Wretch! Slacker...! Oh?
Sir!
Mister, we'll push the cart from behind,
but you stop whipping the ox, please.
Hey! Slacker! Seems like you found
some helpers here.
Come on! Put some muscle, slacker!
Heavy!
Come on!
Yes! Like that! Good! Keep going!
Keep going!
There!
Mister, you're carrying
way too much stuff in that cart.
I know, but I can't throw it overboard either.
What's in there?
Fresh water. They're gonna ferry it to the ship.
Water for the ship, huh?
Hey boy, sorry to bother,
but could you push for a bit more?
Just need to get it to the beach over there,
the ship's crew will then come to fetch it.
Ain't got no choice! We'll push.
We're pushing, mister!
Okay!
Let's Go!
Like that.
Huh?
Hey, boy! If you got nothing better to do,
could you give us a hand?
Sure thing.
What should I do?
Take the barrels and roll them over there, please.
Right. I appreciate it.
When you're done,
we'll treat you to something tasty!
Sir! The current is sweeping away that barrel!
Huh? Oh, that? Just forget about it,
it only had some flour in it!
But these here we can't afford losing.
They're for this business, you know.
But for our family, flour is something
incredibly important!
We've carried enough to the warehouse already.
There's no such thing as "too much flour"!
After all, starting now, we'll be living
in the lands that have never been cultivated!
Listen, boy, if you have that much energy
to pester us with it, why don't you go get it yourself?
Will do just that.
Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it...
Right... That's way! Good! Good-good!
Stop! Stop!
Thanks a lot, you two.
It seems, we finally made it to the destination.
Hey! Good Morning!
Hey!
Oh my, that right there
must be our family's stuff, I swear!
That pile of things?
I wonder where my dad and brother are.
It's just like I thought.
Why would they just dump it here and leave?
This looks like some fancy furniture.
That, I don't know either.
We have time until the evening
to ferry all that water to the ship.
At any rate, the ship
is in a bit of a kerfuffle right now.
How about this - if you don't have any urgent business,
why don't you hang out with us until the evening?
After this, my work would be concluded for today.
But tomorrow morning, I need to pick up
Mr. Popple's belonging and return to Adelaide again.
Well, that settles it. In that case,
let's get to business straight away.
'Aight, pal. Your turn.
Sure.
Ah! Hey, the current carried that boy
way out into the open sea!
Huh?
It ain't nothing to be worried about.
That boy said he likes flour, didn't he?
And here's something we like very much.
Damn it. Damn it!
Damn it!
This is definitely my brother's shirt.
And over here, he dropped his hat.
You think he went for a swim?
Swimming is not among my brother's strong sides.
Oh, there!
Looks like someone's clutching a barrel!
Hey! Help me, please!
Looks like my brother.
Isn't he shouting something?
Could he be just playing?
Doesn't seem like it.
What are you two looking at?
Our brother is all the way out there.
Saying something to us, but we can't understand.
Help me, please!
He just said, "Help me please!"
So he is drowning?!
But he's still clutching onto that barrel.
We need to find someone to help him!
Ah...
Oh cut it, you old wreck!
What do we do?
Help me, please!
Save me, please!
Sister and John found a Koala in the forest.
I absolutely insisted on catching it.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Eve of our Departure".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mom from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you