South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 36 - Five Shillings in the Nest
Come on! Let me go!
Take it easy, Doctor.
I've had enough of your faces!
Let me go I said!
When Lucy and I went to fetch Doctor Deighton,
we were awfully surprised
to see our old cabin in flames.
The one who ordered them
to set fire to our old cabin was Mr. Pettywell.
My, my, if it isn't Mr. Popple's daughters?
You came all the way here to see the show?
Hey, Silver, if he looks at you the wrong way,
feel free to bite him to death, if needed.
Lucy, aren't you going to stop Little?
To tell you the truth, at that moment,
I even thought it'd be better
if Little tore Mr. Pettywell's bulldog to shreds.
Stop it, Little!
Ah?
Let's go, Little, this way.
What? Really gonna stop now?
Wouldn't it be better to let them do it?
No!
It see, that's very clever of you.
There's no dog that's be on par with Silver
in the entirety of Adelaide.
Little wouldn't lose to that bulldog!
Then, why won't we let them do it to know for sure?
Oughta be interesting!
That's enough!
Mr. Pettywell, a man such as you
is indeed the worst calamity that can befall one.
Ah, Doctor Deighton, do me a favor
and leave that house soon, will you?
You're living on my land now, remember?
I said it before, I'll say it now:
I'm not going anywhere! Period.
Why'd that'd be bothersome. Then, how should I
do away with that house - burn it or tear it down?
I said I'm not going...
Either way, I'll wait for just a month more.
In one month from now, I'll put into action
what I just said, without hesitation.
Damn you...
Doctor, I wonder if Mr. Pettywell
is actually gonna drive you out.
Yeah, I'm sure he will.
After all, his plan is to fill that plot
with houses and sell them all separately.
Then, where will you go, Doctor?
I've nowhere to go.
If they tear that house down, I'll just stretch a tent
like in the old times and keep practicing from there.
They'll tear the tent down in no time.
Doctor, I think it's best that you
start looking for where to go next, after all.
No! Whatever happens,
I won't yield an inch there!
I won't yield!
What's the matter, Doctor?
I'm tired.
Just a bit more, Doctor.
If only there was something we could ride,
we'd make it to your place fast and with comfort.
But around here, there's...
Look, look, look, a carriage like that.
Eh...
Doctor, don't give up.
Don't give up, Doctor.
Eh... Right, I'll keep going.
Gotta do my best for a little longer,
until we get to Angas Street.
Don't give up, Doctor!
Almost there, Doctor!
Come on! You can do it!
Ah?
Ah!
Eh... Doctor Deighton has come.
What about Kate and Lucy?
Coming with him.
G'day.
Quite a misfortune you've been through, Mr. Popple?
Just injured my leg a bit due to a misstep.
I owe you one for taking all the trouble to come.
No, no, I'm a doctor, remember?
No matter how far the patient is...
Oh! Don't move, don't move!
So, which of the legs?
The right one.
Oh? This one?
Ah, let's see, let's see.
Ah, that looks awfully swollen.
Yes, and with a bit of throbbing pain...
Oh, this doesn't look good.
If I move it like this...
Ouch!
Huh? That cabin was on fire?
Mr. Pettywell wants to build
a new house there and sell it.
Your father and Ben, as well as Mr. Jamling
all worked hard to expand that tiny cabin.
Even if it's no longer our house,
I wouldn't want to see it go up in flames.
That'd probably sadden your father too.
It hurts!
Yes, yes, yes, yes. And if I do this, how is it?
Ouch! It hurts!
Hurts the most this way.
I see.
Well then, seems you've a fracture in your bone.
I see. That was an awfully inopportune
misstep on my part.
Still, it's a fate vastly preferable
to being crushed under the rock.
This kind of injury can heal perfectly
in just a month or so.
A month?
Doctor, are you saying
it'll take one month to heal?
Perhaps.
But then, I won't be able to work
for a whole month, right?
Well, if you exert yourself,
the fracture will only expand.
One month, huh?
According to Mr. Pettywell,
I also have only a month to leave my house.
That's just outrageous.
You built that house with your own hands, after all.
And I also came to like it quite a lot.
By a stroke of ill fortune,
that land fell into Mr. Pettywell's hands, eh?
I’ve always been an unlucky fellow.
But then... Do you have any other place to go to?
For the time being...
No, I'd rather say it's best that you
refrain from thinking about that.
In that case, would you come to stay with us again?
Eh? I can't do that.
I've already delivered
a great deal of nuisance to your family.
It wasn't a nuisance.
Never mind it. When it comes to dwelling,
I'll find some, sooner or later.
That reminds me.
This time, I could try working
at a new city hospital that opens soon.
No, I said! No! Don't move, Little!
This one is an awfully good soap.
Doesn't it smell good?
Look, the foam is coming out nicely.
Ah! No! You gotta stand still!
Stand still, you! Ah!
Ugh. Tell me, why are you
that opposed to being clean?
Lucy, you’re the one
who detests bathing the most here.
Little is just taking after you.
Listen, I love taking baths now, is that clear?
Come on, don't move, Little.
Ah! No! Didn’t I tell you to stand still?
Hey, Little!
Ah! Oh no! Wait! Hey!
Little!
Huh?
Ah!
Little!
Ah! Geez!
You’re not getting away with it!
Little! Wait!
Little!
Huh?
Oh my, isn't it Little?
What’s with that fancy dress of yours?
Ah! No! Little...
Little!
Delicious.
Why do you find that stuff tasty, Doctor?
A kid won’t be able to understand that.
Oh... John, would you like a shot too?
I’m good, thanks.
John is a grown-up too,
but he detests the booze.
If you don't drink, you can’t become a grown-up.
But John is engaged to Clara already.
Doesn’t that make him a grown-up?
Oh, by the way...
When are you two getting married?
Well... Someday, I suppose.
Doctor, please pour a bit for me too.
Eh? You wanna drink?
Oh, good, good, good. Yes, but no need
to say “a bit.” Have plenty, plenty. Here.
Thanks...
Oh my, John, you drink alcohol too?
I was surprised a great deal too!
Well, Doctor.
Right... Here.
You shouldn't force yourself to drink.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'll drink it normally now.
Oh?
Ah!
There, see?
Oh! Splendid, splendid!
Seems foolish.
Well, let's get to eating now.
What was that ruckus about just now?
John was drinking alcohol.
That’s all?
It's been about a year since I last
had a meal together with the Popples.
Ah, Doctor, come sit down here, please.
Kate, call your father here.
Okay.
Is it true a while month should pass
before father’s leg can fully heal?
Yes.
Then, mother, he wouldn’t be able
to do any work during that time, would he?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
I’m having these thoughts every now and then...
Could it be that the Lord
left our family to our own devices?
Clara, stop saying nonsense like that.
So?
Sleeping soundly.
He looked exhausted, so I let him sleep.
I see. Them, I'll bring him his meal
when he wakes up.
Now, everyone, go ahead.
Thanks for the meal!
Ah... Dear Lord...
I'm going now!
No! I'm not taking you to school ever again!
What's going on, Little?
Are you disobeying what I tell you to do?
You can't come with me!
You understand, don’t you, Little?
Good morning, Little.
Oh. Lucy rejected you
and took flight, didn’t she?
Little, I'm going now.
I’ll put here what we should line up next.
Ah, I'll do it right now.
Don't worry, I can do it myself.
How is your father doing?
His body feels so heavy he can barely move,
so he just complains all day long.
He still can't use his leg, can he?
Besides, he became very irritable.
Oh my, oh my, our Mr. Popple?
Dad is an unlucky man.
You can’t know that for sure.
Still, that’s what I feel keenly
whenever I see him these days.
Despite all his effort up to now,
he couldn’t get any land.
There’s no good job for him either,
on top of that, he got injured.
You should take bad things off your mind.
I’m sure, it’ll turn to better now.
Yes. I’m trying to think that before long,
good things will start happening to us too.
Ah, welcome!
Bye-bye!
Lucy-May is made to stand again!
Shut up! I’ll get you now!
Ah! She spilled some!
We’ll tell everything to teacher!
We’ll tell...
Teacher, I won’t be talking during the class anymore,
so please forgive me.
Teacher! Teacher!
My head is starting to hurt already!
Try to forgive me, please!
Ah, that’s better.
Yeah.
Yeah, good, good.
This despicable guy is coming.
I don’t wanna meet him again.
Huh?
A bird's nest.
I wonder what kind of bird
built its nest at a place like this.
Must be a bird that likes collecting strange things.
A button, eyeglasses, a crooked nail.
Oh?
It’s money.
I'm home!
Little, hear this! I found some money!
So, what will you do with that money?
Gonna buy something.
What exactly?
Something!
You know, on the town square on Carrington Street,
they hold auctions all the time.
I think we can buy something wonderful there.
Not with just five shillings.
Five is more than none at all!
I'm sure this money is something
the Lord bestowed upon me.
It’s just some money that fell on the pavement
that the bird picked up.
The bird carried it to its own nest,
where you snatched it, didn’t you?
Hey, sister!
You’re going shopping with me or not? Answer me!
Be quiet.
Of course I'll go with you
once I’m done with this work.
Hey, you won’t be able to buy much
with just five shillings.
I don’t need much,
just one wonderful thing would do.
After all, it’s the first time
I made some money myself!
What was that? Didn’t you just pick it up?
You can’t use the word “made”
for something like that.
But that’s how the grown-ups use it.
Either way, it’s not the word
the children would use.
Got it.
Hey, how about a cake?
A cake?
In the bakery where Clara works,
they have very delicious cakes, don’t you know?
Five shillings should be enough to buy a cake.
Right...
But a cake would be gone
after we’ve eaten it, right?
Well, of course.
This feels like a bit of a waste.
Then do whatever you want.
It’s fine. A cake is fine.
I've always wanted to know what it’s like
to get full on cakes at least once.
You can’t buy that much.
Hey!
What is it?
Say, isn’t that Clara over there?
You're right.
That's strange. She’s supposed
to still be in the shop at this time.
Looks like she's pondering on something.
My, she didn’t even notice us just yet.
Huh? She’s heading in the direction
opposite to the bakery.
Wanna call her?
Wait a moment. Let's see where she's going
by following her first.
We’ll follow her?
Let's do just that!
My heart is racing, sister.
She entered this store.
What kind of store is this?
Looks like a fabric store, alright.
It’s where they sell fabric for sewing clothes.
This store seems awfully expensive.
You see her?
I don’t.
Wanna come inside?
Clara would notice us at once if we do that.
Isn’t it all the same if she does?
Ah... That's true.
It could only be that Clara came here
to buy some fancy fabric for clothes.
Ah?
Ah!
It's you two again!
Sister!
What are you doing at a place like this?
What are you doing at a place like this, sister?
What I’m doing is of none concern to you,
don’t you think?
But we thought you’d be at work
in the bakery right about now.
Yes, that's right.
But there was something I needed to deliver
to this part of the town.
And on my way back, I made a bit of a detour...
But why did you stop by this fabric store?
Let’s call that my secret.
You know, we saw you there on the main street
and followed you all the way to here.
But it seems you’ve been so preoccupied
with your own thoughts, you never noticed us.
So you followed me?
Sorry. But we couldn’t help
finding it bizarre somehow.
I see. You sensed it too?
You two, if you promise not to spill it to anyone else,
I might tell you what my secret is.
Yeah! I promise.
I promise too.
Well, come inside then, you two.
Mrs. Miller?
Oh my, did you forget something?
It's not that.
I'm sorry to distract you,
knowing how busy you are...
But could you please show my order
to my sisters as well?
Okay, no problem.
What did you mean by “your order”?
Fabric, of course.
Did you buy it in order to make a dress?
Yes, more or less.
I’m wrong?
If you put it that way...
Let’s keep it this way.
That’s a truly wonderful quality item you bought.
I believe, your little sisters would be proud of you.
It’s the very best item we have in this shop.
Such a beautiful fabric!
Could we possibly feel it?
If you’ve clean hands, go ahead.
Wow! It’s so smooth!
True!
It’s for a weddings dress, isn’t it, Clara?
It’s bound to make for a supreme wedding dress.
Then, you were the one who bought this fabric, Clara?
Month after month, Ms. Popple
keeps paying for it, little by little,
until it finally becomes her own.
Wow!
Clara, you're incredible!
Oh my, don't rejoice just yet.
We can’t exactly say it fully belongs to me yet.
What do you mean by that?
In truth, I still owe a bit more for it.
I'm sure it’ll be fully yours
as soon as next month, Ms. Popple.
After all, you’ve only five shillings more to pay.
Five shillings?
Yes. I’m just five shillings away
from really owning this beautiful fabric, at last.
Sister, you can already consider this fabric yours.
Just let me pay those final five shillings for you!
Here and now!
Lucy's money was used to pay for the fabric
that was to become Clara’s wedding dress.
But I still wonder, what kind of bird it was,
the one that picked up those five shillings?
While returning from the port,
we were assaulted by a gang!
Among the passengers riding that carriage with us,
was Mr. Pettywell, carried with him a sum of money.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Robbers on the Prairie".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you