South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 34 - Little and the School
Good morning, Little!
One... Two...
Three.
Huh? Only laid three this morning?
Okay, Little, bring Snowflake outside, please.
You can't go out yet!
We've yet an important job to finish here.
Gathered three eggs this morning.
Mom would be happy to know.
I wish they'd lay at least five a day.
We've got seven hens there, after all.
Try filling a complaint with those hens.
You don't suppose there's a snake
prowling the area?
Huh?
I wonder if there couldn't be a snake,
coming at night for our eggs.
What are you saying?
You should know this better than anyone!
Why'd a snake come, but then leave three eggs behind?
It'd just gulp down all of them!
It deemed three eggs not worth the trouble!
Listen, you. Better just go
finish your breakfast instead!
Otherwise, you'll be late to school.
Aren't you lucky, sis?
Again with that!
But you're lucky! You're so lucky
that you don't have to go to school.
I wonder if they've got
any better job than quarrying...
Not for the moment at least, no.
Besides, quarrying is the one most well-paid.
Well that's because it's dangerous.
No, that's 'cause it's laborious.
So it's both laborious and dangerous...
Hm... Well, I guess it's a little dangerous, after all.
That's 'cause we work with slapdash scaffolds.
Somehow, I'm awfully worried.
Hey-hey, didn't I work at the quarry
countless times before?
Still, this time you're also having
to camp inside a mountain?
Going home and back takes too much time.
I think it'll be enough for me
to only spend one night a week at home.
So our house remains without a man,
save for Saturday and Sunday...
What are you saying?
You still have Tob here.
Listen, Tob. When I'm not around,
be sure to help mom, will you?
Sure.
Only three eggs this morning.
Oh? Really?
Lucy-May, sit down and eat already.
Going to school all alone is boring!
You're still concerned about that, Lucy-May?
You can make many new friends in school too.
Then, you'll enjoy both the studying
and playing a lot more!
Thanks for the meal.
I already enjoy playing quite enough,
but studying - not in the slightest!
With studying, it's unavoidable that you'll hate it.
Kate is old enough to study on her own at home.
But you still can't be trusted with it on your own.
That's why you'll have to go to school, got it?
Well then, I'm done here.
I'm not there yet.
You don't mind if I go first?
Feel free.
Pansy, what happened?
You're not giving much milk at all this morning.
Kate, father won't be coming home until Saturday.
Be sure to see him off when he leaves, will you?
Yeah. Will do.
Dad started working in a quarry
over at the Mount Lofty.
Desperate to ever get the land, dad
stopped talking about farming altogether.
In order to make at least some living, dad had
no choice but to accept whatever job was available.
It's a tragedy that I have to go to school.
Are you coming along?
Lucy-May, please don't do anything foolish.
Listen, bringing Little to school
is absolutely unacceptable.
Do you understand, Lucy-May?
Yes.
Okay, let's walk to the road together.
Come back soon!
Sure.
I'll be sure to return on Saturday.
Please take care of yourself.
Sure. Don't worry about anything.
Lucy-May!
Order Little expressly
to return home right now.
Go home, Little.
You don't understand, Little?
Return home.
I'll hold Little down for now.
You go ahead, Lucy.
Okay.
Little, you can't go where Lucy is going.
Lucy is going to school,
where she'll be studying.
What's wrong?
Thinking about Little not obeying your order?
He always obeys them.
If he'd have really wanted to disobey it,
he'd shake Kate off and chase right after me.
Maybe you're right.
Well, let's return home now.
Will you be walking all the way
to the quarry on Mount Lofty?
Of course not!
The workers get to and from
the Eastern Terrace on a company carriage.
I see. Then, we'll split on that corner, right?
Yes.
Lucy, don't slack off when studying!
Okay.
All right. Mother, I'm off.
Come back soon.
Come back soon!
My sister Clara work at a bakery, ran by Mrs. Mac.
Little!
Ah? Did you forget something?
Uhm... No. I can't find Little.
Isn't he sleeping in the doghouse?
He's not there.
Then... He set out after Lucy!
Hey! What is it? Wild hare there? Hey!
Hey, Lucy!
What are you doing?
Hurry up to get in here!
I'll be there in a moment.
Who are you waiting for?
If you don't come soon,
the teacher will get get mad again, Lucy!
And what could you be doing,
standing over there, Lucy-May?
Yes, teacher.
What do you mean?
That doesn't answer my question!
Yes, teacher.
Now, answer me clearly,
what are you doing there, Lucy-May.
I'm waiting. For Little.
For Little? Who's Little?
Pretty sure there wasn't any pupil
named Little in the roster.
There isn't.
Isn't? Then, this Little you're waiting for...
Who exactly is it?
Ah! There he is! I knew he'd come!
Huh? Where? Where?
That over there is Little.
That... Isn't that a dog?
Little!
You came, after all!
Somehow, I knew you would!
Ah, it tickles! Enough already, Little!
Lucy-May!
Yes?
It's long past our starting time!
You can't be playing with this dog here.
Now get in the class at once!
Okay.
Listen well, Lucy-May.
Next time I find you doing something like this
when you're supposed to be in the classroom...
That dog...
Hey, Lucy, I think this dog
is about to pounce on me...
Little, stop it.
The teacher isn't doing it to bully me.
That mans is Mr. McKenzie.
Don't you forget that, Little.
Seems like he's very susceptible
to what you say.
Yes. Sit, Little.
Listen well, Little. Whenever teacher
scolds me in the classroom,
please don't storm into the classroom to bite teacher.
Bite me?
The teacher doesn't have any reason to bully me.
It's always my own fault
for being so inept at learning.
Do you understand, Little?
Say, it'll be all right, won't it?
He won't try to storm into the classroom or something?
I don't think he'd wanna do that.
I see. Then, get into the classroom already.
But I'm a little worried.
Lately, Little isn't too heedful of what I say.
Huh? What did you say?
I can't stand the dogs!
Go tell him, Lucy-May!
Lucy-May!
Now, how did you get an answer like this?
42 minus 18...
How did you come to 34?
Explain yourself, Lucy-May.
If you can't solve even a problem that simple,
you'll do it over once more!
42 minus 18.
How in the world did it come to be 34?
Lucy-May, are you really a fifth-grader already?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Failing even such an elementary subtraction.
This problem is a third...
No, even a second-grader would crack it!
Hey! Quit looking aside.
And listen well to what teacher says!
No looking aside, I said!
Teacher.
What is it? trying to come up with some excuse?
Look - both Nancy and Dick
can crack the same problem at the count of three!
And both are just seven years old!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself, Lucy-May?
Teacher...
Oh. I see. Ashamed, after all.
Teacher, I need to go pacify Little.
What?
Little is raising a ruckus
by scratching the door from outside.
What ruckus are you talking about?
Teacher! Seems like Lucy's dog
is trying to gnaw away at the school!
Gnaw away at the school?
Hey! Stop it!
Hey! W-what is it??
What do you think you're doing there?
D-Do something about this dog already!
Be quiet, Little!
It just won't stop growling!
That's because Little thinks
you're being too harsh to me, teacher.
That's some rubbish!
He's woefully imperceptive!
T-Tell him firmly to calm down!
Okay.
Little, come here.
Hey, Little, didn't I tell you before?
Teacher isn't bullying me,
only trying to teach.
It's because he can't stand me
being so inept in arithmetic, understand?
We can't have you around
if you're not quiet, Little!
Now, sit here and wait patiently, Little.
Teacher, I explained it to him really well.
So, we can finally get some peace, isn't that right?
Yes.
Ah, teacher, let's continue from where we left off!
Huh? Ah, that's right!
I was livid just a moment ago!
Ah, but what was it about?
About an arithmetic problem.
You were saying I'm hopeless and...
Ah! Right, right.
Now, please rebuke me soundly!
You, erm...
Erm...
Enough already, take your seat, Lucy-May.
I may sit down now?
It's best that you sit down.
My enthusiasm had been hopelessly dampened.
Mom, if we do get to own a farm one of these days,
Lucy also won't be able to go to school, right?
In the farmland, there aren't any schools.
But I'd like you to drop that talk already,
about getting a farm and everything.
Makes sense. Will do.
Do you really think Little went
all the way to the school?
Can't tell for sure from here.
But think of it - bringing a dog to school!
She's getting scolded harshly now, I imagine.
Little just followed after her,
so she can't be blamed for that.
Little sure is one smart fella, isn't he?
I even think, he might actually be
smarter than Lucy!
No way!
Lucy-May!
Stand up!
Okay.
Try to retell us what I just told you.
What's the matter?
I'm merely asking you to retell exactly what I just said.
Teacher said...
Hm?
What you were saying...
Yes?
You said...
What was it?
We get it I was saying something.
What came after?
You said...
Will you ever start telling?
I forgot.
What did you say?
I completely forgot everything you said.
I said it just a moment ago
and you forgot it already?!
Yes.
No! No! No!
You didn't forget!
You were never listening in the first place!
I saw you clearly nodding off!
When you were supposed to listen,
you were looking away!
Um... It's Little again.
Teacher! Lucy's dog is storming the school again!
Ah! I won't tolerate it any longer!
That dog needs to get whipped!
You lousy dog!
Little! Stop it!
I'm not bringing you along to school ever again!
Hey!
Little!
What are you doing, Tob?
Ah! Lucy!
That dog has such a funny face!
This is Mr. Pettywell's dog.
It's called a bulldog.
A bulldog?
A terribly strong dog.
Who do you think is stronger - he or Little?
We can never know for sure.
But I think it'd be interesting to see them fight.
That's awfully foolish of you to say.
Well, let's come home, Little.
You too, Tob! Let's go home!
Tob! Tob!
Ah!
Hey, wanna catch a break?
Sure. I'm thirsty.
What was that sound?
Huh? It's dynamite.
They use it to mine
much smaller stones than this.
The ones used for paving?
Yeah. The ones that the roads are made of.
That sure is one loud way to do it.
They also use gunpowder
because it's much more explosive.
It saves them the trouble of breaking up
large chunks of rock and making them smaller later.
What was that?
They even explode it so close to here?
Yeah.
It's a landslide!
Huh? What?
Hey! Get out of there, everyone!
A landslide is underway!
Run! A landslide is coming! Run! Run away now!
Ah! Run!
Ah, welcome.
That's a real shame, isn't it?
Huh?
They say there's been a landslide
at Mount Lofty today!
A landslide?
An awful lot of dead and wounded there now!
Excuse me, but in what part
of Mount Lofty was it?
Well, dear, at the quarry, of course!
Where the most of folk have been working.
Is that... Is that really so?
You sure you didn't mishear it?
The newspaper worker also confirmed it.
There aren't any exact details known yet,
but it's clear that there's been a major accident.
Ah...
And your father...
What about your father?
I don't know...
We must head out to the quarry right away!
Impossible. They've closed off the road to there.
The place is still in mayhem.
No way...
Now that I think of it, I had this
nasty feeling ever since this morning!
Mom, stay strong!
What's wrong, Clara?
Listen, I need you to go find John
and ask him to come here at once.
Okay.
Hey, what's the matter?
Something happened, Clara?
Hey, mother, what in the world had happened?
By nightfall, we still knew nothing
of dad's whereabouts.
Injured in a landslide, dad returns home.
But when we go to fetch Doctor Deighton,
we find our old house set ablaze.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Showdown".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you