South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 20 - Water in the Well
Hey! Where are you off to, Lucy-May?
Koala!
What?
It's for Koalas! We're going to catch a koala!
Oh? Sounds mighty interesting.
Bring me along, will you?
I was just thinking of taking a stroll or something.
Doctor, you climb trees?
Well when I was a kiddo I didn't do anything much
other than climbing them trees.
Erm... But now, I'm ever so slightly incapable of that.
Then there's no point in you coming with us anyway!
Incapable, you heard?
Climbing trees, huh?
Hm.
Why, it seems, I still can, if I try!
That's it!
Ah!
Doctor, did you drink yourself blind again?
Eh? You think I could pull off
something like that if I were drunk?
Why'd you do something like that
if you're not drunk?
But I can swear I'm not drunk now!
Ah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Ah! That hurt!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. All fine.
You shouldn't be climbing there
after you drink...
I've not drank a drop of it!
It's 'cos Lucy-May shook me off.
Shook you off?
She said I can't tag along with them
if I can't climb trees.
My! Don't tell me those two
left to look for animals again!
Yeah, it was to catch koala, I reckon.
And I was hoping they'd look after Tob for me
while I'm doing the laundry...
Well I could look after him, if you'd like that.
But aren't you busy?
Nah, relax, relax.
As you can see, ain't got crowds of patients now.
If so, I'd like you to do that.
Sure.
Hey, Tob, wanna play with this old bum today? Huh?
Battly!
Battly...
Aight, I'm watching after him, so do your laundry
or whatever it is you want.
Sorry for the trouble.
If you'll manage to catch that,
you're probably a prodigy, Tob!
Battly!
Right.
No!
Almost!
Ah! It's Mr. Parker's oxcart.
You're right. Sir!
Hey, young ladies of the Popple household!
Whoa! Whoa!
You're in a hurry to get somewhere?
We're going to catch a koala.
Oh? Well, I rightly envy you two!
Why so, Mr. Parker?
Unlike us, grown-ups, you kids can afford
just playing around all day, all carefree.
It's not like that! Until just a little while ago,
we also had to help making candles.
Right, Lucy-May?
Yeah!
We're also having to work quite a lot.
Oh? I see, I see.
It's anything but easy!
Yeah...
Back in England, kids just need to go to school
and study to be left alone.
But in Australia, even kids aren't spared
the hardships of life, ain't they?
Well, you can put it this way.
Right, right!
Well, let's be on our way, Lucy-May.
Uh-huh.
Take care, will ya?
And be sure to return home before dark!
Okay!
Move it now!
This time, we couldn't help
feeding Mr. Parker a bit of a line.
We don't really have to work all that much.
We don't experience any hardships either.
Plus, say what you want,
there ain't no schools here.
And that's what we like the most about it!
Sister!
Wasn't it here where we last saw a koala?
It is.
Sitting here, right?
If so, I should be able to catch it!
We get it, alright? You're good at climbing trees now,
is that what you're getting at?
Not a single one here!
And we can't go any deeper into the woods.
Let's try looking there, sis!
No way.
If we don't turn back here,
we'll lose our way for sure!
Come on, just a little more!
We've made it this far already!
To tell you the truth, I might just know...
What is it?
How not to lose our way.
What should we do for it?
If we keep an eye on the position of the sun,
we'll always know which way is which.
And so, we could easily
backtrack to where we came from?
About right.
Let's do that, sis!
Let's see. If I stand like this now,
the sun is to the right from me.
Yeah.
Which means if we keep walking
with sun always to our right,
we'll need but to walk with sun on our left
to return exactly the way we came.
Impressive, sis!
Now, let's go a bit further into the woods, shall we?
There! Can't you see it in the shadow of those leaves?
Where? I don't see anything at all!
Is something wrong with your eyes today?
Look.
From the bottom: one, two, three, four, five, six, seven -
it's where the eighth branch splits.
Eighth branch... That high?
One, two, three, four...
Why, that's just an owl!
It's an owl, no two ways about it!
Ah! You're right. It's just an owl sleeping.
Guess we're out of luck today.
Let's try looking for it some other time.
I thought so, too.
Maybe we'd better resign for now.
Let's return, then.
Oh my!
What's wrong, Kate?
Mr. Sun hid among the clouds.
Eh?
What do we do now, Kate?
Retracing the path we walked just now
shouldn't be that hard.
Good to know.
Let's go back, if so.
We passed through here before, right?
So it seems.
We must've passed through here as well!
Hey, Kate! We passed through here, did we?
Yeah...
What's the matter, Kate?
Let's wait here until Mr. Sun decides to show himself.
We lost the road, didn't we?
Well, there was never
any road in the forest to begin with!
What's with you speaking this way now, sis?
Well maybe it's 'cause I've not a single clue now -
which way should we walk to get home?
It didn't seem to me like we've walked that awfully far.
And that's why we were supposed
to be out of the woods long ago!
That's true.
Let's try walking this way, then.
Why should we walk that way?
I feel that going this way
would be better for us, somehow.
I can say just about the same about this way!
Then, do you suggest we stay here for some while?
Only until Mr. Sun comes out.
But will it ever come out?
The clouds just keep on filling the sky.
But say, those clouds look a bit like a herd of sheep.
Those are the actual sheep!
Ah! You're right, it's the sheep!
But if there are sheep here,
that should mean the grassland is also near!
So the grassland was this way, after all?
Turns out, we were both wrong!
They look mighty nervous, somehow.
The sheep aren't supposed
to be nervous from seeing humans.
But it's beyond doubt they're nervous.
Must be that those sheep
strayed away and got lost.
So it seems.
Say, kids, what's wrong?
I don't think we're anywhere near that scary.
Ah!
What is it?
It's him!
Eh?
You know, when we just came.
When we arrived to Adelaide for the first time,
we were chased by some beast, remember?
The wolf?
Not a wolf, but something similar.
Look, there it is!
I get it now, it's a dingo!
Must be that it's after these sheep!
We gotta save the sheep!
But how?
Don't know yet...
It could as well attack us instead.
Isn't there a stick somewhere?
Even a stone would do!
Ah! It's coming!
See one!
Stop!
Take that! You beast!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Kate! Hurry up!
There! Take this!
Begone!
See this? Come closer and I'll smack you!
Away!
Careful!
Ah!
For how long will we do this?
Until it leaves the sheep alone!
It feels like we'll wear ourselves out
before it ever gives up!
Then let's hold an endurance contest!
That must be the shepherd dogs.
That's it, the dogs are coming!
Better run now, unless you wanna get bitten!
Seems like they're driving the lost sheep
towards the rest of the herd.
That's it. We should also be fine now,
if we follow after them!
Which means we're saved, too!
Good, good, good, good.
He's one particularly intelligent fella.
Thank you, Monocle.
It was really only thanks to you that we were saved.
Consider yourself lucky, Monocle.
You're getting patted on the head by a lady so adorable.
I should say my thanks, too.
Thank you.
Now, you go other there again and keep an eye out.
In case any more sheep lose their way,
I'm counting on you.
That's a truly marvelous dog you got!
Do you like dogs?
Yes. Ah! I never thanked you, sir.
Well I've not done anything here.
Still, it's the second time we meet you thus far.
Now that you mention it, the other time you were also
chased by a dingo, weren't you?
Except that you had one more
beautiful young lady with you.
Sister Clara!
Yeah...
Excuse me, but what would be your name, sir?
Whaddya wanna know that for?
Well, we've been saved by you twice already.
And in both cases I've not been doing much saving.
Just let us know your name, please.
Hmm... My name is Larry Long.
Have you been here for long?
You may call it long, though it's only been two years
since we, the white people, came to live here.
Ah, I see.
I should say, the city construction pace
lags behind thus far.
The land surveying is slugging
and we've neither a church nor a school.
The school can wait, I reckon.
Huh?
Yes! It's best that they leave the school till last, isn't it?
Doesn't seem like you two
are very fond of school, are you?
Is it any different for you, sir?
During my childhood years, the poor
couldn't go to school even if they wanted to.
That includes you, sir?
Yeah, I never went to school.
Thus I don't know how to write or read.
Would be awful pity if you end up like me.
I can write and read already.
I also can read a little!
Good to know that.
It seems, this city has its own newspaper already.
I was hoping you two
would it read it for me sometimes.
Sure, I'll read it for you.
And what about the other one?
I'll read the letters that I can read.
Only the letters you can read?
Lucy-May, you're looking mighty gloomy to me.
Yeah.
We couldn't find it today,
but we'll be sure to find this koala soon enough!
Yeah...
In case mom allows us,
we can go look for it tomorrow as well!
Sister.
What is it?
Do you think they can do it?
Do you think they can't?
What do you mean?
The school.
Eh?
It's about school.
Do you think they can really build it here?
I don't know.
If it gets built, dad and mom would totally
make me go there, won't they?
I suppose so.
And I'd have to go there every day.
Yeah, it's every day.
I'd also have to study, won't I?
Well, it's school, after all.
Both the spinach and carrots are sprouting
that ridiculously soon... What could that mean?
Not only this place has the seasons exactly opposite
to those in Yorkshire where we used to live,
but it's also different in many other aspects.
Until we know exactly what those differences are,
we're always running a risk of ruining our field.
There, look at these radishes.
They're this big already!
They smell great, too!
We'll be feeding on great salads soon.
Ah! I just wish they'd give me the land sooner.
In a country so wide and spacious,
it won't be a problem.
I'm sure you'll be offered
a magnificent piece of land.
It was a sound move from the government
not to sell the land until it's neatly surveyed.
Ugh... Still, it doesn't seem like
the surveying is getting anywhere at all.
Haste makes waste.
Let's just start by rebuilding our lives in this
new country bit by bit, to the best of our abilities.
Right. Bit by bit for now.
Dad!
Mr. Jamling is calling! Come quickly!
Did he hit the water, Ben?
I think so! Hurry up!
Hey, Mr. Popple!
I'd say we did it.
What do you think of this water, Mr. Jamling?
It's good water.
This area seems rich in groundwater.
Oh? Then, how about you climb up already?
Ah? Clara, hold on tight to Tob's hand now.
We don't want him falling into the well.
Okay. The water finally started to accumulate, right?
Thank you, Mr. Jamling.
Though I've only drank a bit,
I noticed the water was cold and tasty.
Right. It's good that we chose this spot, after all.
Quite a lot of water accumulated already.
You'd better wait a bit
until you start drawing the water from there.
The water is beautiful!
I'd love to taste it sooner.
The water is still a little muddy,
so you can't drink it yet.
But in just two or three more days, it'll be alright.
Hm?
What's all the commotion, gentlemen?
Oh, Mr. Parker.
The water started to accumulate in our well.
Oh? That's a great relief.
Because well, there's a place where they can't hit water
no matter how much they dig.
Oh? That must be mighty annoying.
Where is that place?
It's at Mr. Pettywell's plot.
They're digging yet another new hole as we speak.
Alright, cheers.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Ah, I guess, with this, the Popples family can finally consider all the basic life necessities secured.
It's a lot more complicated than that, Mr. Parker.
At any rate, this should help
making the life here a bit more bearable.
Going to the river to fetch water
was becoming quite a feat of heavy labor for us.
This also makes short work of watering the garden.
It's also extremely handy for doing the laundry.
We truly are glad Mr. Jamling
decided to help us out of this plight.
No, I was just doing my job for my hirer,
which is you, Mr. Popple.
By the way, what do you plan to do next?
I was planning to build one more cabin on this very plot.
I think I can handle it on my own, though.
Well, naturally, I'm also counting on Ben to assist me.
A cabin, huh?
We can't have Dr. Deighton
sleep in that tent forever, can we?
Hm?
Oh no, now I'm convinced I'm smelling whiskey.
To the completion of well
and to the well-being of the Popples family,
cheers!
Cheers!
Cheers.
Hold it with those cheers for a bit, men!
Ah?
Oh, Doctor Deighton!
Would you look at that!
Leaving me out when drinking
to the well-being of the Popples is preposterous!
Ma'am, may I have a glass?
Brother, hang on there, will you?
We're almost home!
You go enter the house first, Lucy-May.
Why?
That's one too may "why's" for your size!
Just be silent and enter first.
I don't think we'll get scolded now,
it's not that late yet.
That's all the more reasons you should go first!
That's unusual, a wagon is coming here.
It's Mr. Bernard now, isn't it?
Seems like he brought someone along.
Let's go and see.
If we come any later,
we're definitely getting scolded!
It's alright. Mom's getting mad
all the same if we return now or a little later.
Then I'm coming, too!
Mr. Bernard!
Ah... Kate, Lucy-May, that's a perfect timing.
I need one of you to inform Dr. Deighton,
and the other - to call sister here.
My sister?
Dummy, he means Mrs. Mac.
Then, this man is...
Brother, we've made it home. Brother!
I'll go get Dr. Deighton!
You find Mrs. Mac.
Understood.
Ma'am! Mrs. Mac, ma'am!
Doctor Deighton!
Doctor Deighton?
Well, well, well!
One of the Popple beauties returned.
Doctor Deighton!
What is it?
Doctor, keep yourself together, doctor.
Yeah, I know, I know.
You sure you want it, Doc?
Aye, I don't mind. Drench me to your heart's content,
starting from the head.
Lemme get a little...
Doctor, keep yourself together!
Sure. Now then, now then, what are we waiting for?
Come on, come on.
Alright, douse!
Doctor, I'm doing it!
Yeah, go ahead already!
Whee! Cold!
How do you feel, doctor?
Eh... Yeah, a lot better now. Achoo!
Eh... Do one more!
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's mighty refreshing.
One more bucket of cold water
would wear alcohol out completely!
What's going on, Lucy-May?
Oh?
Say it plainly - what's the matter, Lucy-May?
He passed away!
Passed away?
Mr. Mac passed away just now!
My...
Good heavens!
I'll go see what's what anyway.
Although temporary he regained his strength,
our neighbor Mr. Mac
fell ill the second time during a surveying expedition
to the hinterlands and never made it back.
He was only thirty seven years old.
When we went fishing with brother,
we accidentally spotted a rabbit.
My sister and I will definitely try to catch it!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"The Man Who Designed Adelaide".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you