South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 25 - When I'm Out of Luck...
Here, this problem is for you.
23 minus 17.
Want me to solve something that hard?
What are you saying?
You can subtract 5 from 8, can't you?
5 from 8...
That's easy. It'd be 2, won't it?
Are you kidding me?
Eh?
8, subtract 5 is...
Ah! It's 3!
3!
You're supposed to be doing calculations in silence.
If you can subtract 5 from 8,
you should be able to solve that, too.
Can I, really?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
11, 12...
And this is the problem for Kate.
Divide 125 by 5?
15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
Division is my forte!
20. 20!
Ah...
Kate, I need you to lend me your hand.
Hm?
I need 23 fingers to solve this problem.
Lend me your fingers.
This won't do!
Instead of counting with fingers,
do it in your mind! In the mind.
Easier said than done!
Gosh, you're noisy! Can't you scratch less?
Ah!
Lucy-May! What's with that attitude?
I hate arithmetic!
So what?
Eh?
If you say you hate it,
does that mean you won't do it?
Eh... Um, I mean, yes!
Then, you're fine with growing up
into an adult who can't even do basic reckoning?
Hm...
Come on. Put your mind to it, Lucy-May.
But I really only have 20 fingers.
It's no disaster, Lucy.
Let me teach you just the way to do it:
First, you subtract 17
from your 20 fingers.
Subtract 17 from 20?
Right. And then you just add 3 to that.
Ah! If I do that, my 20 fingers would suffice!
Kate! Enough giving unwanted
instructions to neighbors!
Okay, then, if the total of fingers I have is 20...
Instead, why don't you work on the division
of 125 by 5 which equals 25...
If I subtract 17 from it, it's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
My, you got that right?
Told you, this problem is too much a cakewalk, sis.
6, 7, 8, 9, 10.
My, that's insolent.
In that case, why don't I give you a better problem?
11, 12, 13, 14, 15.
Alright, let's try this one.
16, 17...
2279 divided by 5...
Ah, that's a no-go.
Would you look at that!
It's suddenly too hard?
And now, what remains is... What remains is 1, 2, 3.
I didn't say that.
2279 isn't divisible by 5!
3 fingers, then. 3, that means...
Eh?
Ah, you're so noisy!
To be divisible by 5, the number
needs to end with 5 or 0, doesn't it?
Ah... Yes, that's true...
Eh... And how much was I supposed to add to my 3?
I wonder why did I give you a problem like that.
I guess math isn't your own forte, is it, sis?
How much did she say before?
What are you saying?
Kate, talking back to teacher like that is insolent!
Oh why do I have such loud sisters?!
Ah!
Huh?
Good morning.
Hey, Billy.
Where's Kate?
Studying inside.
Studying?
Gotta be kiddin'!
Yet it's true.
From now on, every Saturday afternoon
they're having classes in the house, and it's set.
Eh? I feel rightly sorry for them.
Why so?
When it's rainin' hard,
classes are more or less tolerable.
But not when the weather's that good.
Eh? So your studying is governed by weather?
Are you sure Kate's gonna study all day long today?
If they do it all day, I bet Lucy would drop dead.
Sure am sorry for those two.
Once I'm done with this work,
I'd probably go help out Kate and Lucy.
What do you say, Billy?
Don't you feel like lending me a bit of a hand
with my work until then?
Sure. Sounds good.
Hanging out with Ben is aight, too.
Is this where you're gonna live?
Both me and Dr. Deighton.
As for the roof, we'll have no choice
but to have your dad make it for us. That's for sure.
Lucy-May, what is this?
How did you come to an answer like this?
Eh?
Well, we subtract 9 from 90, right? So...
Ah! It'd be 81!
Honestly, how can you be that inattentive?
You could've solved it if you really tried!
If you're in a hurry, you can't get anything done.
Can't immerse in anything.
Immerse?
You're busy with doing arithmetic now, right?
At such times, you should focus
all of your attention on arithmetic.
When there are no other things on your mind,
that's called immersion.
Ah... Then it's hopeless for me!
What makes you think so?
Right now, I'm thinking about the goat milk
I'm supposed to give to Little!
Sister.
What?
We've not been studying like this
for a long time, remember?
That's why we've completely forgotten
our scholarly habits.
In particular, Lucy's inability to focus
is probably because of that.
I understand that much...
This time, calm down before starting, Lucy-May.
Okay.
Oh! Look at those two racking their brains
as best they can!
I'm actually done since long ago.
Billy came to see you.
Imagine - he brought his goat along
all the way from home!
Really? Will be there right now!
Me too!
Not you! Not before you solve this problem!
I'll go ahead now, Lucy.
Okay. I'll finish in no time.
Have you finished your work, Ben?
Yeah.
When dad returns, tell him I went fishing.
Okay.
Do your best, Lucy.
Finished!
Eh? Finished so fast?
Yeah.
My!
Lucy-May.
How come 199 minus 109 is 9?
Eh? It's not?
Well, we take 199 and subtract 109, right? Thus...
100 minus 100 is zero.
Then we subtract 9 from 99...
Ah! It's 90!
How inattentive!
Oh?
A pups! Aintcha a cute one?
It's not just a dog, but a dingo.
Eh? Bollocks!
It's a baby dingo.
Say, you're not messing with me, aintcha?
A dingo is supposed to have a habit
of eating sheep and other livestock!
Yeah, that's him.
And his name is Little.
Little?
But you'd better not wake him. There's no telling
which one of you would be more scared.
Eh? So a dingo, huh?
What's more, he turned out to be surprisingly smart!
Right, Little?
Hey! Are you really a dingo?
Ah! He really is! Staring so intently at my goat!
Maybe he just liked it!
He's used to attacking sheep.
So he'd gladly take a bite from a goat, too!
That's not the case.
He only likes goats for playing with them.
Ain't no way...
Lemme show you quickly.
Sure it's aight?
It has to be alright.
Ah! If we also let that goat in,
that'd be like a long-awaited family reunion!
Hm...
Alright.
Those three are almost like siblings-in-law by now!
Eh?
Little had only grown that big
thanks to Sticky's milk.
Oh?
Still, it's almost unbelievable
he'd grow to become a dingo one day.
Alright, here you go.
We're finally home, Tob.
Eh...
Alright! Thanks a lot, you're a saver!
See ya later!
Go!
Seems like Ben had finished working.
But it's a little rough on the edges.
Doesn't look like Ben's work at all.
Hm...
It feels like lately
he's not been very earnest about his work.
Welcome back!
We're back!
Oh my.
What's wrong?
Mrs. Mac finally showed up outside!
Hm?
Isn't she just watering her flowers?
It's good to know she recovered enough
to leave her house again.
Well it's been a month
since her husband passed away...
Yes. But it still pains her a great deal, I imagine.
Hm...
Muster your courage and do another one.
Without that, you won't get any playtime today.
We're home!
Welcome back.
What's the matter, Lucy-May?
I'm trying my best,
but I can't get her to study seriously.
Now that's a problem.
I see Billy came to visit us?
That's why I'm telling her to calm down.
Otherwise, she'll never learn to concentrate.
As soon as she's distracted, she makes a mistake!
Still, I think you should call it a day, Clara.
Kate is already playing outside.
By saying so, you're letting her
abuse your kindness in the future, father!
Listen, Lucy-May. From the next time on,
you'll put every effort into studying, okay?
Uh-huh.
I'm not convinced!
Are you serious about doing it?
Uh-huh!
Good. Go play outside, then.
Okay!
Oh, father, you're hopeless!
If she was slacking off up until now,
only radical measures would've worked!
Hm.
By the way, where exactly did Ben go?
Bleh!
You look properly squeezed up.
Completely!
Billy! G'day!
Aye. Good job, I guess.
Took your sweet time!
That's 'cause I solved ten more problems since then!
Naturally enough, all of them perfectly!
By the time dad returned there,
I was already allowed to go play around.
Though I would gladly keep cracking them.
Liar.
Now that's mighty odd of our fella Ben.
He goes fishing, but brings along a book!
That book is a Latin grammar textbook.
Eh?
Does he hope to increase his fishing luck
through reading that book?
Of course not!
Our brother is one peculiar fella in general!
He said he likes to study, can you imagine that?
Yeah, you're right.
Hey! Where would we go to play now?
What should we play?
Have you decided already?
Aah!
Ah!
I'm alive...
Are you alright, Lucy?
I'm fine...
Suddenly, you've become so heavy, Little!
If I leave my goat in here,
it'll be alright, wouldn't it, Lucy?
It's alright!
Seems like they still remember they're a family!
Good afternoon, Mrs. Mac.
Good afternoon!
Good afternoon.
Been a while since I last visited you.
Ah! And that must be the baby dingo, isn't it?
Yes. Did Mr. Bernard tell you?
Yes, that's right.
Hey, Lucy-May.
It may be docile for now, but even a baby dingo
is still a dingo, you know.
You must keep a close eye on him at all times.
Okay.
Um...
Ma'am, that parcel smells awfully good!
Ah, just some buns.
I've not baked any in ages.
Make sure to try it later.
Okay!
There, Little.
Set out!
Right! Faster now! Faster, faster!
If we catch a wild hare today, what'll you do?
Keep it, of course! No two ways about it!
My! Wait for me!
At first, I was also considering returning to England.
But even if I'd have returned,
I no longer had any close relatives there.
And since even my brother moved here,
I made up my mind on staying.
I see. So you god dragged to here after Mr. Bernard,
your reliable little brother?
I'm not so sure about the reliable part.
Henceforth and forever, please feel free to tell us
whenever there's anything we could help you with.
Okay...
About that... Actually, I came here to ask for a favor.
What is it, ma'am?
It's about Ms. Clara.
How can Clara help you?
I have long planned
to start a business, you see. And for that...
I was hoping Ms. Clara would be so kind
as to assist me with it.
What kind of business?
A bakery. If there's something
I know how to do, it's baking.
My brother had also approved the idea.
He was all for it.
My!
Ah...
I'm sure it'll delight everyone greatly
if you become a professional bread-maker.
Clara, what do you think?
Ma'am, I would be happy to help
in any way I can with your shop!
Ah, I'm so glad.
With that settled, I will start
looking for a shop as soon as tomorrow.
This place is where Colonel Light ran into me.
Did Colonel say that the local scenery
reminds him of that in the English village
of Theberton, where he lived as a child?
Yes.
Colonel's health has deteriorated in recent years.
Now that you mention it,
he was coughing quite a lot while we spoke.
His chest is giving him trouble, it seems.
But because he's the most important man around,
when Surveyor-General's health is failing,
nobody can get anything done.
Because of that, my father also
still can't get the land promised to him.
Hearing that is what actually stings me the most.
Everyone rushed to this country,
allured by its spacious lands.
But in fact, we're now sitting on the piles of land
yet to be surveyed, that we can't sell.
The folk that come here in droves
all find themselves in the same situation as your dad.
That's just too unfair.
I understand. And still, as you said,
nobody can get anything done.
Surveying the wilderness is no cakewalk, Ben.
Thought so.
I'm also considering resigning from office work,
so that I could go conduct actual surveying on-site.
But if you'll be constantly away on expeditions,
wouldn't your sister get lonely?
Leave my sister to me, I'll think of something.
After all, she's got grit in her.
By the way, I've been wondering
about that thing for a while...
Oh, you mean this?
It's a textbook on Latin grammar.
Hmm?
Hm?
Troi... Toroi...
I forgot it all!
I haven't had a single chance to use Latin
ever since I graduated.
Every night, Dr. Deighton
teaches me some of it, one bit at a time.
Eh?
Sure you can rely on that wacky doctor?
I wonder if he even knows what he is teaching you.
Are you saying you don't trust him?
Exactly! You should know that doctor
is a terrible alcoholic.
I'd rather not trust him much with anything.
Latin included. Hm!
But I have no one else to go to.
Say, Mr. Bernard, perhaps, if you know Latin...
Eh?
It's hopeless. Hopeless! Totally hopeless.
Well, goodbye for now.
Oh? This looks a lot
like a heavy rain about to start, Ben.
Ah! Found it, found it!
It's here! Here, Billy!
Ah! It went that way! Catch it now, Billy!
Kate, it's over there!
Ah! Don't get in the way, Little!
Ah... That bunch sure can afford being carefree.
Come on! Almost there!
Just a little more!
Stop, you!
Come on! It's right there! Right there, dammit!
You can do it, Billy!
Got you!
Ah! Why couldn't you do just a bit more?!
Such a shame, you were really close this time.
This doesn't look like it'll stop soon...
Can't be helped. Let's return.
Ah!
Look over there!
Ah! The rabbit from earlier.
It's taking shelter under the tree.
Geez, that's just so provocative!
Wait!
That's our brother right there!
Everyone stay low, will you?
While Ben is so absentminded,
I'll go scare him to death!
Ah! The book!
A success! You should've seen your face, brother!
Idiot!
Ah!
I dropped my Latin grammar textbook in the river!
What am I to do now?!
Forgive me, brother!
Bother, please
I'm sorry, brother!
Brother, I'm so sorry!
How is Lucy-May?
Keeps crying and says she won't eat.
Hm... So be it.
Kate, take your seat.
Okay.
Tell me, Ben.
Aren't you going to forgive Lucy?
I'm not.
But you know, Lucy never wanted
for the book to fall in the river when doing that.
Besides, Ben.
I couldn't help noticing that you work
somewhat half-heartedly these days.
As shown by the brickwork as well.
That grammar textbook...
Is that something you really need that badly?
Enough to say that you'll need Latin to be a farmer?
That was a very important book,
that village pastor Kramer gave me, instructing me to study it when I get to Australia.
I know that.
But let me put this straight for you -
you don't need that book right now.
Just focusing on the work
directly before us is more than enough.
That's how I see it.
Ben!
I'm not eating!
Come to think of it, I'll probably have a chance
to buy a new book later, Little.
Where are you going, Lucy-May?
Will try apologizing once again!
He may be right that I don't really
need that book right now.
But it'll become of the essence in the future!
Right, Little?
It seems, Little is feeling completely neglected, Lucy.
Brother, I'm sorry.
Hm.
I really, really never wanted you
to drop that book when doing it.
Hm.
Will you forgive me, brother?
Lucy, how about we go have our supper?
Uh.
That day, Lucy was well and truly out of luck.
Ah!
What's the matter, Lucy?
No... It's nothing. I'm f—Ouch!
There are days like that, too.
But the incident with brother's Latin grammar textbook turned out to be a particularly nasty one.
During the night, I suddenly develop a fever.
In more pain than I can take, I keep muttering through delirium, "I'm sorry" and "Forgive me".
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"I Fell Ill!"
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you