South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 31 - Little and the Black Dog
Even when you grow big,
you wouldn't be producing any milk, right?
But they say, your meat will sure be delicious.
Ah!
It's best that we don't tell Lucy-May for now.
Kate! Try to pull with a bit more strength.
I feel bad for Little!
You shouldn't underestimate Little's strength.
Little, keep it up!
We're almost home, boy.
We let that sheep out of the enclosure when leaving.
You don't suppose it strayed away?
Unlike goats, the sheep don't like to roam about.
Besides, we asked Clara to look after it, didn't we?
Ah? What's wrong, Little?
Look! Snowflake wandered away from our house!
So that's why Little is barking?
I'm unharnessing Little now, you don't mind?
Not at all. Thank you, Little.
Hey, Little. Someone needs to go herd Snowflake
back home. You can do that, right?
My, what a surprise! Look!
He really is herding the sheep here.
Little must be doing it
after Mr. Long's shepherd dogs.
Ah, good job.
You gathered quite a lot of it today.
That's 'cause Little helped us pull!
Oh? That's good, good.
Ah! I think Little bit the sheep by the butt!
Not at all! He's simply pushing Snowflake
from behind to herd her home.
Eh?
My, that's pretty impressive!
Lucy-May, you did a really good job training it.
I'd never be able to achieve that
with my training alone.
It's all down to Little being born very smart.
It makes me wonder if Little
was really born to a dingo, even.
No. It's apparent he was a dingo pup.
Just that it was an extremely smart one.
Do you think so?
It's easy to ascertain
if you just look Little in the mouth.
He's got some knife-sharp fangs in there.
Those are a wild animal's fangs.
You're right, those fangs are scary.
Yet he hadn't bitten
a human or a livestock not once yet.
I'd sure like to hope it remains so forever.
Whoa!
Dad!
Welcome back!
Yes, yes.
Say, dad, isn't this a Mr. Parker's ox?
Oh my, you could tell it so soon?
That's 'cause I made sure to remember
the looks of this ox's face.
You can even tell away the faces of oxen and cows?
What did you need to borrow the ox for, honey?
Well, I was actually thinking
of taking everyone to look at our new farm.
Eh?!
Our farm?
No, we've not signed the official contract yet.
We'll just look at what is likely
to become our farm soon.
But that place is a bit too far for walking.
Wow!
Is that true, dad? Is that true
you managed to acquire a land, at last?
Of course.
And it's a spacious place, isn't it, dad?
You'll know as soon as you see it.
Well, get ready to set out, everyone.
Okay!
Father, where is Ben working now?
A bit further down the road, on a wheat farm ran by Mr. Jung.
He's probably helping harvest it.
So it's time to harvest the wheat already?
No big wheat fields around here yet,
but those that already exist yield really well.
South Australia must be really good for growing wheat.
Yes. When we start cultivating our land,
we'll also focus on wheat at first.
Will we also keep some sheep there?
I guess so. Sooner or later,
we'll also start breeding cows or sheep.
Then, my Snowflake would become
the pioneer sheep of the Popples' farm!
Hey, dad! That sheep and Little
are getting along mighty well. Right, mom?
Yes. I even witnessed a peculiar scene of it looking after the sheep, almost as if he was a shepherd dog.
Then, it was a good thing
we decided to keep Little, after all?
He'll be looking after our sheep and goats.
And that was why I said
we should bring Little along to show him our farm.
Right, Little?
Hey!
Ah. It's Ben. So this is where he works?
We're going out to see our farm!
Okay!
We're going now!
Next year, do you think Ben will already be
harvesting our own wheat, father?
Yes. I'm sure he will.
Alley-hop!
Thank you, girls.
Sure!
Is it still much farther?
Just a little more. Right after this hilltop,
there's a wide plain. That's where it is.
The farm we'll buy from Mr. Wilson.
Mr. Wilson is having to return to England,
isn't that what you said, dad?
There must be some very serious reason for that.
After all, when you have a land that good,
the farm should also perform really well on it.
Okay! We're here.
Wow! Where? Where is it, dad?
Dad! Where?
Where is it?
Try to look downhill from here.
Look really well.
Wow! It's so big! So big!
Hey, dad! Does Mr. Wilson's farm encompass everything you can see from here? Like, everything at all?
No, no.
Let me explain. There. Look over there.
Do you see that short wooden bridge?
Yeah.
It's limited by that bridge and road on one side,
and then, it follows that creek all the way.
And now, look to your left, please.
Can you see the bridge where this road
we're standing on crosses the creek?
Yes.
That's where Mr. Wilson's farmland ends.
Incredible!
What we got here amounts to 20 acres at least.
20 acres?
It's at least five more
than what our farm in England used to have.
Five more?Impressive!
Is that house also Mr. Wilson's?
Yes, that's right.
Speaking of which, how about we make a round
of the field and stop by on our way back?
I'd rather not.
Why so?
I have no idea what circumstances
forced Mr. Wilson to sell the field.
But I know for sure he didn't have a choice.
But look! It had already yielded
such a splendid wheat!
That's right. I'm sure he didn't really want to sell it.
Isn't that right, honey?
Hm. One wouldn't be likely to part
with this much farmland of his own volition.
That's why I said it's best we don't let him see
how happy we are about it.
Besides, as you said, the official contract
is yet to be concluded.
We've concluded the talks,
which is almost the same.
Except that Mr. Wilson asked me
to wait until the wheat is reaped.
At any rate, for today, we should be contented
with just looking at it from here.
Really, it's a wonderful land. One can't help questioning
if such a wonderful land can really become ours.
Somehow... Somehow, it's almost unbelievable.
Our dream start bearing fruits.
That's exactly what we came to Australia for.
Right, dear?
We can keep a whole lot of sheep
on a piece of land such as this.
How do you think it'll play out
if we let Little look after them?
Knowing Little, they'll have nothing to fear.
But should a dingo come to eat them,
what will Little do?
He'll fight the dingo, of course!
You don't suppose he'll run off?
The sheep are placid, so he can handle herding them,
but if you want him to fight instead, that's a no-go!
He won't run off!
And I think he will,
considering what a scaredy-cat he is!
Don't you mistake Little's
peacefulness for cowardice!
You don't really have to get so worked up.
Little's faint-heartedness
is what keeps him out of trouble.
He's not faint-hearted, you hear?!
What did you say? I think I made it clear
that carriage was reserved for my exclusive use!
But madam insisted
that she absolutely needed to take a carriage.
What can't you understand when I say
I should be the only one using that carriage?!
But madam just wouldn't listen to anything I say!
I even implored her
to ask expressly for your permission!
The only one who really
needs that carriage is me! Me!
But when I said madam ought to ask expressly...
Damn it!
At least tell me when she said she'll return!
Well, she never...
Ah! Damn it!
Ah! Why, you... Out of my way, you idiot!
Why are you giving me that look?!
Dunno why I care, but you've been eating quite well
since I started watching.
Let's see, what was your name again...?
It's no good. I forget things way too quickly.
Was it Rain... No, not rain. Sno...
Right, right! Snowflake!
Yes! I finally remembered!
I've got some patients.
Stay put, will you?
Here, come in.
Good, good, good.
Hmph!
It's awfully fun watching you two.
Blame it on Lucy's stubbornness!
I was expecting you to be the one
more mature in your act.
Hmph!
What's the matter, Little?
Don't run ahead!
We're coming home together, Little.
Dad, stop for a moment!
We're close to home already,
so I'll walk with Little!
I'm getting off too, dad!
Hold it, hold!
Be careful when getting off, you two.
Okay. We'll be fine! Fine!
Ah! Little, wait!
We wanted to come home together!
What could have happened?
Listen. You need to stay home and sleep well
until those pimples on your face are gone.
Okay.
Farewell and take care!
Ah!
Why, you... Hey! What are you doing?!
Get lost from here! Ah!
Hey! Let go! Hey! You idiot! Come on!
Let go I said!
Didn't you hear me? Come on!
What are you doing, you wretch?!
Hey! Get this!
Come on! Get this, this, this!
Get this!
Ah! Away, away, away! Bad! Bad!
Hey, somebody!
Ouch!
Let go! Hey! Let go!
What the...
H-Hey! Stop right there, black dog!
What are you doing?
Ah! It's blood!
Ah!
Little! Little, that's enough!
Can let him go now! Hey, Little! Let him go!
Sister, look!
Looks like it fought someone.
Must've been Little.
I see. That means Little won!
Doctor, what did Little do?
Ah, welcome back, you two.
Is Little all right?
It's nothing. Just got bitten in the leg.
Pettywell's dog had it much worse.
Little is a burly fella!
But why did Little get in a fight with the black dog?
Ah!
Doctor! You're bleeding!
Oh, Happy? I got a little mad earlier.
Sorry I had to kick you away.
It was still mostly your fault, though.
You caught me in bad mood,
at such times you'd better stay away.
Right, don't you agree?
Ah? Hey, Happy, what's the matter?
Ah! Happy! Hey!
Hey! Happy! Hey!
You've a terrible injury!
Who could've done this to you?
Oh, I see...
I get it. It was that dingo living at Popple's place!
Lucy-May, I'm going to ask once more.
Little didn't attack Mr. Pettywell's dog
without reason, did he?
The reason was plain and obvious!
Just ask Dr. Deighton!
The black dog also attacked Doctor
and he's a nasty wound on his leg!
Right, sis?
Dr. Deighton can tell you exactly what happened, dad.
Where is Doctor now?
Treating his wound.
I don't need to ask Doctor anything.
I choose to believe you two for this.
Interesting. Turns out, Little
is actually quite a strong fella.
He took it so hard on Mr. Pettywell's dog,
it walked away hobbling!
That there is a dingo.
I'll do you a favor and shoot it down, Mr. Popple.
Wait a moment, Mr. Pettywell.
Come on, move aside now!
Sir, you can't do that!
Everyone away, I said!
Stop!
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
Let me explain now.
Little can by no means be considered guilty here!
Look at this!
My dog was bitten to death by that dingo!
Little, sit! Sit, Little!
Ah, it's dead.
Now, give me back my gun!
I'm not leaving that thing alive today!
Dr. Deighton saw with his own eyes
how exactly the things developed.
Of us here, nobody else saw it.
Mr. Pettywell, we would first
need to hear Doctor's version.
You're not fooling me with such excuses!
Right now, Doctor is treating the wound
inflicted by your black dog's bite, therefore...
Ah!
There he is. Look.
Mr. Pettywell! That black dog you got
is a devil of a dog!
First, it gnawed at Mr. Popple's sheep,
but then it bit me as well!
If Little hadn't come,
by now, I'd probably already...
Ah? So it died, after all?
Having heard Dr. Deighton's version, Mr. Pettywell
no longer had any grounds for killing Little.
If anything, everything that happened
was Happy's fault.
I'll remember you.
And one day, I'll be sure to repay that!
And then, that's exactly what happens.
As another tragedy
befalls our whole family shortly after.
In order to spite us, Mr. Pettywell
buys the land away from under our nose.
But just as everyone feels utterly dejected,
John finally arrives!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"At the Foot of the Rainbow Bridge."
Please look forward to it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you