South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 42 - A Child Called Emily
We concluded that Lucy
might have gone to see Dr. Deighton.
Dad and I went to the city of Gawler to look for Lucy.
But she wasn't there either.
Just where might Lucy be now?
It could be that she returned home by now.
That's what I hope for.
Father.
What is it?
You also think Lucy didn't really return?
Well... yes.
Lucy cannot spend more than one night
running away from home.
I'm sure she'll return.
Yes.
One way or another, we need to get home soon.
Ah! No! You'll fall out if you twitch.
Relax, Little. Everything is fine.
The carriage can only go a little faster.
Oh my, there's a carriage.
Hey, Silver, you're too noisy!
Ugh, and it's Mr. Pettywell's carriage!
Little, calm down.
Hey, Popple!
Good evening, Mr. Pettywell.
Been to the Gawler, didn't you?
That's right.
That means you also went there
to look at Princeton's farm, didn't you?
What do you mean?
No need to deny it. Princeton's farm
is one spectacular farm.
What is this Princeton's farm you're talking about?
You shouldn't be feigning ignorance.
Too bad for you, though.
I'm going to buy that farm.
It's the best farm in all of Southern Australia.
Now, make haste, Ferguson!
Father.
Don't you think Mr. Pettywell got some wrong idea about us?
Yes. It seems, he thinks we went there
to look at a certain farm for sell.
The Princeton's farm?
Princeton's farm, huh?
For the moment, I'm in no position
to be buying any farm regardless.
Emily?
Emily!
Emily! Emily!
Ah, so you were here, Emily?
I'm sorry. You've been calling out to me for a while, weren't you?
It's fine. You're still to grow accustomed
to being called Emily.
I'm sorry.
Any other name would do too.
Do you have a name you like the most?
Well, in that case,
let's settle on Emily.
Okay.
Wasn't there a parrot perching on your hand just now?
Yes. It's over there.
That bird must be very sociable
to be sitting on your hands.
I called it and it came.
Huh? That's incredible.
I managed to understand a little more about myself.
You remembered something?
About your home? About your parents?
No, I realized something about myself.
It's that I love the animals very much!
Ah, I see. That's why the bird...
I can't believe what a good girl you are, Emily!
You smell very nice.
Really?
When you do this,
I feel like it's my mother embracing me.
Emily.
Huh?
Try calling me mother.
Oh, that is, of course,
until you regain your own memory.
Please, try to call me that.
Mother...
Emily!
Mother.
Emily...
Emily. Emily...
Sir, you have a visitor.
At this hour?
It's almost dinner time.
They said they absolutely need to see you by today...
Who is it?
Mr. Pettywell.
Ah, that man, then?
Will you meet him?
Can't be helped.
Even if I turn him down,
he's not the kind of man who'd just meekly go away.
Take him to the reading room, please.
Okay.
Listen, dear!
Just now, Emily called me mother.
Hey-hey, but she's just...
While she stays here, I asked her to call me mother.
Right. But still, dear...
You have a visitor?
Yes.
Listen, dear, I still think it's a bad idea.
Why?
Can't you see why?
Later... We'll talk it through later.
Now, Emily.
Wait for me in your room upstairs, will you?
Okay.
Mr. Pettywell is here.
Good evening. We've not met
in a long while. Are you well?
Thank you, I'm doing well.
But what is your business here?
May I sit?
Yes, go ahead.
That's pretty impressive, isn't it?
Huh?
This library. I'm sure you're the most avid book collector in all of Southern Australia.
I don't think so.
Now, would you tell me what is your business here?
As a matter of fact, I went to look at your farm today
and found it extremely to my liking, Mr. Princeton.
Which farm do you refer to?
You see, I have farms scattered all across the region.
The one near the city of Gawler.
Oh? That is one remarkable farm indeed.
How does 500 pound sound?
Excuse me?
Then...
1,000 pounds?
Forgive me, but I don't understand what you're saying.
Then, 1,500 pounds!
Let's stop it now.
When did I ever say that I'm selling that farm?
Huh? You're not selling it?
I definitely have no such intention.
I know it's not true.
I know Popple went to look at it before me.
Right? You promised to sell it to Popple, didn't you?
Popple?
Who is that man?
Please don't feign ignorance.
I'm absolutely serious.
I don't know a man by the name of Popple.
Emily? Emily. My name is Emily.
And my mother's name is Sylvia.
No, that's not right.
I... Who am I, really?
Hey, tell me, who am I really, Prospero?
Please tell me.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've been thinking about it, and I can't help feeling
that Lucy didn't really run away from home.
Then, why won't she return?
There must be something else,
preventing her from returning.
What could it be?
That I don't know.
I'm sure that although she wants to return,
there must be something standing in the way.
Do you suppose she's been kidnapped?
Kidnapped? No way...
I also don't think it's so,
but what if someone did kidnap her for some reason?
Then, wouldn't it be better to seek help from police?
Yes. We should at least let them know.
If we ask the police to look for her,
I'm sure they'll find her in no time!
Little miss!
Your dinner is ready!
Okay.
Please keep in mind that I won't give up.
No. Let me put it in no uncertain terms for you:
I am firmly unwilling to part with that farm.
What's wrong? After me, boy!
Come one, hurry! We need to hurry.
Do you have something
against the stairs, Prospero? Come!
Huh?
Come on, hurry.
This way, Mr. Pettywell.
Huh? Y-Yes...
Come, don't be shy now.
You can sit here, Emily.
Okay.
Did you like that bedroom?
Yes.
If there's something you don't like,
just tell Carol and she'll take it away.
Okay. But I really like everything the way it is now.
Hey, Emily.
Yes?
Could you call me that once again?
Huh?
Call me mother.
It's fine even if you only whisper it.
Mother.
Good heavens, what a nasty man!
Let's eat.
A nasty man, I'm telling you!
Your recent visitor?
Yes. That man by the name of Pettywell.
So? Do you like it?
Yes. I like it very much.
Isn't it a pleasant happening, Sylvia?
Eating dinner with a child.
Indeed it is.
However, we can't just let her
stay in our house indefinitely.
You do understand, don't you, Sylvia?
Somehow, I feel like I'm full already.
Oh? But you've barely eaten anything.
I have no appetite either.
Is my cooking that bad today?
It's not that. It's as delicious as any other day.
Everyone is too worried about Lucy
to be in the mood for eating, right?
Indeed, seems like it.
Why won't Lucy return home?
We'd like to know that too, Tob.
What I'm about to say
will probably only aggravate everyone's worry.
It's possible that Lucy's absence is not due to her own volition,
but rather, she can't return due to an external factor.
She'll come back for sure!
O-Of course, I also think she will.
She returned, didn't she?
Huh?
I knew it! She returned!
I'm back.
Ah, that's a fortunate time I returned at.
Ah, I'm starving.
Mom, I hope there's some left for me.
I'm as hungry as a wolf.
What's wrong?
Nobody even said "welcome back."
Ah, welcome back.
Ben, I've finished already,
so you can sit here.
Okay. Thanks.
I thought I won't get to go home this week,
but as luck would have it, I got a day off.
I see. Glad to hear that.
Thanks for the meal.
What's wrong? Everyone is kinda strange.
Well, actually...
Huh? Lucy isn't here. Did she fall ill?
Why do you have to read so many books?
I'm reading them because I like to.
The books?
That's right.
I even went to all the trouble
of delivering them here from England.
England?
You don't remember anything about England?
Nothing.
Have you ever seen this before?
I feel like it's the first time I'm seeing it.
It's called a globe.
A globe?
Yes.
Well, please sit here for now.
Listen, you must remember well
what I'm about to tell you.
Look, this here is Australia.
It's been four years since we, the white people,
have come to live here.
The people living here now, for the most part,
came here on ships from England
and other various countries of Europe.
This is England, this is Germany.
This is France.
France?
Right. Did that ring any bell for you?
Could it be that you used to be French?
I don't really understand.
You had to endure a long ship voyage to get here.
Please try to think of and recall the sea and the ship.
This is a very curious condition indeed.
This, what the call amnesia.
Some tea for the two of you.
It's no use. She can't remember a thing.
Dear, listen, you don't have to rush things so much.
I'm doing this with her parents' feelings in mind.
It could be that Emily lost her memory a long time ago.
And also that her parents abandoned her...
Sylvia!
Hey, Emily, try to remember.
Maybe you still have some memories
from a long time ago?
I don't think so.
She's such an adorable child.
I'm sure her parents are searching for her far and wide.
Hey, Little.
We're going to the police station now.
You don't have to come with us, Little.
Little is one truly intelligent fella.
Hello? Uh... I beg your pardon.
Huh?
I want to report a missing child.
We'd like to ask the police for help with the search.
I almost feel like a kind of queen!
I'm seriously worried now.
Is it about that girl?
No.
It's about you.
This is unsettling. Our own daughter Emily
died when she was two years old.
Nevertheless, you call that girl Emily.
How is that a bad thing?
That girl isn't Emily.
You could choose any other name!
But it's only until she remembers her real name.
Why did you make her call you mother, then?!
I'm well aware of how much you're yearning to have a child.
But that girl isn't Emily who is dead.
But she is oh-so adorable!
It's true, she's adorable.
But she's still someone else's child, not ours.
Tell me, dear. If... If it so happens that Emily
never recovers her memory.,,
Look... Look, you're already considering
that kind of prospect!
Listen. She will recover her memory.
If you intend to become a real mother one day,
you're dealing yourself a heavy blow
by what you're doing now.
You wouldn't believe how much
I'm worried about you.
Oh!
Oh, Emily.
Mother.
Emily! Emily...
The police are short on staff,
so they can't afford arranging a search party
for those who run away from home.
But how do they know
she'd not been abducted by a criminal?
If that had been so,
we'd have received a ransom demand already.
Naturally, in that case,
the police would get on it at once, they said.
Dad, we just have to keep looking for her on our own.
With John's help,
we'll start the search in earnest tomorrow.
Yes. That's the only thing we can do.
Also, we'll take Little along.
Good. We'll do just that.
Little? Little!
Mom! Mom!
Little is gone!
When we woke up in the morning,
Little was already gone.
Am I Emily?
In order to find my family,
Uncle Frank put out a notice in the local newspaper.
Next on Lucy May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Passed By".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you