South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 19 - Today is the Shopping Day
Sis!
Sis, what are you doing?
Whatever it is, do it quicker, sis!
Quicker, quicker!
I jotted down everything we need there.
I see. But if the prices turn out to be
way above the expectations, what do I do?
We'll be in trouble, then.
But even if it's expensive,
we can't do without buying those.
Those are all the absolute necessities.
Sis! What's all that dawdling around?
Would you look at how happy those two are
to finally go shopping again.
They got so excited just from learning
about the town's market district.
You call it market district,
but really it's just three shops.
Well, hurry up now.
Getting to Carrington Street takes quite a while.
If you do it at leisure,
you'll only be back in the evening.
I have those two to rely on.
I hope we'll still be able to walk fast,
even with our bags full.
Come on, make haste, sis!
Ah! Wait! Wait! Why the rush?
What more reason you need
other than going shopping sooner?
Listen now. I understand you may be a little excited
about this, but it's not a reason to lose head.
We won't.
And you need to listen carefully to what I say.
We will.
Good. With that, we can go now.
Miss Clara.
Will you do me a favor?
Sure.
See you later, Doctor.
'Aight. Have a nice walk!
We're off!
We're off.
Right, nice walk to everyone!
Hmm?
Oh, ladies!
Excuse me.
I've been told a Doctor lives
somewhere here. Know anything?
Doctor Deighton can see you
in the tent over there.
In that tent, then?
Well, that's a godsend
Thanks!
Well, let's go now.
Okay.
Say, sis.
The bottle doctor just gave you - what's it for?
Alcohol for disinfection.
I knew it!
Doctor then waters it down in order to drink it
instead of normal booze.
You shouldn't be saying such nonsense, Kate.
But I saw it with my own eyes.
Then just politely forget about it.
Huh?
Mr. Pettywell is able to walk again.
Sir, we're approaching the stairs.
Shut it! I can see that much myself!
Thanks to Dr. Deighton, his waist healed.
He may be a drunkard,
but he's also an excellent doctor.
That may be so, but...
Yes, careful, careful.
Shut it! Idiots must keep silent!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Huh?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Oh! Sir!
What in the world had happened?
Come on, hold on to me! Here!
And... up!
Shut up already! So much ado over nothing!
A fine house, however you look at it.
Our own house stands in no comparison to this!
Hard to believe we could really live in it ourselves.
Didn't I tell you before not to bring it up anymore?
Then, why don't you quit stopping in front of it
to say wistfully "a fine house," whenever we pass by?
Ah? That was pretty brash of you,
you know that?
In fact, I know exactly why dad decided to sell this prefabricated home and buy our current house instead.
Oh? Why was it, then?
I won't tell you because you'll get mad again.
I'm sure I won't get mad.
I can hardly believe it.
Hey, I promise I won't get mad, so speak up!
Thing is...
Yes?
On the second thought, I should stop!
Lucy-May! Hurry up after us!
Okay!
Oh, I'm so sorry, Marsh.
Are you okay, Lucy-May?
Yeah.
That was dangerous.
The roads here haven't been paved yet.
Calling this a road is an overstatement.
Even though they named it already.
In Adelaide, they give everything a name
before anything else.
For instance, they've settled on naming the town Adelaide before they even decided where to build it.
Let's go, now.
I won't be looking to the sides anymore, so don't worry.
Return safely to your afternoon nap.
And what's the name of this one street?
Waymouth Street.
Oh? You know already?
It must be that you've been coming here
to play in secret from me.
I know even without ever coming here.
The street next to Currie Street
is Waymouth Street.
Oh? Not bad at all, Kate.
By the way, about what you said before...
Promise you won't get mad?
Of course!
So why did dad decide to buy that house?
I secretly eavesdropped
on dad's conversation with Mr. Parker.
By Jove, seeing and hearing things in secret
is probably what you do best.
If you say so, I probably shouldn't tell you.
Ah... I won't say a word more.
So come on and tell me now.
Well, Kate?
That's cause our new house was awfully cheap!
That's all? I could tell you that much myself.
But do you know its cost exactly?
Well, of course I can't know that.
It was a measly five pounds!
Five pounds?
And how much do you think
Mr. Pettywell paid for the prefabricated home?
Well, I know we bought it
for 30 pounds back in England.
And here, he sold it for 110 pounds!
110 pounds?
And know what? Mr. Parker
also lined his pockets on that...
Kate.
Eh? What is it?
That's enough. You're being way too nosy
in the grown-ups' affairs.
But just cause I heard it
doesn't mean I wanted to hear it.
I was just taking a nap there...
Then be so kind as to forget that, too.
Children should stick to things befitting children.
I wonder if it would've been better if you were more
like Lucy-May, only going nuts over animals.
Oh? But I'm also concerned with a whole lot of things.
The population increased sharply,
which means various goods became sparse.
Prices also went considerably up!
Yes, that's true.
You even know that much?
My, that's a surprise.
I learned that from the conversation I overheard
between mom and Mrs. Mac.
Ah. So that's where it came from.
But sis.
It's thanks to my fascination with animals
that you get to drink goat milk daily.
You remember that?
That was my point as well.
Ah! Oh no.
What's wrong, Lucy-May?
I was going to give Billy
one of Sticky's babies today.
Ah, is that it?
Billy would probably come for it.
This is bad. I completely forgot!
If we're quick enough to be done with shopping,
we'll be home before dusk.
Let's go now.
I really don't wanna break my own promise...
Doctor, thank you for everything.
And take a break from work for two or three days.
As you can see, my other hand is still alright,
so I can use the saw just fine.
It's your head that I'm most concerned about.
Listen, just stay put for two or tree days, will ya?
If you say so, Doctor...
Morning, doc!
Oh? But Kate and Lucy, while clinging to Clara,
went shopping already.
Just now?
Uh... A little while ago.
Oh?
Ah... I wonder which of the babies
will Lucy-May let me have.
Hey, Billy. You need something here?
Uh-uh. I came here
because of my promise with Lucy-May.
You couldn't find her anywhere?
I was told she went shopping.
Hm?
Hey, Ben, isn't there anything I could help with?
I'd feel bad if I asked you...
I ain't got anything better to do while waiting.
Just say how I could help!
Right? You don't mind, do you, dad?
So you're saying you wanna work, too?
Ben, let him change places with you for a bit.
Okay. Though I still feel bad.
Nothing to feel bad about!
There'll come a day when Billy
would also have to quit playing games.
If his first desire to work had finally hatched,
we let him work.
Listen, we load this dirt onto a sled,
so as to carry it all to the pit over there.
Got it!
You're about the same age
as our Kate, aren't you, Billy?
Yeah.
And Kate had only mastered the art of chatter,
without ever being of any use to us.
This here must be the King William Street, I'm sure.
Yes, correct.
We made it to Adelaide's central street.
Isn't it Mr. Bernard?
My, you're right!
Hey!
Where could you three be heading to?
We're going shopping.
If so, good luck with that.
Mr. Bernard.
Yes?
Is it okay for you to be taking a stroll
during your working hours?
Eh-eh? No way!
You think I'm just taking a stroll here?
I'm returning from Governor-General's residence,
to where I've delivered Colonel Light's report.
Ah... We're so sorry, Mr. Bernard.
Kate! Your audacity really knows no bounds.
You need to moderate what you're saying about the grown-ups' affairs that you don't yet fully understand.
Okay...
Lucy-May, come see it! Come on! Come on!
Say, Clara, what kind of store is this?
Seems to be a store for lamps and furniture.
Oh?
I wonder what they have in that one!
Sister, come quickly!
You should see it, too.
Ah...
Sis, what about this store?
In here, they sell clothes and fabric.
Oh?
That was Mrs. Pettywell!
Maybe she came to order
a new dress tailored for her?
Hey, you saw it? Saw it?
Saw what?
I saw it just now, when they opened
the door wide for her!
What was it?
Kate, you didn't see it either?
I didn't see anything.
I was busy looking at Mrs. Pettywell.
Then you should definitely
come peek at it through here.
You see it?
I don't see anything.
Now, it's about time we left, you two.
That's enough distractions for one day.
Lucy-May, what did you see there?
It was a wedding dress!
Really?
Huh?
But we can't see it
unless the door opens again.
Let's open it!
Eh?
We'll enter in there.
Sure you don't mind, sis?
I don't see why I should mind.
After all, they might have something
that we happen to need, too.
Oh? Ah, welcome!
Would you like to have a dress
tailored for you, m'lady?
Eh... Yes...
Well, well.
Of course, that would be the dress for you, won't it?
Um...
Yes?
How much is this wedding dress?
Huh?
Ah!
Ah, this one? This is not for sale, you see.
Oh? How come?
We're using this dress
as a sort of eye-catcher for the shop.
But if you could sell it hypothetically,
how much would it be?
M'lady.
If you happen to need a wedding dress,
I'd be happy to make one for you in to time.
I'm already in love with this one.
Without a doubt, it's a marvelous dress.
But that's also why, like I said before,
selling it is out of question.
But so be it, if it happens to fit your body perfectly,
I could lend it to you, if you'd like it.
R-Really?
Telling lies is not in my habit.
However, only a person lean enough
would be able to wear this bridal gown.
Would you like to try it on, m'lady?
Eh? Yes.
Ah... But I'm afraid
I don't have any time for it today.
So I'd do it later.
Huh?
Goodbye!
What's with that girl?
Sister! Walk slower, please!
Say, sis, why'd you do that?
I was too embarrassed.
Of what?
I don't really need a wedding dress.
But I nearly ended up ordering one.
Still, when I have enough time,
I'll come to take a closer look at that dress.
It was a really pretty one!
If you put it on, I'm sure
you'll make for a gorgeous bride!
Thank you.
Sis, you've not forgotten John, after all, have you?
Whoa, Kate! You're being impudent again!
But hey - why else would you need
to take a closer look at that wedding dress?
It was a stunning dress,
anyone could see that!
Yes. It's just as you said, Lucy-May.
Let's go now.
Where are you going?
Wanna give it another glance?
We went right past the grocery store.
It was right there, just one house away
from the tailor's shop.
We've come quite a way from it, then.
I'm sorry.
Aside from that, only the flour.
Flour, then?
Your flour.
That's all we can get?
That's a rather small bag indeed.
Just as I thought,
the flour turned out to be expensive.
Anything else you need?
Oh, that's right. I almost forgot
I also need alcohol.
We don't have any alcohol here.
But you have spirits, don't you?
What you need is medical alcohol.
Then, where can we find a pharmacist?
He's over there.
Eh?
My son trades in that.
Please fill it with alcohol.
No problem.
Somehow, it feels like my load
is the most burdensome.
What do you mean?
I'd rather not carry something like salted meat.
But you were the one who said
"I'll carry it myself," weren't you?
That's true. I said I wanna carry some package
that's relatively small but still heavy.
But it smells a lot!
Well that's 'cause it's meat.
Since it's been pickled in salt,
it wasn't supposed to putrefy.
Ugh!
Hey! We ran into Mr. Bernard again.
Hey!
Is that the public office
where Mr. Bernard works?
Wrong.
"Adelaide Times." A newspaper, right?
Then, I'll leave the rest to you, Mr. Cope.
Yeah.
Adelaide even has its own newspaper now?
Yes.
Say, Clara, do you encourage your father
to read newspapers?
Y-Yes...
The one running the Adelaide Times is Mr. Cope,
quite a gifted fellow.
His articles are always 100% accurate.
Do they publish it daily?
On Sunday, they have a day off.
I never had any idea something article-worthy can happen in a place so sparsely populated on a daily basis.
It's not exactly like that...
Ah! Let me carry that bag for you.
Oh, I can handle it.
No need to be so modest.
Okay...
You won't be returning to your office?
Yeah. I've finished my work for today.
Darling, are these the ones?
Yes, lemme see it.
I hope they grow well here.
Don't worry. They should do perfectly fine.
I'd be really delighted if we manage to gather
spinach and carrots soon.
England and Australia have polar opposite climates
and soil qualities, so I can't know for sure.
I think it'll only became clear after we
plant the seeds and let them fully develop.
As for this radish, it sprouted way sooner
than back in England and is already big enough.
Hm. I also feel like the growth
is significantly faster here.
At any rate, we'll try planting carrots and spinach
to see how they would fare.
This tiny vegetable garden would provide
for perfect testing ground.
The thought of it becoming something else than that
is unbearable to me.
By Jove, when in the world
are they going to give us any proper land?
Ben! Billy!
Need a bit of helping hand here.
This hole is now so deep
I can no longer get out on my own.
Yes! Raise me up.
Ugh. And... up!
Thanks. I'll go put together a rope ladder now.
Also, I need to reinforce the walls with wood
so that the soil around it remains in place.
In that case, I can get in the hole
instead of you and keep digging.
Digging should be easy now, as the ground
is already quite damp and soft down there.
Billy, thank you.
I suppose Lucy-May and others
should be returning soon enough.
Thought so. Dad! Once Lucy-May gives me the goat,
I can return home, right?
Yeah.
Alley-hop!
Ouch! Huh?
It's wet. How come there water here, amidst earth?
You're late, Lucy-May!
Your dad hired Mr. Jamling to help him fix the house
and dig the water well, isn't that right?
Looking at it from outside, I couldn't help thinking
it probably cost him a small fortune.
That's because he got some insane money
from selling our prefabricated home.
Oh? I thought so.
Then, I guess, I've been worrying over nothing.
I don't know how that prefabricated home
looks from inside,
but its exterior is outright glorious.
It's just as comfortable on the inside, I suppose.
Why didn't anyone follow Mr. Popple's example
to also bring with them that sort of prefabricated home?
That looks like an easy way to start a comfortable life.
I've had enough of those talks
about the prefabricated home...
Make an effort and walk faster, you two!
But I'm tired!
Me too.
Let's take a break for a bit.
Let's rest!
What are you saying?
We're still a long way from home.
Isn't that why we should take a break?
Isn't your bag a bit heavy for you?
I guess so.
Give it here. I'll carry it, too.
Yay!
Mr. Bernard, I love you!
Here.
Eh? That too?
You can't do that!
There's salted meat in that package.
The scent will spread to Mr. Bernard.
In that case, you carry it.
I took you with me because you promised
to carry your bags properly until the end!
Now, let's keep going, Mr. Bernard.
You're a miser sister!
Here, Doctor.
Yeah, thanks a bunch.
Oh... Billy had been waiting all day!
Didn't you make a promise with him or something?
Yeah, I did!
Well, today we're parting with you.
Because Lucy-May had already promised it,
she insisted obstinately
on delivering the goatling to Billy before dark.
Lucy-May!
I wanna go too!
I hope that before long this goatling would be able
to provide Billy's family with plenty of milk, too.
When we went into the woods to look for a koala,
we found instead a dingo, about to attack some sheep.
Look out! We need to save them quickly!
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Water in the Well".
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you