South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 10 - The City of Greenery
Lucy-May, can't you put more spring in your walking?
It's just...
Just what?
My legs are starting to hurt already.
Oh my.
Is that so?
Makes sense.
We've not had any rest ever since we set out.
Do you want to make a stop here?
No. I think I can handle a little bit more of walking.
Really? Then, let's walk a bit slower.
Sister.
What is it?
We've not been going down the wrong road, have we?
Huh?
Don't scare me like that.
We're fine, Kate.
Look, tracks from the cart
that passed through here recently.
Ah! What a pretty bird!
The three of us had already walked a long way ahead
of dad and mom on our way to Adelaide.
Right, right! Walk straight, you slacker!
Like that!
Mr. Bard, there's no need to be that harsh with the ox...
It's nothing. Unless you whip this fella
that much, he'll never even budge!
But the cart is really heavy.
Madam, if you show that much sympathy for an ox,
you won't make it to Adelaide in this life!
Move it!
They're returning to England.
As for us, it appears,
we're not destined to see England ever again.
If things don't go too well in Australia,
we'll have no choice, but to return to England, right?
I'm not going back.
Why are you saying that, Mr. Parker?
It's not just me.
I'm sure it's the same for your father.
Dad too?
Yes.
After spending several months
just getting to this southern edge of the globe,
this must be the place
where our bones will bleach.
Everyone of us knows, if you hope to carve out a new life for yourself, you have no choice but to work hard.
My dad came to Australia, hoping to own a farm
way bigger than what he had up until now.
But it seems, things won't be that easy for him.
Uh-huh. Things don't seem
to ever go according to plan here
I know. It became clear enough to me,
when me and dad went to Adelaide.
Like, for one, there's no way
you can call Adelaide a proper city yet.
Just some fields and woods, also roads
under construction, but only a handful of houses.
However, it'll grow into a big city one day.
It has all the land you could wish for,
so a large-scale agricultural activity is bound to begin.
I hope it comes true sooner.
Yes, it definitely will.
Now that I think of it, Ben,
who do you intend to become in the future?
Do you plan to follow in dad's footsteps
and pursue agriculture?
No.
Huh? Then, you don't want to become a farmer?
To tell you the truth, I...
You've a dislike for farming?
That's not what I meant. It's just...
There's something I've been
wanting to become since long ago...
Oh? What it is you've been
wanting to become, then?
I can't tell you that.
Why so?
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing?
Besides, if dad finds out,
he would probably be terribly disappointed.
No, he'll definitely flip out right away.
Well, I'm getting more curious by the second.
What do you want to be, Ben?
I want to become a doctor.
Huh? A doctor?
Yes, that's what I thought.
No, I can understand the drive...
But this place doesn't have a single institution
for you to study medicine at...
Never mind that, there are no schools yet, even!
Yes.
There's no way for me
to become a doctor if I stay here.
Doing it with a cart like that...
I bet, they can't transport a lot of stuff at once.
They do what they can,
with oxen and horses being so sparse here.
That, I already know.
I wish we'd have managed to scout a second cart,
so that Ben didn't have to stay behind with our things.
Mr. Pettywell hired two, didn't he?
That's only because he's got money to burn.
It's good to have money.
You don't need to say things so obvious.
But I can't stop wondering why...
What is it, sister?
Why would someone rich and prosperous would go
to all the trouble of coming to Southern Australia?
Like Mr. Pettywell.
Good question. Had he stayed in England,
he'd have enjoyed a carefree life until end of times.
I know! He must have done
something bad back home.
And through that,
he is no longer welcome in England.
Lucy-May! You'd better stop with that!
You can't be saying such things.
Okay.
Grr! I can't take this anymore!
I'm unbelievably mad at myself
for paying such good money to hire an ox that lousy!
It's about time the master
stops with the snide remarks.
More! More!
No point doing any more than that, Mr. Pettywell.
Hey, lemme hold that for a moment.
Let you hold what?
That whip!
Ah! Master!
Go! Go faster than that!
Hurry up! Go faster, you! Hurry!
And you rascals walk faster, too!
Get this! And this! And this!
Why, if it isn't Mr. Pettywell's party?
That's right. And there's our house,
loaded onto their cart.
Now that you've sold it to Mr. Pettywell,
you can no longer really call it "our" house, darling.
Yeah. I shouldn't have sold it.
You've just realized?
The fact I had to sell it to that sort of man
only makes me more convinced I shouldn't have sold it.
Well, it's too late now to say your lamentations.
Residing constantly in remorse
is not like you at all.
Yes, I guess you're right.
What is it now, Lucy-May?
Need you to come here for a sec!
What did you see there?
Ants.
What about the ants?
There are so many of them.
That's nothing unusual at all,
back in England, there was just as many.
And they've such an impressive procession!
Looks like they're carrying something.
Just leave them alone already!
Come on, we need to go!
Ah!
It's sugar! They're carrying sugar.
Stop talking nonsense.
There can't possibly be any sugar around here.
Ah.
I wonder how far will they go.
My, you're right!
A whole lot of ants.
And the white thing is the sugar, see?
Could as well be salt.
Ants never carry salt.
Ah! Over there!
Someone must've dropped these here.
It's that sack. The ants go in and out
through where it's torn.
And inside it - sugar?
Sugar.
I wanna taste it!
Taste it...
We've not tasted any sugar in ages.
I'm trying it!
Ouch! Eh! An ant just bit me.
Ah! Sweet!
That's enough, you two!
Sister, this is sugar.
But it belongs to someone else.
They threw it away!
You know, like the goat we've scouted before.
But with this one, someone clearly intended
to come pick it up later.
But by the time they do...
the ants will totally end up
taking all of the sugar away.
It's yummy!
It is. But the ants are all sour!
Hm? Mhm! They're tickling my mouth from inside!
My... You two are incorrigible.
Sis, you should try it, too.
But it's...
You just need to spit the ants out.
Sweet, isn't it?
Yummy, isn't it, sis?
What's wrong?
One stung me inside my mouth!
But it's still yummy.
Take this! And this! You wretch!
Damn it all!
They dare to make fun of humans!
Move it! Crap! Wretch! Damn you!
Now, walk! I'm talking to you!
Walk! Start walking, you two!
You wretches!
We'll go first, then, Mr. Pettywell.
Damn it! Now this riffraff Popple, too!
Master, I suggest you stop now.
Do what you want!
D-D-Damn it!
We should've taken
that sack of sugar with us, after all.
All better than letting the ants eat it all.
Why don't we return to take it, sis?
But we've walked quite far already.
Now I can't help thinking
we've chosen the wrong road.
Huh?
Sister...
Back when we stopped to taste the sugar,
didn't we turn too far to the right?
Then, we should be fine
if we turn to the left now.
Will we be all right, sis?
Sister.
I really shouldn't have done that.
Sister, can't you walk a little slower?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must've been walking
a bit too fast, haven't I?
Does that mean we really got off track?
So it would seem.
But don't you worry. This must be
the direction to Adelaide now, no doubt about it.
Lucy-May, can you still walk?
Yes.
Sister.
What is it?
Did you notice?
There's some creature
that's been following us for a while.
Huh?
A person?
No. An animal, I think.
Lucy-May, did you notice it, too?
No idea what's this about.
I'm sure of it!
Could it be some beast?
No scary animals prey around here,
so we should be safe.
But I got a bad feeling!
Then, let's keep walking
and see how it plays out.
How about now?
Not sure yet...
Kate, maybe it was just your imagination, after all?
Ah!
What's wrong?
Look, over there.
There is something?
See? It was just like I said!
Could be a dog...
"A dog," you say?
Wasn't it a wolf?
A wolf, you say?!
There shouldn't be any wolves around here.
Are you sure about that?
At least, that's what I'm told.
Could it be aiming to attack us?
I don't know.
At any rate, let's keep walking.
Got it? You two, stick closely to me.
We'll show our disregard for the beast
with our gait.
Okay.
Don't break into a run,
and match your rhythm with me.
One, two, one, two, one, two.
I'm scared.
Me too.
Sis, you're shivering, too?
Of course I am.
One, two, one, two.
The girls must have already arrived
to our new house by now.
Not so much a house, as a shack.
It's a shack, Annie.
Well, aren't they the same thing, anyway?
Is what we call a shack,
not essentially just a small house?
Well, that one is especially small and dirty.
I hope the girls manage to clean it up nicely
by the time we get there.
Well, it seems, that one shack can't ever become tidy,
even after you clean it up.
Tell me, just what kind of shack
did you buy, darling?
At any rate, you'll know when you see it.
Listen, if you want to build a picture of it in your head,
just think of the most miserable shack that can ever be.
This way, seeing the real thing
is not that disappointing.
Is it really that horrible a shack?
Barely a shelter from the weather.
Which means, the girls are bound to get struck
by disappointment, once they arrive to the shack.
One, two, one, two, one, two...
One, two, one, two.
It's still following us.
Ah! My heart is about to stop!
For some reason, it doesn't seem poised to attack.
How could you tell that?
If it wanted to attack,
it would've already attacked by now.
Should we try to dash?
To dash?
Let's dash!
How do you know it doesn't
spring at us from behind?
Ah, I can't bear it any longer.
We're dashing!
Now!
Sis! It's chasing us!
We can't stop! Keep running!
Lucy-May!
Lucy-May, hurry!
This dog doesn't seem to be the one
that's been chasing us.
So it would seem.
At least the dog that's been
chasing us is gone now.
Hey, hey, Monocle!
What are you barking at so loud?
Now! Monocle!
Why are you barking like an idiot
at a bunch of ladies so lovely?
I imagine, you girls are coming
from a place entirely foreign to him.
Excuse me, are we close to Adelaide already?
Oh?
All the folk coming from the shore always ask me one
and the same thing, "are we close to Adelaide already?"
And I always respond,
this here is Adelaide.
Huh?
This here is the city of Adelaide?
Yes, everyone is surprised at first.
And then, you're to ask,
"but there's not a single house around, is there?"
I know what's this about!
This here is the city park area,
that surrounds Adelaide, isn't it?
Now that's surprising
how well-informed you are.
It's thanks to dad telling us.
When he and our brother returned from Adelaide,
dad mentioned meeting a shepherd here.
That's right! It has to be you, mister!
That might very well be true, I've been telling
this very same thing to a number of folk.
Speaking of which, there aren't any roads
at where you're coming from.
We got off track by mistake.
I see.
But well, at least you didn't end up
walking in circles through the forest.
Um...
What is it?
We were chased all the way until we got to there
by some dog-like creature.
Some dog-like fellow?
It was mighty scary! Was that a wolf?
I'd wager it was a dingo.
You could say that thing is like a feral dog.
Ah, actually! Was that why you were barking?
My bad, my bad, Monocle.
Are those dingo things real?
Of course.
The aborigines had some luck taming those enough
to keep them as pets, but they are still quite ferocious,
sometimes even attacking the sheep.
Which means you could keep dingo as a pet,
if you feel so inclined?
For me, it's probably out of question.
But this little lady might just be able to tame it.
I can do it, definitely!
Hmm?
No, no, I was just joking.
Taming a dingo is by all means
a fool's errand, especially for you.
Excuse me, we need to get to this place.
All I was told is that it's
in the vicinity of River Torrens.
Hmm? Let's see...
I hope Ben handles it all right,
being left completely alone.
I was quite surprised myself,
at how responsible he's become.
That's true.
Back in England, he'd use up every excuse
just to avoid helping out in the fields.
If me and Ben work in cooperation,
we'll certainly be able to build
a majestic farm here, in Southern Australia.
Well then, I need to place a sheet
over our luggage again, so I'll head there now.
Sure. And I'll be waiting for you,
after I prepare a delicious dinner.
Doctor. Doctor! Doctor Dayton! Hey!
Who're you?
Son of Mr. Popple, Ben.
Oh, I know, I know!
Mr. Popple who's gone to Adelaide, right?
Yes.
Okay...
Oh, did I catch a cold?
Not the rightest thing to ask of a kid,
but if you could get me some booze...
Did you get off the ship, doctor?
Yes, I got off.
I needed to examine Mr. Jamling's leg.
Ah! That's right!
I need to get on the ship!
Doctor! The ship had already
sailed away long ago!
What did you say?
So I...
So I've been left behind in Australia, huh?
Eh?
And that should be the River Torrens.
Then, our house is in that area!
Probably.
Well, why don't we hurry up
to our new home?
The city of Adelaide, as I saw it for the first time,
was covered in greenery from all directions.
From now on,
we would all be living here.
Adelaide was majorly
a city yet to be built.
Upon arriving to Adelaide,
our goat fell into the river.
Just you wait for me!
I'll save you in no time.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"Our Small House".
Don't miss it.
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Hugo
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you