South Wind Subs & The Sorcery Party
World Masterpiece Theater
Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow
[I want to be a rainbow]
Wasurenai wa hoshifuru yoru ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow I made on that starry night
Kono tomoshibi wo keshi wa shinai to
To not let this flame die
Wasurenai wa akane no asa ni chikatta kotoba
I won't forget the vow made on that brilliant red morning
Wakaba ni somaru haru wo yobou to
To call out for spring, dyed with young leaves
Ono utsu hibiki michi hiraku utagoe
Cutting axes open up roads, under the sound of singing
Kodama ga mune ni hazunde kuru no
The echoes bounce around in my chest
Kono oosora no niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
Kibou ni todoku niji ni naritai
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Ep. 27 - Riding the Kite
At that moment, I was carried away
by thoughts of Lucy's illness.
Little!
Alarmed by Little's shrieking I suddenly heard,
I dashed towards where the shrieking came from.
You again!
Take this!
How dare you bully Little?!
Doctor.
She threw up, isn't that right?
Yes.
But because she didn't eat anything,
there wasn't much to throw up with.
She looks in pain.
Right... Now, if you'd allow me...
Vomiting is also a consequence of high fever,
so you shouldn't be worried.
Tell me, does it hurt anywhere, Lucy-May?
It doesn't.
Hmm.
It hurts!
Ah, I swear... For how long is that quack
going to make me wait?
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Hey, Happy.
Where have you been?
Ah! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Hurts! Hell!
Ah, say, Doctor Deighton not finished yet?
Yes. He'll have to stay by Lucy-May's side
for a while, it seems.
No way...
My sister is in extremely poor health now.
Doctor promised he'll yank my tooth out before.
If he doesn't hurry to yank it out soon...
I'll tell him that.
Huh?
Callous. How most callous!
Fine! I'll go get another doctor.
Right! That's right! I'll do just that.
What happened, Kate?
Little got hurt. The goatling, too.
Both got bitten by that black dog of Mr. Pettywell!
Oh my, how cruel.
You think Dr. Deighton
knows how to heal the dog's wounds?
What are you saying?
You want Doctor to treat Little's wounds?
That'd be rude, I imagine.
But that's awful! Look at his neck, for instance!
My, it's bleeding heavily.
Tell me, where's Doctor Deighton?
He's checking on Lucy-May.
If Little dies, Lucy-May would feel totally dejected.
I'll try asking doctor just in case.
Please do, sister.
And where were you
when this was all happening?
Little, you're a baby dingo, right?
You know you're not supposed to die,
even if that black dog took it out on you!
You just can't die!
Still sleeping tight?
Yes, it's better this way.
Don't worry, ma'am,
Lucy-May will definitely recover.
Yes...
Ah, doctor.
Huh?
I have some tea in the other room.
Right...
Good idea. I'll gladly have it.
Hm?
What's going on?
The disease spread over to Little as well?
He got in a fight with Mr. Pettywell's black dog.
Why would they need to fight?
I didn't see it all so I can't know for sure.
But it seems, the black dog assaulted the goatling.
And he tried to save it.
Is that really so?
The baby goat also got bitten in the leg.
I see.
In the end, there ain't no dingo in Little.
No, it could be that dingo blood is flowing in his veins,
but he's a true dog, a friend to people.
But man, he's been roughed up badly.
I wanted Dr. Deighton to see if he can help Little.
No need. I'll do that myself.
Doctor allowed me to use his disinfectant alcohol.
Ah, no need, no need.
I'll take a look at Little's injury right now.
Ugh, I swear!
It annoys me as hell, but going to the nearest doctor
would be simpler, after all!
Listen, this one's gonna burn a little.
Endure it bravely. You're a boy, after all!
Ah! There you are!
Ah, Doctor, Doctor!
Please hurry up to yank out my tooth!
Haven't I told you before I'm no dentist?
Oh, you shouldn't move, Little!
What are you doing, Doctor?
What does it look like?
Looks like you're treating the dog's skin.
After he got bitten by your black dog!
By my dog? Happy?
That's right! That black dog bit Little!
Oh, that's rubbish!
Why'd he wanna bully such a tiny little Johnny?
I saw it with my own eyes!
I even hit him with a stick for it!
Who did you hit with a stick?
The black dog... 'Cause he's the one at fault here!
My Happy is such an unfortunate fella.
Wherever he goes, he's made a butt of,
with no means of explaining himself.
Are you insinuating that what I said was a lie?
No, I'm not... Just that there was no one else watching
to corroborate your claim.
How barbaric!
Ah! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! It started hurting again!
Doctor, I beg you! Yank it out sooner!
You're gonna have to wait a little
until I'm done with tending to this patient.
You should've helped me first,
rather than this dirty mutt!
In my line of work, I always examine my patients
on the "first-come-first-served" basis.
All right, that's done! Yes. 'Aight...
And up. How about this?
Good, you'll be fine here.
Eh?
That tickles!
I know what you're trying to say!
Eh, that's one cute fella you are.
Now, then, you still wanna get that tooth yanked out?
I wanna put an end to this pain!
Oh, then I guess we've no choice but to yank it out.
So, which tooth was it?
Here. Here, here.
Okay, move the hand away now.
Alright, is this the one that hurts?
N-no, it's not.
Then, this one?
Ah... No, not that again.
But this one was already shaky enough.
Then, this one?
No, not that either. Still somewhere...
Doctor!
What's wrong?
Is this the very same finger that the filthy dog
was licking just a moment ago?
I s'pose so.
Please wash it!
But I don't see any filth.
What are you saying?
That dog... That dog licked it, didn't he?
Maybe I really ought to?
Of course you should! Go wash it real clean now.
Just faster, please!
Very well... Sure, sure, sure, sure.
My, that was amusing!
And what do you need that bamboo for?
Oh, this?
I'll use this to make a kite.
A kite? Like the one that you fly in the sky?
That's right. I promised Lucy I'd make a kite for her.
So that she'd get well soon
and we go fly it together!
Back in England, you used to make them often.
This bamboo is a little different
from bamboo in England.
I hope it's still good enough for flying.
You're making it for Lucy,
so you want this kite to soar real high?
Yes.
That should do.
Well, it's finally about to begin!
Now, then.
Okay, sorry for the delay.
Please open your mouth wide one more time now.
Strangely, the pain seems to have subsided somehow...
No, still, this was not an easy decision to make.
Who knows if it doesn't start hurting like before.
Just do it!
Maybe that one?
Listen here, it's gonna hurt a bit now.
A bit more, a bit... Just bear with it a little longer!
Need you... Not to resist so strongly...
Ah! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Come on, be a good boy and open your mouth now!
You can't be biting others' hands!
Now!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch! Ah!
'Aight, can relax now.
You sure didn't make it any easier for me.
Ah!
Ah... Huh?
Huh?
Doctor! That... That tooth!
What's wrong?
Eh?! That tooth! Nothing was wrong with it!
Eh?
This tooth... was...
Was next to the one with the caries!
Next to it?
That tooth was next to it...
Next to it... Next to it...
You damned quack!
I'm home.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Sure, wait just a bit. It's almost ready.
Father. Have you heard about
what happened to Mr. Pettywell?
No.
It was absolutely funny!
What is it?
Doctor Deighton pulled out
two of Mr. Pettywell's teeth.
Two?
Exactly!
But of those, only one was with caries!
You know, Kate, I'm not really finding it one bit funny.
I mean... I mean, he first pulled out
the tooth that was never hurting!
Mr. Pettywell broke into tears then!
I really, really don't understand it.
Alright, it's finally here.
Kate, invite Doctor Deighton and Ben inside.
And please tell them I'm sorry for the delay.
Okay.
Say, is that true Mr. Pettywell
got two teeth pulled out today?
Yes, that's what happened.
And it sure was amusing, so amusing!
I still don't see how that could be amusing.
Sorry for making you wait, please come to eat!
Got it. Thanks.
Ben, did you hear me?
Yes.
I don't really feel all that hungry today.
Are you that tired, Doctor?
I suppose so.
I still hope you can help Lucy get better soon.
Oh? For that cause, I'll be happy to do my best.
Oh? Seems a lot like a proper kite already.
Little, what about are you?
You don't seem lively at all.
Yeah, so, you see, Mr. Pettywell's mouth
was chock-full of bad teeth.
So I couldn't tell for sure
which tooth was actually hurting.
Ah, now I see!
Doctor, you didn't do that on purpose, did you?
Not in this life! That was but a slip.
Even I can't be that mean-spirited!
Oh?
Lucy...
What's wrong, Lucy-May?
I need to feed Little.
Don't you worry about it,
Kate fed him long ago.
And you still have a fever, you know.
You shouldn't be up yet. Come on.
I'll go check on her.
Yes, sorry for the trouble, Doc.
Lucy still seems pretty sick.
God, please do something
to make Lucy's illness go away!
How does it look for Lucy?
Perhaps, I've always been a quack,
to a much greater extent than I ever imagined.
I suppose, the peak comes tonight.
If the fever doesn't subside by the morning...
No, it's nothing much to be worried about, Ben.
Just as I thought, I want to become a doctor.
Being able to save people's lives...
There's no other job that marvelous, right?
Yeah, I suppose. I suppose so...
I fell asleep?
When I checked yesterday,
her breathing was already very placid.
I suppose so.
The fever is also much milder now.
It's best that we let her sleep
through this afternoon as well.
I'm sure she'll get better. I'm sure.
Finished it!
Finally!
Good morning, Ben.
Good morning, mom.
And how does it look for Lucy?
Good morning.
Good morning, brother.
How are you feeling?
I've finished the kite.
I'm glad.
I used the strings made in England,
so those are very long.
And it'll fly mighty high!
Will you let me fly it, too?
Yes.
Get better soon and we'll fly it together.
I'll leave it here for now. Okay?
It's for you to recover sooner.
I will.
Good morning, Doctor.
Oh? Yeah, good morning.
I've overslept beyond belief.
Ben, you went to see Lucy-May, didn't you?
Seems to me like she is better than yesterday.
Huh? Really?
Good!
I'll go take a look myself!
Oh! Just as I thought. Hm!
Little.
Little, if you hang out around here,
you'll also be covered in mud!
Little recovered mighty fast, I see.
I really admire you, bro.
What for?
You spent yesterday making this kite, didn't you?
Yeah. But I don't think
it was something particularly admirable.
But you made it,
hoping to cheer Lucy up with it, didn't you?
More or less.
Well I, for one, couldn't do anything.
You covered for Lucy in looking after
the goats and Little, didn't you?
But my negligence ultimately led to Little getting hurt.
All the more reasons
why that black dog is one nasty sucker.
Exactly!
So, you want me to come again
in one week from today?
If possible.
By that time, I hope...
we'll be done with the rest,
so there'd only be a roof to install.
As for the roof, I though about shingling it
with eucalyptus bark, this time.
Hm. I'll leave it up to you to decide.
Good morning, Mr. Jamling.
Good morning. Working hard as usual, Ben?
In a week from today,
we've agreed on me installing a roof here.
Then, we'll also have to ramp up the pace
at which we're making bricks, won't we?
Keep up the good work, Ben.
Usually, I'd think Lucy
is of little to no help whatsoever.
But with her gone, we'll hardly be able
to actually make 30 bricks a day.
Something happened to Lucy?
...To not let this flame die
I won't forget
the vow made
on that brilliant red morning
To call out for spring,
dyed with young leaves
Cutting axes open up roads,
under the sound of singing
The echoes bounce
all around my chest
I want to be a rainbow in this big sky
I want to be a rainbow that reaches out to hope
Mom!
Dad asked you to prepare some tea
because Mr. Jamling is visiting us.
Sure, sure.
My... That soup, is it for Tob to drink?
No, it's for Lucy-May.
For Lucy?
Yes, that's right.
She just said she's starving.
Did she...
Did she recover, at last?
Yes, she's a-okay now.
I'm so glad!
I really am glad!
I'll go tell Ben right away!
At last, Lucy's fever started subsiding.
That must mean our usual
cheerful Lucy will also return soon!
While we were flying the kite, the line snapped,
so it flew all the way to the other side of the river.
Some aboriginal kids found it,
but didn't return it to us.
Next on Lucy-May of the Southern Rainbow:
"On the Other Side of the River."
Don't miss it!
TL: Wild Tiger Girl - Check: Cyber Zero - Timing: Kai
JP TLC & adaptation by Perevodildo for [sorcery]
Based on Spanish fansubs made by Alex Risi-Chan
[Let's Go to the Forest]
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you Know? Did you know?
Yuukari no ki ni akachan koara
There's a baby koala in the eucalyptus tree
Kaasan sagashite eda kara eda e
Looking for its mother from branch to branch
Happa no gochisou tappuri morai
It gathers plenty of leaves to eat
Kaze no yurikago ohirune yo
And naps in the cradle of the wind
Shitteru? Shitteru? Shitteru?
Did you know? Did you know? Did you know?
Mizube ni asobu warai kawase ni
The kookaburra is playing by the river
Itsumo youki ni waratte bakari
It's always so merry, so merry
Uhahahaha wuhahahaha
Itazura sarete mo wuhahahaha
Even if mischievous wuhahahaha
Misetai na misetai na mori no doubutsu
I want to show you, I want to show you the forest animals
Misetai na
I want to show them to you