The great human revolution, occurring in one -
before long, it'll start defining the fate of the nation.
Furthermore, it could even remold the fate of the human race.
The Human Revolution
Episode 1           Dawn
The fall of Mariana Islands
Death before surrender on Iwo Jima
There is nothing more inhuman than war.
The fall of Okinawa
There is nothing more tragic than war.
However, that war is not over yet.
Great Tokyo Air Raid
Original work: Daisaku Ikeda
Toyotama Prison, July 3, 1945
Honey...
Honey!
Oh, Ikue?
You came to pick me up?
Is the house safe?
Yes. Everyone is in good health.
I see. I'm glad, so glad.
I've caused you so much trouble.
But you've nothing to worry about now.
So, shall we go?
It was exactly this yukata-clad man
who would later come to be known as Toda Josei,
the great commander and guide of the people.
However, at that time,
Toda's name was barely known to anyone.
He was only known to the authorities
as a criminal offender, charged with a violation
of Peace Preservation Law and lese-majesty
for his refusal to worship a Shinto amulet
and staying faithful to Buddha.
So it was this bad?
And what about Morimoto's place?
Burned down in an air raid,
so they moved to the countryside...
Then, what about Kondo?
Their house as well...
Such a destructive endeavor...
Yet they are looking to prolong it?
Has this war made anyone happier?
Peace and happiness are supposed to be
the shared aspirations of all the humankind.
But instead, once every ten years or so, we find ourselves
plunged into a war where the nation's survival is at stake.
Whatever it takes, we must steer Japan
away from this path.
If anything, the Americans got some fine iron
in their firebomb shells!
Yeah. That iron is top-notch!
I even made a shovel with it once
and it worked wonders!
If you need a kitchen knife,
you can make five or six from a single shell!
Why be so stingy?
You can get away with all ten!
The masses remain resilient
no matter the times they're facing.
Harajuku! Harajuku!
I see. The Meiji Shrine.
What foolish thinking.
Without revering the true Buddha's ways,
they expect a divine protection from all deities at once.
Ignorance towards religion was the faulty notion that propelled
Japan into this reckless war in the preceding years.
And because of that, President Makiguchi...
Imprisoned on the same ideological offense charges as Toda,
President Makiguchi
Tsunesaburo Makiguchi, founder of Soka Gakkai
was subjected to the harsh interrogations and malnutrition.
And on November 18th of 1944,
he passed away in his prison cell.
He was 73 years old.
Makiguchi-sensei, you can trust me to make every effort...
This is the only part of the town
that survived the fires somehow.
I'm glad it did. I still have a home to go back to.
Honey, please watch your step.
Honey!
Toda
The Great Buddha,
I have finally returned.
He's so emaciated...
Nam Myoho Renge Kyo...
But at least, he managed to return home safely...
The Great Buddha, thank you so much.
Honey, the air-raid alert is on.
Well-well.
Just when I got home, there's an air raid?
Honey, let's go to the shelter.
No, I'm staying here.
It's out of question!
What if a bomb lands right here?
Come on, Honey, hurry now!
I'll stay here to protect Buddha-sama.
Huh?
Ikue, make haste and leave.
The darker the night gets,
the closer the dawn must be.
Buddha-sama, Daishonin-sama,
I will disseminate the law of righteousness
and bring the salvation to the masses,
to ensure that the Common Path is achieved.
If we want to pursue the Common Path,
Soka Kyoiku Gakkai has to be rebuilt.
"The first step towards that would be
an establishment of an economic basis."
With such thoughts, Toda immediately directed
his every effort towards rebuilding his business.
And that is the financial statement
of the business you've entrusted us with.
Is this bottom number written in black? Or is it...
It's in red.
Having learned that the business he used to run
had collapsed entirely
during his two-year-long imprisonment, Toda
decided to start anew
with his correspondence courses business,
and the preparations were set in motion.
Which brings me to...
Wouldn't it be possible for us to receive a small loan
with this fire insurance certificate as a collateral?
Sure. Fine by me.
Thank you.
I am truly grateful!
Once a print shop was set up and paper for it procured
with money raised from his old friend,
at last, the reopening of his business was all but ready.
August 6th, Hiroshima
August 9th, Nagasaki
After pondering deeply the general trends of the world
and the actual conditions obtaining to our empire today,
August 15, 1945: End of war
we have decided to effect a settlement of the present situation
by resorting to an extraordinary measure...
Japan unconditionally surrenders
to the Allied Forces, ending World War II
"In their present existence, the clergy of Japan,
as well as the laity revering them, are transforming this country...
...In addition to agonies unknown in previous ages,
will be swarmed by a foreign power.
This is due solely to the workings of deities like
Brahma, Shakra, and the gods of the Sun and Moon."
Nichiren Daishonin's prophecy came true all too exact.
By oppressing those who believe in true Buddhism
and imposing a faulty national Shintoism upon the people,
they brought about the ruin of our country.
But who could've possibly seen this coming?
More than ever,
the time has come for Nichiren Daishonin's
great Dharma to start shining.
Apart from this moment, the Common Path
won't have a chance to take off ever again.
We can by no means let this chance slip!
The Allied Occupation Forces
were promptly deployed to Japan.
General MacArthur, Supreme Commander of the Allied Forces
All political, economic, educational, and other internal functions of a defeated Japan were placed under strict supervision of GHQ.
Hibiya GHQ (General Headquarters of the Allied Powers)
Kamiosaki, Shinagawa Ward, Tokyo
Nihon Shogakkan Publishing Office
Nihon Shogakkan
Watch your back!
Ah! It's here, here!
Now, this is when things finally get busy.
Okumura-kun!
Is everything ready?
Yes!
All right! There it is!
Yes. You're through to Nihon Shogakkan.
You'd like to make an order?
Mere five days after the end of war,
Toda's correspondence courses business started.
English / Mathematics / Physical studies
Nihon Shogakkan
They're here, here!
This much!
It's only natural! We've put an ad
in a nationwide newspaper.
Good. Let's divvy those up and process them.
Okay!
Besides the correspondence courses in mathematics and physics,
aimed at young men and women,
in anticipation of the "English boom," they were among the first to devise and publish a well-received academic course of English.
The business was steadily taking off.
Kanda Ward (nowadays Chiyoda Ward), Nishi-Kanda
And then, in October, Toda moved
into the citadel of the publishing world -
the Kanda Ward, where inside
a three-story building in Nishi-Kanda,
the office of the publishing company
Nihon Shogakkan was officially opened.
Lemme tell you this, Sensei,
that's one fine lot you've found.
One can only ascribe it to a divine grace.
Oh? Yam today as well?
Well, I'd like to say so, too,
but I can't really call yam a divine grace.
Ah? Thank you.
However, it is beyond doubt that this building
was a gift from Buddha himself.
For my devotion to the Lotus Sutra,
I've been thrown into prison for two whole years,
which I spent fighting in deadly agony,
hence this divine reward.
I don't know in which way will this building serve us in the future,
but I'm sure only good things will come out of it.
Let's all take good care of it.
Okay!
Okay.
Well, thank you for stopping by.
I'm counting on you to do your best now.
Yes, I won't let you down.
Thank you very much.
The office of Nihon Shogakkan in Nishi-Kanda
became the main operational base for Soka Gakkai.
And upon learning that Chairman Toda was alive and well,
many pre-war members have gradually started flocking to there.
Toda-sensei!
Sensei!
If it isn't Yamadaira-kun!
Yamadaira Chuhei... has just returned!
How wonderful that you've returned alive!
I'm glad! Really glad!
It must've been awfully hard for you!
Yamadaira Chuhei went to war as a mobilized student,
but managed to return safely.
Thus, men sent to the battlefield, one after another,
were trickling back to Toda.
I see. He is five already?
So? Did you like it?
No need to be shy about it.
We still have plenty more.
Feel free to take some home.
Now, day after day, all I think about is death!
I should probably take this child with me...
What's this nonsense you're saying?
How will your death help things?
"Human life is far more precious and important
than all the treasures in the universe."
That's what Daishonin taught us.
It would be outrageous to take that life for granted.
After this war, countless people, including the Society members,
dwelt in the depths of despair, having lost
their husbands or families to the fire during air raids.
However...
Listen. Your suffering might seem never-ending now,
but as long as you carry on with enough faith in you,
you'll always have brighter days up ahead.
You shouldn't think it's all about you alone!
This kid's future happiness and everything
also hinges on your faith.
What do you say?
Will you be able to persevere for some more?
Ah... Yes! I'll do it...
I'm counting on you.
If you ever find yourself in dire straits again,
feel free to come see me anytime.
Okay! Thank you ever so much!
Cheer up, will you?
Nakano Station
Today must be the day I take the first step
towards inheriting my late mentor's mantle.
First step.
Year when the war ended,
November 18th.
November 18, 1945
Memorial service for the first anniversary of Makiguchi Tsunesaburo's death
A memorial service was held for Makiguchi Tsunesaburo,
the founder of Soka Kyoiku Gakkai,
on the first anniversary of his death.
Sensei, I still remember that day in June of 1943.
Upon the summons from the religious affairs council, we were hurriedly following Makiguchi-sensei uphill to the Taisekiji Temple.
At that time, the sect
feared the oppression from the military,
so to placate the authorities, the prayer book text was altered.
We've effaced some important verses from the scriptures,
thus committing an act of slander against Daishonin's teachings.
And on top of that, something even darker...
Head Temple Taisekiji
...So I hope you understand
why the military is also strung out because of this.
If you keep slandering our divine amulets,
you might just end up pouring oil on the fire.
Therefore, Makiguchi-san, how about
you and your Society accept our amulets just in case?
We will never accept your amulets!
It is not the ruin of a single sect that I lament.
It's the utter destruction of an entire nation.
I solemnly fear the sorrow of Daishonin,
the founder of our sect.
More than ever, the time is now
to try and rectify the leaders' ways.
What in the world are we afraid of, then?
Toda-kun, what are your thoughts on it?
Sensei, I will fight for this cause like my life depends on it!
Come what may, I'll be by your side in everything you do.
After that, the authorities began oppressing us in earnest.
Sensei was arrested in Shimoda, Izu on the same day, July 6th.
I was also arrested at my home in Shirokanedai on charges
of violating the Peace Preservation Law and lese-majesty.
Which makes that
the last time I saw Sensei.
September, 1943
Metropolitan Police Department, Internal Detention Center
Come out. You'll be interrogated.
Could that be Makiguchi-sensei?
It has to be Sensei.
Makiguchi-sensei!
Toda-kun?
Move it! Who said you can stop?!
Ah! Makiguchi-sensei!
Asshole!
Start walking!
Sensei!
Please! Don't be harsh on him!
January, 1945
Sugamo, Tokyo Detention Center, Interrogation Room
Toda-san, it's about time you've come clean about your guilt.
Even if you're telling me to come clean,
I haven't done anything wrong, therefore I can't come clean.
Second verse same as first, huh?
All your other buddies have pleaded guilty already,
swore to convert and had their leave long ago.
You're the only remaining idiot.
That is not true.
Makiguchi-sensei also persists.
Makiguchi is dead.
What?!
Sensei...
Sensei!
Makiguchi-sensei!
A great many yielded to the pressure
and disavowed our cause.
But President Makiguchi never stepped back, and was martyred for his unbending fight against the militaristic authorities.
He sacrificed even his precious life
to the spread of Lotus Sutra Path.
Sensei only passed through the prison gate after he died.
While I, the unworthy disciple of his, made it out alive.
There is, thus, only one thing that I must do next,
lying in the plain sight.
I'm going to say it loud and clear now!
Even if the entire the world gives up on the Common Path,
I, Toda Josei, will keep professing it no matter what!
My sincere devotion to our cause
wasn't shared by a single person there.
Will I really be able use the Common Path to save the people?
A lion roars alone.
That's right. I have to become a lion.
"Common Path" best befits a lion!
Even when I stand all alone,
I must inspire unquestionable confidence in people!
I now receive the Buddha’s decree,
Which is his vow to save all through the Lotus Path.
I stand proudly alone with my head held high -
Friends are hard to come by, foes are numerous.
When 1946 started, Toda truncated the Society's previous name
of Soka Kyoiku Gakkai to just Soka Gakkai.
Soka Gakkai Headquarters
The new signboard was put up at the Nihon Shogakkan office.
Sensei, it's a great thing!
I feel like my body and mind have been
refreshed and tightened up from this!
Yes. It's finally getting a fresh start.
There's no reason the Society's goals
should remain limited to education alone.
Politics, economy, culture, and so on -
in various fields, constituting life,
we must become an omnipresent force
that invigorates the people.
From this base, we need to start sending out into the world
countless promising men, armed with a great ideal of Lotus Sutra.
Otherwise, we can't hope to save this country.
And those capable, promising men...
Right. The youth. It could only be the youth.
Mishima-kun.
So? Are you finding that Editor-in-Chief's desk comfortable?
Yes. Thank you for your continued support.
I'm counting on you for our next project.
Okay!
Is this book performing well?
Yes. It gained an enormous reputation already.
We barely manage to keep up with the demand.
So I thought. These days, all and sundry,
young men in particular,
are jumping ecstatically into the feast of democracy
they've never tasted before.
But let me tell you.
This is not what true democracy looks like.
Philosophy & History
Nihon Shogakkan
Huh?
Democracy in the true sense of the word
cannot be achieved through merely replacing the ruling party
and reforming the societal structures.
It must first establish itself in the minds of individuals.
That's the starting point, the foundation of democracy.
So? Are you following?
Establish itself in the minds of individuals
by means of Human Revolution!
Kiyohara-san.
Yes?
Listen. This is your own Human Revolution.
I have mine...
And Yamadaira-kun has his!
All must undergo their individual Human Revolution.
That's where the democracy is being born
and that's what it boils down to.
It's never just about institutions and policies.
It's about people!
It's about lighting the way for people!
It's these people, suffering greatly from this defeat in the war,
who need someone to light the way for them!
The youth are earnestly pursuing the Buddha Dharma.
I must do my utmost to teach these young men
the greatness of the Buddha Dharma.
Maybe my perfect chance is now...
All right. Let's go for it!
Yamadaira-kun, Kiyohara-san, I'm doing it!
Course of lectures on the Lotus Sutra.
Toda-sensei is finally starting to give lectures on Lotus Sutra.
I've never been this happy!
I should probably also tell Izumida-san
and gather as many people as I can!
Huh? Toda-sensei is giving lectures? That's just amazing!
Let's split the work now and send express mail
to everyone whose address we know!
But many evacuated because their homes
burned down during the war...
Will they be able to receive it?
No point worrying about that now!
For now, let's just do whatever we can!
Agreed! Let's do just that!
Kiyohara Katsu, an elementary school teacher,
was the Society's female division leader.
Izumida Tame was the wife of a soldier, whose husband was deployed in the South and was still considered missing in action.
Both used to be Makiguchi's disciples
and managed to maintain a pure faith.
Oh? Isn't that Kiyohara-san?
My, Konishi-san!
Eh? Chairman Toda?
Yes. His company is located in Nishi-Kanda,
and that's also where the new headquarters are.
There, he keeps rebuilding the Society brick by brick.
I had no idea!
Damn, I miss him!
Ah! And this coming Monday,
Sensei will be giving a lecture on Lotus Sutra!
Are you coming?
Oh! I would absolutely love to join!
Seki-kun, who is an elementary school teacher just like us,
also works in Kamata, so I'll bring him along!
Really? Wow, I'm so glad.
Soka Gakkai makes a new precipitous start
towards the Common Path.
At his new headquarters, in the same building
as Nihon Shogakkan, Toda began lecturing on the Lotus Sutra.
In short, my lecture on the Lotus Sutra boils down to this:
What exactly is Daishonin's "Nam Myoho Renge Kyo" about?
That's really all you need to know.
We start with the basics - first,
what does "Nam" stand for in Nam Myoho Renge Kyo?
Unfortunately, it has nothing to do with ham.
Nam is a word from Sanskrit,
which translates to "devotion to Buddha."
Devote - from Latin "dedicate by a vow."
Are you following?
Yes!
Therefore, when we say "Nam," it means we believe in Buddha
and offer our bodies and souls together to him.
As for Myoho Renge Kyo part,
it refers to the 28 chapters of Gautama Buddha's Lotus Sutra.
In the present Degenerate Age of Dharma, Daishonin's Buddhism
was mainly defined by Nam Myoho Renge Kyo.
The line we must draw clearly and firmly here is...
If we don't uphold Daishonin's Buddhism,
the living creatures of the Degenerate Age cannot be saved.
On the next lecture...
Next would be Seki-kun's part.
Read it for us, will you?
Okay.
"Siddhartha became Buddha.
And by extension, various Buddhas
of ten directions and three times.
Particularly, his true form..."
Hm. Their drive to seek the truth becomes stronger and stronger.
Furthermore, on the next lecture...
With every session, the number of listeners increased.
The air was thick in Nihon Shogakkan hall,
heated by both the passion of the one giving the lectures
and those listening intently, trying not to miss a word.
Then, Sensei, if we are also tasked with a noble mission of saving the people, does that make us the Bodhisattvas of the Earth?
Of course it does. No doubt about it.
What do you guys think?
Can you feel that you are the Bodhisattvas of the Earth?
No, not really...
Yes. It's a bit hard to tell on your own.
But as Daishonin-sama put it once,
"If it wasn't for the appearance for the Bodhisattvas of the Earth,
this chant would've fallen into oblivion."
By saying so, he decreed it sternly:
in the Degenerate Age of Dharma, only those who chant
Nam Myoho Renge Kyo get to become Bodhisattvas of the Earth.
That's something to be proud of!
We, my friends, are the Bodhisattvas of the Earth.
Wearing some rags, with a constantly growling stomach...
Konishi-kun,
Seki-kun,
Kiyohara-san as well.
It is beyond doubt for me
that you are the Bodhisattvas of the Earth.
That's something I want everyone of you
to realize clearly today.
Can you do that, friends?
Yes!
Chairman! Thank you so much.
No need.
Actually, I'd like to organize a roundtable discussion.
So I was wondering if I could get you to join us.
Oh? A roundtable discussion? Good, I like it! When?
This coming Sunday night.
Konishi's house in Kamata
Oh? I see this place was spared the ravages of war.
Yes. The Great Buddha was kind enough to protect it.
My, it's been a truly long while.
Has everyone been doing well?
Yes! We're all right!
We're ready for action again!
I see, I see. Good to know.
Thus, the first roundtable meeting
after the reconstruction of the Society was held in Kamata.
The roundtable-centered activities that had been a tradition since the times of the first president, Makiguchi, were revived.
Young men from the local community gathered at a house
in Morigasaki, near the venue where Toda was attending.
They were the members of the Reading Circle.
As the established system of values collapsed due to the defeat in the war, people earnestly searched for how they should live now.
They actively sought to absorb the new knowledge.
There was among them a young man
quietly listening to his friends from the very front.
The young man seemed to reside in deep contemplation,
searching for something intently.
We've had quite a productive reading session today.
I feel that I have something in common
with the way of life of Uchimura Kanzo, who became a Christian.
Oh? You've started reading it already?
Miki Kiyoshi's Notes on the Theory of Life. It looks awfully difficult.
Yeah. I'm having a hard time reading this.
I'm a somewhat slow-paced fella,
so I can barely read one book a month.
They call you Bookworm Yamamoto-kun,
so you probably read like five or six, right?
No, I wouldn't say...
The youngest of the group, this young man
was named Yamamoto Shinichi.
By day he toiled for a tiny printing company,
and by night, he attended
Oriental Commerce School in Kanda-Misakicho.
How does it look for your health?
I seem to get a bit of a fever in the evenings, but I'll be fine.
Don't push yourself.
Yamamoto already had an ailing chest.
He became ill while working at a munitions factory in Kamata.
Presently, he takes medications from the hospital
to stave off the progression of disease.
The doctors' diagnosis was that he probably won't even live to 26.
Yamamoto and his friends often strolled along Morigasaki Beach,
talking literature and arguing philosophy.
The discussion was endless on questions such as "What is a patriot in this day and age? What is the criterion for good and bad?"
Finally, "What is the true and righteous life?" -
They didn't have a single spiritual fulcrum in sight.
In the end, I've made up my mind on trying Christianity.
Are you coming along?
No. Honestly, I don't feel drawn to Christianity.
I will still try to pursue my own path
in a way unique to me.
With my friend by the shore, Morigasaki
Pungent seaside smell, waves withdrawing
Nineteen-year-old boys, struggling to choose a path
Philosophy talk as the hours go by
Always troubled being poor, my friend utters:
"The way of Christ is the one I'll follow"
Eyes flashing keen in the moonlight,
To that firm heartbeat, the waves roll in...
Thus, Yamamoto Shinichi's deep contemplations kept piling up.
But before long, he would find himself overwhelmed,
when time comes for his fateful encounter with Toda Josei.
Raw provider:
Translation:
Quality checking:
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Muzussawa
The Human Revolution
Episode 1
The End