koro
Okizari Fansubs presents
A Good Time for an Adventure
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh!
I met you at a party
Welcome My Sweet Cat wo-o-oh!
A fairy in jeans
I chased you to the motor pool, "Let me walk you home"
Putting my ulterior motives on the side seat
No!
Whoa, but the radio is giving me bad news
Ow!
Hurry, hurry!
My mood is sold out, you're only joking
Hey there, Junpei here again.
Switch on my heart, it's all right!
.Protagonist
Koganei Junpei
My first foray into
major motion pictures ended in a big hit.
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh...
And now, we're in the middle of secretly filming our next AV production.
No! Stop it!
Cut!
.Apollo Productions Director
Wakaba Miwa
Good, now let's do another take of running through the car.
This time, run all the way to the front and get cornered by the thug.
Let's do it without rehearsing.
Of course, there was no way we could get permission,
so we shot everything guerrilla-style.
At least it's going well for now.
Action!
Why you!
No!
Hey! What the hell are you guys
doing on my train?
...Or not.
Oh crap, get the Chief!
W-Wait for me, guys!
Hey, Junpei! Equipment! Our equipment!
Throw me the tripod already!
Right... Here!
Good!
Nice catch.
No way!
No way...
H-How cruel!
Apollo Guerrilla
Film Crew Arrives  !
Stationmaster's Office
For the millionth time,
we were making a film called
"Romantic Journey on Private Railway Lines."
"Romantic Journey on Private Railway Lines"
sounds like an innocent film.
Why is there a half-naked girl
in such an innocent film?
Well, you see...
We just thought it would be nice
to include a pretty girl in it, right?
Works for me.
I like it better when there's a cute girl too.
But a bare-breasted or even a fully naked girl is going too far!
There is something called common morality.
But you didn't even bother getting a permit.
Excuse me, sir.
Right?
You said you were with
Apollo Productions, right?
Yes.
Their president said they've never heard of anyone with your name.
Koganei Junpei?
No, we don't have an employee
by that name.
Th-That can't be!
In your position, it's better to tell the truth
now so we can all can go home sooner.
Hey, you! Wait!
Geez! Now I'm fucking pissed!
Sign: Apollo Productions, Ltd
Chief!
How could you?!
I kept my mouth shut until the end
for everyone's sake!
"Koganei Junpei? Nah, we don't have any employees by that name."
Can you believe it?!
I don't know why I've been working
so hard if you do that to me!
Huh? Really, they went home already?
They're all so cold to me.
Ch-Chief!
Good evening, Koganei-kun.
Huh? You're Director Shibuya's secretary.
What are you doing here so late?
I... I came here to ask a favor of you, Koganei-kun.
.Secretary
Ogawa Masako
Junpei-kun is probably really mad right now.
Junpei-kun, nice work!
Sorry we abandoned you today.
Sorr... What?!
You horny, hard-on pervert!
The second I let you out of my sight, you do this?!
No! It's not what you think!
Oh, you're...
Sorry about that.
I told you it wasn't what you thought!
I'm sorry. It's my fault for causing all this commotion.
But I need your help too, Wakaba-san.
Please star me in your next adult video.
Isn't... Isn't it strange
that I'm still a virgin at age 20?
I haven't had any luck with men since
a traumatic experience I had as a child.
Since then, I just can't figure out how to conduct myself around men.
So I was hoping
that maybe if I was with Koganei-kun,
I could manage to lose my virginity happily.
And you want to be in our adult video for that?
Yes.
I wonder if Ogawa-san will be any good.
Don't worry.
She has a decent-sized chest and,
even more importantly, she has guts.
I'm sure the chief will like her. Right?
Still, that was really moving.
What?
Well, you coming back for me and all...
Don't get ahead of yourself. I just came back to collect something I forgot.
That's pretty cold, you know!
I endured hours of lecturing in that nasty stationmaster's office,
thinking that I'm doing it for you!
Not even a word of thanks?
Just kidding.
Everyone is actually
very grateful to you, Junpei-kun.
I mean, if you hadn't taken the fall
for everyone back there,
they would've confiscated the tape,
and we'd've had to scrap the project.
You also saved all of our equipment.
Miwa-san!
So you're saying that the tape and equipment are more important than me?!
I am. It's a fact of life.
Miwa-san!
Keep up the good work, okay?
Junpei-kun.
Hurry, get inside me.
Junpei-kun, hurry.
Miwa-san!
H-Hey!
You never learn, do you?!
So cruel!
You see, in essence, adult videos are sort of like fresh fruits.
.Apollo Productions President
Ujiki Masami
The fresher and spicier the girls are, the better.
Like, for example, a girl who says,
"You're kiwi, papaya, and mango."
.Video Engineer
Ishikawa
Isn't that right, Chief?
Uh? Yeah, that's... Right.
This is where you come in, Koganei.
Yes?
Your duty for today
is to find Apollo's next star.
That's right!
In Harajuku, Shibuya, and Roppongi, we'll be scouting out powerful and exciting girls!
Y-Yes, exactly!
U-Um, Chief...
Actually, Miwa-san and I have
already found the perfect girl.
What the hell was that?
You already found someone?
I guess you're just doing your thing again, you horndog.
Horndog! Rake!
Hey, you bastard!
You're just stealing everything
I wanted to say!
This is to keep you shut for a while!
Koganei, you've done it!
You've done well!
Well, hearing that from you is reassuring...
Lighting Designer
Tanaka
Junpei-chan, when did you trick her
into joining? Hurry up and introduce us!
I also can't wait to meet her!
Cameraman
Ujitani
Well? What's she like?
If she's anything like Diane Lane,
I'll die a happy man!
Y-Yeah, I guess there is a certain resemblance...
If only a little, Junpei-kun.
Really? Are you serious?
Where is she?
Where is my Diane Lane-chan?
Oh! Those sexy legs!
Oh-ho-ho! Those tantalizing hips!
Woo-hoo! That chest is the real deal!
And most crucially, her face...
It's just like Diane Lane! Look! Look!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ogawa Masako.
Koganei, she's no good.
Wh-Why's that?
For starters, she doesn't look like Diane Lane.
Sh-She does look a little like her,
doesn't she? Maybe her hair...
No, she doesn't!
S-Still, that's no reason to turn her down!
He's right! You're being rude to her!
This is my job. I have to leave concerns
about rudeness or whatever else behind.
U-Um... Do I really look that bland to you?
Am I really so hopeless?
Ogawa-san!
Hold up a minute!
Allow me to tell you
why you're no good.
Try fucking Koganei on my desk.
Come. Lie down.
Keep it together, won't you?
This is all part of the job,
isn't it, Miwa-chan?
She's totally faking it.
She's not turned on at all.
It hurts!
That's enough!
I'm sorry!
I guess... I'm just... I'm no good!
Ogawa-kun, isn't that right?
Yes.
And you're a virgin, right?
But how did you know?
It's your smell.
Hey, wait...
I feel like it's about to suck me in.
No! Not that kind of smell!
I always play that "Virgin Search" game in magazines,
and so far, I haven't been wrong even once.
Then, Chief, are you suggesting Miwa-san...
That's none of our business!
But there's one more reason.
One more?
You should know it yourself
better than anyone else.
S-Still, Chief, why can't we record Ogawa's first time with Koganei-kun on video?
The moment a girl changes into a woman
is the most beautiful her body will ever be!
Why can't we do it, then?
If I say no, that's final.
Bullshit! Give me a real reason!
That's fine.
Koganei-san, Miwa-san,
I've changed my mind.
Thank you for everything.
Ogawa-san!
What was all that about, Chief?!
Explain yourself!
I have to admit, she does have something special about her.
Then why not film her?!
Because she's too gloomy.
What I want to capture is
the carefree brightness of today.
Apollo Video has no need
for wet blankets!
Is that the only reason
why you won't take her?
I hate that about you.
Wait!
Cover yourself before going outside.
Ah! G-Good idea!
Where are you from?
From Higo
Where in Higo?
From Kumamoto
Where in Kumamoto?
From Senba
In the mountains of Senba,
there is a raccoon
A hunter shot it with a gun
He cooked it, then roasted it and ate it
He covered it with leaves from a tree
I shouldn't dwell on it.
It's not like me
to get discouraged by this.
Well, chin up!
Welcome, sir.
Blended whisky.
I didn't order that.
It's from that lady.
Are you here alone?
No. I was waiting for someone.
Was waiting for someone?
So you no longer expect them to come.
Not necessarily. The one I was waiting for
is sitting next to me right now.
I've been waiting for you,
President Ujiki.
How did you know my name?
You still don't get it?
Do you remember now?
At your office yesterday.
I-It's you?!
I had no idea!
What are you doing here?
I'm seducing you.
Wh-What?
I mean, you said I have no appeal.
So I came here to seduce you.
Is that funny?
Do you really think
an inexperienced girl like you
can seduce a seasoned man like me,
who's been around the block?
What if I succeed?
You won't.
Is that so?
S-Stop it. Stop!
Wanna bet?
Bet? F-Fine by me.
If I win, you'll star me in your next video.
And if I win?
I'll dance naked at the Shinjuku Hokoten.
Very well.
But I doubt you'll really
be able to seduce me.
Then I'll show you otherwise.
Driver, to Ichigaya please.
Certainly.
Where are you taking me?
My apartment.
Good grief...
First, she threatens to seduce me,
then she makes me wait for ages!
Sorry for the wait.
Please come in.
Th-This is the aroma of a home-cooked meal
that'd make any bachelor cry with joy!
I hope you like it.
I'll cut the pickles now.
Oh, my?
Chief?
What are you doing?!
Enough with this silly charade.
Have a fun night with Uncle Ujiki!
Right?
That means I won the bet.
The bet?
I don't know what you're talking about...
I figured you'd say something like that.
Wh-What's this?! The hell!
Let me down! Let me down!
Let's me down!
Good! Cut!
We've got it all on tape!
Infallible proof!
I see now. You were all in cahoots
to put one over on me!
And so, the video of Masako's defloration was now in the works.
I was struggling mightily
with the screenplay.
The location was already set,
so it became a vacation romance story.
Good luck.
I live for moments like these...
Shibuya Shozo's Office
Masako-san, you seem in high spirits.
Did something nice happen to you recently?
Not telling.
I'm going out for a bit.
Can you answer the phone for me?
Sure thing.
Thanks. See you later, then.
No problem. Take your time.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Ah, this warmth!
Oh! Masako's smell!
Chief Asst. Director
Gondo
What's that?
B-Bad news, sir!
It's Koganei!
Film Director
Shibuya Shozo
It's that bastard Koganei!
He's putting my secretary in a porno?
I won't allow it. I'll never let him!
Yes?
Ogawa-kun, do you have a minute?
Excuse me.
Ugh! Help me, Koganei-kun.
Help me!
Then zoom in there, got it?
Okay.
That's strange.
It looks like she left a while ago.
Something must be up.
She's not the type of girl to cancel
a meeting without warning.
I hope she didn't get in an accident.
I'll go and have a look.
Shibuya Shozo's Office
Hello?
Is anyone here?
That's strange. It's not supposed to be their day off.
It just got even stranger.
Shibuya Shozo
Could she be here?
I... I knew it!
Junpei-san!
What have they done to you?!
I'll come help you right now!
Keep it together...
Koganei!
What are you doing here, you creep?!
What am I doing?
I should be asking you that!
Why did you do this to Masako-san?
What can someone like you...
What can someone like you
know about how I feel?!
Ow!
Junpei-san! Behind you!
What's the meaning of this, Director?!
Exactly what it looks like.
We're locking you up.
Locking me up?
Listen, Koganei, I'll never let my sweet
Ogawa Masako star in your vulgar AV!
Do you get it?
Ya get it?
All right, Gondo,
keep close watch on them both.
So, Koganei, wanna eat some gruel?
What's up?
Why you keep fidgeting like that?
You wanna take a piss or something?
What'll it be?
Hold up!
What the hell! Let go, you!
Masako-san, wait for me!
I promise I'll come back for you!
Wh-What?!
They're holding Ogawa-kun hostage?
Horrible!
They're not getting away with it!
But I don't understand.
Why would a man like Director Shibuya
be so possessive about his secretary?
Look who's talking, Chief.
You fell for her charms.
Sh-Shut up!
Still, if they resorted to the extreme measure of tying her up,
Apollo Productions will also have to take drastic measures.
Then, you're saying...
To the Unopened Locker!
Unopened Locker?
Roll call!
One!
Two!
Three!
Four!
Five!
U-Um, Chief, what are we going to do, exactly?
It's "Captain"! Call me Captain.
We will now storm Director Shibuya's residence
and liberate Ogawa Masako!
But if we do that, Director Shibuya will only get even more pissed off at us!
And then we really
won't be able to film her.
Why don't you get it?!
Our filming has already started!
We'll forsake all formalities now
in favor of guerrilla filming!
Guerrilla filming?
The unscripted snafus
are always the most fun.
Let's go! Move out,
fearless soldiers of Apollo!
Sir, yes, sir!
Junpei-kun, hurry!
Y-Yes, sir!
Masako-san, you can't keep playing it tough and refusing all food forever.
Besides, you've been holding in your pee for a while too.
Why not wet yourself again?
You're a brute, not even a human!
It's not like I'm doing this
because I like it either!
Masako-san, I don't want to lose you
to the likes of Koganei!
We just can't let them film you
in some dirty porno!
That's for me to decide, not you.
Masako-san, I've been in love with you ever since the director hired you as his secretary!
Why must you appear in a dirty AV
with that stupid hard-on pervert, then?
Th-That fucker Koganei won't have you!
If you want to be in a porn, I'll direct it myself and give you the masterpiece you deserve!
Hell no. Your worldview is too dark.
I'm drawn to the brightness
of Koganei's films.
Only then will I be ready to...
Only then will you be ready to what?
In the end, you're just an ordinary woman,
who only wants Koganei for his prick!
It's all about sex!
If that's the kind of woman you are,
there's a solution.
You whore!
Stop! Stop it!
Rape... I'll rape you!
What are you doing?!
Why? Why can't you understand
that I love you so much?
If that's what it comes to,
I'll just have to do it.
Why are you here?!
The Apollo guerrilla film crew arrives!
You bastards...
Fire! Fire, fire, fire!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You'll regret this!
Ogawa-san, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll free you now.
Hey, Junpei-kun, could you help me?
Wh-Why you...
horny, hard-on pervert!
Why only me?!
Ogawa-san, you can rest easy now.
The crisis is over.
Koganei-san! I was scared.
So awfully scared!
And now, we'll be filming
the all-important defloration scene!
Jeez, Miwa-san, not so direct...
But I'm not quite ready yet.
You'll be fine.
If you leave everything to me, I'll make you mesmerizing, just like Cinderella.
Okay.
Junpei-kun, you swine!
You've got some nerve spouting cheesy lines like that without anything to back them up!
So you're here at last, Apollo riffraff.
Setsuko-san, your daughter is growing up so fast that I can't reach her anymore.
But rest assured,
I haven't forgotten my promise to you.
Scenario Transformation!
I'll show Koganei that we're not kidding around.
Impressive installation.
The setting is unexpected,
but shooting in a loony bin cage would make for quite a scene.
Yes. It was a blessing in disguise.
Wh-What's that?
Hold up, what's with the ray of light?
It wasn't in the original manga!
You're too naive. Deviating from the manga is what anime does.
By rewriting the story,
the director leaves his own mark on it.
I won't let you free Masako!
Prepare yourselves!
My tackle will cut through that key like it's not even there!
Chief!
We'll be fine.
The bars are sturdy,
and the lock is custom made.
It's go time, Gondo.
Yes, sir.
Ugh! I-I'm dying!
Director! Director!
It's not a drill!
He's having a heart attack!
M-My heart hurts!
Oh no! It's just like the last shoot! This is bad!
His pills!
Where are his pills?
O-Over there.
Unlock the gate and only release Gondo.
He'll take care of Director Shibuya.
Miwa-san!
You fell for it!
Now we're on equal terms!
But you fought dirty!
President! What about Miwa-san?
Silence! Now's not the time to let
personal feelings get in the way.
You just have to bang Ogawa-kun.
Some sacrifices are inevitable
for the success of our operation.
Gimme a break!
Oh, Ujiki, it seems you understand
where this is going.
We'll have to answer appropriately, then!
Miwa-san!
Chief! If we don't do something, Miwa-san...
Don't falter! Shibuya is impotent!
He won't be able to rape Miwa!
No!
You shouldn't underestimate the director.
Director Shibuya has a secret weapon
that lets him violate a woman
without even laying a finger on her.
That sounds nice.
Hey, won't you please teach me your trick too, Director Shibuya?
There's nothing nice about it!
He uses an arousal technique to push women
into continuous orgasms,
eventually breaking their sanity
and driving them mad.
It's a frightening technique!
So you're saying he can make
an orgasm last forever?
Then Miwa-san will...
I, arousal artist Shibuya Shozo,
will awaken your whore's blood!
Miwa-san!
Junpei-kun, don't worry about me.
Enjoy saying that while you still can.
Awaken, whorish blood!
Miwa-san!
Ow!
Wh-What was that?
My suggestion beam was deflected!
That's it! Now's your chance, Koganei!
Quick, bang her! Pierce her!
No! Koganei-kun, you can only look at me now! You can only love me!
All right.
Here I go.
Junpei-kun...
What are you waiting for, Koganei?!
I-I can't do it.
S-So cruel!
This is no ordinary girl. Normally, she'd have fallen completely under my spell by now!
Wh-What's going on?
Masako-san...
Masako-san!
Shit! I accidentally cast it on Gondo!
Masako-san...
No! Get away from me!
Ogawa-san, watch out!
Koganei! Fucking move it!
Give my Masako-san back!
No way! I'm not going anywhere!
If you don't move,
then I'll make you!
Holy crackers! It melted the iron!
Shit!
Wait, Koganei! Can't you see it?
The stuff of legends—the red thread!
Masako-san...
No! Stop it!
What are you doing?
Looks like it's going to be the first real fuck
I've seen in a long time!
What's happening to me?
I used to reject men firmly for so long,
but now I seem to be losing strength.
Gondo, you're dead!
Is this how you repay my kindness?!
Director, it's okay now.
I know you've been extremely careful to avoid triggering my traumatic childhood experience.
In the mountains of Senba,
there is a raccoon
A hunter shot it with a gun
He cooked it, then roasted it and ate it
He covered it with leaves from a tree...
What's this gentle, nostalgic feeling that strikes me right in the heart?
That's it! It's love! It's love!
Ogawa-kun, you kids taught me something. It's love!
Love is the necessary ingredient of real sex!
M-Miwa-san!
Miwa-san! Are you okay?
Miwa-san...
Y-You feel great.
What are you doing?
Miwa-san, you're awake?
Thank God! I was so worried about you!
Then how about you take your thing away from me!
For crying out loud! I let my guard down for a second, and this is what happens!
You goddamn horny hard-on pervert!
Ah... No, wait!
I-It's not what you think!
And it was this video that brought the two of them together.
Even rewatching it now
still moves me deeply.
Ogawa Masako's mother was my Madonna
when I was just an assistant director.
I finally was able to make good
on my promise to her.
That's how it felt to me.
In the end, that guerrilla AV
became a major hit.
Wakaba Miwa
And as a result of it,
Gondo-san and Ogawa-san got married.
Wakaba Miwa
I've never been to a wedding before.
I wonder if Miwa-san and I will also end up married one day, heh.
Koganei Junpei
Christ, Koganei!
There's a time and a place
to get hard, you numbskull!
Asphalt, the lonely building
Standing frozen in the familiar city
Pushed by the flow of time
It's not so bad to be alive
But I don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
Tired of looking at a crowd of masks
At the terminal, I walk down the concourse
It's almost
5 o'clock PM
I can escape from my working time
But there's no way out of the puzzling days
I'm alone, heading toward tomorrow
Just a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to reality!
I don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
It's a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to...
A puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to reality!
Original subtitles
Erobeat
TLC & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
anonymous
Paul Geromini
Encoding
anonymous