Stop
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh!
Scene    Cut
I met you at a party
Welcome My Sweet Cat wo-o-oh!
Bou
ken
shi
A fairy in jeans
te
I chased you to the motor pool, "Let me walk you home"
mo
i
koro
Putting my ulterior motives on the side seat
A Good Time for an Adventure
Whoa, but the radio is giving me bad news
Okizari Fansubs presents
My mood is sold out, you're only joking
Switch on my heart, it's all right!
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh...
.Protagonist
Koganei Junpei
I'm living my youth to the fullest, aiming to become a world-famous film director one day!
.Protagonist
Koganei Junpei
Are you ready for this second adventure of Koganei Junpei?
Start!
Youth! The Burning Start of Filming
Junpei-kun, let's swim!
Fine by me!
Junpei-kun...
Miwa-san...
Hurry!
I think we're safe now.
Lucky!
Wanna have some fun together in the cabin?
So you're in the mood for another round?
Just a dream?
That fucking shark! Why'd he come along just as things were getting good?!
Moron. Moron.
Apollo Productions Ltd
Good morning!
Ribbit, ribbit.
Oh, crap.
Chief! It's finished!
.Apollo Productions President
Ujiki Masami
Shut up! It's still morning!
I'm just a little strung out.
Don't mind me.
So?
The script for our next film!
A script, huh?
Chief, what's wrong?
Koganei, we're putting it on hold.
What?! On hold?!
I chased after rabbits on that mountain
But why are we putting it on-
We've got no money for it!
N-No way.
But didn't we make a ton on the last one?
All the profits went to paying off our debt.
Apollo Productions Ltd
.Apollo Productions Director
Wakaba Miwa
Apollo Productions Ltd
So what are we gonna do now?!
That's what I'm thinking about,
as the president!
Oh man, so that all-nighter was for nothing?
Title: Holy Angel's Temptation
Screenplay by Koganei Junpei
Junpei, it looks like you'd better start thinking about your future.
No way! To hear that from you...
Good morning! Hi, everyone!
Chief? Chief, please use this.
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
It's not much, but it's all I have.
A-Awesome. Lucky!
I wish it were that simple,
but I can't accept it.
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Savings Account
Passbook
Sukeroku Bank
Chief!
Miwa, I appreciate the gesture,
but no thanks.
But...
Don't worry.
Apollo Productions won't go under so easily.
But do you have funds for the next project?
We do!
You're lying!
Everyone, gather round!
Friends. As you're well aware,
Apollo Productions is facing a serious crisis.
I'm going to need your full support
if we're to get through this.
Our support? What sort of support?
To put it simply, we'll all work part time to raise the funds.
What?! Part time?!
HOST CLUB
HERCULES
Ta-da!
You're a cute one.
H-Hey, stop! Please stop! Hey!
Somebody!
HERCULES
Welcome, Miss.
Take care of the car.
Actress
Mina Yoshiko
Yes!
Go! Yeah!
Go! Go!
Welcome, Miss. Let me help you.
So sexy.
Go! Go!
I'm sorry it's not much...
Thanks.
Stop! I'm getting too excited!
Like this.
You really are a funny boy.
I'm Koganei Junpei.
Miss, you're the actress
Mina Yoshiko, aren't you?
Lucky!
I've seen all of your movies!
I had no idea I had fans among college students. I'm flattered.
I'm not in college.
I'm training to be a film director.
You're a director wannabe?
I like you.
Want to dance?
Working at a host club to raise money.
What a fall from grace!
I'm not complaining.
Because you got to meet Mina Yoshiko?
Bingo! Correct!
Lucky!
I got her kerchief and business card.
And she promised to introduce me
to her film industry friends.
It's just courtesy, you dumbass.
Hang on, Chief!
I know it's for work, but that's no excuse to drink yourself stupid.
Piss off! You think I can do
this sort of thing sober?
I won't let Apollo go down,
even if I have to drink myself into oblivion.
If it's for our precious company,
that everyone worked so hard for...
I'm sorry.
Wow, capital! Miwa-san...
Junpei-kun, how was your first day on the job?
I hope you like this midnight dinner.
I'm starting to plan our next film,
using your scenario as a base.
My scenario, huh?
Being a director is about writing scenarios.
I'll introduce you to my friends
in the film industry.
That's it!
Where was it?
Not here.
Okay! I'll fix this up and
send it to Mina Yoshiko.
Take Me to the Sea
Scenario by Koganei Junpei
Okay! Time to double down on this!
Flying out into the world, Koganei Junpei!
I'll talk business with Coppola.
I'll shake hands with Spielberg!
And drink sake with Lucas!
Yeah, I wish.
Three million! No, two would be enough. If only...
But that's...
I see. No good? Thought so.
How should I introduce you?
I'm Koganei Junpei. I called yesterday.
Please wait just a moment.
Unfortunately, Madam is at her villa in Izu.
Oh, I see. Then, will you give this to her when she's back?
Most certainly.
Thanks!
Yahoo!
HOST CLUB
HERCULES
Go!
Go, go!
What are you doing? Stop!
Whoa! Ouch...
Let go of me! That hurts!
She's got a cute ass.
Shit!
Stop it!
You little punk.
Get him!
Motherfucker!
Shit, it's the cops!
Fuck.
You'll regret it!
Are you okay?
More importantly, are you okay?
Hey! Hang on!
Mr. Superman!
Idol singer
Mikami Shoko
Oh shit! Why am I in someone's room?!
No... Pervert...
I gotta go!
Wait, though...
This certainly is my own room.
Why, then...
Morning.
It's you!
It was a real pain dragging you home
when you were dead drunk.
Don't tell me you did that?
You really don't remember?
Really.
Not even what you did to me?
"What I did to you"?
Don't tell me I've done
the unthinkable to you?!
Oh shit...
No way!
It was my first time.
If I get pregnant, what will you do?
I... I was drunk,
so I don't remember.
Just kidding.
Well then.
By the way, are you close to Mina Yoshiko?
Why do you ask?
Well, you even have her number.
Not really. We just talked once at work.
Did you know she was married to the grand fromage film director, Shibuya Shozo?
Huh? Shibuya Shozo?
They even had a child, I think.
Oh? So she's a single divorcee, then?
But right now, she's the mistress
of Nanto Conglomerate's president.
Oh, so that's how it is?
Nanto Daigo and Mina Yoshiko, huh?
Hey, wanna have lunch?
Oh, so you're an aspiring film director?
Guess so.
But it's not easy.
But you're charging straight
at your goal. That's impressive!
By the way, what's your name?
Shoko. Mikami Shoko.
Nice to meet you, Koganei-kun.
Huh? How'd you know my name?
I saw your business card.
Yikes! I need to be somewhere!
Um, hey...
Well, bye!
Shoko-san, huh?
She's like a good fairy.
Junpei-kun?
M-Miwa-san!
Since when are you friends
with the idol singer Mikami Shoko?
Idol singer? Her?
That's right, even if she's
a bit past her prime.
So you rescued Mikami Shoko?
And then I woke up at my apartment.
So that's where she spent the night, huh?
B-But nothing happened between us!
I'm not sure what I'm supposed to think.
Uh, p-please believe me!
I-I only have you on my mind!
Well, I guess I'll believe you.
Lucky!
Huh? You want me to star?
Co-starring with Takamura Toru and me.
My manager will contact you for details.
I look forward to it.
Junpei! Mina Yoshiko called.
She wanted you to meet some producer.
Hey, Junpei, cut out the solo act.
You're defecting to Mina Yoshiko?
I'd never do that!
We're just a stepping-stone to you?
Now that's going too far!
Junpei.
We'd understand if you quit Apollo Productions.
Not you too, Chief!
Excuse me.
What you did was a major slap
in the face of Apollo Productions.
That's why I'm going
to turn down Mina's offer!
You'd let such a great chance slip?
I think an offer like that
comes once in a lifetime.
They're all grumbling now,
but they'll see you off with a smile.
What are you talking about?
I'll never leave Apollo Productions!
You shouldn't have any reservations because of me.
In this trade, everyone hopes to make it big
one day and move on to the major leagues.
That thought never even crossed my mind.
You should go after your dreams
without hesitation, Junpei-kun.
But I love you, Miwa-san.
And I want to keep working
with you forever!
What do you think you're saying?
Miwa-san!
I'm serious.
But you never let me see your true self,
only the mask that you choose to wear!
But I'm not...
Then show how you truly feel!
Junpei-kun...
I'm gonna go meet Mina Yoshiko.
Don't go! You'll regret it!
I'll be fine.
You're turning it down?
Yes.
But Ujiki-chan said
I can have you all to myself.
He did?
Oh, and for this next film, I'm planning to hire everyone from Apollo Productions as staff.
Are you serious?
In return, I'll finance the next Apollo Productions flick.
Ujiki-chan and I go back a long way.
He may be making TV shows now, but he used to be an outstanding assistant director.
I'm very grateful for the opportunity.
Don't thank me yet.
I still don't know what terms
my boss will lay down to finance it.
We're talking about Nanto Daigo, right?
Yes. So you already know?
This whole Apollo affair hinges on
getting Nanto Daigo's permission.
Come with me.
O-Okay...
Don't be ridiculous.
You really think you can pull in
young viewers with that?
Veteran or not, Director Shibuya is just not about that.
So you're saying he's too old-fashioned?
Exactly.
Nanto Conglomerate President
Nanto Daigo
Your times have passed.
Our audience is eager to move on.
It doesn't have to be that way!
To boost appeal for younger audiences,
we'll cast idol singer Mikami Shoko in the lead.
We'll also staff it with young people
who are passionate about filmmaking.
You still don't get it?
You no longer have the sex appeal
to attract young male viewers.
I don't know how you can be
sure of that so easily.
So you're saying that you, Mina Yoshiko, can still make a young man get hard?
I do.
Then prove it to me.
If you manage to convince me, I'll fund it.
Very well.
You'll see this young man right here
get hard because of me.
No way!
Very well. Can't wait to see you try.
Keep your eyes on me.
Okay...
What's wrong?
He's not aroused in the slightest!
I was just warming up.
Don't rush me!
Oh?
See? Well?
How's this?
Junpei-kun, what's wrong with you?
I'm truly touched by you undressing for me,
but I'm not really feeling it down there.
I understand. It only appealed to the noble part of your soul.
That means you can perceive me
as more than just a sexual object.
You need to stop fooling yourself.
You simply no longer have any appeal.
You're wrong, Nanto-san!
Mina is very sexy and alluring!
She's plenty appealing!
Really? Why can't you get hard, then?
That's because... something's missing.
I think something is missing.
Something...
What are you doing?
There! Now everyone in the opposite building can see Mina Yoshiko nude!
Are you trying to embarrass me?
You won't get away with it!
Come on! Give them all a good long look of your body.
Hey! Stop that!
That's it, please watch.
Stop it!
Go! Go!
H-Hey! Are you out of your mind?
No! What are you doing? Stop it!
Windowsill sex is an instant arouser!
No!
N-No...
His erection is strong enough
to support Yoshiko's entire body!
What amazing power!
Enough! You've convinced me!
This natural, off-the-screen form of yours is still mesmerizing.
Your rod also has tremendous power.
I lose. I'll give you 1.5 billion to make this movie.
Darling!
Mina-san!
Junpei-kun, thank you!
I think I also ought to thank you.
I've been impotent for five years, but seeing Yoshiko just now, it sprang back to life! See?
See? Look!
Whoa! What a hard-on!
Oh my! That's wonderful, darling!
Yoshiko!
Hurry up!
I'll leave you kids alone.
Oh, that's nice!
Oh, darling!
Our fortunes are changing.
Now things are getting interesting!
Whoa!
Moron. Moron. Moron!
What the hell?
This new big-budget movie,
Who Saw the Tears?,
"Who Saw the Tears?" Production Presentation
will star Mikami Shoko and co-star
Mina Yoshiko and Takamura Toru.
"Who Saw the Tears?" Production Presentation
With the renowned Shibuya Shozo in the director's seat,
and the full cooperation of Apollo Productions,
filming will begin in the summer.
Miwa-san was asked to help
Director Shibuya with the storyboards,
and I was selected as the third assistant.
And here's to our future hit! Cheers!
Cheers!
Chief Asst. Director
Gondo
Who would've thought Shibuya Shozo would cast a fading idol in his film?
And also complement it with a hag and a newbie. It's sad, right?
How dare they say that!
Just let it slide.
We're totally out of place here, aren't we?
That's true.
Hey, Koganei-kun.
I'm Shibuya Shozo's chief of staff, Gondo.
I'm Nakajima, the first assistant.
This is my first time doing actual cinema,
so please take care of me.
It was rash of Shibuya to appoint
a complete rookie as his third assistant.
It took me eight years to get there.
I see...
The path of an assistant director is thorny.
Just a little advice as your superior:
real films and porn have nothing in common!
B-But I never...
Well, I hope we get along.
Junpei-kun!
What's wrong? You still haven't said a word.
How can I work in that environment?
I don't even know the basics of filmmaking.
I shouldn't have come!
Don't worry.
I know you're perfectly capable.
If you sprint right out of the gate,
you'll be gasping for air in no time.
Just give them a taste of your talent.
Miwa-san...
Let's show those jerks just what we AV people are made of!
Be strong. You're a man, right?
Yes.
Knack Films Studio
And so, the filming began for "Who Saw the Tears?"
The story is about a female teacher and her daughter, Hitomi.
Film Director
Shibuya Shozo
It's a tale of love and hatred.
Okay, let's do a serious take now.
Ready? Action!
Hey, cutie. Wanna play with us?
How 'bout you take off your panties?
I should have known you were like this.
No, no! That's not how you take them off!
There's no feeling in it!
No girl's shyness!
But isn't Hitomi acting tough,
pretending she's ready to undress?
Yes, but she's only pretending to be okay with it.
Come on. One more take!
Action!
Cut! No, that's no good!
No, no!
No, not that! Cut! Cut!
Let's take a coffee break, everyone.
Wanna go to my room?
Yes, but...
Come on. You need a break.
Here. Just relax.
Look, think of this as the actual filming.
No!
Come on.
Miwa's plan worked.
The awkwardness of her first time
with another woman helped Shoko-chan
put on a convincing act.
You're adorable, Shoko-chan.
You know that?
Try to remember this feeling.
Ready. Action!
Fucking brat!
Who do you think you are?!
Who are you calling a brat?!
Cut, cut, cut, cut!
Oops, did I accidentally flash it?
That was great, just great! Okay! Good!
It was so much better when you put your feelings into it!
You sure are a sweet little thing.
That was really great! Okay! Good!
Knack Films Studio
Next day, we started shooting the scene of the students assaulting Hitomi's mother at school.
Ready... Action!
No!
No...
All right, time to get into action!
So how was it?
You liked it, didn't you?
Let's stop this.
Did I do something?
You really don't get it?
You're just too small.
I can't act convincingly scared of that.
Huh? Did you mean my...
Huh, my willy? Shit!
Mina Yoshiko-san nominated me,
Koganei Junpei,
to replace Toru Takamura as the lead,
so it's gonna get real now!
Oh, no!
Not there!
Cut!
Huh? Oops...
HOSPITAL
How's Director Shibuya?
He had a stroke.
He'll need to rest for a while.
You must find a deputy director to finish the film.
Shoko. Do your best until the end.
I will.
By the way, Miwa-kun...
Yes?
Would you be so kind
and replace me as the director?
Me?
Yeah.
Because you helped me
with the storyboards,
you understand my vision better than anyone else.
Please, take care of it.
But...
A director, whether of an adult video
or a major motion picture,
must be able to manage the staff,
give accurate acting instructions to the cast,
and have passion for creating the film.
Loving the work you do
is what matters the most!
You have that in you, Miwa-san.
Miwa-san, please do it!
I agree. Please help us!
Miwa-san!
Director Shibuya, I'll do my best.
Thank you.
We're right behind you.
Don't give up, Miwa.
Okay!
Good.
Show them what an AV director is made of.
Knack Films Studio
Shit!
He bypassed me, his chief assistant,
and appointed some amateur porn director!
Well, Gondo-san, she still can't film anything without our help.
Uh... Y-Yeah!
Let's just see her try!
Porn director? Don't make me laugh!
Bad news, people!
A boycott?
Both the cameraman and
the chief assistant protested.
How did it come to this?
I'll go beg them not to quit the project!
Please, gentlemen, help us finish the movie!
We need you.
No fucking way!
Gondo-san!
Why did they send you?
Why won't "director" Wakaba Miwa face me personally? Huh?
That's just protocol.
At a film studio, if you don't follow protocol,
everyone will turn their back on you!
You'd better fucking remember that,
you greenhorn!
Please help us.
Gondo-san, we need your cooperation.
I'm begging you.
Y-You jerks! You're still not satisfied?!
Wh-What?
You're just gutless and talentless cowards!
Junpei-kun!
That little shit...
Now you've done it.
Junpei-kun!
Asshole!
Let go!
Sto...
Stop it!
Junpei, enough!
Miwa, if they won't cooperate, forget them. We'll shoot that movie ourselves.
I'll be your chief assistant.
Director, we can do it.
This scene is the film's climax.
The college students
are about to violate Hitomi.
That's when her mother, Mina-san, the teacher, rushes in to save her.
She's just a porn director,
Actor
Takamura Toru
yet she acts like a big shot.
D-Damn it all... She just stole the spotlight from me, Takamura Toru!
J-Just you watch, wench!
We'll make a total mess of this movie!
Hey, guys, I'll let'cha guys in
on a little secret.
Get closer.
Bang Shoko?!
Shh! Don't let everyone hear you.
During the actual take,
I'll get my thing into Shoko for real!
Let's shoot!
Ready!
Action!
No! Stop!
What are you doing?
No. Stop...
You're too loud.
My pan-
What are you doing?
You boys. What are you doing?
Shaddup! I'm gonna fuck her!
Stop this now!
Fuck off!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Stop struggling!
No!
Stop-
Th-That feels nice...
Fucking hell!
Wh-What the fuck?
D'you like it?
You fucking grandma!
Let go! Let go of it!
D-Drop it, you!
There.
How's this?
Go, go, go!
This is the terrifying Ashura for you!
Well?
You like it?
To save my beloved daughter,
I'd even become a vampire if I had to.
Mother...
Hitomi.
Mother!
Hitomi!
Cut!
Thanks to the tireless efforts of Miwa-san and the Apollo Productions staff,
we finished filming.
Released during the New Year season, the movie was a big hit,
Who Saw the Tears?
largely because Miwa-san substituted
as director for Shibuya.
It also shot Shoko-chan back to stardom,
and everything turned out fine.
Congratulations.
And with that, our Apollo Productions now deals in major motion pictures too.
Thanks to the financial support of Mina Yoshiko-san here.
Thank you, everyone.
The movie topped the list
of New Year releases.
Thanks to that, Mikami Shoko's
popularity has risen dramatically.
I'd like to think that with that,
we made things right with my Shoko.
The truth is, Shoko is my real daughter
with Director Shibuya.
We divorced when she was in grade school,
so we sent her to a fine arts boarding school.
So that's how it is?
Good thing nothing happened between you two, Junpei-kun.
I will also take this opportunity to retire from acting and become a producer.
I look forward to working with you.
She's retiring?
What a waste!
Then that makes Mikami Shoko
the shadow savior of Apollo Productions?
Seems so.
Then Junpei-kun is my prince.
Just kidding!
It feels so chilly and refreshing!
You've let your true feelings show.
Let's race, Miwa-san!
Remember, I'll always be by your side!
What was that? What side?
I can be so cheesy sometimes!
Oh geez! Where are you hiding now? Come on!
And so, my second adventure was also a crazy circus!
And with that, everyone...
have a nice day!
Asphalt, the lonely building
Standing frozen in the familiar city
Pushed by the flow of time
It's not so bad to be alive
But I just don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
Tired of looking at the crowd of masks
At the terminal, I walk down the concourse
It's almost
5 o'clock PM
I can escape from my working time
But there's no way out of the puzzling days
I'm alone, heading toward tomorrow
Just a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to reality!
I just don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
It's a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to...
A puzzle that I have to piece together
Original subtitles
Erobeat
TLC & Timing
Perevodildo
Editing, & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
anonymous, Paul Geromini
Encoding
anonymous
Next Episode
Hello! Junpei here!
How did you like my first movie?
Well then! In the next episode of
A Good Time for an Adventure...
A Good Time for an Adventure
Returning to the AV world again,
Miwa and I scouted out a certain girl.
But actually, it turns out
she's Director Shibuya's secretary!
What the hell, Junpei?
You're gonna cast my secretary in a porno?
I won't allow it!
I'll never allow it.
Why does it have to be you?!
You goddamn weasel!
Why do you get all the action?!
Fine. I'll remember this.
That said, Director Shibuya seems really delighted and moved by that.
And that's the craziest part!
Furthermore, that secretary
was kidnapped and held captive just before we were supposed to start filming.
When Junpei learns about this,
he rushes to save her,
but instead he gets beaten to a pulp
and has to retreat.
Really, Junpei-kun, how sloppy can you be?
I-I can't help it, Miwa-san.
I'm just that weak.
Junpei-kun, don't lose heart.
We have an Unopened Locker of our own.
A forbidden locker?
Next time on A Good Time for an Adventure,
episode three,
"Apollo Guerrilla Film Crew Arrives!"
Dangerous guerrilla filming and a series of mishaps!
Naturally, it's also full of sex
and 120% more fun!
Don't miss it, guys!
Apollo Guerrilla
Film Crew Arrives!
A Good Time for an Adventure
Episode Three
Coming Soon
Don't miss it, guys!
Look forward to it  !!