Stop
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh!
Scene    Cut
I met you at a party
Welcome My Sweet Cat wo-o-oh!
Bou
ken
shi
A fairy in jeans
te
I chased you to the motor pool, "Let me walk you home"
mo
i
koro
Putting my ulterior motives on the side seat
A Good Time for an Adventure
Whoa, but the radio is giving me bad news
Okizari Fansubs presents
My mood is sold out, you're only joking
Switch on my heart, it's all right!
Welcome My Sexy Cat wo-o-oh!
Mischievous shining eyes
Welcome My Sweet Cat wo-o-oh!
You're just my type
Rambling exchanges on the bay road
"Please drop me off by 12:00," you whisper
I pretend not to hear you, it's a comedy
I want you to take off your watch
You're like a machine gun, shooting tricks
So this is the place?
Welcome My Sexy Cat
Rainbow Mansion 5055.
It's like the F.G. page of "Marie Claire"
Welcome My Sweet Cat wo-o-oh!
Number 19! I'm asking you out
Whoa, time's up, the signal tells us
First Challenge !!
Into the World of Adult Films !!
It's just a little while longer until 12:00
Apollo Productions Ltd
Switch off the radio, it's all right
So I'm finally here.
You flipping moron!
College is so yesterday. Just quit it.
It's the era of self-made men!
Come work for me!
We're currently seeking new staff.
Working in porn is great, man.
You'll get to see them for free, you know.
Ishikawa-senpai sounded
so confident and assertive.
But to think I ditched college entrance exams to work at a porn video company...
If my mom heard about that, she'd probably get mad.
Oh no! Can I really? Can I?
This is so lewd!
What became of my innocent dream to become a world famous filmmaker, once so strong?!
I'd talk business with Coppola.
Shake hands with Spielberg!
Share a drink with Lucas!
My dream was to make movies
together with all those geniuses!
Guess I'll go home.
Oh! Sexy!
S-Sorry!
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Beautiful...
Y-Your papers...
Apollo Productions Co., Ltd
U-Um...
Thanks!
Apollo Productions? But that's Ishikawa's porn film company.
Is that girl a porn star? No way.
Here I am again.
No path in life is set in stone!
Even if it's a winding, thorny road...
Koganei Junpei, age 19!
Protagonist
Koganei Junpei
It's a good time for an adventure!
Oh?
N-No, I'm...
Oh, I see. You're Koganei-san, here for the interview, right?
H-How did you know?
Come on in.
Ishikawa-san told me a lot about you.
"A lot"?
Wow, you've got quite a clean place.
All the company staff are away now,
but they should be back soon.
R-Right, thanks.
No bra!
Is something the matter?
Uh? No, I mean... Pardon my curiosity, but who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Wakaba Miwa.
Apollo Planning & Director
Wakaba Miwa
I'm this company's exclusive porn star.
That means...
this sweet looking girl...
does this on camera...
and that...
It can't be!
A-And from that angle too!
No more!
Junpei-san! You're too good!
Is something wrong?
You're covered in sweat.
N-No! It's nothing.
Don't worry about me.
Hey, Koganei-san, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
Hey, Koganei-san, are you a virgin?
Aw, come on. Gimme a break.
So you're not?
No, it's more like... Yes.
Does it show that much? I thought so.
What are you doing, Wakaba-san?
Boys mustn't be shy.
Now, what do we have here?
Th-This is going too far too quick!
Wow, he's a big boy.
But he's pretty shy. How cute!
N-No, that's not right! Just let me roll it up.
It's a pseudo-phimosis!
See? See?
You're a strange guy.
Well...
I'm glad you liked it.
You know, I'm a very bad girl.
I can't hold back anymore!
Miwa-san!
Please accept my love!
That's just your dick speaking!
Miwa-san, I'm not afraid of the responsibility!
No! You just came here
for an interview, didn't you?
Doesn't matter! I don't care about that stupid interview!
Cut!
"C-Cut?"
'sup, Koganei!
I-Ishikawa-senpai?!
What's going on?
What's going on? What's going on?!
This is your interview. This is the way we haze newcomers at Apollo.
A-An interview? Is that all?
I suppose so.
What do you think, Chief?
I'm sure he'll make a good costar.
What do you say? Did you like it?
Koganei, let me introduce you.
This is the company president, Ujiki-san.
Apollo Productions President
Ujiki Masami
And the cameraman, Ujitani-san.
Cameraman
Ujitani
You're a godsend.
We're always short on staff.
Our lighting designer, Tanaka-san.
Lighting Designer
Tanaka
Nice to meet you, Foreskin-chan.
W-Wait a minute!
I'm the video engineer, Ishikawa.
Video Engineer
Ishikawa
And this is our prodigy director,
Wakaba Miwa-chan.
D-Director?
Hello and welcome to Apollo Productions.
N-No way!
I guess we could try him out.
You pass!
Koganei, I'm proud of you.
W-Wait just a minute!
Don't just make the decision for me after dumping this joke of an interview on me!
This wasn't what you promised me!
I didn't come here to audition as a porn actor!
But you seemed pretty into it just now.
Ah, no...
That was that, and this...
I take that as a "yes."
Just don't embarrass me.
You know, for the newcomers,
a lot of this stuff is brand new to them.
Meanwhile, we'll get
the camera rolling, all right?
You're getting too ahead of yourself!
Even I have a sense of honor!
I came from a small village in the north,
determined to become a world-class filmmaker while holding my head high!
How am I supposed to look my family and friends in the eyes
after doing full frontal in a porn video?
They had such high hopes for me!
You're already doing it!
My bad.
You! The snot-faced boy!
Don't you look down on us!
I'll have you know that porn videos
are the ultimate martial art of the senses!
It's not some half-baked student experiment or a bland, lifeless commercial flick!
I can't breathe!
Ch-Chief, easy, easy.
It's eat or be eaten!
Anyone who looks down on porn has no right
to make lofty claims about cinema!
Get out!
D-Don't mind if I do!
Hey! Koganei!
Can't you move it, jackass?
Boss Kanekura!
Ujiki, I came for your answer.
I'm sure you know what I mean.
Unscrupulous Loan Shark
Kanekura
No, just 20 more days...
No! Please give us two more weeks!
I'll have your interest by then!
I didn't come here to listen to excuses!
It's either to smash Apollo
or settle it the other way. You choose.
Well, I...
Do it!
Right.
Sure.
Wait!
If you do that, we won't be able to film!
Miwa-chan!
No! No!
I'd hate to scare you.
Got it, Ujiki? It's in your hands.
Yes! Just give me two weeks!
Shut up!
Do it!
A love hotel?
Please don't make me say it twice.
To put it bluntly...
I wanna do it with you.
N-No way! This is all so sudden!
A-Are you sure?
Come.
O-Oh, no, Miwa-san!
Not in public!
This isn't gonna end well!
I don't mind being watched.
Are you sure you want to do it with me?
We're just a man and woman having sex.
We don't need an excuse.
W-Wow. So this is what it looks like?
Don't stare at it like that.
Just do it already.
You're right.
At times like these, we must shrug off our insecurities and shame.
Miwa-san!
Ah, just a dream?
But what a vivid dream it was!
She had such an innocent look
at the interview yesterday,
but she didn't even blush
at the sight of my dick.
I guess she's used to it.
She's probably got a boyfriend,
but maybe she'll still let me ravish her
if I ask for it really hard.
Ah! My right hand!
Being young sucks!
Dammit!
I wanna fuck Miwa-san!
I wanna fuck her!
Ah, that's better.
Y-Yes? It's open! Come in!
Hello!
Miwa... Director Miwa!
Declaring your aspirations so loudly is a nuisance to your neighbors.
Ishikawa-san gave me a map
to where you live.
He's just really pushy.
And here I was about to give up on you.
W-Wait just a minute!
T-To what do I owe
the pleasure of your visit?
You want to bang me, don't you?
Those gangsters yesterday must've scared you.
I suppose....
That's not an unusual occurrence in our line of work.
Don't hold back. Eat up, Koganei-kun.
No, i-it's just that I'm so honored
to go on a date with you, Director,
b-but I'm not sure about being in a porno.
We're just out, eating hamburgers, is all.
I thought I had studied a little bit about film,
although it was only 8mm films
at a rural film club.
I would love to be on the Apollo staff.
I-I'll do anything to help you, Director!
You say you'll do anything for me.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious!
Then I'd like you to appear in my next film.
You see, Apollo Productions will probably go under if our next project fails.
Unlike mainstream cinema, indie films constantly struggle with tight budgets.
With budgets and talent.
In order to really communicate a moving experience,
planning, execution,
and acting must be good.
And more than anything, we need to come up
with new characters constantly.
I'm sorry. I should probably stop complaining.
I shouldn't be telling you this,
but when we were really strapped for cash,
the Chief went to the man called
"The Shadow King of the Industry."
And that's how he ended up
in debt to Kanekura.
So now, he can buy all our new works for cheap, and he gets to meddle with production too.
And I have to...
He tried to get to you?
Yes. That lecherous old fart
is pressuring our president to make a secret film for him, starring him and me.
N-No way!
This time, he was counting
on our new project, "Love Juice Angel,"
starring Shinohara Chie,
to be our next big hit and help pay off the debt to Kanekura before he comes to collect.
Wow! The Shinohara Chie?
Yes. She agreed to be paid afterward,
but in exchange, we gotta find her a costar to her liking.
When I saw you, it hit me hard
that you'd fit that role perfectly.
It's hitting me hard too.
I'm a huge fan!
If it'll save you from your predicament,
I will bang Chie-san with all my might!
Koganei-kun?
Miwa-san, could you stop calling me "Koganei-kun"?
You can just call me Junpei.
W-Walking like this m-makes us
look like lovers, doesn't it?
Then let's go somewhere lovers go.
Y-You mean this hotel?
Yup. To scope out the location.
We're going in?
Of course we are.
This next film mostly takes place in a love hotel.
Awesome.
This room fits my image perfectly.
Let's turn on the video.
M-Miwa-san...
Miwa-san, I can't hold back anymore!
W-We can't! A director mustn't get involved with an assistant!
Then let's get involved as man and woman!
N-No! Stop!
Ah, help me!
What a great view, babe.
I can totally see all the dirty stuff.
There's no point in resisting!
It was your idea to come here,
so it's all consensual!
P-Please stop! I had no idea
you were that kind of person!
It was your own fault for going
to this kind of place with a guy, babe.
You had it coming all along!
Th-That's not what I had in mind!
I'll fuck you up!
Hey, are you having that much fun
mumbling to the video?
Well, since we're already here,
let's make use of the facilities.
Will you put this on?
Miwa-san, are you...
Your perception is too dull if you only realized it now. Call me "Queen"!
Cry more!
You are my dog !
I stooped too low!
What's wrong?
Come on. Hurry.
Are we really gonna do this?
Ah! Miwa-san, untie me!
No can do.
Miwa-san! Do you really
distrust me so much?
I really do.
Weren't you the guy screaming from inside his apartment that he wanted to bang me?
I already paid for the room, so I might as well use the shower, right?
This is torture!
Porn Star
Shinohara Chie
Shinohara-san.
We did it, Junpei-kun!
She liked the script, and she liked you!
R-Really?
But I'm feeling kinda strung out.
Don't worry.
When push comes to shove, you're the type
who can transform completely to fit the role.
Next, let's move on to the flashback scene!
Um, are we doing it for real in this take?
I was just thinking that maybe
we can't do it without love involved.
What's wrong, Junpei-kun?
You can't get hard?
N-No...
Let me see.
You've nothing to worry about!
Th-That's not what I meant!
J-Junpei-kun?
I can't have sex with another woman
while the girl I like is watching!
But I couldn't bring myself to say it.
I guess she will end up...
No! Stop!
Okay, here we go. Start the VTR.
The camera's rolling.
Scene    Cut
5...
4...
3...
2...
I've gotta pee!
What's his problem?
He's too slow!
Junpei! What'cha doing in there?
Wh-What was that?!
You're calling from where?!
I-I'm sorry.
I just couldn't...
How is your "Sorry" going to help?!
Come back here at once!
What's wrong?!
I-I'm sorry... Is Miwa-san there?
No, don't put her on the line.
You're in love with Director Wakaba?
And you can't give up your virginity
in front of the woman you love?!
Wake up, you dumdum!
Fuck my life.
Junpei-kun?
M-Miwa-san?
Thank you. I'm flattered.
But you see, we've already started filming.
You can't undo the work of all these people.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
Oh no, it's not your fault.
But it's clear to me now.
I misjudged you.
Where are you right now?
P-Phone booth at the intersection with Street Two.
Stay there.
What a pathetic wimp!
I had no idea he was like that.
Director, what should we do?
Bring him back, of course!
Just be gentle with him, okay?
He's your future husband, after all.
Gimme a break!
It's not the time for jokes!
Just a minute.
I was the one who was stood up.
Miwa-
Chie-san?
You'll catch a cold like that.
I've got clothes for you in the car.
U-Um...
Get in.
U-Um... We're going the opposite direction of the hotel.
Of course we are.
We can't get any work done today.
I'm sorry.
You even brought your director to tears.
Girls simply don't know how to handle
such a sudden and awkward confession.
What's worse, you did it when her head
was already full of her duties as director.
She's very talented.
That's why you love her.
D-Don't say it like that...
It seems like she actually
has a thing for you too.
Is that true?!
Woman's instinct.
This is my true form.
We have some personal time today.
Ch-Chie-san?
Of course, it's only a rehearsal of tomorrow.
I'll make a man out of you.
There's no director and no camera in here.
Just the two of us alone.
Ch-Chie-san!
We really shouldn't be doing this!
It's that kind of attitude that is putting Miwa-chan in a tough spot.
B-But I...
That's enough talking for tonight.
If... If you do that, I-I'll...
Come here.
O-Okay.
You're big. Wow!
You're hitting me all the way inside!
I can't hold back anymore!
That was great... Just now...
Cut!
Okay, that's good!
That was fucking intense!
See? You can do it if you want to!
Well done! Here ya go.
It's all thanks to Shinohara-san.
What a relief.
You were great.
It's a wrap! Good work, Shinohara-san.
D-Director!
Yes?
Did you get some good shots?
Yes, it was good.
I hope it wasn't awkward.
I was trying my best.
I need to do some editing now,
so I'm heading out.
Huh? Leaving already?
Leaving?
We'll take some stills
tomorrow at 9, thanks!
Director...
Shinohara Chie in
Love Juice Angel
A-And now I, Ujiki Masami, will be singing "Father and Son," with all due respect!
Shinohara Chie in
Love Juice Angel
Oh, leave it be, Chief!
That's your eighth song tonight!
Miwa-san...
Will it sell well?
Most likely. I think it will be
one of the best in Chie's filmography.
If that's the case, you could look happier.
I'm sorry. I don't feel too well.
Th-That's awful!
Ujitani-san, drink up!
Let's make some noise tonight!
Yeah, we got some great shots.
This will revive Apollo Productions for sure.
A toast to Miwa-chan.
Let's try the other one!
Hey!
What are you doing over there?!
Scram!
Hey! Wait up!
Come back here!
It's been a long time
since I've run this much.
Looks like we lost the others.
Huh? This is close to your apartment, isn't it?
Should we go back to where we last saw them?
No way. I'm too drunk to walk any further.
C-Could this be h-her way of seducing me?
Miwa-san...
She's asleep.
She's heavy!
Hey, Miwa-san, wake up, please?
You'll get a cold.
U-Um, Miwa-san?
Your panties are showing!
Miwa-san?
No!
It's your own fault for showing me
your colors like that!
No! I don't want it!
How's that, you slut?
How d'ya like this?
Fucking awesome!
At least I wish that would happen,
but I lack the balls.
Junpei-kun?
M-Miwa-san...
Morning glory
You lowlife!
Wh-What was that for?
You're the worst!
Stealing my body when I was drunk!
W-Wait just a minute!
Let go of me, you pervert!
Why won't you just listen
to me for a moment?
What are you gonna do? H-Hit me?
Mornin'.
You motherfucker.
Running off with Miwa-chan like that last night...
Good morning.
Oh, here she is.
They came to work together.
That thing on Koganei's face looks bad.
And Miwa-chan's wearing
the same clothes as yesterday.
U-Um...
D-Damn you, Koganei!
How dare you treat our poster girl like that!
I didn't do anything.
Yes, you did.
I keep telling you, I didn't!
But if I'd known you were gonna accuse me, I wish I had!
I can't believe you would claim it so brazenly!
Now I'm convinced you did it!
Hey, Koganei, are you guys still fighting?
Yeah.
Do I really look like that much of a pervert?
Well, I don't know.
When I see your face on that screen...
Oh? But that was just acting!
Was it?
Director, that's the face of someone
who's cumming for real, isn't it?
That's right.
And it's scary to think that he also looked
like that when he was on top of me.
J-Just a minute, Director!
Just hear me out once, please!
M-Miwa-san...
Senpai, I just don't understand Miwa anymore.
If this keeps up, it'll look like I really did violate her!
You really didn't do anything that night?
Of course I didn't!
Miwa-san simply jumped
to the conclusion that I did!
And why didn't you?
Y-You ask why I didn't violate her?
But that'd be so...
She does seem to hold some weird prejudices against men.
She slapped me once too.
Well, don't lose your spirit just yet.
I'll smooth things over for ya.
Senpai...
But first, take care of this.
Your senpai needs to go.
I would be happy to!
Good, good.
Thank you for helping me!
Really, you're up here, after all?
Where are the others?
Still in the studio.
And Koganei is still down in the dumps.
Ishikawa-san!
What?
Will you give Junpei-kun
a message from me, please?
I've been thinking about it, and...
I was still in my pantyhose,
and my body didn't feel any different.
So I'm worried that
I may have made a mistake.
Ah, yes. Right, I see.
Yet for some reason, whenever I see Junpei-kun,
I feel kind of awkward around him.
Besides, when I woke up, he was sleeping separately under just a sheet.
He acted like a gentleman.
And in comparison, I'm just...
Wh-What the hell?
She's already talking like he's her boyfriend! I gotta act now!
Forgive me! I was actually gonna keep quiet about this,
but seeing you like this,
I can't hold back anymore!
"Man, she was quite something!
I still remember pounding her so hard."
Th-That can't be true!
How is that possible?
You really don't remember?
He said you also enjoyed yourself a lot.
N-No way!
H-He's so dead! To think I was almost about to let it go!
Thank you. You've done well by telling me!
No matter what happens,
I'm on your side, Miwa-chan.
He's still in the studio, right?
W-Wait...
Maybe I went a little too far?
Well, if I don't go this far,
I won't stand a chance with her.
Are you sure, Senpai?
Yes, my friend, rejoice!
I cleared up the misunderstanding.
But she's actually kind of pissed now:
"Why did he take me back to his place
and not do anything to me?!"
That's what usually happens.
It is shameful to reject
the advances of a woman.
Miwa was actually after you, you dunce.
B-But she was seriously mad,
and I don't quite understand why.
You really are a nitwit.
With women, what they feel and what they show are two very different things.
She's only acting embarrassed and mad.
Actually, she's feeling the opposite!
Women sure are complicated.
Miwa-san!
Miwa-san, um, I...
I just didn't really understand how you felt up to now.
How dare you grin at me
with that radiant smile?!
You despicable man!
You even had the nerve to talk at length about how you took advantage of me, you swine!
When did I ever enjoy it?!
I don't want to see your face ever again!
U-Um, I don't really understand what you're saying.
Could it be that you still
mean the opposite thing?
What do you mean?
That you, like... That you actually want to sleep with me?
You dirty worm!
Geez, I was so naive.
I should've known
that men can't be trusted!
I really don't get women!
Who said you can buy our videos for cheap and get away with it?!
Wh-Where did all this money come from?
Thanks to Junpei and Director Miwa,
Love Juice Angel was a big success.
Did you see the look
on that scrooge's face?
Hey, Miwa-chan!
That greedy old fart, the adult film industry loan shark, was just here.
Paper: Resignation notice
Resignation?
What's this?
I'm quitting Apollo Productions today.
Why? Did someone else poach you?
No.
I was hesitant to bring personal feelings into the situation,
but I can't continue working in a company with a man I can't forgive!
Goodbye.
Thanks.
Hey... Wait!
Excuse me.
M-Miwa-san!
Wait a minute!
I'm so sorry, sir!
Move it. I'm going home.
I'm not letting you get away.
Not before we both have some good old fun.
Wh-What are you saying?
Why the hell not?
We've done it once before, didn't we?
Do you even realize what you're saying?
What harm would it do
if we did it a couple times more?
You're a monster!
Whoa there!
Surely, you don't expect to win
against a man like me?
Somebody help!
This is just right.
I'm starting to get a feel for it.
Coward!
I don't need lectures from you!
I'm gonna fuck your brains out!
No!
Miwa-san. Miwa-san?
Um... Promise not to laugh?
This feels too miserable
for me to remain hard.
I'm sorry for holding you down.
There's no way a weak-willed guy like me
could force a girl to have sex with him.
Even that night, seeing a woman
who passed out drunk,
I couldn't force myself on her.
Especially on someone I love.
Please believe me.
Junpei-kun...
Ah, that felt refreshing!
Now I can quit with no regrets.
I'll take responsibility for scaring you like that
and quit this company tomorrow.
I'll make sure you never
have to see me again.
I didn't get to know you for long,
but it was fun!
No way!
Please don't quit!
Junpei-kun!
Junpei-kun...
M-Miwa-san?
I'm sorry!
I was so blind!
Forgive me!
Miwa-san, don't cry.
So you'll forgive me?
Of course!
Don't quit!
Ouch!
That's the spirit!
Did you forget about us?
Get off me!
Hey, cut it out!
What the hell?!
C'mon, don't push!
Asphalt, the lonely building
Standing frozen in the familiar city
Pushed by the flow of time
It's not so bad to be alive
But I don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
Tired of looking at a crowd of masks
At the terminal, I walk down the concourse
It's almost
5 o'clock PM
I can escape from my working time
But there's no way out of the puzzling days
I'm alone, heading toward tomorrow
Just a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to reality!
I don't want to spend
these puzzling days faking a smile
It's a puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to...
A puzzle that I have to piece together
I have no choice but to live riskily
Never say no to reality!
Original subtitles
Erobeat
TLC
Perevodildo
Timing, Editing, & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
anonymous, Paul Geromini
Encoding
anonymous
Next Episode
The future great filmmaker
and the Apollo Productions newcomer,
I, Koganei Junpei, am ready for my next adventure!
HERCULES
HOST CLUB
Wh-What's this? The Apollo staff ends up
HERCULES
HOST CLUB
working part-time at a host club
that is struggling financially!
At the host club, Junpei-kun and others
meet former great actress Mina Yoshiko.
And when he finds out that she's the mistress
of one of the world's wealthiest men,
the president of a major consulting firm,
Junpei-kun just...
If I stop here, my manhood will be ruined.
For the sake of the company and Miwa-san,
this is the time to throw myself into attack after attack!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
With dreams and ambitions for love,
Junpei the man
sets out on an adventure!
Who Saw the Tears?
Production Presentation
An unexpected accident occurred just as filming began.
Takematsu Film Studio
Director Shibuya collapsed in the middle of filming,
and I was suddenly appointed acting director.
On top of that, the lead actress, Mikami Shoko, disliked her costar Takamura Toru,
and chose Koganei Junpei,
our Junpei-kun, for the main role!
Miwa-san and I are fired up to complete this big movie!
And then it won't be long before
I'm united with my beloved Miwa-san!
A Good Time for an Adventure,
episode two, is heating up for you!
On shelves soon. Stay tuned!
Look forward to it  !!
A Good Time for an Adventure
Episode Two
Coming Soon