Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Mercy of the god of the Sun
and the god of the Moon.
Protect us from being possessed by evil deities.
Remove from us the afflictions of death.
Stay strong, Tenku!
He has awakened.
The seal of memories has been broken.
A storm is brewing.
The coming of the Dark World
is close at hand.
The awakening of the Remnants begins.
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
Beyond an ancient gateway lies a world
mankind knows nothing about.
Now, the long period of peace is about to end.
Once again, mankind is about
to encounter this Dark World.
At the same time, the surviving dark warriors from ancient battles,
left behind on this side of the gate, the Remnants,
prepare to open the gate
connecting our two worlds
and lead their dark brethren
into our world once again.
However, there are warriors
who protect the Gateway Campus,
built on the site of the sealed gate in readiness,
known as "Guardians."
Now, unbeknownst to the populace,
the new clash between the two armies approaches.
Throbbing☆Excited★
Dangerous Siblings!
D
Hey, Yuka! Do you know
where Hazumi is? Hazumi.
Hey, it's Takumi! Do you know
where your sister went?
No. I was just about to go look for her too, Kazuma-senpai.
Come to think of it,
I saw her a little while ago, wolfing down ramen instead of working, just like Hagiwara,
I can't believe it!
She's run away from work!
What? She's gone home? You can't be serious!
Without even saying a word to her boyfriend!
Who's her boyfriend?
Beats me.
Wait, Yamashiro Kazuma!
You could stop being so formal
around me, Honda-senpai!
What's with the nasty look?
I'm not talking to you
because I particularly like it either.
So... what thing did the sophomores from the Sakura Group lug in?
What is it?!
That thing? Ah! It's a powered suit.
I'm not talking about a powered suit!
How on earth did you manage to build something that huge in the student hall-
Hey, you! No motorcycle riding in the hallways!
Where has Hazumi-chan gone?
You guys aren't all that hot as fighters!
Oh well, whoever dares to face McCoy,
the all-mighty Boss of the Tabasabu Remnants,
including you, little baby Guardians,
is dog shit anyway!
D-Dog shit?!
D-Damn you!
Beautiful Hammer Punch!
Right! All dog shit, like I said!
Well then, should I give you my lovely final blow?
Taste this, fools!
McCoy-sama, what is that?
Dog shit!
Who's that?
Reinforcements?
Called by Heaven, Earth, and my beeper.
A-Are you...
The strongest Guardian, supporting those who protect the seal of the gateway to the other world.
The Ultimate Saint Swordswoman,
Jinno Hazumi, has arrived!
My sword can cleave entire galaxies!
Who's that girl?
She just introduced herself.
Ah! It's Hazumi!
No! We're all gonna die!
Excuse me?
It's Jinno Hazumi, the ally-killer!
How rude!
Here I am, taking the trouble to save you,
and you're making fun of me?
Seriously, don't do it!
Stay away!
No! You monster!
The Dark Goddess of Destruction!
Y-You guys...
That nasty bitch hit me
in the face with dog shit!
I won't let you get away with that!
You just made the beautiful Lord McCoy very angry.
You're a lively little slut.
My sensitive butt-hole shrinks in excitement
when I think about what I'm going to do to you!
I won't show you any mercy.
We Remnants will tear you Guardians apart
to achieve our cherished dream of the last 30,000 years!
Now, prepare yourself, little bitch!
I'm gonna turn you into mincemeat!
How dare you wound
the frail heart of a delicate girl!
Who's "delicate"?!
I'll never forgive any of you!
A-And I didn't even say anything yet!
Go to hell!
Jinno Hazumi...
Gotcha!
Mom!
You've still got a lot to learn, Hazumi.
Bye!
You cheater!
Good morning, Takumi-chan.
Good morning, Mom.
This sucks! I lost again this morning!
Come on, Hazumi-chan! Hurry up!
Wait up!
We'll miss the bus!
You're always late because you fight
with Mom every morning.
It's her fault, for competing with me at her age.
Look! You've got breadcrumbs on your face.
Don't you have a handkerchief, Hazumi-chan?
A tissue?
Look, Takumi, I'm not in kindergarten-
You okay?
You'll fall if you don't hold on to the strap.
You should really be more careful, Hazumi-chan.
Hey, Takumi, have you gotten taller again?
Seems so.
I've been worried about a certain careless person,
so I hurried to grow up before her.
That's not a nice thing to say about your older sister! Show some respect, you!
You get upset so easily, Hazumi-chan.
I was just joking.
Hey, ladies! As well as little perverts
who infiltrated the floor!
I want all of you to make even more noise!
Now, let's thank the student council president
for renting "Juliana" for us!
The student council paid for everything!
You're an imbecile, Kazuma!
You've sealed your fate
by bringing the student council into this-
Gateway Campus
96th Summer Festival
Move it, move it, move it!
Takumi...
So we're siblings not related by blood?
What is tormenting your soul, Hazumi-kun?
Huh?
Feel free to open your heart to your senpai.
Why are you talking to my underwear, you pervert?!
Damn it, I can't let my guard down.
Getting overexcited like that
will harm your health.
You're harming it the most!
Well, it's good to see you so lively.
Chiryuu-senpai, do you need something?
No, not really.
I was going to peek into the girls' locker room
when I noticed that you looked a little worried.
Hazumi-kun.
Yes?
A great battle is approaching.
The Remnants aim to capture the gate
within this campus and Takumi-kun, the Key.
Be careful.
Okay.
I like pure white too.
You slimeball!
See you later!
Pervert!
Senpai, this is the girls' locker room!
L-Lucky!
No... I'm not here to take your clothes!
He's not really a bad guy.
A great battle.
The Remnants will come looking for Takumi.
When that happens, I've got to protect Takumi!
Commemorative Match: Monzen High
Yay, Takumi!
Takumi!
Takumi!
Takumi! Do your best!
Guess I can't cover the entire school with a barrier?
Mercy of the god of the Sun
and the god of the Moon.
We owe our lives to you.
Protect us from evil deities.
Remove from us the afflictions of death.
Sis, the game is starting soon,
so would you mind keeping it down a little?
If you keep yelling, Sis,
the players will be distracted.
Dear me! Was I really that noisy?
No. Just a tiny bit.
You smelly idiot!
Why don't you try acting your age?
Don't try to be friendly with me, kid,
calling me "Sis" every time!
You're his sister, remember?
What are you thinking of?
Finally tired yourself out, Hazumi-chan?
U-Uh, yeah.
When it's over, wanna hit the food stalls together?
No, Takumi-kun! You promised
to walk me around the festival today!
Oh, right.
Then let's all go together!
What? All three of us?!
You intrusive cow! What a pain!
Just go home, you old bag!
Well, see you later.
See you later.
Jinno Hazumi, I need to have a word with you.
Come with me now.
Jinno Hazumi!
Ah! You boys are all so cute!
Let's all have a little fun together!
Don't stop, Takumi-san!
Commemorative Match: Monzen High
Hm? He's pretty cute too.
Uh, sexy boy!
Let Lady Aoi take good care of you.
Last night, on the 4-26-3rd block of Miyato-cho,
He loves me...
He loves me not...
a building under construction mysteriously collapsed.
He loves me...
He loves me not...
Jinno Hazumi, it was your doing, wasn't it?
He loves me...
He loves me not...
Even though the Remnants were repelled,
He loves me...
when the building collapsed, three Guardians from our campus were seriously wounded.
He loves me not...
He loves me...
Your lack of self-control is absolutely outrageous for a Guardian!
He loves me not...
He loves me...
Therefore, you must hand over guardianship of the Key to the gate, Jinno Takumi, to us,
He loves me not...
the public morals committee!
He loves me...
Besides! The Remnants are definitely
poised for an all-out assault,
coinciding with the opening
of the gate to the Dark World.
We can't trust you to handle it
all by yourself any longer.
I refuse!
I'll protect Takumi.
That's my mission.
How dare you speak that way to your seniors!
Sexy whip!
Takumi-kun!
A Remnant?!
Could it be...
What did I just tell you?!
Yield Takumi to us!
Takumi!
Been a while.
I'm so pleased to see you again!
As long as our dark boss,
Chijima Touta, is here,
you Guardians are nothing but goat shit!
I don't need anything from you!
Oh, but I do need something from you!
I want my beautiful body back!
I won't let you lay a finger on my Takumi!
A little girl dares challenge
the erotic powers of Lady Aoi!
Sexy whip!
Now I'll never get married!
Hime-chan! Look out!
Are you all right, Hime-chan?
Ah! I was so scared!
If you weren't here to save me...
If you weren't here...
Hime-chan...
Takumi-kun, I love you!
You did well to deliver me this pleasure.
For that, I'm going to give you
my ultimate love, boy.
You've no idea how much
we power up with each passing day!
Iron Kick!
Iron Kick Two! Two!
I've got to hurry.
Hazumi! Where have you been?
Because of you, we lost the cooking contest and had to disband!
Y-Yuka, I don't have the time for this.
Takumi is...
Geez, you were going to stalk
Takumi-kun again?
Freeze!
I was never a big fan of ice queens.
You look like one of them:
the type that loves 'em and leaves 'em.
Thanks for the compliment!
Which means a stunted dick
and premature ejaculation.
How did you know?!
Freeze!
You bastards!
You low-ranking Remnants think you can beat
Honda Yasumasa of the public morals committee?
Listen, Remnants over there!
Don't you dare enter the campus!
Mercy of the god of the Sun
and the god of the Moon.
We owe our lives to you.
Protect us from evil deities.
Remove from us the afflictions of death.
Your face is the last thing I wanted to see.
How about we give you some Monzen crackers
as a souvenir and both go home?
Unless... you've got no place to return to?
All we want to do is release our world.
Then we're in a pickle.
You see, we're also finding
this world pretty convenient.
If we let you do that to our world,
it'll definitely be ruined beyond repair.
Soon, the gate will be opened.
So it would seem.
But what can be opened can be closed as well.
I'll kill the Key.
You said the same thing 30,000 years ago.
The scars are still burning, huh?
Do you still hold a grudge against her?
We've lived in disgrace for ages, but unlike us,
she has no memory of that time.
But she'll be sure to guard
her brother with her life.
Emerge, my Soul!
I don't have time to be dealing with you!
So arrogant!
Deadly Table-Flipping Technique!
I can't stand cockroaches or stuff like that.
You're like flea shit in comparison to my beautiful power!
Hey, old hag, prepare yourself!
Old hag?!
I can sense you're jealous of our youth!
Deadly Kitty Punch!
Go, Dirty Wolves!
What the...
Oh no!
Hime-chan!
Beautiful Woody Kick!
Here I come!
Please do!
New...
Beautiful Hand Punch!
See? You didn't stand a chance
against my beauty!
You're one stubborn bastard!
What?! "Stubborn"? What coarse language!
Anyone who stands in the way of me protecting Takumi won't get away with it!
You're beating your head against a wall!
New Beautiful Iron Punch!
How?!
Deadly...
Didn't you hear me?!
Single Stroke Giant Diakon Cut!
Pretty boy, you'll die now!
Oh, what a pain!
Takumi!
Hazumi-chan!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm so glad!
I'm sorry for arriving late, Takumi.
I knew you'd come, Hazumi-chan.
Oh, Takumi, enough! I'm so embarrassed!
Thank you, Hazumi-chan.
Look out!
I've been worried about a certain careless person,
so I hurried to grow up before her.
I goofed up again.
Takumi...
Ouch!
Whoever hurts my Takumi...
is gonna pay for it!
The Divine Soul Spirit sits in flames.
Die!
Deadly Technique: Blazing Tulips!
Wh-What? What the hell?!
What are these things?!
Hey, follow the rules, I said!
Behold Japan's Number One!
My! You're seriously hurt!
Are you all right, Hime-chan?
I'm so happy that you care about me!
Hime!
Hazumi-chan!
Thank you for guarding Takumi.
Don't mention it, Sis.
You did a great job too.
That doesn't mean I'll ever give Takumi up!
Takumi-kun's mine!
What?!
You heard me!
Jinno Hazumi, I'm arresting you on charges
of destroying the gym and the campus building!
Your lack of self-control as a Guardian...
Oh, my girl! Bravo!
Hazumi-kun, you fought well.
Think you could wear T-Backs next time?
You're a little late!
For goodness sake...
She's right. You missed it all, Chiryuu-senpai.
Where have you been all this time?
The man in control of the Remnants,
Kijima Touta, has finally awakened.
Will the Guardians be able to guard
the gate to the Dark World and the Key to it?
Also, what cruel fate awaits the two siblings,
Hazumi and Takumi?
Right now, love and hatred
will intersect on our Earth...
maybe.
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
Leave behind the hypocrisy of caring about others
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
Instead, just wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's much nicer, so much nicer
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
If you live your life as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty, I'm sure!
aishiau kokoro nara
If we love each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's go cleanse our world of pretenders, kick their butts
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those hypocrites
shinjiau kokoro nara
If we believe in each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
aishiaeba
When we love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry!
So, as you've seen,
the Remnants' attack has begun.
But why are they only targeting Takumi?
Something happened between Kijima and Takumi 30,000 years ago?
And that's Takumi's most well-guarded secret?
Next time on Bakuen Campus Guardress:
Anxious, Fearful:
Are Finals Worse Than the Enemy?!
Takumi, I'll protect you with my life.
Episode 2
Anxious☆Fearful★
Are Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
Scheduled Release Date, July 22nd
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
bananadoyouwanna,
Topper3000, Uchuu
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs