Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Everyone watching, can you believe
that this is happening for real?
Can you believe that this
enormously big gate is real?!
It suddenly appeared in Monzen City,
and it's more than a kilometer in height!
Quite obviously, it can
only be an artificial structure.
But who built it?!
And for what possible purpose?
Ah! Could this be a divine prank?
Or better yet, the devil's conspiracy?
Furthermore, a supernatural battle
is currently taking place all around the gate.
Hazumi. Takumi.
Wait for me, Takumi!
I became the Key for your sake alone.
T-Takumi...
I'll be protecting you now and forever.
Like when we were little.
Don't be so hasty!
I'll always be by your side, Hazumi-chan.
You can't die, Takumi!
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
Shred Shred☆Crumble Crumble★
There Are Many Ways to Win!
Why? Why sacrifice so many of them
just to go back?!
Shut up!
You were born to protect those filthy humans.
You'd never understand!
I'll smash you to pieces!
I'll crush you!
I'll break you!
Hate!
Hate.
I hate everything so much!
I hate... I hate... all of you!
All of you make me want to puke my guts out!
That's it.
That's what drives Kijima Touta.
Not the desire to return, not the desire to rule,
not even the ascension of the Dark World.
It is...
hatred!
Those damned humans.
They're no better than dung beetles,
but they act like they own the world.
What makes you think you can help them,
you stupid monkey?
You're nothing but a nuisance!
Look!
You're not worth shit, yet you keep trying
to oppose me. Don't make me laugh, you!
I didn't stay alive for this long
just to waste time dealing with your crap!
I'll smash everything you have to smithereens!
That includes your shitty notion of love!
I'll destroy it all!!
Puny humans! Now it's my turn!
I get punched. I get stepped on.
What a dirty job.
Don't get so serious.
You should learn to take it easy, Kijima.
Don't you think this world is great too?
You stubborn asshole.
Psycho Stampede!
Are you really a fool?!
Or are you just making a fool of me?!
You're the only fool here.
Wh-What?
Kijima, you're screwed up.
Just like the last time.
Are you sure, Takumi-kun?
Yes.
Takumi!
Don't be so hasty!
I'm on my way!
It was a laudable attempt, little girl.
But it ends here.
You're too late now.
The Key to the gate, Jinno Takumi, will die!
And the gate will be wide open.
Shut up!
Like hell I'd allow that!
What's this amazing Soul?
Whatever! We'll just power up too!
Get ready, little girl!
We'll beat ya to a pulp!
And now...
Combination attack: Sexy Dyna-Bust!
Slrrpp, slrrpp.
Come closer.
Hurry.
Boing, boing.
Straight to hell you go!
Nobody who hurts Takumi will get away with it!
I will protect Takumi!
From both of you and his fate!
Even if Takumi likes some other girl.
I don't care if I'm just his sister!
Protecting Takumi with all I have
is the only thing I know!
Really? This pathetic looking ball is all you have?!
Ah! No way!
G-Goal!
Takumi!
Principal, there're still so many Remnants!
Please, Tenku-sensei.
Hurry and perform the Sealing Ceremony!
Takumi-kun. I'll only ask you one more time.
Once the ceremony starts,
it can't be stopped.
And so, Takumi-kun, your life...
If my life can protect the ones I love...
Kijima Touta!
Chiryuu-senpai!
Isn't it the same as before, little girl?
Just like the day your continent sank
30,000 years ago.
Everything's going exactly the same way.
I'll never forgive you!
I-It's starting to open?
Now we're really screwed.
B-Be careful, Hazumi-kun.
Chiryuu-senpai! Thank goodness!
The Kijima Touta you face now has gone completely nuts with hatred for you... no, for all mankind.
What're you doing,
even during the final battle?
Oh, c'mon. Can't I take the memory of your
pure white panties with me on my last voyage?
Go on your trip by yourself!
You dumb jerks never learn.
Jinno Hazumi!
It's the same as 30,000 years ago,
but this time, I'll crush you into little pieces!
I'll make you suffer so much,
you'll forget that you were ever human!
Come on and give me your best!
Kijima Touta.
You're a pitiful man.
It's important for humans to have friends,
have fun, and live and laugh together.
You hate people and think about nothing
but fighting and killing.
Shut up!
What's so good about having fun?!
Lightning Stride!
Hazumi-chan Special!
Why?
Why are you suddenly
so much stronger now?!
'Cause I won't lose to someone like you!
Oh, no! You've stepped in some dog shit!
Huh? What?!
Touta-sama!
D-Dog shit?
Did I? Did I step in it?
Damn you, Jinno Hazumi!
Stop!
Yeah! As if! I have to get somewhere else first!
Hazumi-kun, you mustn't
repeat the mistakes of 30,000 yea-
Touta-sama!
The gods that reside alive and present
at the time of the great water purification,
the god Yasomagatsuhi,
the god Ohomagatsuhi,
the god Kamunahohi...
Takumi!
Get out of my way!
You're not getting away!
Let me go, you pervert!
If I don't hurry, Takumi will die!
Touta-sama!
The Sealing Ceremony has begun.
Before the girl, we should deal with the Key.
You shut up!
T-Touta-sama, if they conclude the Sealing Ceremony, we'll be stranded in this world again.
The cherished wish of all Remnants-
So what?!
I don't give a damn if the gate opens or closes.
Touta-sama...
I've waited 30,000 years for this day.
Tenku and Chiryuu's spell stripped away
my identity and my powers.
They made me forget all about who I was.
And still, I waited for this day!
All alone, without relying on anyone else,
I've waited for a day when I could attack her
with all of my hunger and hatred!
I don't give a damn what happens
to humans or Remnants!
Die, Jinno Hazumi!
Now suffer!
Suffer!
Suffer until you die!
You... poor thing...
You poor thing...
What?
You were so starved
that you'd fill the void with anything.
For all your life, you've been suffering...
That's how you came to hate others
and want to inflict the same suffering on them.
You were like that last time as well.
Kijima Touta, I've never met anyone
as insecure and pitiful as you.
What are you saying?
Wait for me, Takumi!
IRIS
Eye Cleaner™
Did that stinking, gutless fiend figure it out?
Crap!
Super Kijima Power Buildup!
Jinno Hazumi!
God, you're ugly.
Die!
Die! Die! Die!
Takumi...
The god Sokotsuwadatsumi,
Lord of life Sokotsutsu,
the god Nakatsuwatatsumi,
Lord of life Nakatsutsu...
No matter when...
Hazumi-chan was there.
Hazumi-chan has always cried for me,
gotten angry for me, laughed for me.
Hazumi-chan!
Takumi...
Love doesn't exist in this world.
All that exists is hatred!
You're wrong!
There's a girl I've always loved.
Don't tell me. It's Hazumi, isn't it?
The girl I love isn't my sister.
Takumi.
I can't get up anymore.
I'm sorry.
Jinno Takumi and Tenku!
I'll kill two birds with one stone!
Kijima Touta! What a fiendish form!
Yuck! He's ugly!
In the name of all gods, be purified!
Hazumi-chan!
T-Takumi... am I dreaming?
Hazumi-chan! Hang on!
Takumi... it's too late for me.
Hazumi-chan!
I'm happy to die in your arms like this.
My time is near, it seems.
But really, it's a little sad.
I mean, you have a girl you love, right?
But I'm nothing more than your sister.
That sucks.
Hazumi-chan, you're not my sister!
I kind of knew it for a long time.
That we weren't really related by blood.
After all, both you and Mom
were always so attentive to me.
Takumi...
Hazumi-chan, the girl I love is...
Yes! Finally!
BIG
SKY
BEAUTY
Called by Heaven, Earth, and my beeper,
the strongest Guardian has been summoned!
The Ultimate Saint Swordswoman,
Jinno Hazumi, has arrived.
My sword can cleave entire galaxies!
Great Masamune
Impossible!
Wretched Kijima Touta, who never found love!
We have created our own miracle of love.
Take this Soulful hit!
Prepare to fly,
my Soul!
Unparalleled Beauty's Ultimate Sword Technique!
Die, you damned bitch!
So this...
So this is love?!
O-Oops.
muishiki ni sono kokoro osaeteru
Unknowingly, I'm suppressing my feelings
jooshiki no han'i de zutto gaman shiteru
I try to hold myself back inside the practical world
sorede nantoka naru dounika naru
So we'll work it out, we'll work it out somehow
kitto ashita yoku naru to
Tomorrow will be a better day!
ommote ikiteirunone minna
Everyone thinks that's what they're living for
Monzen Town
Fire Brigade
Now that the gate is broken,
the two worlds are closely intertwined.
Fire Brigade
Monzen Town
shihon shugi no dorei-tachi ga hishimeite
The slaves of capitalism are all over the place
Fire Brigade
Though there are still occasional skirmishes.
Former Middle School
Hi! Look at all these delicious accessories I have!
are ya kore ya magaimono o tsukuridasu no yo
They keep making this and that up, keep faking things
Greetings, everyone!
I'll exchange anything for tissue paper.
sorede aa de mo nai ko demonai
And they say, "No, not like this! No, not like that!"
Those who need my love, come over here!
semakute chitchana kakoi no naka de sukebe no yume o mite warau
Meanwhile, I keep laughing at the lewd dreams
I'm seeing in my tiny world
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
So it wasn't necessary to destroy the world.
Nope, it wasn't.
You want some ice cream too?
daijobu soko no okata
Hey over there, are you all right?
Sure, bro.
moshikashite ano kimochi wasuretenai yo ne
Don't tell me that you forgot that feeling already?
shinjiau kokoro nara
If we believe in each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
aiashiaeru
When we love each other
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
Leave behind the hypocrisy of caring about others
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
Instead, just wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's much nicer, so much nicer
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
If you live your life as your heart desires
tsumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty, I'm sure!
aishiau kokoro nara
If we love each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible!
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's go cleanse our world of pretenders, kick their butts
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
aishiau kokoro nara
If we love each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
The world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible!
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's go cleanse our world of pretenders, kick their butts
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
Gateway High,
First Year
Sakura Class,
Jinno Takumi
Today, we all went
to the beach.
daijoubu! Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
Even down at the beach, Chiryuu and Kazuma
tussled with every Remnant they met.
(Boy, they're tough.)
jooshiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those hypocrites
I'm getting a little sunburned,
but the wind feels good.
shinjiau kokoro nara
If we believe in each other from the bottom of our hearts
Hazumi came back saying,
"Ah, I'm tired!" and went
to sleep without changing
out of her bathing suit.
(She's hopeless.)
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
aishiaeba
When we love each other
The sunset was neat.
Summer's almost over.
It was a hot, tough,
and very busy summer.
But...
I'll never forget
all the things that
happened this summer.
daijoubu
Don't worry!
Don't worry...
Behind the happy tears.
there were men who risked their lives.
Afterward, drink, get rowdy, get tipsy,
grab her, and get slapped by the Guardress.
Akahori Satoru
Greetings! How was it? I enjoyed it very much.
I'm glad I was able to work with many people
to make this anime.
Hazumi, Takumi, Chiryuu, Tenku, Hime,
Kazuma, and the Rems are still running
around the combined world in my mind.
See you again someday.
Hagiwara Kazushi
Ep 1: Throbbing☆Excited★                Dangerous Siblings
Ep 2: Anxious☆Fearful★Are                 Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
Ep 3: Nervous☆Scared★                The Stressful Final Battle!!
NOW ON SALE!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
bananadoyouwanna,
Topper3000, Uchuu
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs