Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Is it Takumi's fate to die in order to seal the gate?
Because that's what being the Key entails?
Why does it have to be like that?
Why does Takumi have to die?
Why did my Soul disappear
at such an important time?!
I can't stand it!
I don't know what the hell's going on!
Geez, you're pathetic!
You've been so busy growing your butt and bust,
your brain is still completely smooth!
Spare me your overprotection!
You may not know it,
but this is turning into a serious traged-
Oh, you don't have to tell me. Don't you understand that this shock therapy is for your sake?
Shock therapy?
Oh, yeah. With a great enough shock,
my Soul can reappear.
All right!
To me, Masamune!
Oh no, Mommy!
Pull yourself together, Hazumi!
You can't afford to lose your spirit like that.
You're Takumi's only sister, remember?
Even if you're not related by blood.
I envy you, Hazumi.
You get to spend time with Takumi.
Well, today's your last fun
school day of the semester.
Let's go!
Yeah.
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
When I wake up to a clear breeze
Something wonderful's gonna happen
That's the kind of (the kind of) feeling I have (feeling I have)
I'm more energetic than ever
I feel like it's nothing to worry about
My heart flutters and my heart sinks
It's that (it's that) subtle thing (subtle thing)
Gateway Campus Graduation Ceremony
Diary of my love
I'm sitting at the window overlooking the schoolyard
This won't do.
No! No! No!
I gotta act more like a big sister!
If I don't protect Takumi, who else will?
I'm looking for you, my notebook is still empty
Takumi has no one but me!
Pull yourself together, Hazumi!
Hazumi
Charm
You refuse to notice know how I feel
Hazumi
Charm
So I just can't confide in you
It's okay even if we pass each other by
Hime-chan?
Takumi-kun...
You don't have to turn around either
I love you.
As long (as long) as I can (as I can)
Honestly, I can't stop worrying about you.
That Remnant, Kijima, is nothing like
the Remnants we've encountered before.
Stare at your back, it's enough for me
He's super serious about it!
I want you to smile back at me one day
I'm serious too...
I want you to call me by my name
when I say I've loved you for eternity.
For now (for now), this is how far (how far)
Is there anyone you love, Takumi-kun?
I've filled in my diary
Basketball Club
I'm sorry, Hime-chan.
But there's a girl I've always loved.
Is it someone I know?
Diary!
Yes.
Don't tell me. It's Hazumi-san, isn't it?
But she's your sister, Takumi-kun!
It can't be her, right? Right, Takumi-kun?
No.
The girl I love...
isn't my sister.
Ah-ah, diary!
ITOEN TEA
KATAOKA MOTORS
VICTORY FISH
Fresh Fish
Ah-ah, diary!
Ah-ah, diary! Yeah...
Nervous☆Scared★
The Stressful Final Battle!
Ah-ah, diary! Oh!
Nervous☆Scared★
The Stressful Final Battle!
Can't you feel it, your blood boiling?
Your flesh trembling?
That's it! The time has arrived
for the gate to appear!
Looks like the imminent advent
of the Dark World is having its effect.
You boys are so susceptible.
I'm jealous.
My fellow Remnants!
The humans will be destroyed soon!
Death is preferable to consorting
with these worms!
Don't dither! Don't hesitate!
Slash them and burn them
with your anger and hatred!
Now go.
Kill the Key to the gate!
Destroy the altar!
And slaughter all the miserable humans!
Thanks. Come again.
Let's have some tea, Chiryuu-senpai.
Ramune
Cheerios
So cold...
If you're cold, why don't you come out?
Outside, it's hot.
Whatever you say.
Ramune
Cheerios
But man, I was surprised
when Hazumi's Soul disappeared.
Must be from the shock she got.
If you hadn't gone in to rescue them,
Kijima would definitely have killed them.
Dealing with Kijima is my job.
You think the Remnants will come?
Must be tough for Takumi too.
Being the Key and all.
Only 16, huh?
Such a short lifetime.
But...
that's his destiny.
Takumi! What do you think you're doing?!
Stop that! It's a bad omen.
I was just getting rid of things
I won't need anymore,
now that first semester's over.
R-Really? That's okay, then.
You're weird, Hazumi-chan.
I'm sorry, Takumi.
For what?
That my Soul disappeared.
Oh, that? So that's why you're so depressed today.
It's not like you to brood about things.
It's no big deal!
Here. Look.
I found this when I was cleaning the bookshelf.
Our roles were reversed back then.
Before you gained your power,
you seemed strong, but deep inside,
you were just a crybaby.
From now on, I'll be protecting you.
Just like old times.
Now that you've become an ordinary girl,
you'll probably be happier.
Hey, Takumi?
You...
I-It's nothing.
Chichibu!
Let's go to our Chichibu villa!
Chichi...
The Remnants will never find us there.
I bet it's safe!
That's it! We'll just have to elope!
No time like the present.
Great! Let's leave right away!
H-Hold it right there, Hazumi-chan!
It's finally happening, Realtor Guy!
Yeah, Ramen Guy.
Principal, what's this?
We'll hold on to the road leading to the gate till the end.
It stopped?
It's just the prologue.
A carnival happening every 30,000 years.
It's the Remnants!
Takumi! Run!
A message from Chiryuu-san.
Go to the principal's room at Gateway Campus.
The principal's room?
Go. It's your way to escape.
Since when did we have this...
I'm counting on you, Hazumi, Takumi.
We're on our way, Mom.
Now, hurry up, you two!
Anti-Monster Projectile!
Guardians, huh?!
You did well gathering
the butt-ugliest losers.
These Remnants are way nastier nowadays!
Sorry to disappoint you after coming all this way,
but not a hair will fall from the Key's head!
Watch out!
We're eloping!
It's a shotgun marriage!
Hazumi-chan, this isn't the way to school!
It's okay! It's okay!
Just trust your older sister!
We're running straight to Chichibu!
We're eloping, hand in hand!
FOOD COURT
Keep it up, kid!
Chinese   Cantonese
SAYOKEN
Thanks!
Chinese   Cantonese
SAYOKEN
Chinese Dishes
Cantonese
Restaurant
We got clients!
Special dish from our
Monzen City's Food Court!
No empty stomach will pass!
Hama's Noodle Summer-Rain Attack!
Tell me! How'd ya like
these hand-made noodles?!
Jackpot! Rapid-fire Fever!
Seduction Cards. Pink Shuriken!
Good going, Porno Books Vendor!
You too, Pachinko Guy!
Hey, don't take those, Oden Chef!
I never realized there were
so many Guardians in this town.
But this also felt so cool!
Everyone's cheering us on as we elope!
Hazumi-chan, "elope"?
Outta my way!
Where the hell did my Soul go?
Hazumi-chan!
Hey, my sweet honey! Sorry I'm late!
Kazuma-senpai!
Geez! You're kinda late to the rescue!
What if something happened to Takumi?!
Relax and let your super bodyguard
escort you all the way to Gateway Campus!
Hey, Hazumi!
Hey, wait up!
Hey, Hazumi-chan!
Gateway Campus isn't this way!
It's okay. It's okay.
Hazumi-chan!
So you are planning to go to Chichibu?
I'll make sure you're safe, Takumi!
Hazumi-chan!
Go! Go! Don't stop!
Fellow Dark Warriors! Take over
the altar in the principal's room!
If I should happen to be struck down, Aoba-kun,
then you must assist Takumi in the Sealing Ceremony.
I beseech you.
The Sealing Ceremony? Tenku-sensei...
Hazumi-chan, we have to go to Gateway Campus!
Forget it!
Hazumi-chan!
It's my job to protect you, Takumi.
That's why I'm taking you to Chichibu.
But Hazumi, if the Key isn't at the campus,
the Dark World gate can't be sealed.
B-But...
If that gate opens, then the Dark Army
will overrun our world, Hazumi-chan!
Even so... Even so, I can't...
Shuddup!
Bubble Spa!
I wish there was some way
for that boy to protect our town.
Don't worry. I'm sure those two will do something!
Ramen Chief!
We'll raze everything in this world to the ground!
And that includes you!
Damn! We can't even get to Chichibu!
How're we ever going to elope now?!
Shit! Laundromat Guy!
Damn! Now you've done it!
Declared bankrupt!
This new model is something!
A toast for the winner!
Keep it up!
They're all trying so hard to protect Takumi.
But...
Hazumi-chan!
Dammit! Nobody's going to stop us from eloping!
What the hell was that?
JAPANESE FOOD
SAKURA
Snacks
JAPANESE FOOD
SAKURA
Snacks
JAPANESE FOOD
SAKURA
Snacks
JAPANESE FOOD
SAKURA
Snacks
Hold on tight, Takumi!
JAPANESE FOOD
SAKURA
Snacks
Guess I'm a bit late this time as well.
Kazuma!
You think I'll let you pass any further?!
Senpai!
Kazuma! Hang in there, Kazuma!
I'm just happy to be in your arms, Hazumi.
If I only had my Soul with me...
I'm sorry, Kazuma.
Hey, hey, that's not like you.
These corporeal wounds are nothing,
compared to what you're going through.
That's one more reason to admire you.
How well you're holding back your grief
and fighting with full resolve,
even though your beloved brother is the Key.
Go now, Hazumi.
Take care of Takumi.
For my sake too.
K-Kazuma...
So it's finally arrived?
Wh-What the hell is that?
The gate!
What? The gate was under the campus?!
Our school!
The temple of learning,
steeped in the sweat and tears of youth!
I had practice exams at such a crucial time.
Honda Yasumasa of the public morals committee
has committed the most grievous of sins!
It's dangerous here, President!
We've gotta take cover! President!
No! I'm not going. Let me go, you two! Shit!
Takumi... Hazumi...
No! Don't head back to Gateway Campus!
Takumi! Don't!
Who cares if the gate doesn't close!
Takumi, come on!
You don't have to do this!
Takumi, you don't know this,
but for the gate to close,
the Key... the Key...
has to die!
So please! Don't go!
I can't stand to lose you!
Takumi!
Because of me...
Kijima Touta!
Jinno Hazumi.
Jinno Takumi!
And the Dark World gate.
The actors and stage are set.
This time we'll do it right!
Unlike what happened 30,000 years ago!
What're you talking about?
I'll never forgive you for making
Takumi go through all this!
So you plan to face me even without your Soul.
Hmph. What a protective older sister.
Shut up!
I don't need you to tell me
how it should be between Takumi and me!
Besides, I don't care what happened 30,000 years ago!
All that matters is that I love Takumi.
Yes. I love him more than anything in the world!
Brother or whatever,
I just want to live with him happily ever after,
like we've always lived up to now!
There's no way I'm letting you stop us!
Hazumi-chan...
Pathetic!
You're spitting out the same crap as that lowly life form called humans keep pulling out of their ass.
Your rotten world is covered in shit.
In words alone, you humans
keep professing universal love.
But can't you see that in reality,
this world is ridden with ugly conflict,
you pussbag?
That's because the love you're talking about
is the same as hate, understand?
Every time you say you love someone,
that means you hate them.
You all talk about your love for peace,
but at the same time, it's what you hate, huh?
Understand yet?
Hatred is what love is all about.
You bastards!
Damn! He noticed!
I'm gonna kill you both!
Chiryuu-senpai!
What a pessimist, Kijima!
I thought my ears would fall off from listening
to that long-winded speech.
Fool! I'll swat you aside,
just like I did 30,000 years ago!
This time, I will protect those two!
All right! All right! The heat's on!!
It's nothing!
Playtime's over.
Takumi!
Hazumi-chan.
Thanks for everything.
Now I can go without worrying.
Takumi, did you know about the fate of the Key?
I'll be okay, no matter what.
Thanks to this little something I got from you.
The charm I made.
No! Don't go!
You don't have to sacrifice yourself!
Why do only you have to die
for the sake of the world?
It's not only me.
You and everyone else are fighting
with their lives at stake.
But it wasn't for everyone's sake
that I became the Key.
Nor was it for the world.
I became the Key for your sake alone.
T-Takumi...
From now on, I'll return the favor
and become the charm protecting you forever.
Like when we were little.
Didn't I tell you I'd protect them both?!
I'll always be by your side.
From now on and forever.
Takumi!
Ooh! That's the miracle of love for ya!
Huh?!
I refuse to accept it!
You're not getting to me!
Just touch me and I'll beat you to a pulp!
Hazumi-kun, restarting the circle
of reincarnation again won't do.
Chiryuu-senpai...
Don't let Kairen's death
from 30,000 years ago go to waste.
Hurry to Takumi-kun's side.
Go and find a new answer yourself!
Chiryuu-senpai.
Let me handle the rest here.
Now go, Hazumi-kun.
Okay!
Takumi!
This is as it should be.
That bitch!
H-Hazumi-kun! On second thought,
maybe we should both take care of him first!
Now that the Dark World gate has finally appeared,
will the tragedy be repeated?
Can Hazumi rescue Takumi, who is intent
on sacrificing himself again to close the gate?
Finally, what will be the final fate
of love and the world?
To be continued.
To be continued
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
Leave behind the hypocrisy of caring about others
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
Instead, just wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's much nicer, so much nicer
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
If you live your life as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty, I'm sure!
aishiau kokoro nara
If we love each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's go cleanse our world of pretenders, kick their butts
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those hypocrites
shinjiau kokoro nara
If we believe in each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
aishiaeba
When we love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry!
The gate... The gate has finally appeared!
No way! I absolutely won't stand for it!
Not if Takumi has to die!
I've gotta find a way to stop this!
Trying to do that,
I'm absolutely having kittens!
Why the hell are you in my way, Kijima?!
I don't give a damn about your grudge!
Next time on Bakuen Campus Guardress:
The final episode!
Shred Shred Crumble Crumble:
There Are Many Ways to Win!
Final                              Episode
Scheduled to be released November 25th
Shred Shred☆Crumble Crumble★
There Are Many Ways to Win!
Takumi! I love you so much I could just die!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
bananadoyouwanna,
Topper3000, Uchuu
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs