Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Kairen-sama!
Kairen-sama, please stop!
Please! Don't die!
Kairen-sama!
A dream, huh?
I have finals starting today!
I haven't studied at all!
What am I going to do?!
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
The death toll from the last month's earthquake off the coast of Wales has reached 1,263.
Natural disasters have been hitting all parts of the globe this year.
Earthquakes, tsunamis, volcanic eruptions,
and freak weather conditions
have already claimed over 20,000 lives.
The number of large cities decimated by these disasters is now eight.
With rebuilding efforts stalling,
every nation has been forced
to take emergency measures
against these continuing natural disasters.
I'm heading out.
Hurry up, Hazumi-chan!
"Tsu, nu, ri, tari form...''
That hurts, Hazumi-chan.
Wait!
We're getting on!
Anxious☆Fearful★
Are Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
First Period
Modern Japanese
Geez! I can't take any more
finals in a place like this!
I give up.
I can't solve any more problems.
You don't have a right to complain.
Yeah, that's our Hazumi for you.
The number one school destroyer in Japan!
I'm sowwy.
The first session's finally over?
And I flunked both Modern Japanese and Math.
No use grumbling about it now.
Just do your best tomorrow.
You're always so positive, Yuka.
Oh, I have to go. See you tomorrow.
Takumi-kun again?
You two really are close.
Okay, then. Bye-bye!
Bye!
Just siblings who are really close?
Takumi.
Oh, darn, it sucks that we're siblings, even though we're not related.
That's it! I should just confess
to Takumi and be done with it!
A white chapel, a white carriage,
and a white wedding dress!
And then, the two of us...
No, no, no! Oh, Takumi...
Did something really good happen to you, Hazumi-chan?
It must be that you nailed today's exams!
But of course!
It was a disaster.
You'd do better if you bothered to study.
I know! When we get home, let's study English together. I'll spend the rest of the day with you.
T-Takumi, I'll try my best!
You'd better do that, Hazumi-kun.
Lacore shadow-print panties, size M.
You've got perfect childbearing hips, Hazumi-kun.
You're always up to the same thing!
Damn! What is he thinking?
Let's go, Takumi.
Hazumi-kun, you're not getting any summer vacation.
If you fail any of your exams, you'll spend
the whole summer in a supplementary school.
S-Supplementary school?!
You've gotta be kidding!
Camping, going to the sea,
the amusement park.
I thought I'd actually spend my summer vacation
doing all those things with Takumi!
Right, Takumi?
I see. No more joking around, huh?
You're the joke around here!
Nothing to do here now.
I need to return home and study.
Let's go, Takumi.
Sure.
Oh, I almost forgot!
What's wrong?
I have a basketball meeting this afternoon.
What? But it's finals week.
Apparently, it's an emergency meeting,
according to our manager, Hime-chan.
I've got to go now.
T-Takumi!
You need to study as hard
as you can, Hazumi-chan!
No way, Takumi! Don't tease me!
She's got herself involved in a painful battle.
Yeah.
Let's hope the main trouble waits
at least until finals are over.
When will we have to face the Dark World?
In another few days.
They'll be here within a week, at the latest.
I'm sorry I'm late...
Huh?
Where is everyone?
Hime-chan, where is everyone?
"P-Particularly."
Tokuni.
"Take care of."
Sewa o suru.
"Difficult. Diffi... Difficult..."
Oh, this is stuff is difficult!
I won't let some summer school ruin
my summer vacation with Takumi!
Being siblings...
Takumi
Loves
Really, it's such a pain.
Takumi
Loves
Kasumi
Yo.
Mom, what was that for?!
Oh? Then, what did you draw it for?
M-Maybe it's a dead end
right now, but someday...
Someday, I'll tell him the truth,
and we'll get married!
Takumi is your brother!
B-But...
Don't you have a more important duty
than chasing empty dreams like that?
I remember. Protect Takumi, right?
Compared to finals,
fighting the Remnants is a walk in the park!
You don't seem to realize yet how difficult it will be
to keep protecting Takumi until the very end.
Takumi-kun...
H-Hime-chan...
Y-You shouldn't be doing that, Hime-chan.
Takumi-kun, I'm giving you...
all of my body!
Hime-chan...
Go! Go!
We'll suppress the altar
and then slaughter all the Guardians!
Make sure you eliminate the Key, Jinno Takumi!
Mom!
Amore, amore, amore mio!
A Remnant!
Bonjour, Mademoiselle!
For thirty-five years,
I have been seducing beautiful ladies.
And by my name of Michel Yamada, I thank God
for finally letting me meet you, mon amour!
S'il vous plaît!
Bah! Cut the crap now and get out of our way!
Madame, I won't let you go tonight. Yes, tonight.
This is disgusting!
H-Hazumi!
Mom, you two look good together.
I'm leaving him to you.
I'm off to save Takumi! Later!
Hey, that's not fair!
Please join us too, Mademoiselle!
M-Madame had been so gentle with me before-
Shut up! Hurry up to save Takumi, Hazumi!
Thanks, Mom.
Looks like you've found somebody middle-aged like you. Good luck!
M-Middle-aged?! Who are you calling that? You ungrateful...
Takumi, I'm on my way!
You bastards! Who permitted you to enter here?!
Remnants are prohibited
from the school grounds!
Haven't you read this rules
book even once?!
I've found you, my boy.
And it's all to Lady Aoi's credit.
I won't let you get away today!
If I were you, I wouldn't take another step.
You're handsome, even if you're a Guardian.
I'll give you a score of 83.
You've passed my test, boy.
Thanks. I'm truly pleased.
Even the gaudy old bags can be nice sometimes.
Old bag? Me?
You rude son of a bitch!
What are you doing?!
Oh, je t'aime! Are you hurt somewhere, Madame? Oui.
You French swine!
Let me give you a taste
of a Japanese housewife's power!
Housewife's Osakan Kitchen Knife Fire!
It's still pretty easy to make advances to the madames of Japan!
Housewife's Perfectly Cooked Noodles!
It's no use fighting.
These are Jinno family secret handmade noodles.
Be quiet now!
Oh, Madame, you are so strong,
and that's why you are my mon amour.
Je t'aime!
I'll defend it from here.
But please, take care of Takumi, the Key.
Hime-chan, are you all right?
Yes.
Takumi-kun!
Regrettably, your game is over now.
Regrettable indeed.
You're wearing trousers.
Eat this!
Hime, Takumi-kun, keep close to me!
You're good, dammit.
So are you.
Get out of my way!
Watch out!
I'm sorry! My brakes gave out!
Are you all right, Kazuma?
I-I don't think I'll make it.
Do me a favor, Hazumi.
G-Give me one last kiss... kiss... kiss.
You bastard!
I thought so.
Takumi's fine. He made his getaway.
Really? Thanks, Kazuma!
If I were in a better shape now,
I'd hug you too.
Takumi went to the docks.
Hime's with him, so don't w-
Hime's with him?
Unacceptable!
Welcome to my fairy tale.
Will you play with me in this fairy tale
till morning, Madame?
No way, you pervert!
Keep that nonsense to yourself.
You're dealing with an Edoite,
and we've no time for sissies!
Non, non, Madame.
No, I mean, Mademoiselle.
Your passionate eyes,
your sweet lips,
your shining auburn hair.
If you were a flower,
you'd indeed be this deep red rose!
Yes, this rose, Mademoiselle,
I was growing it to dedicate to you.
Oh, really?
Ah! Shit!
How low can you go?!
Such is the life of a gigolo, Madame!
The color of this rose is pure red,
like human blood!
Now, let us darken the petals further!
This Japanese housewife will not lose!
Secret Technique: Ethnic Champ!
Tabasco!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Real Wasabi!
Red Pepper!
Ouch-ouch...
Topped off by Hundredfold Hot Curry!
Curry! It's curry! Curry!
The Jinno Family Secret: Kasumi Special.
Have a taste!
Hime-chan!
Don't worry. All those Remnants flocked around Chiryuu-senpai, so we should be safe here.
Why are there Remnants even here?
Because the advent of
the Dark World is really close!
Hime-chan.
I'm all right.
Hime-chan special:
Bow-Wow Punch!
Hime-chan, this way.
I remembered something from when I was a kid.
It's just like hide-and-seek.
I used to play it with my neighbor, Ken-chan.
Kijima Touta!
Jinno Takumi.
You are the reincarnation of Kairen.
What do you want?
I won't let you live if you touch Takumi-kun!
To prevent the gate from ever being closed again, Kairen...
I'm going to kill you!
Little Bird Attack!
Takumi-kun!
No!
I'll never forgive anyone who hurts Takumi!
Let's go!
Your power is like an elementary school kid's.
Your abilities don't match your large physique.
How disappointing.
Now freeze!
For such a cute girl,
you sure have a foul mouth.
I like you.
Slimeball.
Yeah! That cool air sure feels
good and refreshing!
Say, why don't you go out with me?
I need an air conditioner.
How long are you gonna play brave?
But in the winter, we'll have to break up, I guess.
And here's my alimony check!
Uh, Christ, it's frozen.
She was damn good for a villain.
Takumi, hang on!
Takumi!
Damn! Now you've pissed me off, you hear?!
Heavenly Lord Stroke: Comet Tornado Drop!
How'd you like that?
It can't be!
I was hoping your Soul
might've grown up a bit since then.
But now, I'll just break you down,
along with the Key.
What are you mumbling about?!
It's just like in my morning dream.
Kairen-sama!
Please! Stop this!
Please don't die!
It was you.
You've finally remembered your previous life.
My previous life?
All the more reason why I must kill you.
Kairen, I will kill you
before you can throw yourself in.
I won't allow you to close the gate now.
Whatever the cost, I will...
protect Kairen-sama!
I will protect Takumi!
You fool.
Now I will obtain the vengeance
I have sought for 30,000 years.
Struggle. Groan.
Drink fully of your humiliation!
With this, the world will be
enveloped in darkness.
H-How can you still stand?
I won't let you lay a single finger on Kairen-sama!
N-Nonsense!
There's no way someone like you
could possess such power!
I will protect Kairen-sama!
Die!
What?!
In a battle, you don't know
what might happen until the very end!
Now, this is the true end!
Kairen-sama!
Kairen!
S-Stop!
Kairen-sama!
Do you understand, Hazumi?
In order to close the gate and seal off the Dark World, I, the Key, must sacrifice myself.
I have no choice.
Kairen-sama!
He's got to die to be the Key.
In order to seal off the gate, the Key...
Takumi has to die.
That can't...
That can't be!
No!
Takumi! Don't die!
Takumi, you don't need to die!
Takumi!
Takumi-kun!
Takumi! You don't need to die!
Whatever happens,
I will protect you with my life!
In order to seal the gate to the Dark World,
Takumi's life had to be sacrificed last time.
In that shock of discovering Takumi's fate,
Hazumi lost her Soul.
Now Hazumi and Takumi once again have to face
their cruel fate from 30,000 years ago.
With all her power gone,
will Hazumi be able to protect Takumi now?
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
Leave behind the hypocrisy of caring about others
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
Instead, just wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's much nicer, so much nicer
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
If you live your life as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty, I'm sure!
aishiau kokoro nara
If we love each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's go cleanse our world of pretenders, kick their butts
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those hypocrites
shinjiau kokoro nara
If we believe in each other from the bottom of our hearts
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Our world is a brighter place. Look, anything is possible
aishiaeba
When we love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry!
It can't be!
Somebody say it's not true!
Takumi is fated to die.
I'll never let that happen!
What happened to my Soul
at such an important time?!
Finally... Finally, the gate has appeared.
Next time on Bakuen Campus Guardress:
Ache Ache Pant Pant: The Stressful Final Battle!
Takumi, if it's come to this, we'll have to elope!
Episode 3
Ache Ache☆Pant Pant★
The Stressful Final Battle!
Scheduled Release Date, October 7th!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
bananadoyouwanna,
Topper3000, Uchuu
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs