Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Kairen-sama!
Kairen-sama, please stop!
Please don't die!
Kairen-sama!
It was a dream.
I have finals today!
I haven't studied at all!
What am I going to do?!
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
The death toll from the earthquake off the coast of Wales has reached 1263.
More than 20,000 deaths this year have been caused by a series of disasters,
including earthquakes, tsunamis, volcanic eruptions,
and freak weather conditions.
The number of large cities decimated by these disasters is now eight.
The delay in rebuilding has forced every nation to take emergency measures
against these continuing natural disasters.
I'm heading out.
Hurry up, Hazumi!
"Tsunuritarite...''
That hurts, Hazumi-chan.
Wait!
We're getting on!
Excited☆Fearful★
Are Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
First Period
Modern Japanese
Geez!  I can't take any more
finals in a place like this!
I give up!
I can't solve any more problems!
You don't have a right to complain.
Yeah, she's right, Hazumi.
You're the number one
school destroyer in Japan!
I'm sowwy.
The first session's barely over.
I didn't do too well in Modern Japanese or Math.
Don't let it bother you.
Just hang in there for tomorrow.
You're always so positive, Yuka.
Oh, I have to go. See you tomorrow.
Takumi-kun again?
You two really are close.
Bye-bye!
Bye!
We're as close as brother and sister...
Takumi.
Oh, darn, it sucks that we aren't related but are still siblings.
That's it! I'll tell Takumi the truth.
A white chapel, a white carriage, and a white wedding dress.
The two of us together forever.
No, no, no... Takumi...
What are you so happy about, Hazumi-chan?
I guess you did really well on today's exams!
Of course!
I did terribly.
You'd do better if you bothered to study harder.
I got it! Let's study English together.
I'll stick around you all day long.
Takumi, I'm going to try harder!
Hang in there, Hazumi-kun.
Racole shadow-print panties, size M.
You've got perfect childbearing hips, Hazumi-kun.
You're always doing this!
Damn! What is he thinking?!
Let's go, Takumi.
Hazumi-kun, you won't get a summer vacation if you fail any of your finals.
You'll go straight to summer school.
Summer school?!
You've gotta be kidding!
Camping, swimming, amusement parks.
I wanted do all those things with Takumi.
Right, Takumi?
You're right. No more joking around, huh?
You're the joke around here!
I can't stick around here anymore.
I need to get home and do nothing but study.
Let's go, Takumi.
Sure.
Oh, I almost forgot!
What's wrong?
I have a basketball meeting this afternoon.
What? But it's finals week.
According to our manager,
Hime, it's an emergency.
I've got to go now.
Hey, Takumi!
You need to study as hard as you can, Hazumi-chan!
No way, Takumi! Don't tease me!
She has many difficult battles ahead of her.
Yes.
But hopefully they'll wait until finals are over.
When will we have to face the Dark World?
In another few days.
They'll be here within a week, at the latest.
I'm sorry I'm late...
Huh?
Where is everyone?
Hime-chan, where is everyone?
--Tokuni--
"Particularly.''
--Sewa o suru--
"Take care of''
--Muzukashii--, Muzuka...Muzukashii...
Oh, this is difficult!
Dammit, I won't let summer school ruin my vacation with Takumi!
The fact that we're brother
and sister is really a pain.
Takumi
Loves
Kasumi
Yo.
Mom, what was that for?!
And may I ask what that was all about?
I-I shouldn't be thinking
about it right now, but I wish...
Someday, I'll tell him the truth,
and we'll get married!
Takumi is your brother!
But...
You can't go chasing dreams like that, right?
You have an important duty.
I know. Protect Takumi, right?
I'd rather face the Remnants than tackle a final.
You'll never realize how difficult it really is to guard Takumi until the end.
Takumi-kun...
H-Hime-chan...
Y-You shouldn't be doing that, Hime-chan!
Takumi-kun, I'm giving you...
my entire body!
Hime-chan...
Go! Go!
We're going to take the altar and kill all the Guardians!
Make sure you eliminate the key, Takumi!
Mom!
Love, love, ah, my love!
A Remnant!
Bonjour, Mademoiselle!
For thirty-five years, I've been teasing beautiful ladies.
This soul, Michael Yamada, thanks God for finally leading me to my heart's true love!
Bah! Cut the crap now and get out of our way!
Madame, I won't let you go tonight. Yes, tonight.
This is disgusting!
K-Kasumi!
Mother, you two look good together.
I'm leaving him to you.
I'm off to save Takumi!  Later!
Hey, that's not fair!
Please join us, Mademoiselle!
Madame, be gentle with me.
Go and save Takumi!
Thanks, Mom.
Looks like you've found somebody middle-aged like you. Hang in there!
Who's middle-aged?! You ungrateful...
Takumi, I'm on my way!
You bastards! Who gave you the right to come here?
Remnants are not allowed on school grounds!
It's in the rules, can't you see?!
I've found you, boy.
And it's all to Lady Aoi's credit.
I won't let you get away!
I won't let you go one step further.
You're handsome, even if you are a Guardian.
I'll give you a score of 83.
You've passed my test, boy.
Thanks. Nice of you to say so.
It's nice to see a middle-aged woman trying her best to look young.
Me, middle-aged?!
You rude son of a bitch!
Are you hurt, madame?
You French-thing!
Let me give you a taste
of a Japanese housewife's power!
Housewife's kitchen knife fire!
Maid of Japan, you have been vanquished.
Housewife's perfectly cooked noodles!
It's no use straining yourself.
They're made from the Jinno family's secret recipe.
Don't try to resist!
Madame, you are strong, and you are my love.
You are my soul.
I'll defend from here.
So, Takumi, the key, please.
Hime-chan, are you all right?
Yes.
Takumi-kun!
I regret that our game is over.
It is regrettable.
You're wearing trousers.
Eat this!
Hime, Takumi-kun, keep close to me!
You're good.
So are you.
Get out of my way!
Watch out!
I'm sorry! My brakes gave out!
Are you all right, Kazuma?
I-I don't think I'll make it.
Do me a favour, Hazumi.
G-Give me one last kiss... kiss... kiss...
You bastard!
I didn't think you would.
Takumi's fine. He made it past here.
Really? You did great, Kazuma!
You look so happy that I could hold you forever.
Takumi went to the docks.
Don't worry. Hime's with him.
Hime's with him?
Unforgivable!
Welcome to my promenade.
Play with me in our promenade, Madame.
No way. You pervert! Keep those dirty thoughts where they belong.
You're dealing with a native of Edo! One more word and you're dead!
Non, non, Madame, I mean, Mademoiselle.
Your passionate eyes,
your sweet lips,
your shining auburn hair.
Figuratively speaking, you are a flower. a pure red rose.
This rose, yes, Mademoiselle, is your everlasting symbol.
Oh, good gracious...
How can you sink so low?!
It's the life of a gigolo, Madame!
The color of this rose is pure red, like the blood of humans.
Now let us darken the petals further!
This Japanese housewife will not be beaten!
Secret Technique: Ethnic Champ!
Tabasco!
Ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Genuine Wasabi!
Red Pepper!
missing
The final stroke is hundredfold hot, Curry!
It's too hot! Hot! Hot!
The Jinno family Secret: the Kasumi Special.
Taste this!
Hime-chan!
With all those Remnants around Chiryuu,
we're safe if we stay here.
Hime-chan!
Why are there so many Remnants?
Probably because the Dark World is growing closer!
Hime-chan.
I'm all right.
Hime-chan special:
Bow-Wow Punch!
Hime-chan, this way.
I remembered something from when I was a kid.
I used to play hide-and-seek here
with my neighbor Ken.
Kijima Touta!
Jinno Takumi.
You are the reincarnation of Kairen.
What are you going to do?
I won't let you live if you touch Takumi.
To prevent the gate from
ever being closed, Kairen...
I'm going to kill you!
Little Bird Attack!
Takumi-kun!
No!
I'll never forgive anyone who hurts Takumi!
How can you be their leader with such pathetic powers?
You're the lowest of them all.
Only your body has any worth.
How disappointing.
Now freeze!
For a cute girl, you sure have a foul mouth.
I like you.
Slimeball.
Oh, yeah! Man, does that cool air feel good!
Why don't you go out with me?
I need an air conditioner.
How long can your sense of humor save you?
We'll have to break up in the winter.
And here's my alimony check!
Christ, it's frozen.
She was good, even for a villain.
Takumi, hang on!
Takumi!
Damn! You're driving me crazy!
Heavenly Lord Stroke: Comet Tornado Drop!
How'd you like that?!
It can't be!
I thought your soul would be elevated...
but I'll break you down,
along with the key.
What are you talking about?
It's just like the dream.
Kairen-sama!
Please stop!
Please don't die!
That was...
You've finally remembered your previous life.
Remembered my previous life?!
If that's so, I must kill you at all costs.
Kairen, I shall kill you before you throw yourself in.
I will not allow you to close the gate.
I will protect Kairen-sama!
I will protect Takumi!
You fool.
Now I shall obtain the vengeance I have sought for 30,000 years.
Struggle... Groan...
Drink fully of my disgrace!
With this, the world shall be enveloped in darkness.
Why do you continue to resist?
I won't let you touch Kairen-sama!
Unbelievable!
I can't believe someone like you has such power!
I will protect Kairen-sama!
Die!
What?!
Nobody knows what will happen in the final battle!
This will not be the end!
Kairen-sama!
Kairen!
Stop!
Kairen-sama!
Do you understand, Hazumi?
In order to close the gate and seal off the Dark World, I, the key, must sacrifice myself.
I have no choice.
Kairen-sama!
He's got to die to be the key...
In order to seal off the gate,
the key, Takumi, has to die.
Takumi must die.
I can't...
No!
Takumi! Don't die!
Takumi doesn't need to die!
missing
Takumi-kun!
I will protect you with my life!
In order to seal the gate to the Dark World,
Takumi's life had to be sacrificed.
Hazumi's soul was thrown into turmoil by the shock of discovering Takumi's fate.
Now Hazumi and Takumi face
their cruel fate from 30,000 years ago.
With all her power gone, will Hazumi be able to protect Takumi to the end?
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
You don't have to worry about hurting me
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
So wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's better, much better
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
Even if you act as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty
aishiau kokoro nara
Love each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Things are going well, anything can happen
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's kick some liar's butt
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those stupid liars
shinjiau kokoro nara
Believe in each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Things are going well, you can do anything
aishiaeba
If you love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry
It can't be!
Somebody say it's not true!
Takumi is fated to die!
I'll never let that happen!
What happened to my soul at such an important time?
Finally... Finally, the gate has appeared.
Next time on Bakuen Campus Guardress:
Ache Ache Pant Pant: A Battle Full of Suffering!
Takumi, there's nothing left to do but run away!
Episode 3
Anxious☆Fearful★
A Battle Full of Suffering!
Scheduled Release Date, October 7th!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
ninjacloud
Collectr
QC1
QC2
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs