Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Is it Takumi's fate to die just to seal the gate?
But that's what being the Key means.
Why does it have to be like this?
Why does Takumi have to die?
Why did my soul disappear
at such an important time?!
I can't stand it!
I don't know what the hell's going on!
Geez, you're pathetic!
You've developed your butt and bust,
but you haven't worked on your brains!
It's none of your business!
You may not know it, but this is turning into a serious traged-
Oh, you don't have to tell me.
Don't you realize my shock treatment was because I care about you?
Shock treatment?
Oh, yeah. The shock made my soul...
All right!
To me, Masamune!
Wah, Mommy!
Pull yourself together, Hazumi!
You can't get depressed like that.
You're Takumi's only sister...
even if you're not related by blood.
I envy you, Hazumi.
You get to be with Takumi.
Well, this is your last fun semester at school.
Let's go!
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
I'll wake up to a clear breeze
Something wonderul's gonna happen
I have (I have) a premonition (premonition)
I'm more energetic than ever
It's nothing to worry about
I'm excited, I'm down
It is (It is) subtle (subtle)
Tobira School Graduation Ceremony
Love Diary
I'm sitting at the window overlooking the schoolyard
No!
No! No! No!
I gotta act more like an older sister!
If I don't protect Takumi, who will?!
Looking for you, my notebook's in the sky
Takumi has no one but me!
Pull yourself together, Hazumi!
Hazumi
Charm
You don't even know how I feel
Hazumi
Charm
I just can't confide in you
It's okay if we pass each other by
Hime-chan!
Takumi-kun...
I don't have to turn around
I love you.
I can always (always) see your back (your back)
I can't stop worrying about you.
That Remnant, Kijima, is different from the other stupid Remnants.
I just want to stare at you
It's because he's so serious.
I want to smile at you someday
I'm serious, too.
I want to be called by name
I've loved you for a long time.
But for now (for now), this is it {is it)
Is there anyone you love, Takumi-kun?
My Diary
I'm sorry, Hime.
But there's a girl I've always loved.
Is it someone I know?
Don't tell me. It's Hazumi, isn't it?
But she's your sister, Takumi-kun!
It can't be her! Right, Takumi-kun?
No.
The girl I love...
isn't my sister.
Nervous☆Scared★
A Battle Full of Suffering!
Can't you feel it, your blood boiling?
Your flesh trembling?
That's it! The time has arrived for the Gateway to appear!
It looks like the proximity
of the Dark World is having its effect.
You boys are so easily influenced.
I envy you.
All you Remnants!
The humans are to be destroyed!
You will suffer more than humiliation if you consort with the worms!
Don't hesitate! Don't hold back!
Use your anger and hatred to slash and burn!
Now go.
Kill the Key to the Gate!
Destroy the temple!
And kill all the humans!
Thanks. Come again.
Let's have some tea, Chiryuu!
Ramune
Cheerios
It's cold in there!
If you're cold, why don't you come out?
It's hot outside.
Whatever you say.
Ramune
Cheerios
But man, I was surprised
when Hazumi's soul disappeared.
Must be from the shock she got.
If you hadn't gone in to rescue them,
Kijima would definitely have killed them.
Dealing with Kijima is my job.
You think the Remnants will come?
Must be tough for Takumi too.
Being the Key and all.
Only 16, huh?
Such a short lifetime.
But...
that is his destiny.
Takumi! What do you think you're doing?!
Don't be so fatalistic!
I'm just getting rid of things I won't need anymore.
Now that first semester's over.
Oh. That's okay, then.
You're weird, Hazumi.
I'm sorry, Takumi.
For what?
That my soul disappeared.
Oh, that. So that's why you're so depressed.
It's not like you to worry like this.
It's no big deal!
Here. Look.
I found this when I was cleaning the bookshelf.
Our roles were reversed back then.
Before you gained your power,
you were strong-minded, but still just a regular crybaby.
From now on, I will protect you.
Just like old times.
Now that you've become an ordinary girl, that's probably for the best.
Hey, Takumi?
You...
I...It's nothing.
Chichibu!
Let's go to the Chichibu Resort!
Chichi...?
The Remnants will never find us there!
I betcha it's safe!
That's it! We'll elope!
Now that we've decided, let's go!
Let's leave right now!
H...hold it, Hazumi!
It's time, Mr. Realtor!
Yeah, Mr. Ramen.
What's happening, Mr. Superintendant?
We will protect the road to the Gate!
It stopped?
It's just the prologue.
A carnival happening every 30,000 years.
It's the Remnants!
Takumi! Run!
A message from Chiryuu:
Go to the Superintendant's room at Tobira High.
The Superintendant's room?
Come on. Get out this way!
When did you have this...
I'm counting on you, Hazumi. Takumi.
We're on our way, Mother.
Well. Hurry up, you two!
Emergency Monster Projectile!
Guardians, huh?!
Really, they've sure got a bunch of butt-ugly losers!
These new Remnants nowadays!
I'm sorry you came all this way,
but you ain't getting to the Key!
Watch out!
We're eloping!
It's a shotgun marriage!
Hazumi, this isn't the way to school!
It's okay! It's okay!
Just trust your older sister!
We're running straight to Chichibu!
We're eloping!
FOOD COURT
Keep it up, kid!
Thanks!
The group's all here!
Food Court Specialty!
No empty stomach shall pass!
Hama's Noodle Summer-Rain Attack!
Howd'ja like the texture of these hand-made noodles?!
Jackpot! Rapid-fire Fever!
Seduction Cards. Pink Shuriken!
Good going, Mr. Porno Books!
You too, Mr. Pachinko!
Hey, don't take those, Mr. Oden Shop!!
I never realized there were so many Guardians in this town.
But this is so cool!
Everyone's cheering on as we elope!
Hazumi! Elope?!
Outta my way!!
Where the hell is my soul?!
Hazumi!
Hey, my sweet honey! Sorry I'm late!
Kazuma!
Geez! You're kinda late to rescue us!
What if something happened to Takumi?!
Relax!   I, your super bodyguard, will lead you to Tobira High!
Hey, Hazumi!
Hey, wait up!
Hey, Hazumi! Tobira High's not this way!
It's okay. It's okay.
Hazumi!
So you ARE planning to go to Chichibu!
I'm going to protect you, Takumi!
Hazumi!
Go! Go! Go!
Dark Warriors! Take over the shrine in the superintendant's room!
If I should happen to be struck down, Aoba...
...then you must assist Takumi in the Sealing Ceremony.
I beseech you.
The Sealing Ceremony? Master Tenku.
Hazumi, we have to go to Tobira High!
Forget it!
Hazumi!
It's my job to protect you, Takumi.
That's why I'm taking you to Chichibu.
But Hazumi, if the Key is not at the school...
...the Dark Gateway can't be sealed.
B...but...
If that Gate opens, then the Dark Army will overrun our world, Hazumi!
But that... but that means...
But I...
SHUDDUP!
Bubble Spa!
I wish there was some way that boy could protect our town.
Don't worry, I'm sure those two will do something!
Mr. Ramen!!
Destroy everything in this world, utterly!
And that includes you!!
Damn! We can't even get to Chichibu!
How're we ever going to elope now?!
Shit! Mr. Laundromat!
Damn! You dirty bastard!
I'll bankrupt you first!
Now that's what I call new and improved!
Good job there!
Keep it up!
They're all trying so hard to protect Takumi.
But...
Hazumi!
Dammit!  NOBODY's going to keep us from eloping!!
What the hell was that?!
Hold on tight, Takumi!
Guess I'm a bit late this time, too.
Kazuma!
They don't give up, do they?
Senpai!
Kazuma! Hang in there, Kazuma!
I'm just happy to be in your arms, Hazumi.
If I only had my soul...
I'm sorry, Kazuma.
Hey, hey, that's not like you.
This is nothing compared to what you're going through.
You're holding back your grief and fighting very well.
Even though your beloved brother is the Key.
Go now, Hazumi.
Take care of Takumi.
For my sake, too.
K...Kazuma...
So it's finally arrived.
W...what the hell is that?!
The Gate!
What? The Gate was under the school?!
Our school...!
The school where we sweated and shed our tears to...
Of all the time to be away taking my practice exams...!
I, Honda Yasumasa, the student president, have committed the most grievous of sins!
It's dangerous here, Mr. President!
We've gotta take cover!
Let me go, you two!
Takumi...  Hazumi...
No! Don't head back to Tobira High!
Takumi! Don't!
Who cares if the Gate doesn't close!
Takumi, you don't have to do this!
Takumi, you don't know, but for the Gate to close,
the Key'll...the Key'll...
...have to die!
So please!  Don't go!
I can't stand to lose you!
Takumi!
Because of me...
Kijima Touta!
Jinno Hazumi!
Jinno Takumi!
And the Dark Gateway.
The actors and stage are set.
This time we'll do it right!
Unlike what happened 30,000 years ago!
What the hell are you talking about?
I'll never forgive you for doing this to Takumi!
So you would face me without your soul.
Hmph. What a protective older sister.
Shuddap!
Don't you dare talk about Takumi and me like that!
Besides, I don't care what happened 30,000 years ago!
All that matters is that I love Takumi!
I love him more than anything in the world!
Brother or not...!
...I just want to live with him happily now and forever!
There's no way I'm letting you stop us!
Hazumi...
How pathetic!
You're spitting out the same crap as those lowly humans!
Your world is full of shit!
People may talk about love,
but why is this world still full of conflict!
You pussbag!
It's because love is the same as hate, understand?
Every time you say you love someone, you're hating them!
You say you love peace, but at the same time, you hate it!
Understand yet? Hatred is what's real!
Damn you both!
Damn! He noticed!
I'm gonna kill you both!
Chiryuu!
What a pessimist, Kijima!
I thought my ears would fall off  listening to that long-winded speech!
Fool! I'll swat you aside like I did 30,000 years ago!
This time I WILL protect them!
All right! All right! The heat's on!!
missing
Playtime's over.
Takumi!
Hazumi. Thanks for everything.
Now I can go without worrying.
Takumi, you...knew what would happen to the Key?
I'll be okay no matter what!
Because of the charm you gave me!
The charm I made...
No! Don't go!
You don't have to sacrifice yourself!
Why do you have to die for the sake of the world?!
It's not only me.
You and everyone else are fighting with all you've got.
But it's not for everyone's sake that I'm the key.
Nor is it for the world.
It's because of you that I'm the Key.
T...Takumi...
From now on, I'll be the charm protecting you.
Like when we were young.
I told you I'd protect them!
I'll always be by your side.
From this moment on.
Takumi!!
Oohhh!! It's the miracle of love!
I refuse to accept it!
Don't you dare lay a hand on me!!
Touch me and I'll beat you to a pulp!
Hazumi, you mustn't repeat your past!
Chiryuu...
Don't waste Kairen's death 30,000 years ago!
Hurry to Takumi's side.
Go and find a new answer!
Chiryuu...
Let me handle this.
Now go, Hazumi.
Right!
Takumi!
This is as it should be.
That bitch!
Ha...Hazumi! On second thought, maybe we should both take care of him first!
Now that the Dark Gate has appeared, will the tragedy be repeated?
Can Hazumi rescue Takumi who is intent...
...on sacrificing himself once again to close the Gate?
What is the final fate of love and the world?
To be continued
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
You don't have to worry about hurting me
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
So wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's better, much better
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
Even if you act as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty
aishiau kokoro nara
Love each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Things are going well, anything can happen
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's kick some liar's butt
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those stupid liars
shinjiau kokoro nara
Believe in each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Things are going well, you can do anything
aishiaeba
If you love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry
The Gate... the Gate has finally appeared!
No way! I absolutely won't stand for it!
Not if Takumi has to die!
I've gotta find a way to stop this!
Now I'm so busy I don't know what to do!
Why the hell're you in my way, Kijima?!
I don't give a damn about your grudge!
Next Combustible Campus Guardress: Final Episode:
Final Episode
Scheduled to be released November 25th
Shredded☆Crumbled★
There Are Many Ways to Win!
Takumi! I love you so much I could just die!!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
ninjacloud
Collectr
QC1
QC2
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs