Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Be strong, Tenku!
He has awakened.
The seal of memories has been broken.
A storm is brewing.
The coming of the Dark World
is close at hand.
The rebirth of the Remnants is near.
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
Beyond an ancient gateway lies a world
man knows nothing about.
Now, the long period of peace is about to end.
Once again, mankind is about to come into contact with this dark world.
Now, the surviving dark warriors
from ancient battles, the Remnants,
prepare to open the gate
connecting our two worlds
and lead their dark brethren
into our world once again.
However, Tobira High School was built
on the site of the sealed gate in readiness.
Its defenders are warriors known as "Guardians.''
Now, unbeknownst to the populace, the final battle between the two armies approaches.
Throbbing☆Excited★
Dangerous Siblings!
D
Hey, Yuka! Do you know
where Hazumi is? Hazumi.
Hey, it's Takumi! Do you know
where your sister went?
No. I was just looking for her too, Kazuma-senpai.
Well, she was eating ramen a little while ago,
just like Hagiwara is, instead of working.
That can't be true! Did she leave?
What? She's gone home? You can't be serious!
And she didn't even tell her boyfriend!
Who's his girlfriend?
Beats me.
Wait, Yamashiro Kazuma!
Man, stop being so formal
around me, Honda-senpai!
What's with the nasty look?
I don't especially like having to talk to you either.
What exactly is that thing the sophomores lugged in for the festival?
What is it?!
Oh, that thing? It's a powered suit.
I'm not talking about a powered suit!
Don't play dumb with the chairman of the Student Council.
How on earth did you get that thing past...
Hey, you! No motorcycle riding in the hallways!
Where has Hazumi-chan gone?
You guys aren't all that hot as fighters!
That doesn't matter. Anyone who dares face the all-mighty Remnant, McCoy,
is dog shit anyway, including
all of you little baby Guardians!
Dog shit?!
Damn you!
Beautiful Hammer Punch!
Like I said, you're all dog shit!
Should I give you my lovely final blow?
Taste this, fools!
Lord McCoy, what is that?
Dog shit!
Who's that?
Reinforcements?
Called by Heaven, the Earth, and my beeper.
It's...
To support those who protect the seal of the gateway to the other world,
the strongest warrior of the Guardians
and the ultimate female sword-saint,
Jinno Hazumi, has arrived!
My sword can cleave entire galaxies!
Who's that girl?
What did she say again?
It's Hazumi!
We're all gonna die!
It's Jinno Hazumi, the queen of "friendly fire''!
How rude!
Here I am, taking the trouble to save you,
and you make fun of me.
No, I'm not !
Stay away!
You monster!
The Destructive Goddess of Darkness!
Y-You guys...
That nasty bitch hit me
in the face with dog shit!
I won't let you get away with that!
You've made the beautiful Lord McCoy very angry.
You're a lively little slut!
My ass quivers when I think about what I'm going to do to you!
I won't show you any mercy!
We Remnants will tear you Guardians apart
and achieve the goal
we've waited 30,000 years for!
Come on, you little bitch!
I'm gonna turn you into mincemeat!
How dare you wound
this sweet, delicate girl's heart!
What do you mean, "delicate"?!
I'll never forgive any of you!
I didn't say anything yet!
Go to hell!
Jinno Hazumi...
Gotcha!
Mom!
You've still got a lot to learn, Hazumi.
Bye!
You cheater!
Good morning, Takumi-chan.
Good morning, Mom.
This sucks! I lost again this morning!
Come on, Hazumi-san! Hurry up!
Wait up!
We'll miss the bus!
You're always late because you fight
with Mom every morning.
That's because she's still trying
to compete with me.
Look! There are crumbs on your face.
Do you have a handkerchief, Hazumi-chan?
A tissue?
Look, Takumi, I'm not in kindergarten.
You okay?
You'll fall if you don't hold on to the strap.
You should be more careful.
Hey, Takumi, have you gotten taller?
Seems so.
I guess I've had to grow up because I've been worried about a certain clumsy person.
That's not a nice thing to say about your older sister!
You're pushing it!
You get upset so easily, Hazumi-chan.
I was just joking.
Hey, hey, listen up boys and girls on the floor!
I want all of you to make me a little noise!
Let's thank the man who made this all possible - the chairman himself.
He got the student council
to pay for everything!
You're a dead man!
How dare you bring the council into this!
Garden Gate
Tobira 96th Summer Festival
Move it, move it, move it!
Takumi...
We're siblings not related by blood?
What are you so worried about, Hazumi-kun?
Huh?
Tell me why you're so "uptight.''
Who are you talking to, you pervert?!
Damn, I don't need to deal with this!
It's bad for your health to get overexcited.
You're bad for my health!
Well, it's good to see you so lively.
Chiryuu-senpai, do you need something?
Not really.
I was going to peek into the girls' locker room
and noticed that you looked a little worried.
Hazumi-kun.
Yes?
A great battle is approaching.
The Remnants aim to take the gate
within this school and Takumi-kun, the key.
Be careful!
Okay.
White sure is a good color...
You slimeball!
See you later!
No!
Who is that?!
L-Lucky!
Oh, yeah!
He's not a bad person.
A great battle...
The Remnants will be looking for Takumi.
I've got to protect Takumi!
Commemorative Match: Monzen High
Yay, Takumi!
Takumi!
Takumi!
Hey, Takumi! Do your best!
Covering the entire school weakens my barrier?
Sis, the game is starting soon, so would you mind keeping it down a little?
If you keep yelling,
the players will be distracted.
What?
Dear me! Was I that noisy?
Just a tiny bit.
You bitch! Why don't you try acting your age?
You called me, "Sis''! "Sis''!
Don't try to be friendly with me, kid!
What are you thinking? You're his sister!
Are you finished, Hazumi-chan?
Uh... yes.
Why don't we walk around
and see the vendors together?
No, Takumi-kun! You promised to go with me!
Oh, right.
Then let's all go together!
What? The three of us?!
You cow! What a pain!
Just go home, you old bag!
Well, see you later.
See you later.
Jinno Hazumi, I need to have a word with you!
Come with me now!
Jinno Hazumi!
All of you are so cute!
Let's all have a little fun together!
Yahoo!
Taku-nii-san!
Hm, he's pretty cute.
Sexy boy!
I'm Lady Aoi, and I'm going to make you my love pet.
Last night, on the 4-26-3rd block of Miyato-cho,
He loves me...
He loves me not...
a building under construction mysteriously collapsed.
He loves me...
He loves me not...
It was your doing, wasn't it, Jinno Hazumi?
He loves me...
He loves me not...
Even though you defeated the Remnant patrol,
He loves me...
a building was destroyed, and three Guardians were seriously wounded.
He loves me not...
He loves me...
Your lack of self-control
is absolutely out of hand!
He loves me...
He loves me not...
It is for this reason, Jinno Takumi,
that you must hand over responsibility
He loves me...
He loves me not...
for protecting the gate-key over to us.
He loves me...
The Remnants are planning an all-out assault
to seize the gate and open the Dark World.
When they do, you will not be there.
You are relieved of your duties.
I refuse!
I'll protect Takumi.
It's my mission.
How dare you speak that way to your seniors!
Sexy whip!
Takami-kun!
A Remnant!
Could it be...
It's as I predicted! Hand Takumi over to us!
Takumi!
It's been a long time.
I'm so pleased to see you again!
As long as our dark boss, Kijima Touta is here,
you Guardians are nothing but goat shit!
Sign: Ramen Yokocho
I don't have time for this!
Oh, we sure do!
I want my beautiful body back!
I won't let you touch my Takumi!
A little girl dares challenge the erotic powers of the exotic Aoi!
Sexy whip!
Now I'll never get married!
Hime! Look out!
Are you all right, Hime-chan?
I was so scared!
I don't know what I'd do if you weren't here, Takumi-kun.
Hime-chan...
Takumi-kun, I love you!
What you did pleased me.
For that, I'm going to give you my ultimate love, boy.
We're powering up more each day than you could ever imagine!
Iron Kick!
Iron Kick Two!  Two!
I've got to hurry!
Hazumi! Where have you been?
All our dishes are broken, and now,
because of you, the band has run away!
Yuka, I don't have time to discuss this!
Takumi is....
Geez, you've been hanging around Takumi again.
Freeze!
I was never a big fan of ice queens.
You look like the type that just loves 'em and leaves 'em.
Thanks for the compliment!
And let me guess - a stunted dick and a premature ejaculator?
How did you know?!
Freeze!
You bastards! You think you low-ranking Remnants can beat Yasumasa Honda?
Listen, Remnants! Don't go into the school!
I didn't want to face just you.
Why don't you take your souvenir
Monzen rice cracker and go home?
Of course. You don't have any place to return to, do you?
All we want to do is rejuvenate our world.
You don't understand.
We have various purposes and activities in this world too.
You'll wreck this world
if you go through with it.
Soon, the gate will be opened.
It seems so,
but anything you can open, we can close.
I'll kill the key.
You said the same thing thirty thousand years ago.
Do the scars still burn?
Do you still hold a grudge against her?
We've lived in disgrace for far too long.
Unlike us, she has no memory of that time.
She is sure to guard her brother with her life.
Emerge, my Soul!
I don't have time for you to bother me!
We'll see about that!
Super table-flipping technique!
I can't stand cockroaches or stuff like that.
You're like flea shit in comparison with my beautiful power!
Old lady, give up!
Old lady?!
Why don't you admit that you're just too old for this sort of thing?
Super Kitty Punch!
Go, Dirty Wolves!
What the...
Oh no!
Hime-chan!
Beautiful Woody Kick!
Here I come!
Come on!
New Beautiful Hand Punch!
You weren't able to stand against my beauty!
You're really stubborn!
No, you are!
I will never forgive anyone who interferes with me protecting Takumi!
Whatever you try, it won't work on me!
New Beautiful Iron Punch!
Super Technique...
What are you doing?!
Single Stroke Giant Diakon Cut!
Pretty boy, now you die!
Ouch!
Takumi!
Hazumi-chan!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm so relieved!
I'm sorry for coming so late, Takumi.
I knew you were going to come.
Oh, Takumi! Wow!
Thank you, Hazumi-chan.
Look out!
I guess I've had to grow up because I've been worried about a certain clumsy person.
I goofed up again.
Takumi...
Ouch!
I'll never forgive anyone
who tries to hurt my Takumi!
missing
Die!
Super Technique: Blazing Tulips!
What the hell?!
What are these things?!
That's against the rules!
I'm Japan's Number One!
Oh! You're hurt!
Oh, Hime-chan, are you all right?
I'm so happy that you care about me!
Hime!
Hazumi-chan!
Thank you for guarding Takumi.
Not at all. You did a great job too.
But I'll never give up Takumi!
He's mine!
What?!
Say what?!
Jinno Hazumi, I'm bringing you up on charges of destroying the gym and the main building!
missing
Bravo!
Hazumi-kun, you did a great job!
I still think a "T-back'' would be better for next time.
You're a little late!
For goodness sake...
She's right. You missed it all, Chiryuu-senpai.
What have you been doing?
The man in control of the Remnants,
Kijima Touta, has been brought back to life.
Will the Guardians be able to guard the key
and the gate to the Dark World?
What has fate planned for
the lives of Hazumi and Takumi?
Now love and hate will cross each other on the Earth...
maybe.
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
You don't have to worry about hurting me
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
So wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's better, much better
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
Even if you act as your heart desires
isumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty
aishiau kokoro nara
Love each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Things are going well, anything can happen
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's kick some liar's butt
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
joushiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those stupid liars
shinjiau kokoro nara
Believe in each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Things are going well, you can do anything
aishiaeba
If you love each other
daijoubu
Don't worry
So, as you've seen, the Remnants' attack has begun.
Why are they attacking Takumi?
What?
Something happened 30,000 years ago between Kijima and Takumi.
What is Takumi's secret?
Next time on Bakuen Campus Guardress:
Anxious, Fearful:
Are Finals Worse Than the Enemy?!
Takumi, I'll protect you with my life.
Episode 2
Excited☆Fearful★
Are Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
Scheduled Release Date, July 22nd
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
ninjacloud
Collectr
QC1
QC2
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs