Production
Yamagata Hiroyuki
Planning
Nakano Kazuo
Torishima Kazuhiko
Original Work
Hagiwara Kazushi
Akahori Satoru
Everyone watching, can you believe this?
It's an enormous gate!
It suddenly appeared in the Monzen District, and is over one kilometre in height!
It's obviously an artificial structure.
But who could have...?
And for what purpose?
Could this be a divine prank?
Or the devil's conspiracy?
Furthermore, this supernatural battle around the Gate is...
Hazumi. Takumi.
Wait for me, Takumi!
It's because of you that I'm the Key.
T-Takumi...
From now on, I'll always protect you.
Like when we were young.
Don't be so hasty!
I'll always be by your side, Hazumi.
Don't die, Takumi!
COMBUSTIBLE
GUARDRESS
Shredded☆Crumbled★
There Are Many Ways to Win!
Why?! Why sacrifice so many of them just to go back?!
Shut up!
You, who were born to protect those filthy humans, would never understand!
I'll smash you to pieces!!
I'll crush you!
I'll break you!
Hate!!
Hate!
I HATE everything!
Hate! I hate all of you!
All of you make me puke my guts out!
That's it.
So, that's what's driving Kijima Touta!
It's not going back, it's not power, nor is it for the Dark World.
It's...
It's... hatred!
Those damned humans...
They're no better than dung beetles, but they act like they own the world!
Just what use are you to them, you damned bastard?!
You're nothing but a nuisance!
Look!
Your power is nothing! Don't make me laugh!
I didn't stay alive this long just to be covered with shit like you!
I'll destroy everything completely!
And that includes what you assholes call love!
I'll destroy it all!!
Puny humans! Now it's MY turn!!
I get punched. I get stepped on.
What a dirty job.
Take it easy, Kijima! Don't get so serious.
This IS a great world, you know.
You asshole...
Psycho Stampede!
Are you a fool?!
Or are you just making a fool of me?
'Cause you ARE a fool.
Wh...what?
Kijima, you're screwed up.
Just like the last time.
Are you sure, Takumi?
Yes.
Takumi!
Don't be so hasty!
I'm on my way!
Nice try, little girl.
But it ends here.
You're too late now.
The Key, Jinno Takumi, will die!
And the Gate shall be opened.
Shut up!
I won't allow that!
What's this amazing Soul?
So what? We'll just power up, too!
Get ready, little girl! We'll beat ya to a pulp!
And now...
Combination attack: Sexy Dyna-Bust!
Slrrpp, slrrpp.
Come on.
Hurry.
Boing, boing.
Now go to hell!
I won't forgive anyone who hurts Takumi!
I WILL protect Takumi!
From both of you AND his fate!
Even if Takumi likes some other girl.
I don't care if I'm just his sister!
The only thing I can do is protect Takumi!
What's this pathetic looking ball?!
No way!
G...Goal!
Takumi!
Superintendant, there're so many Remnants!
Please, Master Tenku. Hurry and perform the Sealing Ceremony!
Takumi. I'll ask you once more.
Once the ceremony starts, it can't be stopped.
And so, Takumi, your life is...
If my life can protect the one I love...
Kijima Touta!
Chiryuu!
It's the same as before, huh, little girl?
Like the day your continent sank 30,000 years ago!
Everything's the same!
I'll never forgive you!
It...it's starting to open!
This is REALLY bad!
B...Be careful, Hazumi!
Chiryuu! Thank goodness!
The Kijima you face now has gone mad with hatred for you...no, for all mankind.
At a time like this, how can you...?!
Oh, c'mon. It's my last chance to peek at your panties before my last voyage...
Go on your trip by yourself!
You dumb jerks never learn!
Jinno Hazumi!
It's the same as 30,000 years ago, but THIS time I'll crush you into little pieces!
I'll make you suffer so much you'll forget you were even human!
Come on and give me your best!
Kijima Touta.
You're a pitiful man.
What's important to people is to have friends...
...to have fun, and to laugh and live together.
You hate people and think about nothing but fighting and killing.
Shut up!!
What's the use of just having fun?!
Lightning Stride!
Hazumi Special!
Why?!
Why are you so much stronger now?!
'Cause I WON'T lose to someone like you!
Oh, no! You've stepped in some dog shit!
Huh? What?!
Lord Touta!
D...dog shit?
Did I? Did I step in it?
Damn you, Jinno Hazumi!
STOP!
No way!
I'm in a hurry!
Hazumi, don't repeat what you did 30,000 yea...
Lord Touta!
These gods appear at the time of purification...
...the god Yasomagatsui...
...the god Oumagatsui...
...the god Kannaoi...
Takumi!
Get out of my way!
You're not getting away!
Let me go, you pervert!
If I don't hurry, Takumi will die!
Lord Touta!
The Sealing Ceremony has begun!
Before the girl, we should get the Key to the Gate!
You shut up!
L...ord Touta, if they seal it, we'll be stranded in this world again.
We Remnants will...
So what?!
I don't give a damn if the Gate opens or closes!
Lord Touta!
I've waited 30,000 years for this day.
Tenku and Chiryuu's spell stripped away my power and my identity.
They made me forget who I was.
And still, I waited for this day!
Alone, without help, I waited.
So I can strike back with my hunger and hatred!
I don't give a damn about humans or Remnants!
Die, Jinno Hazumi!
Now suffer!
Suffer!
Suffer and die!
You...poor thing...
You poor thing...
What?!
You were so starved that you'd fill the void with anything.
You suffered and suffered, so you hated others and wanted them to suffer too.
That's how you were before.
Kijima Touta, I've never met anyone so insecure and pitiful like you.
What are you saying?
Wait for me, Takumi!
IRIS
Eye Cleaner™
That stinking, gutless bastard figured it out?
Crap!
Super Kijima Power Buildup!
Jinnnno Hazzzumi!
God, you're ugly.
DIE!!!
Die! Die! Die!
Takumi...
...the god Sokotsu Wadatsu...
...the Lord Sokotsuo...
...the god Nakawatatsu...
missing
No matter when...
Hazumi was there.
Hazumi has always cried for me, gotten angry for me, laughed for me.
Hazumi!
Takumi.
Love doesn't exist in this world.
All that exists is hatred!
You're wrong!
There's a girl I've always loved.
Don't tell me, it's your sister Hazumi!
The girl I love isn't my sister.
Takumi.
I can't get up anymore...
I'm sorry...
Jinno Takumi and Tenku! I'll kill both of you together!
Kijima Touta! What a hideous figure!
Yuck! He's ugly!
Divine Purification!
Hazumi!
Ta...Takumi... Am I dreaming?
Hazumi! Hang on!
Takumi... it's too late for me.
Hazumi!
To die in your arms like this...
I'm so happy. I'm...going now...
But, I'm a little disappointed.
I mean, there's already a girl in your life.
But me, I'm just your sister.
That sucks.
Hazumi, you're not my sister!
I kind of knew that we weren't related by blood.
You and mother were always too nice.
Takumi...
Hazumi, the girl I love is...
Yes!! Finally!!!
BIG
SKY
BEAUTY
Called by the sky, the earth, and my beeper!
Summoning the high school babe!
The greatest warrior maiden, Jinno Hazumi, 17 years of age!
My sword can cleave entire galaxies!
Great Masamune
Impossible!
Poor Kijima Touta, you've never found love!
We have created a miracle of love!
Take this soulful hit!
FLY...
...my soul!
Unparalleled Beauty's Ultimate Sword Technique
Die, you damned bitch!
So this...
So, this is love?
O...oops.
muishiki ni sono kokoro osaeteru
You're unknowingly suppressing your feelings
jooshiki no han'i de zutto gaman shiteru
You keep holding yourself back inside the practical world
sorede nantoka naru dounika naru
That'll do it; everything'll be all right
Tomorrow will be better
ommote ikiteirunone minna
Everyone thinks that's what they're living for
Now that the Gate is broken, the two worlds are joined.
There are occasional skirmishes.
Hi! Look at these delicious accessories!
Greetings, everyone! I'll exchange anything for tissue paper.
Those who need my love, come over here!
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
Beautiful
Tissue
Paper
Exchange
So the world didn't get destroyed.
Nope, it didn't.
You want some ice cream, too?
daijobu soko no okata
Hey over there, are you all right?
Sure, bro.
moshikashite ano kimochi wasuretenai yo ne
Don't say that you forgot the feeling
shinjiau kokoro nara
Believe in each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Things are going well; you can do anything
aiashiaeru
We can love each other
hitonokoto kini shiteru gizen yori
You don't have to worry about hurting me
yaseiteki na sono ude de dakitomeru noyo
So wrap your arms around me passionately
sore ga zutto suteki gutto suteki
That's better, much better
kokoro no mama ni ikite mo
Even if you act as your heart desires
tsumi nado dokonimo naiyo kitto
You don't have to feel guilty
aishiau kokoro nara
Love each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Things are going well; anything can happen
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's kick some liar's butt
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
aishiau kokoro nara
Love each other
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo ari dayo
Things are going well; anything can happen
daijoubu Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
yononaka no petenshi yo saa taoshi ni yukou yo
Let's kick some liar's butt
kakumei dayo
It's a revolution
Tobira High,
First Year
Sakura Class,
Jinno Takumi
Today, we all went
to the beach.
daijoubu! Listen to my heart
Don't worry! Listen to my heart
Chiryuu and Kazuma are
still playing with the Remnants
down below. (Boy, they're tough)
jooshiki no petenshi wo ima uzumete shimaou
Now let's beat some sense into those stupid liars
I'm getting a little sunburned,
but the wind feels good.
shinjiau kokoro nara
Believe in each other
Hazumi came back saying,
"Ah, I'm tired!'' and went
to sleep without changing
out of her bathing suit.
(She's hopeless.)
yononaka wa karui mono hora nandemo dekiruyo
Things are going well; you can do anything
aishiaeba
If you love each other
The sunset was neat.
Summer's almost over.
It was a hot and
very busy summer.
But...
I'll never forget
the things that
happened this summer.
daijoubu
Don't worry
Behind the happy tears.
there were men who risked their lives.
Afterward, drink, get rowdy,
let the alcohol take hold, grab her, and get slapped by the Guardress.
Akahori Satoru
Greetings! How was it? I enjoyed it very much.
I'm glad I was able to work with many people
to make this anime.
Hazumi, Takumi, Chiryuu, Tenku, Hime,
Kazuma, and the Rems are still running
around the combined world in my mind.
See you again someday.
Hagiwara Kazushi
Ep 1: Throbbing☆Excited★                Dangerous Siblings
Ep 2: Anxious☆Fearful★Are                 Finals Worse than the Enemy?!
Ep 3: Nervous☆Scared★                A Battle Full of Suffering!!
NOW ON SALE!
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
ToyRC
ninjacloud
Collectr
QC1
QC2
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs