Shinjuku, May
10th Ave
That was hella scary...
Which hospital are you taking me to?
Chichibuyama Clinic.
Ch-Chichibuyama Clinic?!
Let me out!
No! Help me!
Please stop! I don't wanna go there!
Dr. Chichibuyama, we have an emergency patient.
Please hurry up to the operating room.
Scalpel.
There's nothing to be afraid of. Just follow me to underworld, won't you?
Doctor Chichibuyama
Part 2
Sorrowful Separation
A new female doctor?
So cute!
But she's still not here. Being late for your first day on the job is unacceptable!
Once she gets here,
I gotta tell her off decisively.
Yes, decisively!
Excuse me!
I'm Toda Midori, I have recently been appointed to Chichibuyama Clinic.
Sorry I'm late!
Y-You're cute, so I don't mind!
This new female doctor is cute and has a wonderful smile!
That's Dr. Midori.
She is cute indeed...
Okay, let's give you an injection.
Sure!
Oh, my bad! I gave you the wrong injection!
You're cute, so I don't mind!
Umehara-san, what are you looking at?
I'm sorry!
Y-Y-You're cute, I don't mind!
Oh!
I'm sorry, another one just died.
You're cute, so I don't mind!
Oh! Sorry! My hand slipped again.
Y-Y-Y-You're cute, so I don't mind!
Isn't Dr. Midori cute?
She's a bit clumsy, though.
That only makes her even cuter.
Hi!
Dr. Midori!
I-Isn't the weather nice?
Wanna know a secret?
Huh? What is it?
Your illness will never be cured!
Huh?
There's one more thing...
Wanna hear it?
Huh? Wh-What is it?
You only have half a year to live.
C-C-Cu-Cu...
He doesn't mind.
Doesn't mind.
Did I say something wrong?
You're cute, so I don't mind!
The Return of Dr. Koshigaya
What? You've got a hangover?
Don't yell, my head's throbbing!
That's what happens
when you drink cheap alcohol.
I think I asked you not to yell!
That's for leaving your yesterdays' operation unfinished and then going drinking without me!
Serves you right!
Ugh! Will you ever quit yelling?!
Not my fault the operating room is so tiny!
Let's cancel it, then!
Now, now.
Yeah, calm down, won't you?
Right. And give this back.
Now, please continue.
Speaking of that, I wonder what Koshigaya has been up to lately.
Doctor Chichibuyama
headed to Africa in search of the missing Dr. Koshigaya.
Koshigaya, I hope to find you in good health...
It definitely smells of Koshigaya down here.
Don't tell me Koshigaya let himself get eaten!
Ah! Is that...!
Anyone wants to play submarine?
Soft... So soft...
Ko-Koshigaya!
...So nice!
Oh, Chichibuyama-kun!
I-I see you're still in high spirits, Koshigaya?
Chichibuyama-kun, did you come to pick me up?
Yes, yes! Such a welcome sight!
By the way, Chichibuyama-kun, you've had your shots against yellow fever and malaria, right?
Well, I'll take my leave now.
Dr. Koshigaya, you don't have to return to Japan anymore!
Whoa there, Chichibuyama-kun! Wait a minute!
Hey, wait, Chichibuyama-Chan!
No! Oh no, you can't do that, Dr. Koshigaya!
Come back!
A Frog Call to You
W-W-What panties do you have on you now?
Try to guess.
The ones with a hole in the middle?
Mi-ssed it.
Better luck next time!
Jeez, so many perverts on the phone these days!
Beautiful World
It's cloudy...
Yeah...
I was hoping to show her
a more beautiful scenery.
Hmm... But summer sun might also be too strong for her first time seeing.
Perhaps it's a blessing in disguise for her.
Now, Hiroko-Chan, let's take off the bandages.
Go ahead, Hiroko-kun.
Slowly open your eyes.
For the first time in life,
you'll see this world as it is.
I'm scared!
It'll be okay, Hiroko-Chan.
Come on, be brave.
No! I can't do it.
How can you say that, Hiroko-Chan?
You should stay strong.
I'll be here, watching over you.
So don't worry, okay?
Hiroko-Chan, hang on!
What on earth are you thinking?
Beautiful world.
A sturdy world.
Come on, muster up your courage
and take a look, Hiroko-kun.
Angels and Demons
Okay, next patient.
Doctor.
Get seated.
Where does it hurt?
M-My type exactly!
Um, my symptoms are very severe...
Right, right, let's listen to your chest first.
O-Okay...
Perfectly round!
She is my ideal, in everything!
Take advantage of my position and grope her breasts?
No! If I do that, it'll damage my reputation as a doctor...
Go for it!
Yeah, you're right—that's what the doctor's position is for.
No, on the other hand,
that's such a cowardly act...
You'll later regret letting this chance slip!
You don't have any reputation as a doctor anyhow.
Do it! Do it! Do it!
H-Hold up, you two. Usually, there'd be an angel and a devil fighting in my mind.
What the hell happened to the angel?
Who even cares for that guy?
Dunno nuffin'.
I'm going home, Doctor.
No, wait a minute!
I should have groped it...
Patient's Grave
Chichibuyama Clinic Cemetery
Forgive me, everyone.
You died because of me...
You're cute, so we don't mind...
No! No more!
Just you wait, everyone.
It won't take long.
Hold it, Midori-kun.
Dr. Chichibuyama!
I don't know what you're looking for, standing there, but the answer won't be beyond that edge.
I can't find the confidence
to continue working as a doctor.
All I do is mistakes.
Because you're cute, you can make all mistakes you want and I won't mind.
No! No matter how cute you say I am, there must be a limit to how many people I can kill!
How many do you think that is?
Something like 300, I believe.
In that case, why not raise it just a bit?
Target: 358 people!
But I can't do it anymore..
Midori-kun, don’t let the failure scare you.
A doctor must have a strong spirit
that is unafraid of failure.
Oh, I know. I'll train you to have a strong spirit myself.
Dr. Chichibuyama!
That's the spirit, Midori-kun!
Keep up the good work!
Yes!
I'm not Midori!
It's "Mistress" for you!
Drive Safely Today
Safe driving—are you adhering to it?
Fasten your seatbelt
Road Safety Week
Have you fastened it—you seatbelt?
Quack right. Can't forget about my seatbelt.
Megumi-chan's Case
I want to tell you something!
That's enough.
Roberto...
I want to kiss you.
What should I do?
Won't our noses bump into each other?
It's true!
They didn't get in the way.
I can do it now...
Oh? Where are you going, Megumi-Chan?
Don't run in the hallway, it's dangerous.
Wow, you made it!
Don't push yourself too hard, Megumi-Chan.
Oh, Megumi-Chan, you shouldn't enter without permission.
What's the matter, Megumi-Chan?
Tell me, doctor!
What is it?
Don't your balls get in the way when you do sex?
What?!
Balls clink against each other!
Sayuri-san's Case
Hey, Doctor...
Wh-What's gotten into you, Sayuri-kun?
Oh no, you're feigning innocence again.
But didn't you say I have pretty lips before?
W-Well, maybe I did...
You made me so happy!
Hey...
Hold it! What is it you're doing down there? Hey!
No need to hold back.
You'll like me playing your flute.
Ah! I like a good flute tune. You're right!
Well... T-T-There's no denying that, you playing is quite something.
Stethoscope
A Doctor's Friend
What's wrong, Doctor?
Right, I just need to find my stethoscope.
Now, where did I put it?
Oh, there it is!
It wasn't a stethoscope...
Come on! Put your chest here. Your chest!
I've changed my mind about going to your clinic.
Pearls
Make Women Happy
Y-You see, I wanted to ask you for a pearl implant.
Now then, Chichiko-Chan, where does it hurt?
Here? Maybe here?
No, Doctor!
That's not where it hurts!
Oh, no need to be shy,
let me rub it some.
No, no!
Are you gonna implant pearls in me or not?!
I think I'll need to operate you! Rub-rub.
No, no!
Are you deaf or what?!
Implant fucking pearls into me there!
Very well.
Operation underway
Ugh. It was the most rewarding surgery in a long time.
What the hell?!
Who asked you to implant it in my forehead?
Do you think I'm Buddha or something?!
It comes with a death ray module.
What?!
I wouldn't overdo it if I were you.
It only lasts 3 minutes on Earth.
Thief Cat
A Cat That Steals People's Fish
Ah! Get back here, you thief cat!
It's going that way!
After it! Ueee!
What? After it?
After it?
Lady Has a Weak Constitution
Oh? Hey, Lady...
You have a weak constitution,
you shouldn't be lifting such heavy things.
It's fine.
But if you overstress your body...
It'll be touched
by fatigue.
You have a weak constitution, Lady.
If you subject your body to such extreme stress,
it'll be touched... Touched...
I wanna touch it.
Not happening!
My God, this clinic's director...
Whoa there, Lady!
You have a weak constitution.
If you lift such heavy things,
your body will be touched...
Don't come near me!
Jeez...
W-Was it something I said...?
I'm a doctor.
I've been one for a long time.
And so, I've seen many cases
that left a sour taste in my mouth.
Yukari... Yukari, open your eyes!
Yukari!
Not even the most gifted doctor can bring the dead back to life.
Black magic can save what medical science can't.
Who's there?
A-Are you a snake oil salesman?
N-No...
W-Where did that come from?
I'm an honest-to-god witch!
Witch?
What's this?
Sprinkle of Life.
Sprinkle of Life?
A sprinkle on top that breathes life into the dead.
Should I give it a try?
My panties are too revealing!
Okay, it seems to work.
How would I live my life now?
Doctor?
Bringing your wife back to life is my responsibility.
Is that true?
It might just me.
Sayuri!
Dear!
Hold it!
Chichibuyama's reserving magic!
Here, reserved for Chichibuyama.
Reserved for Chichibuyama
Reserved for...
Chichi...
It feels good once you get used to it—
extra large enema...
Chichibuyama-kun.
Don't you think our number of customers...
I mean, patients has decreased?
That's true... Are we gonna have to go promote our clinic like in the old times?
Yeah, let's do that.
You, Lady!
That complexion is no good.
How about a hospitalization?
You'll enjoy our intravenous drip!
Ah! You, the young lady!
Why don't you take the plunge and get sick?
We have the greatest pathogens available!
So?
Ah, I'm stonewalled...
Hey, young man, wanna get hospitalized?
We have some fine nurses.
Ah, but we'll also find some male nurses,
if that's your jam!
If you hospitalize now,
the first injection is free of charge!
How does that sound?
Chichibuyama Clinic is all the rage now!
How is it going, Chichibuyama-kun?
A complete waste of time.
Chichibuyama-kun!
Dr. Koshigaya...
It's stopped snowing.
By the time they realized it,
Ueee Birds covered the sky completely.
No, more like the Ueee Birds have completely engulfed the Earth.
This unexpected second invasion by the Ueee Birds led to the downfall of Earth.
Doctor Chichibuyama Part 2
Sorrowful Separation
The End
The Earth turned into a sea of fire,
and soon, it was covered in ashes.
Doctor Chichibuyama—Part 3
Dawn in the Burned Ruins
People's spirit was broken.
Hey, you! The minors aren't allowed to drink and smoke!
That's why I'm fuckin' doin' it.
Hey, you! You're not allowed to ride the bike in school!
Cretin, that's why I'm fuckin' ridin' it!
Hey, you!
Whaling is prohibited!
I don't care!
Will the human race continue descending into the abyss of chaos?
Isn't there a way for us to put the human spirit
back on the path of kindness?
Setogai Elementary School
Let's start playing baseball.
We're in trouble!
Natsume-sensei, those birds are occupying our field again!
We'll win today.
We've trained so hard for this day!
Ain't no way this works.
They're too strong!
What are you saying, people?!
We won't know until we try!
Let's fight to the end!
Ueee
Seto
Do your best, everyone!
Sorry!
Don't worry!
We'll get them!
Sorry...
Don't worry! It's nothing.
Stay strong!
Ueee
Seto
Come on! It's still nothing!
What's with you all?
Cheer up! We might still win tomorrow.
Fight on! Don't cry, everyone!
Nothing's over yet! Fight on!
Tomorrow brings a brave new day.
What a resilient young man.
He's the one I've been looking for!
Huh? You want me to work at a hospital?
Yes, what the world needs now is people like you.
Operation underway
Oh crap!
I-I-It's okay... I-It's o-okay...
Ah! Bungled it again!
It's okay! It's okay...
Oops!
Another one died!
You're cute, so I it's okay!
Oh no!
It's okay!
Ah, did it again!
There goes another one!
You're cute, so I don't mind! It's okay!
Shit, it slipped!
It's okay!
It's okay! You're cute, so I don't mind!
It's okay! It's ok... Ah!
You're cute, so I don't mind! It's okay!
It's okay! You're cute, so I don't mind!
It's okay! It's okay!
You're cute, so I don't mind!
Thus, with the help of "It's Okay Boy,"
the world regained its spirits.
Doctor Chichibuyama—Part 3:
Dawn in the Burned Ruins
The End
All we just do is just a little acupuncture
With some hypnotherapy on the side
Biofeedback is technical
With a dazzling simulation
People are born crying
They die disappointed
Everyone is on their own journey with no idea where they're going
This is so troublesome
And that is troublesome too
I won't do that surgery, it's a pain in the ass
I'm not in the mood,
I can't feel his pulse
Even if he was still alive, he isn't anymore!
The probe won't come out!
It just won't!
But wipe your tears,
there's plenty more!
RAW acquisition, encoding
Translation
Quality check
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Anonymous
I won't help, he won't recover,
won't come to his senses
No!
So boring, but I don't lose hope,
'cos this is the end!