Chichibuyama Clinic
Dr. Chichibuyama, we have an emergency patient.
Please hurry up to the operating room.
Operation in progress
Scalpel.
There's nothing to be afraid of. Just follow me to underworld, won't you?
Doctor Chichibuyama
The Last Leaf
From that tree...
What is it, Michiko-Chan?
When the last leaf falls from that tree...
My life will end...
No! You shouldn't lose heart!
Michiko-Chan...
Dr. Chichibuyama!
Don't worry.
The last leaf will never fall.
Because it's this one!
What the hell?
Is he supposed to be my doctor?
That's what I'd like to know.
Wait! Wait, leaf! Leaf...
I certainly think that Dr. Chichibuyama is a humorous and interesting person.
But…
Don't you think this is going too far?
Reserved for Chichibuyama
How uncultured can he be?!
He's a disgrace to all doctors!
Let's tell it to him openly today!
Well then...
Reserved for young moms
Groass...
Hot Night with a Lover
Oh no! You're being so impatient, Doctor...
Oh?
You're so naughty, Doctor!
No! It tickles!
Let me show you something interesting.
Huh?
Transform! Kamen Rider!
She didn't buy it...
She didn't buy it!
Doctor, I liked it.
Hey, I liked it!
I liked it a great deal, you hear?
I liked it!
Who's there?
K-K-Koshigaya!
Chichibuyama-kun, look!
Porn
Semi-nude,
urinating
It's a bit embarrassing,
but please watch
I got a new good video.
K-K-Koshigaya...
"Porn, semi-nude, urinating.
It's a bit embarrassing, but please watch."
Looks interesting.
By the way, Chichibuyama-kun,
what have you been up to?
Uh? No, no! It's nothing.
But I'm afraid even I'm not abnormal enough to appreciate this...
Don't worry, once you get into it,
it's a lot of fun.
Well, if you say so...
Embarrassing! Embarrassing!
Semi-
nude.
Urinating.
As indeed.
It's a bit embarrassing, but please watch it again.
Chichibuyama-kun!
Why, you!
W-Wait! The TV and deck aren't to blame.
Just the tape in it!
If you're going to crush it...
Who's there?!
Chichibuyama-kun...
K-Koshigaya! But we're on the second floor!
Don't worry about that.
Look at what I've got instead.
Porn
Pretty girl's embarrassing moment
Koshigaya, it'll work this time, right...?
Certainly.
Sexy video, pretty girl.
An embarrassing moment.
An embarrassing moment for a pretty girl!
Pretty girl's embarrassment...!
And...
Looks like it worked this time.
What should I do?
Really? You can't even solve such a simple problem?!
I can't even solve such basic problems...
I'm... embarrassed!
Embarrassed...
Pretty girl's embarrassing moment
The End
Chichibuyama-kun!
Motherfucker...
The TV or the deck aren't to blame!
I'll say it again,
if you're going to crush it...
Who's there?
K-Koshigaya!
Wow, you could recognize me by my butt alone, Chichibuyama-kun?
Of course I did! You and I are the only two people on earth who'd do something like this!
Chichibuyama-kun,
I've got something solid this time.
Video draw!
Is that a monster?
Wh-What?!
Porn: a young naked woman spreads her legs apart and takes a naughty pose.
Porn: a young naked woman spreads
her legs apart and takes a naughty pose
How could that possibly be a dud?
You've found the real thing!
Listen, you can't screw this up.
You know what the enemy does to the enemy spies who fall to them, don't you?
Screw up! Don't take too long!
Wait, Chichibuyama-kun.
Don't rush it.
Password.
A young naked woman spreads her legs apart and takes a naughty pose.
An advance for our next project.
End of play
Ch-Ch-Chichibuyama-kun!
Take this! This!
Shit! Shit!
Die, die, die!
Ch-Chichibuyama-kun!
W-Wait! The TV and the deck are not to blame.
If you're going to kill, kill me! Kill...
Huh?
Die!
Really! What's your deal, destroying your own hospital?!
Pipe it down!
How could a woman ever understand our devastation?
Idiot.
Kumiko-chan's Case
Okay, open your mouth, Kumiko-Chan.
A-a-ah!
Yes, you're a good girl.
Well then, why don't you bare your tummy now
and lie on the bed over there?
Oh?
What seems to be the problem?
Kumiko-Chan, let's take your shirt off.
You're a big girl, so you can do it yourself, right?
All right. But I want you to understand something, Doc.
I'm really not in favor of sex without love.
But if it's for work, oh well...
Come on, let's get this over with.
M-M-May I, madam?!
Examine her properly!!
Groass.
Madoka-chan's Case
Not happening!
I won't sleep!
This won't do, Madoka-Chan.
It's late, so you have to go to sleep.
No! I always have a stuffed panda with me when I sleep at home!
I would never go to sleep without it!
Madoka-Chan, can I come in?
I can, can't I?
I'm comin' in, then!
What? What's going on?
No! Weird doctor from the corridor is not allowed to enter!
Hey! Why won't you open up?!
Dammit! They're always harassing me for being a stuffed panda!
Here you go, Panda-san.
Thanks for the meal!
Reiko-chan's Case
Sweat.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hey! Don't play hide and seek
in the operating room!
8, 9, 10...
Found the Doctor!
Ready or not, here I come!
Let's see... Who do we have here...
Ah! Found the patient!
Tsk. Found already.
Sachine-chan's Case
Middle school for girls "Shomu Chichibu"
Lively
Hey, did you know?
It seems, the boys' balls have something like a stitch at the back.
Oh? Really?
Wow!
Lively
It's true!
So cute!
Lively
Middle school girls are the worst!
Sayuri-san's Case
Hey, Dr. Chichibuyama...
What's gotten into you, Sayuri-kun?
Oh no! You're so insensitive for a Doctor...
What do you mean?
Doctor, you don't find my body alluring?
S-Sayuri-kun...
What's wrong, Doctor? Don't you feel our two bodies gravitating together?
I-I-I probably do...
There's something wrong with my body...
Don't you want to find out?
What's wrong with it...
What is wrong with it?!
Sayuri-kun!
Ready or not, here I come!
Huh? Doctor,
is something wrong with Sayuri?
No, I don't see anything wrong at all.
Chichibuyama-chan's Case
Doctor! What time do you think it is now?
I don't care! I won't sleep!
I won't ever sleep without a girl in a sailor suit by my side!
I said I won't sleep.
Doctor, if I were you, I'd hold the door just about now.
Hold it!
Argle-bargle!
Here I am!
Idiot.
Doctor Chichibuyama
Born in Saitama
Specialty: Surgery
Personality: Playful
Hobby: Picking up girls
Doctor Koshigaya
Born in Saitama
Specialty: Pediatrics
Personality: Kind
Hobby: Picking up girls
Whoa there! Chichibuyama-kun,
you definitely look dressed to nines today!
It's still nothing.
You're the one who looks so young,
casually draping that killer summer sweater!
Where are you two going dressed like that?
Isn't that obvious?
We're going to find and pick up
some hot chicks!
Well then, shall we go, Dr. Koshigaya?
Sure.
Let's go!
They'll be picking up girls while we're swamped?!
Hey, pretty ladies!
How about some tea,
and some disco afterwards?
You'll see why everyone
wants to be friends with me, General Nogi! Yes!
Chichibuyama-kun!
I'm not seeing any women to pick up down here!
Koshigaya! Forget about picking someone up,
pray that some ship picks us up!
Huh?
Is that why you called it a "pickup session"?!
No! That's why we're not picking anyone up!
Is that why it's called "pickup" session?
No! Not that pick-up!
If so, why did you call it that...
'Sup, ladies! Would you like some tea... with me?
They agreed.
Oh no, you won't make good tea by boiling me!
What I meant is, "would you like to drink some tea together?"
Croaker
Origin: -
Specialty: -
Personality: -
Hobby: Groass
It doesn't work...
Whistle for Small Birds
Doctor!
Ah, Hitomi-Chan? What is it?
The whistle for small birds doesn't work.
Let's see.
Doctor, blow it again.
Very well.
Hey, Doctor.
What is it?
Ocarina for small birds!
I can't play it well.
Let's see...
Doctor, try blowing it again.
All right...
Doctor!
Flute for small birds!
I can't play it well.
Let's see.
W-Wait just a moment, Doctor.
W-What are you doing?
Hey, Doctor!
Balloon whistle for small birds!
Ah, wait! Hitomi-Chan,
why don't you go outside instead?
Okay? We'll go get some juice together!
Doctor, I can't play the harmonica for small birds well.
Let's see.
Stop it, both of you!
Just take a look!
What on earth are those?!
Ueee Bird
Origin: Space
Specialty: Ueee
Personality: Ueee
Hobby: Ueee
And the world descended into panic
New York
Paris
London
Hong Kong
Moscow
Alaska
South Pole
Australia
Africa
Japan
The world is on the brink of destruction because of the monsters from outer space!
Isn't there a way for us to repel these invaders?!
So far, there's nothing for us to broadcast but more destruction from all over the world!
Is there no hope for humanity?!
No cutting-edge weapons seem to have any effect on them at all!
They just toy with anything we throw at them!
Ah! The flames have already reached here!
People are on fire!
That car just exploded! Anyone...
Is anyone still alive?
Is there anyone watching this broadcast at all?!
Things were just starting to look up!
But now the whole world is a scorched hellscape!
How many people do you think have already died?
It's probably over 100 million already!
Ah, how did it come to this?!
Why is this all happening to us?
W-Who are you?!
I-I-It appears the time has come
for my final broadcast!
It's been a pleasure to know all of you!
Praying for the future of humanity,
I bid my farewell to you!
As a news announcer, I'm happy to have been able to broadcast for you until my final moments!
There had never been a creature as marvelous as a human! Banzai!
Where are you going, Doctor?
To save the earth!
Isn't it a doctor's duty
to save people's lives?
Dr. Chichibuyama...
Switch on!
Eat this!
Chichikitoku, come home soon
—Mom
Chichikitoku, come home soon.
Ueee Birds left.
And so,
I saved the earth gloriously.
The sun of the next day, which the world had already given up on, has risen.
Life returned to its usual course, as if nothing had happened.
Feels nice!
Doctor Chichibuyama—Episode 1:
Sturm und Drang—The End