Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Ah, I’ve eaten far too much lunch.
I’ll never be able to keep awake next lesson.
It’s all right.
We’ve got art with Miss Walker this afternoon.
Whatever you do, it doesn’t matter.
Hey, don’t say that,
that's not fair to Miss Walker.
She’s a kind and nice teacher.
That’s true.
Of course you two always enjoy it.
You’re good at drawing
and get praised every time.
Hm!
I don’t enjoy it one bit.
Don’t be silly, Doris.
Come on, it’s time!
Let’s go!
Quick!
Well then, I’ll use it for a bit of a rest.
And I’ll catch a nap.
Episode 21
Miss Walker’s Gift
Today we’ll be making trinket boxes
from these boards.
You may design them however you like—
carve on the lid, paint on the surface—anything.
What I want is something original and pretty.
I’ve written the steps out
on a handout for you.
Next week, at the end of this lesson,
we’ll have a review.
So you must finish them by then.
Miss Walker, we can’t possibly
do it in so short a time.
You’ve a whole week, haven't you? The art room
shall stay open after school until bedtime.
You may use the tools freely.
Now, let us begin.
I need to use my time wisely...
What kind of trinket box should I make?
Sigh... Perhaps, I’ll paint a picture on the lid?
Ah... So much for a nap today.
Never mind—Miss Walker always says the same thing afterwards, remember?
“Set yourselves free,
and savour the joy of imagination!”
Okay!
See now?
Once she starts sketching,
it’s always the same.
She's so carefree!
It's as if we were on another planet entirely!
You're right.
Let's make a productive use of it, then.
Doris and Vera aren't in the least bothered
about running out of time!
We’ve no time to waste worrying about others.
We must hurry too.
Y-Yeah.
What’s the matter?
It swerved!
You gave me such a fright!
I thought you’d cut your hand or something.
It's not easy for me.
Joan, you’ll ruin the saw like that.
First, hold the board steady.
Grip it like this.
Only put in your strength when you push,
and find your rhythm.
Oh, I see...
Don’t rush, go for "slow and steady."
What matters is creating something yourself,
even if it’s clumsy at first.
Whoa! I’ve done it!
Look, Isabel!
Wow! You're a natural, Pat.
I’m a rather handy girl, you know.
It’s nothing much, so why even bother?
Nonsense! Better to be able to do it than not.
Oh, by all means!
I'm sure the furniture shop will come begging you
to become a master craftsman before long.
Furniture shop, right...
Bother... All the teachers set us up
with extra work this week.
Exactly! Miss Roberts
with her problem practice handouts,
Mam’zelle with her essay...
Miss Lewis and her timeline tables,
and on top of it all—
that wretched trinket box!
The mistresses only ever think
of their own lessons.
Especially Miss Walker,
just living in a world of her own.
Talk about eccentric artists.
Say, Doris, weren’t you given extra work by Mam’zelle?
Can you manage?
Yes, I did a bit during art just now.
Figures. But what about the art class?
You’ve not done a thing yet.
Ah, it’s quite all right!
I’ve got it all thought out.
You’ll be too late if you don’t hurry. Quick!
Wait for me, Doris!
Where are we going?
Never mind, just come along.
I’m sure it was around here somewhere…
Ah, there it is!
Good afternoon.
G-Good afternoon.
Are you a craftsman here?
Not yet, I’m still an apprentice.
Making things must be a wonderful job.
I’m Doris—what’s your name?
Me?
S-Steve.
I see. Well then, Steve, could you make something like a little trinket box, about this size?
I can make anything!
Could you make one for me?
I haven’t much money, though.
Doris! What are you...
Just a plain box will do.
Nothing fancy, just a box.
I’d have to ask the master.
I’m not allowed to take on work by myself.
That’s all right, Steve.
Rest assured, charming young ladies—
he's only half-trained, but keen as mustard!
Let him do it for practice.
Really, Master?
Aye, but only so long as you make one
that won’t bring embarrassment to our shop.
I won’t!
What a relief!
Thank you, sir!
Vera, what about you?
Er... I mean... we shouldn't...
We’ll just get the box made
and then paint something on it.
Yes, I think I will, then.
Right! I’ll work my hardest on it!
Eh? You asked a furniture maker’s apprentice?
You can’t do that!
It’s only the box!
Only because I’m hopeless with a saw myself.
I’ll do the finishing touches myself.
We’ve heaps of other homework,
there’s simply not enough time.
He said if we brought our own wood,
he’d only charge for his time.
Only five shillings!
Eh?
Well—that’s rather cheap.
Isn’t it? And you should see
that apprentice boy, ever so shy and sweet.
When we barely smiled at him,
he blushed scarlet!
Really, it’s not right to tease
or take advantage of such a simple soul.
We're not taking advantage—
he said himself he wanted to do it for practice.
Anyway, now I can tackle
the rest of my homework in peace.
What will Miss Walker say if she finds out?
It’s all right! She's so kind, more like a friend than a teacher. She won't even punish us.
Quite so. She’ll just frown a little
and say, “Why, Doris, you seem suddenly clever with your hands!”
Now, that’s the end for today.
It's half past eight, we must go.
Indeed.
Pat, what about you?
I'm almost finished.
Go on ahead without me.
Very well. Goodnight, then.
Don't take long.
Aye.
Not too shabby…
Oh, crumbs! The lid doesn’t fit!
Right, I could trim it down...
No, that won't do.
I've carved it right to the edge—
if I cut it, it’ll ruin the art.
How didn’t I notice before?
And after all the work I’ve put in…
Over there!
Here we are, the planks,
for Vera’s and mine.
Be a sweetheart, won't you?
Sure.
Ah, this is my friend, Pat.
She’s something to ask you.
Good evening, Steve.
Hm... The measurements are all a bit off.
It won’t make a proper box like this.
But this picture is ace!
Do you think so?
Yes, quite remarkably done.
Thank you! I carved it myself.
And this is meant to be the lid, isn’t it?
Then I’ll make the box to fit it.
Eh? Oh, no...
That’s not what I meant, I just hoped
you'd help me get the measurements right.
Go on, let him do it.
But Doris...
You carved the lid yourself, all right.
No harm in letting him make the box.
I suppose.
Let's do that, then.
Sure thing.
Honestly, Pat! You mean you’ve had that apprentice Steve make it for you?
Hm... I didn’t really mean to.
It just sort of happened.
But remember what Miss Walker said—
what matters is creating it yourself, however clumsy.
Aye, I know.
But I did carve the lid myself.
Pat…
Anyway, I’m off to do my history charts.
It's for both of us, mind you.
Pat!
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
The Twins at St. Clare's
There! French prep finished!
Mam’zelle won’t be able
to call it abominable now!
I wonder if the others are still in the art room?
I expect so.
Wasn’t it lucky we asked Steve?
Yes! We're already drowning in other homework, we did the right thing!
R-Right...
Ah! Bother!
What's wrong?
I’ve chiselled away too much!
It’s all right—just do the same on all the other notches,
and it'd look neat when finished.
You think so?
Yeah... It might even be better that way.
Hold it steady.
I’ll tie the string now to keep it in place.
Sure.
Yours is coming out so neat, you're lucky.
It was hard at first,
but once I got the hang of it, it was fun.
I’m going to use mine for jewellery.
And I’ll keep sweets in mine!
That’s just like you, Joan!
Can I help you?
Er... Which way to the dormitory?
This is a girls’ school, young man!
Gentlemen are not allowed in the dormitories.
Oh... That's a nuisance.
I was looking for a certain Doris...
Steve!
Thank goodness!
I came to deliver this,
but didn’t know where to go.
Patricia O'Sullivan!
M-Mam’zelle!
What is the meaning of this?
W-Well, we just asked the carpenter in town
to do a bit of repairs for us...
R-Right...
H-Here you are.
You can pay me next time you’re in town.
Bye!
Pat!
Yes?
Next time, fetch it yourself.
To have it delivered—by a boy, too!
Oh, abominable!
I—I’m sorry, Mam’zelle.
I’ll be more careful.
Criminy! My heart very nearly stopped!
Dash! He's finished them all already!
Steve's even decorated
and varnished them for us.
He meant well.
We never told him it was for our art class.
What shall we do?
Why not? It’s beautifully made.
I’m handing it in as it is.
Yes, they’re all a little different, so it's all right.
Right...
It may be a little too fancy, though...
There! Just a coat of polish and mine’s done.
Good! I think I’ll manage to finish mine
in time too. Thank goodness!
I feel like celebrating!
I can’t help feeling uneasy
unless I’ve added something myself.
Time’s up! Let’s go.
Sure...
What do you think?
I-It's very well done, but...
Well, this will have to do.
I’ll hand this in.
Now then, let’s unveil your works.
Please place your boxes on the centre table.
When they're all on display like this,
ours look the smartest, don’t you think?
Considering the time limit,
you’ve all done well.
Each piece is different,
and very interesting.
Now, what do we think of this one?
I’d say it’s most carefully done.
And the carving is lovely.
Yes—the shape is plain, but the rounded corners
give it a soft, modern feel.
Who made this one?
I did.
So I thought.
It feels very Isabel-like, doesn't it?
If I were picky, I’d say it’s a little too perfect.
Perhaps it could have used a bit more colour.
Hm! This one has real presence in it.
E-Excuse me.
When I tried to assemble it,
the measurements didn’t quite match,
But somehow, it feels warm and inviting.
It really shows Joan’s character.
I also should have done
everything myself, after all.
This dahlia carving is beautiful!
Miss Walker, that’s actually a rose.
Oh? I beg your pardon.
Well, that concludes today’s session.
Um, Miss Walker, but there's still...
Those whose work has been reviewed may leave. The rest of you, stay.
Pick up your pieces now.
All three are really well done.
But what's this feeling?
I can’t hear your voices in them.
Look closely.
All the other pieces seem to be chattering away.
They’re all asserting themselves,
showing who made them.
Even if they’re a little uneven,
aren’t they charming?
This one is certainly very precise and skilfully done.
Yet it doesn’t say anything about you.
Miss Walker, I had someone else make my box.
I carved the lid myself, but the measurements were wrong, and it became a hassle.
I’m sorry.
Miss Walker, I didn't make mine either.
There wasn’t enough time.
There was so much homework this week...
Mam'zelle said I’d be thunderstruck
if I scored poorly on the next French test.
Honestly, I’m not good at art.
I’m clumsy...
I’m hopeless at both drawing and craft!
I can only dance, somewhat.
I figured if I could just dance well,
the rest didn’t matter.
“Just dance well,” you say?!
Y-Yes.
With that attitude,
your dancing will never improve.
Oh, no…
Doris, Pat, Vera—hands out, like this.
The thing that makes human hands different from other animals is that we use them to create things.
We all have similar hands, yet what Van Gogh,
Cézanne, Picasso created are all different.
That is called individuality.
That is what we call art—
creating something only you can make.
Anyone who can’t uphold this basic attitude,
can't get good at dancing,
let alone live her life in her own way.
It’s a shame.
These hands could do so much more.
I want them to know the joy of creation.
Today's lesson was very disappointing.
I’ll give marks later.
Now, everyone, it’s tea time.
O-Okay...
I didn’t expect Miss Walker to get so angry.
Ah, it’s all over now...
We failed.
But it’s our own fault.
Oh, I don't doubt Miss Walker
knows the joy of creation, all right!
After all, she spends class time drawing
whatever she likes while leaving us to our own devices!
That’s not true, Doris.
Uh?
Miss Walker is drawing for your sake.
For us?
She gives her drawings as parting gifts
to the graduating students.
She sketches your work
during first form lessons.
Eh? So then, those sketches…
These are portraits of you
Miss Walker draws with all her heart,
so you would never forget how you felt
when you first started studying at St. Clare's.
Eh?
That’s my drawing.
And this one’s mine.
Miss Walker...
Yes?
Do let us try making it again, Miss Walker.
Please!
I feel ashamed for the careless attitude
that I was taking your classes with.
I’m sorry! I was so wrong
in my judgement of you!
Miss Walker!
It's so frustrating!
I'm incredibly angry at myself now.
That feeling is important.
If you pour it into your work, it will surely become something wonderful, such as your dancing.
Miss Walker...
Pat and the others sure are late.
I bet they're gonna work all night.
Criminy!
Pat, Doris, Vera... do your best!
We’ve got special permission from Headmistress,
so pace yourselves accordingly.
Okay!
Good. I'll get to it too.
Is Vera the model today?
Yes. Finally I can draw her as intended.
After all, during my regular classes, Vera...
I'm sorry. I promise I won’t doze off in class again.
Isabel, I’ve finally realised
the joy of making something yourself.
And how much thought and care
Miss Walker puts into her lessons.
She’s such a remarkable artist,
and an extraordinary teacher too.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Pat, do you know Gladys?
The girl working out in the dining hall lately, right?
Yes—have you seen her hands?
They are awfully red and cracked!
Poor thing.
She washes hundreds of plates every day.
Her father passed away, they said.
So she’s working instead of going to school?
Yes! I've got an idea!
Me too, Pat!
Let’s start a cheering club for Gladys!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Run, Gladys!"
Episode 22
Run, Gladys!
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End