Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Okay, that should be settled.
I wonder what Mother will be sending us.
I wrote and told her we’ve plenty of friends with good appetites here, so have no fear.
There’ll surely be a feast so big
it could feed us for a month.
I can’t wait...
Let’s make it a splendid party.
Of course.
Oh, shall we pop by the cake shop?
Good idea!
Wow, that looks delicious!
I daresay Mother will bake us
a pie or something as well.
But I’d like a cake smothered in whipped cream.
Something like that would please everyone.
But it’s dear—perhaps a bit extravagant?
What of it?
It’s our birthday,
it only comes once a year.
True enough.
Episode 17
The Big Birthday Bust-up!
Now then, do keep up with your studies
and your games this week,
and spend your days in good cheer.
But there’s one recent thing
I must caution you about.
It concerns birthday parties.
It’s all very well to celebrate
one another’s birthdays—
but some of these parties
are becoming rather too grand.
Please do take care not to spend too much money,
nor to make a competition of the presents.
Well, that’s dampened things a bit.
Just when our birthday was round the corner...
And I was all set to hatch a plan too...
So that’s what the headmistress
was talking about?
Exactly.
After all, those third form girls had food brought up from a town restaurant
and gave a grand party!
They must be rolling in money!
It caused such a stir that word reached the headmistress herself.
Oh, so that's what it was?
In that case, there’s no problem.
No problem?
We’ve no intention to spend a fortune on it.
Just a clever idea or two and a party with a twist—
there’s nothing wrong with that!
Such as?
Well, we had a midnight feast
for Janet’s birthday,
so it ought to be something
that takes everyone by surprise.
Pat, let’s not do anything fancy.
Just sit down to tea.
What are you saying?
On our birthday?
We could play games, or...
I know! A fancy-dress party
would be marvellous!
Do be sensible, Pat.
Are you simply going to ignore
what Headmistress said?
You’re so timid, sis.
It’ll be fine, as long as we don’t get caught.
Well, I won’t stand for it.
You, I know—you never back down
once you’ve got something into your head.
That's one dreadful fault you have.
And you, Isabel, are always playing
Goody Two-Shoes!
If you’re told not to do something,
you just give in without a word.
Don’t you think that’s dull?
I'm not trying to play Goody Two-Shoes at all!
It's you who is reckless,
heedless, even!
Like with Mam’zelle’s essay that one time.
Oh, is that so?
Is everything bad that happens my fault now?
Well, I never asked you to follow my lead.
Pray, do as you please!
Very well. I shall do exactly as I please.
All right. I’ll do just as I like too.
What? You mean you’re giving
two separate birthday parties?
That’s right.
Mine's at two o’clock this Sunday.
Mine's at three.
The time’s short, but do come to both.
I don't mind, but what on earth
is the matter with you two?
You girls are acting oddly.
Don’t tell me you’ve quarrelled?
How strange!
The twin sisters, quarrelling?
We’re allowed to differ sometimes, you know.
Exactly! Just because our faces are alike
doesn’t mean our minds are too.
Well of course. We’d hate it if you
were alike in every way. That’d be horrid.
Janet, this is no laughing matter.
What on earth started it?
Quarrelling’s not at all like Pat and Isabel!
That’s right.
A birthday doesn’t mean a thing
unless you celebrate it together.
Oh, let them be! Better to quarrel it out
thoroughly than not at all.
Yeah! We’ve always been lumped together in everything.
But from now on, we want to be treated as two separate people.
Yes! We’re giving up being the twins.
That’s right. I am Isabel O’Sullivan.
Pat is Patricia O’Sullivan.
And you’re never, ever
to call us “the twins” again.
Yeah, sure, understood, the twins!
Janet!
Good night!
Good night, Janet!
Janet, stop teasing.
You’ll only make it harder for them to make up.
Don’t worry, Hilary.
Those two are always in step with one another.
You want to change rooms?
Yes, I’d like to move next door.
Sheila has offered to swap with me.
But why, for Pete's sake?
There's a reason...
Look, Patricia.
Unless there’s a very special reason,
you can’t change rooms in the middle of term.
But...
Has something happened?
No, I understand.
Here are your test papers back.
Far too many mistakes this time.
Do listen and make notes properly.
Now then—Patricia and Isabel.
Oui.
Yes.
Hm?
Tiens! Have you changed seats?
Oui. Mam’zelle, I’ve also got a favour to ask.
What is it?
You always call up
Isabel and me together.
I’d like you to stop that.
My... But why?
You make it sound as if the two of us
only add up to one person.
You call the others one by one, don't you?
Well, that’s true, but...
Isabel, would you prefer it that way too?
Either way is fine.
How odd! You two are behaving strangely today.
What’s the matter?
Mam’zelle, they quarrelled yesterday,
and now they’re fighting
a war of independence from being twins.
Mon dieu! Bringing a family quarrel
into class—how abominable!
Patricia and Isabel,
you both come here at once!
Yes, Mam’zelle!
Bien.
There you are, twins!
Would you take this to the classroom for me?
Okay!
What’s up with them?
Here they come.
Why are you coming in here?
I swapped beds with Vera.
Eh?! With Vera?
Don't tell me...
Yes, I also swapped with Doris.
Eh?!
Vera! You knew, didn’t you?
Of course not!
Not like we plotted it together.
Right, Doris?
Certainly. We were each asked separately.
Right, Vera?
Yes.
Now, now, end this silly quarrel already.
You stubborn twins.
Twins?
That was silly. You really didn't have to say it, you know.
If only Janet wasn't teasing us still,
we might've made up by now.
I’ve never quarrelled this long with Isabel before.
And the cause was nothing much.
So why am I being so obstinate?
Isabel is usually the first to try to make up...
Pat must be waiting for me to give in.
And it’d be easy enough...
But why must it always be me?
Our long-awaited birthday...
Will be utterly spoiled at this rate.
The Twins at St. Clare's
Isabel!
Pat and I are going into town to do the shopping.
Wanna come with us?
Yeah.
I'll pass today.
Really?
Right, then.
Let's go, Pat.
Very well. That will do nicely.
By the way, Miss Roberts,
have you taken notice of the O'Sullivan situation?
Oh, I most certainly did.
It seems they had
a most uncharacteristic quarrel.
They have not spoken for three days, it seems.
My word! Three whole days?
The cause must be trifling, but it seems they're locked in a battle of stubbornness.
One can well believe it of those two.
They are displeased at being treated
as one in all things.
A sure sign they are growing up, perhaps.
Indeed; they are dependable girls,
and I trust they will settle it between themselves.
We shall watch and see for the present.
I see. Perhaps they need
some little push to make up?
Goodness, I do wish they’d stop this nonsense.
Really! At this rate, we'll never see the feast
they might've prepared for their birthday.
Never fear, Joan. When a good feast
finally appears before you,
you'll forget all your worries and just dig in.
Oh, come on, Doris!
Ah! Sorry, my bad.
We have tried many ways to make them reconcile,
but every time it only made matters worse.
Is there anything we can do?
The only thing clear is that both are
frightfully obstinate, and aren't going to budge.
Is that so?
They are usually so approachable and pleasant.
They merely seem tangled
in their feelings this time.
In any case, they must not be allowed
separate parties.
Th-That's exactly it!
What?
We won't allow them
to hold separate parties.
Eh?
We will all insist that we will only attend
if the two celebrate together.
I see! That's a capital notion, all right.
If they celebrate together,
they may well make up naturally.
Agreed. But that is our last resort.
If by Saturday they are still at odds,
we shall all declare it so.
What a pair of tiresome twins they are.
Let us leave it there for today.
Also, Patricia, Isabel...
Y-Yes?
Headmistress wishes to see you.
Go to the headmistress’s room after school. Understood?
Yes, miss.
Ah, and also, change into
your work smocks before going.
Goodness me, quarrelling over birthday parties?
I have some responsibility in this matter then.
Oh, you shouldn't bother...
What you said during
the weekly address was right.
But, Headmistress, didn't you mean to tell us
that it's wrong to think
the answer lies in lavish spending?
That is part of it too.
What really worries me is that birthdays seem to have turned into nothing more
than excuses for overindulgence and rowdiness.
But when one marks the day of her birth,
surely it's meant to be enjoyed in cheerful company?
Really? The day of your birth?
Is that all a birthday is to you?
Now, you two, work together
and plant these rose saplings.
Okay...
Take care not to spike yourselves.
My German friend sent me these roses.
It is a new variety.
It will bear great, pure white blooms.
My parents are fond of roses too,
and we often helped tend them.
Why, that is most comforting.
Our Mum used to say, when tending flowers,
speak to them kindly.
Praise and encourage them gently,
and they will grow fair.
Indeed, that is so.
It's just like talking to the child
in the mother’s womb:
with gentleness and affection.
And did the roses bloom finely?
Why, of course they did!
And how did you feel when you saw them?
I was so delighted
I wanted to cuddle them like babies!
I even boasted of them to the postman!
Your mother, too, must surely
have spoken tenderly to you
each day while you were still inside her.
And what do you suppose
she felt when you were born?
What joy, what pride,
what a radiant moment it must have been.
The day your parents, with hearts brimming over with love,
brought you into the world—
that's what your birthday is.
For your mother, it's the day
she bore you and became a mother.
For your father, the day he became a father.
A day of remembrance for Dad and Mum?
I never thought of it like that before.
Makes sense. It is a remembrance
tucked deep in your parents’ hearts,
and since no one marks it outwardly,
you scarcely notice it.
But we live our lives upheld by many—
family, friends, neighbours, teachers,
our seniors—and it is a splendid thing.
Think on that.
Now, that is enough gardening for today.
We shall have lovely blossoms in time, you’ll see.
Let us look forward to them.
Okay!
Ah, that reminds me.
There is a parcel from home for you at the Matron’s.
Run along and fetch it.
Yes, will do!
Excuse us!
Blimey!
I wonder if Mum wanted us to invite
the whole school to a feast.
It’s a present for us!
Let’s open it.
How sweet!
Mother made them herself!
There’s a card!
"I long to see your faces, grown a little more, Patricia and Isabel.
A very happy birthday to you both."
I always thought birthdays
were simply for getting festive.
So did I. But really, we have
our mother, father, and everyone else
to thank that we are here at all
to celebrate our birthday!
A birthday is a day for gratitude.
That is what Headmistress meant!
Yes.
Hey, Pat, let’s celebrate as well...
Mum's remembrance day!
We'll write a card...
And post it express!
And enough of this quarrel.
I’m sick and tired
of not speaking to you for days.
It's been far too long.
It’s miserable not having you to talk to.
I’m sorry.
And I’m sorry too.
Mother, happy day of giving birth.
Father, happy day of becoming a father.
With all our thanks on our birthday—Pat...
and Isabel.
Day of giving birth and day of becoming a father, eh? Interesting.
Our little girls...
Who knew they even think of things like that?
It's because they're our little girls.
P.S.
Thank you for the presents and all the delicious sweets and tinned things.
It's looking to be a splendid party.
We’ll write again with all the details.
This chocolate cake is heavenly, Pat, Isabel!
And that pie too!
Did your mother make everything?
She did. Why, when Mum’s in the kitchen,
she’s a regular magician.
I only wish you could taste
her orange soufflé!
Right?
Let’s hope you two have inherited
some of her gift, our dear twins.
Janet!
But truly, I am glad you two made up.
I thought today’s party
would be ruined altogether.
Yes, quite so.
You gave us quite the scare.
We were all on edge.
Joan most of all.
Yes, indeed.
Honestly, you two are a trial!
We’re sorry. We were glad to at last realise
how much you’d all been worried about us.
It’s thanks to everyone that we’ve been able
to have this party today.
We’re ever so grateful!
I think it’s best when you two stay the jolly twins we know.
Yes! We think so too.
Come on, let’s open that tin as well.
Okay!
Stop it, Binks!
Do something, Kathleen!
Binks! Leave it!
What’s the matter with Binks?
Oh, nothing...
Miss Lewis, won’t you have a slice
of this delicious homemade cake with us?
It’s the twins’ birthday party today!
My! Many happy returns, then!
Eh? Did you say a birthday party?
You're welcome to join us too, Mam'zelle!
Merci! Be there at once!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Janet’s gone quite dotty
over fortune-telling with Tarot cards.
It’s all because Margo in the fifth form does readings that are said to be uncannily accurate.
Everyone says they don’t believe in such things—
but all the same, they’re curious!
Fortune-telling! Everyone’s losing their heads over it. It’s ridiculous!
And now Janet says that three disasters
are going to befall Pat!
As if! It’s obvious nonsense!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Great Tarot Fortune-Telling Craze!"
Episode 18
The Great Tarot Fortune-Telling Craze!
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End