Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
We’ve stirred up quite a few commotions
since we came to St. Clare’s.
And it finally caught up with us the other day.
After we turned in our French homework
in the middle of the night,
we were summoned by the Headmistress.
And our classmates seem to get annoyed
by just about everything we do.
It looks like this kind of thing
will just keep happening!
Episode 4
Janet is up to Tricks
Pat, you made the same mistake
on that same question again.
Didn't you prepare for the lesson?
I did! Though, I've been busy with this and that...
Your attitude isn’t at all
like the one of someone who’s really trying.
Y-Yes...
Work through these questions
and hand them in again before the final bell today.
Huh?
Do we have a deal, Pat?
Y-Yes, I understand.
Oh, what a pity.
Wasn't Pat going to go and see
the concert after school today?
Shut up, you!
Pat!
Y-Yes.
Going to the concert is all very well,
but it’s no excuse to neglect your duties
or your own improvement.
Those are the sort of young ladies
you ought to strive to be.
Now, turn to page 45.
Miss Roberts is unusually strict
for someone with her face.
Why did God create maths in this world at all?
I fail to see how working through all those equations with ease will help me in life.
Studying maths helps you
organize your thoughts.
Miss Roberts said it can even enrich your ideas.
Is that so?
I was looking forward to that concert...
Say, how about secretly finishing it
during history class?
Secretly finish it?
Yeah, that's right.
Ignore the history class
and do your math homework instead.
But can you really do that?
Of course you can!
After all, it’s taught by Miss Kennedy.
Miss Kennedy?
Yes, she’ll be coming to take
Miss Lewis’s place, as she’s taken ill.
And Janet says that Miss Kennedy
doesn't belong in this profession.
Huh?
What, why?
Quiet, please.
Please keep quiet!
Right, I see now.
Okay, then I might as well
try sneaking in some maths...
Stop it, Pat!
Look, Hilary does it too.
See? Now, where was I...
No way, really?
That sounds made up!
Keep it down, Janet!
Wait, really?
Janet! Go back to your seat!
So what happened next?
Janet!
I-I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
Ah... The notes I made
for the solved maths problems...
Maths?
No, I...
Maths...
Maths, right.
Pat!
Sheila, let's head out!
Okay!
Oh my, what a pity!
Doing Miss Roberts’ homework?
Huh?
Keep up the good work.
Going out somewhere?
Yes, we’re off to see a concert.
Yeah, good for you. With a fluttering ribbon and all—
probably the height of fashion for a St. Clare’s girl.
What was that?!
Look who's talking—a girl who has to stay behind and study extra hours!
No one ever dared speak about us
like that at our old school.
And the program...
They used to teach us differently at our old school,
which is why we're so confused here.
Oh, really?
Why is it that all we ever hear is,
“our old school, our old school, our old school…”?
“The O’Sullivans used to be the best
at studying, sports, and everything else!”
“We're not going to clean the seniors' boots!”
You call that humour? Pathetic!
It's unseemly indeed.
Aren't you embarrassed of yourselves?
Let's go now, Isabel.
Wh-Who does she think she is?!
Wait a minute, you!
What did you mean by that?!
Don’t forget, we pride ourselves
on our witty and refined humour.
So we find yours to be a crude embarrassment!
Listen here, you...
I pride myself on never doing anything cowardly
and on having the best sense of humour in the class!
Then you’d best stop taking pride
in that, starting today.
What do you even know about real humour?
Hm. Let's go.
We're not done here!
I’ve yet to show you
just how good my sense of humour is!
And the subject would be...
Miss Kennedy’s class is first thing tomorrow!
Sounds like a carefree morning.
Yes! We'll make it Miss Kennedy.
Look forward to it, twins!
Tomorrow, I’ll turn history class
into a whirlwind of laughter!
What can I do to make them
pay attention in class?
She's here.
Today's the day I do it right.
They're all in their seats!
Oh, I see someone even prepared the map?
Thank you very much!
Today, I want to tell you how the people of England
lived in the seventeenth century.
At that time, in the seventeenth century...
Ah! It won't write!
What's going on?
I'm sorry...
Geez, what kind of prank is that?
Ah, how strange.
What's with this chalk?
What's that awful sound?
It's the squeaky chalk.
How did you manage
to swap it with the teacher’s?
Nothing is impossible for the great Janet!
So childish.
We're just getting started.
Wh-What am I going to do with this?
Miss Kennedy, behind you!
Huh? What is it?
Th-That's going a bit too far.
Any prank should have a limit, you know!
Oh, would you look at Pat!
What happened?
What's so good about this?
Just some corny tricks.
Then how about you demonstrate to us
your sense of humour?
Fine, then!
Yes! Miss Kennedy, I have a question.
Miss Kennedy!
Y-Yes, Patricia. What is it?
Did people wear clothes
in the seventeenth century, or just skins?
Of course, They weren't cavemen!
Surely you know that they wore clothes!
Huh? So then, did people in the seventeenth century have no skin?
Not even their own skin?
Th-That's true, b-but you see...
How lackluster.
Total flop.
That joke wasn't any good at all.
S-Somebody please take this poster away.
Okay!
Here I go, the finishing touch!
J-Janet?
One...
Two...
Three!
There!
No, stop...!
As expected from Janet!
You're a legend, Janet.
You're a genius at humour!
How'd you even come up with a prank like that?
My brain's just built different,
unlike someone else here.
That know-it-all...
The Twins at St. Clare's
Ugh... No more!
Where are you going?
A toy store!
I need some new toys
to keep up with Janet.
Did you think I'd just suck it up
and accept defeat?
I had no idea you and Janet were so alike.
What was that?!
See? When you get stubborn
and fly off the handle, you lose all sense.
But despite all that, you’re really quite simple
and good-natured at heart.
That's not true!
Don't lump me in with the likes of Janet!
How could you!
Fine, then!
I'll find them on my own!
Bye!
Ah... Pat!
Gee, Pat...
That won't do.
I wonder if they have
something more unusual here.
Something that'd leave Janet speechless.
This is just too dull.
I wonder if they have
something more unusual here.
Something that'd leave Pat speechless...
Ah! Janet!
Pat!
I won't lose next time!
Oh, really? Too bad.
Because I'm gonna win the next one too.
I already have a special trick
ready up my sleeve.
Special trick?
Yeah, that's right!
I expect a parcel from my brother to come today.
A parcel full of firecrackers!
Firecrackers?
Yes! I'll plant them under the teacher's desk,
and they'll go "Pow-pow" all at once!
Imagine Miss Kennedy's face when that happens!
That'd surely scare the pants off Miss Kennedy!
But if it were me,
I'd plant them in the stove.
The stove?
Ratatata!
Explosion!
It was my idea, though!
I'd have figured it out even without your help!
Why not do it, then?
I jolly will!
Who could that be?
Miss Kennedy.
Let me help you.
Thank you, Isabel.
Thanks for your help, Isabel.
Is this your room?
Yes, that's right.
And all the books in here are about history?
Yes, each thing I look into leads to another,
and before I know it, my room’s crammed with books.
Could I take a peek into some of them?
Yes, by all means.
You're the first student
to ever come to my room.
I would love it.
This is an illustrated guide
to Ancient Greece—isn't it wonderful?
So pretty...
The Parthenon, the ruins of Troy,
and the legends of various gods.
When I’m studying history,
I fully lose track of time.
A heroic epic, a beautiful work of art.
I'm an emotional person, so I want to share
this excitement with everyone else.
With us?
Yes! Just look—I make notes every night
for the next day’s class.
But I can never follow through with them,
because I lose control of the class.
I feel so guilty towards my students
and Miss Lewis, whom I’m standing in for.
If only I were a better teacher...
Now, where was it...
Miss Kennedy...
Yes! If I can explain this one piece properly,
I’m sure it will spark everyone’s interest.
Wow! Are those firecrackers?
Sounds like fun!
Let's use them soon, Janet!
Just you watch.
What are you gonna do?
I'll plant them in the stove.
That's a great idea.
I can't wait!
Get seated, everybody.
Miss Kennedy is here.
Here we go.
There!
Janet...
R-Right... There's something
I'd like to say to you today.
I believe I've been a bit too lenient up until now.
Because of that, your history classes...
What on Earth is going on in there?!
I-I'm scared, Miss Kennedy!
Me too!
It's all fine.
Pat, Janet, it’s probably a very gassy piece of coal, that's all. Calm down now!
Scary!
Yay! Those firecrackers are something else!
Nicely done, Janet!
Did you say "firecrackers"?! G-Girls!
There will be no history lesson this morning.
I refuse to teach an unruly class like this!
Miss Kennedy!
Miss Kennedy...
I didn't think she'd cry like that.
It was just an innocent prank.
I can't believe it, Pat!
So you were in on this too?
You all have no idea
how much Miss Kennedy cares about us!
Look, it's Miss Kennedy's diary...
Wow...
Pat, she writes about you as well. Here.
"I'm sure Pat will be interested in mythology..."
"I want to tell Janet about Athena.
After all, she's a strong-willed goddess, just like Janet..."
There's something about me.
It has my name written there too!
Miss Kennedy blamed herself
for not managing to teach us properly.
Where have you ever seen
anyone so big-hearted?
The kindest, most genuine people
often find it hardest to show it.
I’m ashamed to even be in the same class as you,
when you can’t even see that!
Isabel...
What happened here?
Ah! Miss Roberts...
What was all that noise?
And where is Miss Kennedy?
Well, she...
It's you—what did you do?!
W-We only...
Ah! Yikes!
What's going on with that stove?
Did someone put firecrackers in it?
Girls!
I am going to the common room
across the passage.
I expect the girl who played this stupid
and dangerous joke to come and own up at once.
Is that clear?
Why did it have to come to this?
Miss Roberts won't let me off the hook for this!
But I’m in for it now...
Wait, I'm coming too.
Huh?
I egged you on to put
those firecrackers in the stove.
I’d be an awful coward
if I let you go on your own.
Pat...
You got the squibs and put them in—
but I shared that joke with you,
with no consideration
for Miss Kennedy's feelings.
I'll go too.
Me too.
If you girls are going, then, sure enough, I must come along too, as the head-girl of the class.
Me too!
Me too.
I'm going too.
I'll go too!
Well, I guess our whole class
is to blame for this prank.
Let's all go, then!
Yeah!
Miss Roberts...
I did it.
I wanted to give Miss Kennedy a scare...
But we were all a part of it!
We're sorry!
Very well.
I'm glad you found it within yourselves to own up to it.
And that your camaraderie is so strong.
That said, you'll still face punishment
for what you did today.
First, we’ll deduct the cost of repairing
the stove from everyone’s pocket money.
Secondly, you forfeit your free time today.
Instead, you’ll use that time to tidy up
the mess you’ve made in the classroom.
Is that clear?
Yes!
Miss Kennedy!
We're sorry!
I only wanted to play a little prank on you.
I never meant to hurt you! I'm sorry!
We allowed ourselves to think little of you,
since you were Miss Lewis' substitute.
And now we're awfully ashamed of it!
We've come to realize how kind-hearted
and considerate you are!
Miss Kennedy, we're sorry!
Miss Kennedy!
Miss Kennedy, I won't play
pranks like that ever again.
Janet...
Miss Kennedy, I'll do my best
to come to love history!
Me too!
Thank you, everyone.
I was myself always timid and not at all
like a teacher. I promise to be stronger now.
You're a wonderful teacher, the best ever!
We want to see you act a lot more confident!
A hundred times more!
A thousand times more!
Miss Kennedy, you can do it!
To see you girls so united in this drive...
It's only because someone showed us.
Right, everyone?
Yes. Though they're stubborn at times,
they can be really caring too!
All right, then. We've got a classroom
to tidy up. Right, Pat?
Yeah.
I'm going first!
No, me!
I said, I'm going first!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
JmePenseBon
Next time
I'm Pat.
I'm Isabel.
Hey, Isabel, Janet received some sweets from home for her birthday celebration.
Does that mean
we'll be having a midnight party?
Yeah! For some reason, eating in the middle of the night is so thrilling and delicious!
That's true.
Hey, let's bring Sheila and the others onboard
and do it in the class!
Agreed! The more the merrier!
Shh! Not so loud, Isabel!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Great Midnight Feast."
Episode 5
The Great Midnight Feast
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End