Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
Dear, I brought tea.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Oh? It's that letter...
No, I was just...
Really, dear, how many times do you need to read that letter from Isabel and Pat to feel satisfied?
Not my fault all they do is make us worry.
I can't believe those mischievous twins.
Making lots of friends is great,
but all they ever write about is fun stuff—
like going to the circus or how cute that puppy is.
Not a word about what actually matters—studying!
Come to think of it, are they really paying enough attention to studying? I'm worried too.
They say exams are around the corner.
It seems we need to give them a little scare.
A scare?
Without that, they might even end up
yawning openly during class.
Episode 11
Isabelle is Cheating?!
And that's how we solve it...
All right?
You must keep this formula in mind at all times.
Do you understand?
Huh?
I-Is that true, Miss Roberts?
This formula?
Wh-What happened?
Everyone snapped out of it so suddenly...
This formula will be on the exam.
Miss Roberts said her usual keyword.
When she says "Do you understand?"
It's a given!
Your exams are finally coming up next week.
That means you'll have to start taking it seriously, no slacking.
A total of nine subjects.
Do study in earnest so you won’t regret it later.
That's all for today's class.
It's no fun...
Our first exam after coming to St. Clare's, huh?
I'm not confident at all!
Me neither.
St. Clare's education is on a whole other level.
Even just keeping up with the form
took all my strength this term.
It's good to be you, Binks.
No exams, no worries.
Pat, Isabel!
Knew I would find you here.
You've got a letter.
Oh? Pat, it's from Dad!
From Dad?
"Isabel, Pat, your exams
are around the corner, aren't they?
But I'm not worried.
After all, you two gave me your word
before leaving for St. Clare's:
'Since we've always been #1 and #2
back at Redroofs, at a school such as St. Clare's...'"
What about a school such as ours?
N-No, you can't!
No! Don't read it!
Give it back!
So, what do we have here?
"At a school such as St. Clare's,
where their level of education is so low,
we both swear to be the very best
in every subject."
Whoa! Did you really say that?!
Please stop!
We didn't really mean it.
"I believe that my daughters
aren't the kind to break their promises.
Dad."
What are you going to do?
What are we to do?
That’s what comes of having
too much faith in yourself.
Pat, let's prepare.
Huh?
I've decided.
Isabel!
What's gotten into you?
What are you doing?
I'm calling home.
I figured that much...
Ah! Is that you, Mum?
My, Isabel? What's the matter?
We're gonna keep our vows!
Maybe not in every subject, but we’ll get the top marks in the school on this exam!
Huh?
You'll see!
Ah... Hey, wait a minute!
I can't believe you!
What's the big idea, Isabel?
You really didn't have to go that far.
I really want to please Dad and Mum.
Don't you?
Huh?
I was being selfish, saying things like
"I don't want to go to St. Clare's,
adults are the worst," and all that.
But the truth is, both Mum and Dad
really do care about me and you wholeheartedly,
so I want to show them how grateful I am,
get good grades on these exams,
and show them how much I care!
But with our current abilities...
Pat, just imagine it for a moment.
How happy do you think Mum and Dad
will be if we get the top marks?
Mum will probably...
I know! She’ll put on a feast.
A huge party as if it were both a birthday
and Christmas at once!
And as for Dad...
He never praised us in front of others...
But when the lawyer Mr. Edgar...
and Aunt Morley come...
he'll brag about us!
"My word, it turns out my naughty twins
can be quite capable too!"
Exactly! And then he'll go like...
I'm a bit embarrassed, though...
All right, then, Isabel.
If we work together, there's nothing we can't do!
That's right, Pat! Exactly!
That's it... I'll blast through it!
We'll get them top grades!
Our number one rival is Hilary.
Certainly!
There hasn’t been a single year when she didn’t come out on top in the maths and French exams.
And then...
there's Joan!
Second place is informally reserved for Joan.
But in natural sciences,
she's even better than Hilary.
Need to stay sharp.
Is Janet an unlikely contender?
Kathleen also seems to be serious about it.
But it's Sheila who's the expert in classic literature.
Oh… so the whole form are our rivals?
That just means we too...
must fight back!
Let's do our best!
One-two...
French Revolution,
in the Gregorian calendar.
1789.
And who was the king at the time?
U-Um...
Binks!
You decided to study with us?
I remembered! Louis XVI.
Correct!
Sleepy?
Who're you calling sleepy?
Let's strive on for ten more minutes.
No, twenty minutes!
All right, your exams finally start today.
I believe all of you
have been preparing earnestly.
That's what I heard.
Don't worry,
we've done everything we could.
Well then, everyone,
please begin.
How was it, Pat?
A total flop.
I got stuck on the very first maths problem.
I spent so long wrestling with it
I got nothing on everything else.
And my French prep completely misfired.
Ah... Why do I always get questions
that I haven't prepared for?
They say they'll announce today's results
tomorrow morning already.
Ah... God help me.
Yesterday's test results have been posted!
Ah... What am I gonna do?
Did you see it?
No.
Wow! Incredible! Hilary is number one again!
Even in maths and French!
Amazing! That's our Hilary!
Congrats, Hilary.
Thank you, Joan. You're first
in natural sciences yourself. Congrats!
Thanks.
Ugh, just as you'd expect...
We might still be number two...
Geez, did I really lose to the twins?
Huh? Where? Where are we?
There, in maths.
I'm number 13, and Isabel...
Number 9...!
Number 12 for me.
The exams went by in a flash, and before we knew it,
eight of the subjects were over.
Ah, Grandma? Hear this!
I was number two in natural sciences!
That's because you cheered me on.
What? A trip to Scotland as a reward?
Wait, seriously?
So you were number three
in classic literature and grammar?
Yes. And I can't wait to tell
my Dad and Mum about it.
I was also number two in history.
Amazing!
So the best we ever got in the eight subjects was Isabel’s fifth in classical literature?
And I fell flat completely.
All that remains is geography tomorrow.
It's our last chance.
Let's focus all your strength on geography,
and you’ll ace it tomorrow.
Yes. Let's go to the study
and review my notes again.
You've arranged them so neatly!
I think there’ll be questions
on Africa’s climate and produce.
Got it. Let's recheck everything.
The names of towns and harbours too.
Yeah.
The Twins at St. Clare's
This is as perfect as it gets.
My head feels like it weighs a ton.
Let's take a break.
Affirmative!
Are you still knitting that sweater?
Yes, little by little.
Now, my knitting book is...
Huh?
Maybe in the classroom?
Ah, that's right!
I'll go take it.
Ah... I just can't bring myself to remember
the names of rivers in Africa.
Hm... I know! Let's go and write them on your desk in the classroom now.
Are you cheating now, Janet?
Just kidding.
Besides, Miss Roberts never allows anyone
to enter the classroom during exam week.
What? Why?
Ah, that's because the test questions
are in the classroom.
Huh?
You didn't know?
That's how it is at St. Clare's.
Really?
What should we do?
Isabel is there right now...
Hey everybody!
Hilary is handing out cookies.
What? Cookies?
Where are you going, Pat?
Huh?
They look heavenly delicious!
It's chocolate cookies with roses.
Really?
But…
Oh, whatever.
Isabel will be back
as soon as she gets her knitting book.
If you don't come now,
there'll be none left for you!
Oh, no, you don't!
Geez, it's pitch black!
Oh, crumbs!
Tomorrow's geography questions!
D-Don't be stupid.
What are you thinking, Isabel?
Get going.
What am I doing? I know full well
I mustn't look at it!
How happy do you think Mum and Dad
will be if we get the top marks?
Mum will probably...
I know! She’ll put on a feast.
A huge party as if it were both a birthday
and Christmas at once!
They're questions on Africa, after all.
And what I've just studied.
This too?
This too!
Took you long enough.
Huh? Where's your knitting book?
Ah... M-My knitting book...
R-Right...
It wasn't there?
N-No, I found it. It's just...
Um...
That's enough, I'm going to bed now.
What's the matter?
You're strange.
Not at all!
Isabel what happened?
I can't tell you, Pat.
Don't ask anything. Just don't!
Isabel!
No matter what happens,
we'll get through it together, remember?
It's different this time.
You wouldn't forgive me if I told you, I know...
Isabel, d-did you...
The test questions were there,
on the teacher's desk.
And I've seen them all!
Something's gotten into me,
I've lost control.
It's a lie, right?
It has to be!
You'd never do something so...
It's true!
I don't want to believe that!
We, the O'Sullivan twins,
aren't about all that sly stuff!
That's what we took pride in.
If what you say is true...
I despise you!
Pat!
Pat is right. I'm a cheat.
If I take first place by peeking at the questions,
nobody will be proud of me—
least of all Dad and Mum!
I'm such a fool!
If I were Isabel, I would've done
the same thing for sure.
So how can I...
Sorry, Isabel.
Pat...
You know, I think...
Don't say it.
I already know.
You're gonna withdraw from the exam, right?
Confess everything to Miss Roberts.
I can see right through you!
That's what I'd do if I were Isabel.
Isabel, I just wanna say...
No! I can't do that!
Are you going to withdraw
from the exam too, Pat?
To share my plight with me, right?
But how...
I can tell. That's what I would've done if I were you.
Isabel...
We're twins, remember?
Yeah.
Please, you take that exam, for both of us.
Good morning.
Good morning!
You're finally taking
your last exam today—geography.
Some of you are satisfied
with the marks you’ve got,
some regret not working harder,
but either way, you’ve one more subject to face.
I will hand out the question sheets now.
Miss Roberts!
Yes?
What is it?
I must confess something to you.
What is it, Isabel?
I'll accept any punishment you deem fit.
I...
Well, last night...
Goodness me!
I got the wrong questions here.
These are for the second form.
Not the first form.
The questions for the first form
are probably in the second form classroom.
Hilary, would you please go and swap them?
Okay!
And that means...
Isabel!
The questions you saw
were for the second form.
They weren't meant for us!
Isabel!
What was it you wanted to confess?
Ah, right... It's that...
No, it's nothing at all!
Um… last night, we both munched
on some cookies when we were already in bed.
That's... That's what it was, right?
Yeah...
We're sorry.
What'll I do with you children...
Okay, now these are your actual questions.
Did everyone get a sheet?
Yes!
You can get started, then.
They're questions on Africa!
But they're completely different
from what I saw.
It's just the stuff me and Isabel studied last night.
I might just be able to pull it off!
The exams are over, at last.
I had this strange tremor in my hands,
I probably got it all wrong.
Who knows.
But that's fine too.
Strangely enough,
I feel completely refreshed.
It doesn't even matter that I'm not the number one,
I feel so relieved now!
It's over!
Geez Louise, who's that belching here?
The geography results are out.
So who's number one?
Hilary? Joan?
One-two...
Patricia O'Sullivan!
You're the number one!
Huh?
What kind of reaction is that, Pat?
We just said you've got first place.
Pat...
Isabel...
Congratulations, Pat!
Isabel, we earned that first place together.
We did it!
"Dad, Mum, we’ve done it at last—
the coveted first place!
I was only number six,
but I have no regrets!
Because no other exam has ever made me understand so deeply both the pain and the joy of studying!
We may have been number one time after time
in many subjects at our old school,
but now I realise—
ending up in sixth place after worrying,
pondering, and giving it my all
is worth far more than winning a first place
you can't help but take for granted!
Dad, Mum...
I really wish I could've gotten even better results
to make you even happier.
That's the feeling I want to convey right now.
And on the next exam, for sure...
It's a promise!
Dear...
They're wonderful kids,
the kind we can be proud of.
Our two mischievous treasures.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
The long-awaited school concert
is almost upon us.
I memorised Romeo’s
long speeches to perfection.
Everyone just waits for the actual show.
However, with the school concert being less than a day away...
A terrible incident happened.
Vera, who plays Juliet,
fell off the set and hurt her leg!
What to do?
It's impossible to suddenly give the role of Juliet to someone else.
Ah... Just as everything
was coming along so nicely...
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"A Disaster! Who Will Take the Role?"
Episode 12
A Disaster! Who Will Take the Role?
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End