Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
This time, the second form
had prepared a class full of cats,
to the consternation of Miss Kennedy who hates cats.
They've pushed her to the point
of quitting St. Clare's.
But Miss Kennedy proved
the strength of her spirit
when she slapped the second form girl
who called Catherine a thief!
And when she said that being considerate to others is the most important thing,
everyone was moved to tears.
In the end, we convinced
Miss Kennedy not to quit.
Thank God!
Episode 8
The Four Presents
Hey, have you heard, people?
Galliano's Circus has come to town!
Huh, really?
Galliano's Circus is famous!
Wow, I wanna see it!
Me too!
A circus, huh?
Can't wait to see it!
I'm in awe of it, truly!
My...
Did you see a poster in the city?
Yeah! And now I wanna go there!
Girls, the circus talk
can wait until after class.
Okay!
I do have this to add, though.
Headmistress decided that two forms
will take turns going to the circus each evening.
Is that true?!
Nice! How fortunate!
Quiet, everyone.
Let's go see the poster later.
Yeah, let's go.
Nice, here it is!
Galliano's Circus
is famous for its flying trapeze performances.
And their star performer
is a young man about our age!
I can't wait to see it!
Their star turn is a flying trapeze artist.
It should be marvellous!
Hey, wanna go and see their tent?
Yes, let's take a peek!
I wonder if we'll meet that boy there.
No, better forget it.
He's their pride—a star, remember?
That's right. Not a chance.
Look, there're the clowns!
Yeah.
Amazing!
Yeah...
Ah! Look there!
Hey, hello.
H-Hello!
Say, are you girls the students from St. Clare's?
How could you tell?
The troupe leader said your whole school
will be coming to see us, that's how.
Each evening, two forms will come.
Our form's turn is this Wednesday.
Then I'll be waiting for you.
Right... I'm Jimmy Brown.
What about you?
I'm...
I can't understand if you're
talking all at once.
I'm Isabel, nice to meet you.
I'm her twin sister Pat!
Wow, you two really are alike.
It's my turn!
I-I'm Janet...
Um...
I'm Kathleen.
Pleased to meet you.
Hey, Jimmy!
C'mere for a moment!
Got it! Will be there in a moment.
Wednesday, then.
If I spot you girls in the crowd,
I'll make a sign.
I'll be waiting!
That's right!
When I see Jimmy on Wednesday...
I should bring him a gift!
I'll be the only one with a gift!
I wonder if I can find
something suitable to gift to him... Ah!
This is it. This will be my gift for Jimmy!
Those keychains are all the rage right now.
Thank you!
Jimmy...
Jimmy Brown, huh?
Thank you, Isabel.
Oh no...
Isabel, what is the matter with you?
N-Nothing, I'm sorry!
Is that clear?
Whoever broke the glass
in this classroom must own up
before the last lesson of the day is over.
Understood?
But Miss Roberts, I already asked all the girls,
and the culprit really isn't in our class.
I see. However, if the culprit is not found...
What will happen?
The window panes here are a special order.
If we can't establish who did it, Headmistress
will make it a collective responsibility.
Though it still won’t be enough
to cover the full cost, you’ll have to forfeit
the twenty-shilling circus entrance fee.
Does that mean we can't go
to the circus tonight?
Yes, that's right.
Understood?
In such cases, it is the school's duty
to have everyone take collective responsibility.
Let's start the lesson now.
Please open page 42.
And they left...
What the heck!
We definitely didn't do it!
Why should we be punished?!
Miss Roberts explained it already.
That's how it's always done at our school.
Hey, people!
Are you just gonna suck it up like that?
What do you mean?
Look, there are two circus shows each evening.
One at 6.30 to 8.30
and the second at 8.45 to 10.45.
Are you saying we could still
go see that later one?
Bingo!
But the curfew’s at ten o’clock.
We shan’t be able to get back by then.
And all the dorm entrances
will be closed by then!
I know that.
And I have just a plan for that.
You know there are ladders in the shed, right?
We'll use that ladder to enter the dorm
through the window.
Just make sure it's not locked.
That's all nice,
but what if you get spotted?
They might expel you!
Then we just need to make sure
we don't get spotted. Who's with me? Here!
Me!
Me too!
What, no one else is coming?
I'd rather not.
All right, then it's the four of us.
Hold on!
Kathleen, you're going too?
Yes.
After all, I've already promised
I would come today...
To whom?
To whom... that's...
Right?
We need to leave the campus unnoticed.
Avoid using any light.
Who's that?
Me...
Then do something about it!
Careful, Kath!
Sorry...
We need to hurry.
We don't wanna be late!
Yeah.
So pretty!
Incredible!
That's a relief.
No one can stop us now.
We're finally at the circus,
and we'll see Jimmy again!
How about here?
Yeah.
We're lucky to find these empty seats!
Yeah!
True!
But will Jimmy really be able to spot us?
We just need to cheer him on loudly enough.
Right.
"Jimmy!"—like that?
Yeah, exactly!
Ah! Oh, no!
What's wrong, Isabel?
Quiet.
Look—Headmistress is here!
Huh?
You're right!
With this, we can't afford being loud.
Why did she have to come now, of all times?
Ah, what do we do now?
The Twins at St. Clare's
And now, a lion tamer's show!
Will he be able to guide this golden lion
through the ring of fire successfully?
Thank you for waiting!
And now, Jimmy Brown's
Amazing Flying Trapeze Show begins!
Jimmy!
She didn't notice.
You'd be surprised how boisterous Kathleen can be in situations like this.
That's true!
Don't judge a book by its cover, they say.
And now, at last, Jimmy’s trump card—
the double mid-air somersault!
Hey, let's leave before Headmistress does.
Good idea.
Ah, that's right!
I still need to say my goodbyes to Jimmy.
M-Me too!
Me too!
But where could he be?
E-Excuse me...
Do you know where Jimmy's dressing room is?
In the yellow trailer up ahead.
Thank you!
Wh-What's wrong?
It's Headmistress all right!
That Hilary...
Can't you trust her for anything?
It's shut.
Wh-What do we do?
Maybe try another window?
It's open!
Thank God!
What's up with all four of you sneezing today?
Are you girls okay?
Y-Yes.
We're fine.
Perhaps something did happen, after all?
N-No, not at all.
You’ll never grow up into proper ladies
if you keep sneezing non-stop in front of everyone.
That said, I'm still very happy today.
And I have great news for you.
The person who broke
the window pane owned up to it.
And it was a second form girl.
While playing with a lacrosse ball, she broke the glass
in this classroom, and chose to run away at first.
But she was going to confess
at the end of that day.
Unfortunately, due to a bad attack of flu,
she was suddenly bedridden with fever.
So she just couldn't confess in time?
That's how it is.
Then, we'll still be able to go to the circus?
They're still performing today!
Of course!
Headmistress also said that their flying trapeze program is exceptional, so make sure to watch it.
And one more thing.
To make up for upsetting you so much earlier,
she will treat you to tea with cakes in the town first.
Miss Roberts...
What is it, Kathleen?
I...
don't feel so well.
Kathleen!
Are you okay, Kathleen?
My, what awful fever!
Miss Roberts, Janet too!
Isabel with Pat too!
Goodness!
We don't know yet if it's just
a bad case of fever, or something else.
Either way, they’ll have to miss
today’s circus outing, won’t they?
Yes, that is absolutely out of question!
I feel sorry for them, but it can't be helped.
Usually, they're the most animated
of our students...
Still, they have been perfect bricks about all this—
not a grumble, not one word of complaint.
I wonder what's gotten into them.
Who knows...
I wonder whose performance
they're watching now...
Probably the clowns...
Probably the lion tamer's...
Probably not the flying trapeze yet...
Hey, if we didn't catch a cold,
would we have gone today anyway?
I'm not sure about that.
I now feel awfully mean for going to see it
last night without everyone else...
But we invited them all right...
Either way, we shouldn't have gone.
And it's no use thinking about all that now.
But the last night in town
is the best time to see the circus.
I was a fool...
Seems so.
Welcome back.
Any developments?
Yes, it seems their fever has subsided.
Good to know.
At least they didn't catch a flu, it seems.
I brought them some
of the chocolate cakes we had.
My, they should be properly delighted!
But not just now—
they're fast asleep, I think.
We're not!
You didn't forget about us, Miss Roberts!
Thank you very much!
I love those chocolate cakes!
Don't mind if we do!
Goodness! Are you sure you should
get out of bed already?
Yes, as long as there're cakes!
It seems their illness
has magically disappeared already!
This is all the medicine we need.
Yeah!
The circus truly was jolly fun.
I so wish you could've seen it too.
Miss Roberts, the clowns' performance
was only second to the flying trapeze, wasn't it?
That's true!
Ah... But how do you know that?
Um... Sh-She just saw some posters in the town!
Th-That's right!
Wow, it looks delicious!
That's true!
I hope Jimmy is still there...
Ah! Where are you going, Pat?
Something came up.
Going first!
Isabel?
Hey, wait!
Here I go! There!
Ah! A keychain!
Say, did you...
It was for Jimmy.
No way!
Seriously? We all bought the same?
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Hey, Isabel, why does Sheila
keep boasting about being rich?
I don't know, and I wonder
why she decided to behave that way.
Her mother is a very down-to-earth person,
but Sheila is the complete opposite.
She must not be right in the head.
It was especially bad today,
with even Janet finally erupting with rage.
Ah! I've had enough of this fuss!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Sheila's Secret."
Episode 9
Sheila's Secret
Look forward to it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End