Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Yippee, lessons are over!
Hey, shall we all go to the pictures?
The pictures, huh?
I wonder if we should.
Don’t you two have
rather more pressing business?
Huh?
O’Sullivan twins,
Headmistress wants to see you.
What?
Final Episode 26
Thank you, St. Clare's
Pat, whatever have you done this time
to get summoned by Headmistress?
It must've been you.
Remember when you gave
such a huge yawn during morning prayers?
So she wants to scold...
Ah... It's not that! Could it be...
about Headmistress’s roses?
We are very sorry, Headmistress.
Even though we were on duty...
But it was only twice
that we forgot to water your roses.
N-No, it was closer to five times...
Goodness!
We're sorry!
Was that so?
I didn’t know.
Huh?
You’ll have to take your punishment duty properly later.
What?
Today I had meant to bestow
a great honour upon you both.
An honour?
I’d like you two to represent us
at the National Speech Contest in London.
The National Speech Contest?!
The one where top pupils
from schools across the country compete?
And only those with excellent results, talent in sport
and outstanding character may enter?
A-And you're sending us?!
Yes. I consulted both staff and pupils
at St. Clare’s about whom to choose.
And...
B-But we recommended Hilary.
But Hilary insisted that you two should go.
Huh?
Janet, Kathleen,
and all the teachers agreed as well.
B-But why?
Honestly, if we'd known about the roses
we might have changed our minds!
We're sorry.
Perhaps they thought the theme
suited you two perfectly.
The theme?
“Our Dreams.”
“Our...
Dreams”?
I also think it’s a theme where your
cheerfulness and upbeat spirit will truly shine.
Patricia, Isabel,
live up to the whole school’s expectations.
Give a splendid speech at the contest.
Okay!
Yippee!
Fancy that—we’re to represent St. Clare’s!
What an incredible honour!
Hey, twins!
Congratulations!
Thank you, everyone.
It’s the first time twins have ever
been chosen as contestants, you know.
Hooray for the twins!
Huh?! You two, the representatives for the National Speech Contest?
And with “Our Dreams” as the theme!
Oh, I feel that we can nail it!
Starting today we’ll write
a brilliant draft together.
See you!
Dear...
Those mischievous girls,
chosen as St. Clare’s representatives?
With “Our Dreams” as their subject.
I wonder what they’ll say.
Whatever they’ve learnt during their time at St. Clare’s, their speech will lay it all out.
“Our Dreams,” is it?
Dreams...
They sound simple,
but can be rather difficult.
Yeah...
Are you writing your draft already?
Yes.
Say, Hilary, what’s your dream?
Hm...
To follow in my father’s footsteps, of course.
Right... As a teacher
at the school for the blind?
At present, he’s translating
the world’s classics into Braille.
Oh?
How marvellous!
The blind want to know and learn, too.
My dream is to help them in any way I can.
Oh?
And Kathleen, you want to be a vet?
Yes, I decided when I saved Binks’s life.
A vet, no matter what.
There are so many animals
on the brink of extinction right now.
I want to do work that will save their lives.
And me, I’ll be a judge!
Huh?!
You, Joan?
A judge?
Girls must go out into the world
and make their mark too.
When I leave St. Clare’s,
I’ll sit for the bar exam.
Brilliant, Gladys!
You’ve cut your time again.
Nearly at the Olympics now.
Here.
Thank you.
I’ll make my dream come true
by my own efforts, just you wait.
They’re all amazing.
They have real dreams,
and work so hard for them.
Then look at us—
we can’t think of anything.
We simply drift along day by day,
never once thinking seriously about
what we want to do when we’re grown up.
It’s pathetic, really!
And we're already fourteen!
What?
Isabel, what have you been
studying for every day?
Oh, really?
What about you, then, Pat?
I... Well...
You know, I said it before—
I wanted to be an illustrator.
Nonsense! You gave that up the other day,
said you had no talent.
Well then, I’ve talent for being a novelist.
I’m writing a detective story now.
Gave up after two pages, haven't you?
Your dreams never last more than a week.
That hardly counts as a real dream.
Oh, is that so?
And what about you?
I haven’t forgotten, you know.
That time...
Children, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
Me! Pat wants to be a ballerina.
Then Isabel too, a ballerina.
Then Pat will be a policewoman.
Then Isabel too, a policewoman.
Th-That was ages ago!
But nothing’s changed now.
"I don’t know what my dream is.
Pat doesn’t, so I don't know either!"
You're so indecisive,
always worrying about what others think.
Don't you have a will of your own?
What did you say?
No wonder no true dream
can be born here.
How cruel! You’re always so pushy,
and I just have to go along with you.
What was that?
I have a dream of my own.
A far bigger dream than yours!
And I’ll not lose to the likes of you.
I have a genuine dream
no one else has ever thought of.
What, two separate drafts?
Yes. We’ll split the ten minute limit
and each will give her own speech.
Oh... Really...
My own dream...
Yes, a nurse!
I’ve always rather admired them.
That’s it!
Hey, Isabel, is your draft coming along?
You're writing about nurses, right?
Yes, but... it’s no good.
I can’t write it well at all.
I can’t believe it!
The contest is tomorrow!
Yes...
Then what about a barrister?
It doesn’t feel right.
Then maybe Prime Minister, bold as you like?
Wait, Pat!
You too, Isabel?
My word, what on earth
are those twins going to do now?
If it comes to this, I shall...
Miss Lewis!
Leave them be.
It is important for them to struggle as well.
But surely it is a teacher’s duty
to give some guidance to pupils in difficulty?
I have faith in the girls of St. Clare’s.
As for Patricia and Isabel, in the end,
they will surely find the answer for themselves.
If you wish to be a true educator,
you too must learn to trust your pupils a little more.
Isabel, how goes it?
Y-Yes…
All sorts of dreams keep coming to mind...
A nurse, a nursery teacher…
But when I ask myself why I want to be one,
I can’t find the confidence.
So they’re not real dreams at all.
Perhaps you’re thinking of dreams too grandly.
I believe what we call dreams
are something much closer to hand.
Closer to hand?
Yes—ordinary, honest dreams.
I can’t bear it.
You’ve been brooding so much, haven’t you?
I don’t mean to pry, but it got me curious.
I don’t understand.
I can’t, for the life of me,
discover what my dream is.
I’ve thought and thought until my head aches,
yet nothing comes.
It must be because I have no
real sense of responsibility as a person.
To think I’m such a pitiful girl...
Oh dear—you’re in luck!
Eh? Wh-What do you mean?
Why, two eyes!
This joke is too old
for your generation, it seems.
At any rate, if you wear such a gloomy face,
no dream will come to you.
Y-Yes...
Hold your heart large and open.
Okay.
Oh?
That's just like Mam’zelle.
Self-confidence must be supple.
Okay.
Like a soft spring.
Arrogant self-confidence snaps at once,
but supple confidence makes a person
strong all the way through.
If only you have that confidence in you,
dreams will come naturally.
Naturally…
Right... I see now!
Mais, Pat...
Oui, Mam’zelle?
The Twins at St. Clare's
"That may have been my dream all along..."
"My dream…
I don’t yet know it clearly,
but if there’s one dream that's dearer to me than anything else, it’s Pat's.
Ever since I was little,
I’ve been just a little jealous of her.
She’s so bright, so straightforward.
While I…
I fret too much about what others think,
rather than deciding for myself.
I wish I could become a girl
with Pat’s crisp, infinite energy.
That, perhaps, has been my dream."
What? You heard it?
Hey, Isabel,
read this.
Huh?
"I have been envious of my
twin sister Isabel from my childhood..."
Huh?
"Because she is kind, calm, and honest.
She has plenty of character that I do not have.
I am too quick a temper, and too rough a tongue,
and sometimes I hurt people unconsciously.
I wish to be the sort of person,
who is warm and tolerant, just like Isabel.
That may be my dream."
I never knew you thought of me that way.
Nor did I know that about you.
Fourteen years together,
and still so oblivious...
How silly we’ve been.
This won’t do for a proper
public speech, though, will it?
No. Not until we find some more confidence
to speak of our true dreams...
Our true dreams?
Ordinary...
honest dreams.
I know! Let’s just say it straight out.
Yes!
That's right.
“To become a natural scientist,
and safeguard the beauty of the earth—
that is my dream.”
Well, how was that?
I got too tense, with the Crown Prince
and even the Lord Mayor of London present!
Pat...
Are you truly going to give that speech?
They might throw us out of the hall for it!
T-Take courage.
Come on.
Okay...
Next we have St. Clare’s School.
Patricia O’Sullivan, Isabel O’Sullivan—
twin sisters, with their speech.
Dear…
W-Well...
F-First, we must apologise to you all.
We’ve not been able to find our dreams after all.
We’re sorry.
We don’t know what our dreams are.
That is the honest truth.
If we ever had a dream...
it was to escape as quickly as we could
from that St. Clare’s School we loathed.
U-Unbelievable!
What are they saying?!
What were they thinking, choosing those two
as the school's representatives?
Um...
It's not all!
My, so clumsy!
Please—let them speak!
Kathleen?
I know best of all why these two
were chosen to represent St. Clare’s.
You see... I once stole money from a friend!
Stole?
What?
Shameless!
But it was Pat and Isabel
who first forgave me.
So gentle and considerate—to me,
who had done something so base,
they gave the greatest treasure of all—friendship!
I trust them.
And I!
Hilary…
When my father fell ill
and I had no choice but to leave school,
Pat and Isabel did everything they could
and even more to let me stay till the very last.
They taught me so many things
never written in any textbook.
Pat!
Isabel!
We're with you!
Fear nothing!
With supple confidence!
Good luck, twins!
Y-Yes!
When our parents first made us
come to St. Clare’s,
our only dream was indeed to run away.
But then, lo and behold,
forty-six miracles shattered that dream.
One was Kathleen.
Always kind, always smiling
in the background—Kathleen!
But when someone was in trouble,
a sudden, unexpected courage emerges in her.
She amazed us time and again.
And Hilary.
Her character wins
everyone’s respect without effort.
Deeply emotive as a forest, warm as the sun.
Janet, so cheeky and stubborn,
is my eternal rival.
Joan, who could always laugh away
our sorrows, no matter how deep.
They, who gave us fresh energy
to carry on fighting—
Sheila, Vera, Alison—our classmates.
And Headmistress.
We spoiled, selfish girls
never trusted grown-ups.
Yet one glance into the Headmistress’s eyes and,
as if by magic, we felt that we could be completely open with her.
The Headmistress has magical eyes.
And the teachers who laugh with us,
weep with us, and scold us when we need it...
as people, and as women,
you are shining examples to us.
We were moved time and again
by each and every one of you.
Each day felt like a miracle.
To be learning at St. Clare’s—
that is now our greatest pride.
We shall go on searching for our true dreams,
hesitating, struggling, failing, and trying again.
But...
we have faith.
We know that dreams will be born here...
At the wonderful school of St. Clare’s.
We feel the first shoots of those dreams
are already stirring within us even now.
St. Clare’s is our soil,
nurturing the buds of our dreams.
And the tears, laughter, and encouragement of all forty-six of us, are the sun that shines upon them.
That is why...
we hold our heads high.
As we continue to walk towards dreams yet unknown,
dreams that lie dormant deep in our hearts,
but shall one day branch out,
spreading far and wide!
I just stared out the window all through class,
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, St. Clare’s.
Always dreaming away.
Thank you, for everything!
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Thank you
for sticking with us!
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Blasphemboys
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End (For real this time)