Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Binks!
This way!
Come back!
Binks, here boy, this way!
He’s got so much faster, hasn’t he?
Yes, when we first found him he was so tiny
we could outrun him easily.
Binks!
Binks, Binks!
So this is where you’ve been?
I’ve been searching for you!
Ah!
Who are you?
I’m Kelly.
You don’t mean to say
you owned Binks before?
That’s right. He was mine.
Episode 25
Give Back Binks!
Oh goodness! Oh goodness, oh goodness!
Oh goodness!
The owner of Binks has turned up!
I must tell Miss Lewis at once.
Miss Lewis!
Over here!
Say, Kelly, what do you mean,
you had him before?
You’re slow on the uptake, sis.
It means this dog belongs to me.
That can’t be...
Binks belongs to Kathleen now.
It seems all of you here
are slow on the uptake.
Wh-What was that?!
Try to think—that lass Kathleen
found Binks, didn’t she?
How do you know that?
I just heard you two talking.
What, exactly?
Well, all that about how small he was
when you first picked him up and so on.
Come on, hurry now.
Well then, thank you for looking
after my Binks all this time.
I’ll take him back now.
Hold it, Kelly.
What proof have you
that you’re his owner?
Proof?
Look how fond he is of me.
See?
Binks is friendly with everyone.
He’d wag his tail
for anyone who liked dogs.
Then come to my place.
I’ve a kennel ready for him.
Just a moment, Kelly.
You keep calling him Binks.
What was his name before?
Binks, of course.
Eh?
It was written on his collar.
Isn't that why you called him that too?
He never had a collar.
I did put one on him, though.
Ah, Miss Lewis!
Miss Lewis!
Miss Lewis, there’s a boy called Kelly
who says Binks belongs to him!
Where is he?
Ah! Kelly!
Wait!
Stop!
Hey!
Hold on!
Stop there!
Wait!
Stop!
Wait! Binks!
Wait!
Hey!
Why aren’t you eating, everyone?
Alison, how can you tuck in
at a time like this?
What do you mean?
The bus driver would know
where Kelly got off.
Even so, that doesn’t tell us
where he lives.
If we go round each house
patiently enough, we’ll find it.
Maybe so, but how long will it take?
But even if you do find him,
Kelly's still the owner, so it's out of your hands.
But there’s something odd.
What do you mean?
He seemed far too slick about it all.
I thought the same.
Headmistress!
Have you discovered anything?
Yes. We’ve found out where Kelly lives.
Eh?
Truly?
Here’s a map.
You get off at the second stop from here.
Pretty close!
What’s his home like?
His parents keep an orchard.
I’d like Miss Lewis
to call on them this Sunday.
Of course I’ll go.
Even if only on paper, I’m Binks’ owner.
But I… it doesn’t matter any more.
Eh?
What do you mean?
Even if you go, it won’t bring Binks back.
But it’s necessary to meet his parents
and speak with them properly.
Now the owner’s appeared,
there’s nothing else to talk about.
Nothing else…
What, you’re going to Kelly’s house?
Yes, we can’t wait until Sunday.
B-But…
You would give up on him straight away,
so it's best if you don’t come with us.
Ah... That’s not fair.
As I said, I really do think
there’s something fishy about Kelly.
He may not be Binks’ true master at all.
Surely not.
It's true.
I only wish it were so indeed, but...
Anyway, we’ll bring Binks back.
Just wait for us, won't you?
Isabel, Pat!
What about the map?
Safe and sound,
I know it by heart.
That house?
Ah!
Binks
Binks!
Hey, stop!
Ah!
Wait!
Binks!
Kelly?
Kelly, what’s wrong?
Is it your chest?
H-Hell no it doesn't...
But...
What are you doing here?
We never told you our names.
I’m Isabel.
And I’m Pat. We’re twins.
No wonder you're so alike,
thick as two short planks, the pair of you.
You little shit!
Sheesh...
Where are your father and mother?
Not here.
Where have they gone?
What business is it of yours?
When will they be back?
Not tonight.
Huh?
You’ve really come to see
if Binks is mine, haven’t you?
That’s right.
Then come and look.
See, the kennel has Binks painted on it.
I see, though it could
have been made only lately.
Look properly, it’s old.
It is indeed.
But the name seems freshly painted.
Because we've just touched it up.
Is that a problem?
If you understand, then be off.
Go on, clear off!
Kelly, may we ask something?
What now?
Won’t you let Kathleen have Binks back?
No! No way, I said!
I told you, he’s mine!
We understand, but to Kathleen,
he’s like a brother.
Since you've taken Binks away,
she’s been quite crushed.
Forget it! I’ll never give him back,
no matter what you say!
We're not saying forever.
Only until Kathleen gets over it.
Please, Kelly, do it for Kathleen.
Hell no! Binks is my friend!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Kelly, we understand.
We'll leave for today.
Don’t bother coming again.
But in exchange,
take good care of Binks.
That's obvious!
What’s the matter?
Do you want some water?
But to keep a dog chained up like that—
you can’t really call that looking after him with love.
What do you know about that?!
Dogs love to run about freely.
No chains—that’s what’s best for them.
Binks will become faster and faster from now on.
Take off the chain and let him
run about to his heart’s content.
Please wait.
I’m William, Kelly’s father.
I’m Lesley.
I’m Isabel.
And I’m Pat.
The truth is, I overheard
my son talking with you just now.
That dog, Binks—he wasn’t actually
Kelly’s to begin with.
I’m sorry for the lie.
I must apologise on Kelly’s behalf.
He’s always alone, and we are so busy
that we can’t often spare the time for him.
So sometimes he does things like this
to ease his loneliness.
Hasn’t he any friends?
He can’t make them.
Can’t?
The truth is, he suffers
from a serious heart condition.
What?
He can’t join in with ordinary children
in strenuous exercise.
That’s why, earlier...
Kelly can’t climb hills,
play in rivers, or even go to school.
Yet we told him to let Binks off the chain...
We promised to reward him
with a dog of his own if he undergoes a surgery.
But he just...
Why won’t he undergo the operation?
Because he’s learnt it’s a very difficult one.
Since then he’s been too frightened
even to go to hospital.
This operation requires the patient
to possess a strong will of his own to get better.
And... And what if Kelly
doesn’t receive that operation?
Within a few days,
we’ll certainly return the dog.
No, you won't!
No, no!
I won’t give Binks back!
Kelly!
Wait!
We’ll leave Binks with you.
Binks!
Kelly...
Be good friends, the both of you.
Huh?
B-But that's...
No, it's all right.
Kelly, we're counting on you
to look after Binks.
But they already said they’d return him...
How did it end up like this?
Good question.
But maybe it's for the best, right?
Yes! It could never have ended otherwise.
Still...
What on earth are we to tell Kathleen?
We promised we’d bring him back...
She’d given up once already,
and we raised her hopes again.
Kath's despair will be all the harder now.
Isabel! Pat!
Where’s Binks?
So it didn’t work out after all?
Sorry, Kathleen.
But at least we learnt
Kelly wasn’t Binks’s real owner.
Truly?
Then why didn’t you bring him back?
There’s... a good reason.
You should explain it to Headmistress.
Okay.
So that was the situation?
Now that I’ve heard the reason,
I see why you couldn't
take Binks away from Kelly.
Exactly.
That is why we had
to come back empty-handed.
And Miss Lewis, we’re sorry
we went off without permission today.
You only wanted to help Kathleen
as quickly as you could.
I can forgive that.
And if I’d been in your place,
I daresay I’d have done the same.
But even if it’s all good for Kelly,
what about Kathleen?
To be honest, when I first heard
Kelly wasn’t the owner, I was so happy.
But... I should rather
truly give up Binks this time.
Kathleen!
You don’t have to decide all at once.
That’s right!
You’re his owner, after all.
You have every right to take him back.
But I’m not really his owner either.
And besides, I’m already healthy,
with lots of friends.
I can’t take Binks away from Kelly.
Headmistress, please, I beg you too.
Let Binks stay with Kelly,
and let's leave it at that.
I...
I can bear it, even without Binks.
I’ll be all right.
Kathleen...
Kathleen!
Y-Yes?
Come and do the problem on the board.
O-Okay.
It's Binks!
Binks has come back!
What?!
Binks?
Binks!
Oh? There’s something tied to him.
Huh?
A letter!
“Dear twin sisters, I’m sorry I lied the other day.
I’m going to Switzerland now for the operation..."
Hooray, Switzerland!
"I do it because I want to become Binks’s true friend and run with him...
But even if the operation succeeds,
the rehabilitation will be tough
and it'll be a long time until I get home.
So I’m giving Binks back to Kathleen.
In Switzerland, they’ll let me
have a dog of my own.
I’ll call him Binks the Second.
When I come back,
I’ll bring him to meet Binks.
Then we’ll all run through
the hills and fields together.
Run to our hearts’ content!
Until then—goodbye.”
Kelly, we’ll miss the train if we don’t go now.
R-Right.
Kelly!
Goodbye, gals!
Goodbye!
Kelly! Best of luck!
Kelly! Stay strong!
The operation will definitely succeed!
Obviously!
Yes, Switzerland has
the best doctors in the field.
He’ll be right!
Come on then, let’s give Kelly a cheer!
Yeah!
Go, go, Kelly!
Keep it up, keep it up, Kelly!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
We’ve been chosen to represent St. Clare’s...
at the speech contest in London!
But Pat, the theme is “Our Dreams”!
“Our dreams”?
Yes.
Kathleen wants to be a vet.
Hilary wants to teach at a school for the blind.
Everyone has dreams but us...
Ah, how can we ever
write a speech for the contest?
What shall we do?
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
Final Episode,
"Thank you, St. Clare's."
Don't miss it!
Episode 26
Thank you, St. Clare's
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End