Shiori Fujisaki's Beginning
An interview with voice actress Mami Kanetsuki
At first, she was such a perfect girl
that I couldn’t even tell
how her emotions rose and fell,
or whether she ever felt things like hatred toward someone or deep sadness.
I wasn’t even sure if she
was capable of such feelings.
I thought maybe I had to portray her in this very neat, flawless way.
That’s what I was thinking at the beginning.
But through the drama CDs and
all the different routes of Tokimeki Memorial, Shiori-chan, too, experienced many different episodes.
And through that, I also started to understand how she would feel about things.
How should I put it…
It felt like I could see the subtle folds of her heart, especially in this OVA.
Yes, I really felt that.
What was the intention behind the lyrics for the episode #2's opening theme "Beginning?"
Starting with the game, Tokimeki Memorial as a series expanded into things like CDs and radio dramas—
it’s had many different branches.
And through all of those, each character has gone through worries, and had fun, too.
But up to this point, we hadn’t really shown the very human side—
those inner struggles, like wondering what is everyone going to do in the future.
It didn’t feel like we’d explored that before.
But in Volume 1, you can see the characters worrying about their future paths and love lives.
And I also thought,
“Yeah, that’s how it is at that age.”
So I also found myself cheering for them.
I wanted to create a kind of cheer song for the character.
That was the feeling I had when writing the lyrics.
Among those who’ve watched the video,
I think there might still be some who haven’t realized this yet,
but that Tokimeki Memorial OVA has a lot of foreshadowing woven into it.
And one of those is the CD listening scene.
I think it was Volume 1?
Shiori-chan receives a CD as a birthday present from the boy she likes.
Wait, no—it’s Volume 2.
That scene appears in Volume 2.
So she receives it, and she says,
“This is a CD I really wanted. Thank you.”
That CD—in scene where Shiori-chan is studying,
she always plays that CD while she studies.
Of course, part of it
is because she likes the music, but more than that, she cherishes it because it came from someone she likes.
And in the very first classical music listening session,
she’s actually playing that same CD.
She doesn’t talk about it much in depth,
but at the end of Volume 1, she realizes, “That’s right, I love him,”
and from there, as she begins to try and convey or nurture those feelings,
that CD becomes a very important, symbolic piece of music.
Will we ever meet again?
(From a fan)
Many of you may be wondering, “Does that mean the world of Kirameki High School is gone now?”
Well, who knows?
You see, from my perspective,
Part 2 is a new story set in the neighboring town,
but at the same time, Shiori-chan’s world will continue to expand in parallel.
So with your honest vote
for an interesting project,
maybe the interaction between the towns will deepen more and more,
and a huge new drama might be born.
Who knows—maybe Shiori-chan and the new heroine from Part 2
will sing a duet together, or even have a kind of rivalry or battle.
Please look forward to that.
I know I always say all sorts of things off the cuff,
and I always end up causing trouble for Konami...
So let’s see how Konami handles everything I’ve just said!
Everyone, look forward to it!
Translation: Perevodildo