I'm Fujisaki Shiori.
Today, I'm going to the production office
for the Tokimeki Memorial anime.
I'm going to visit the production company, Studio Pierrot.
Studio Pierrot
Digital Animation Room
This is Studio Pierrot.
Scriptwriter, Kuroda-san,
director, Kamegaki-san and character designer,
Motohashi-san are having a brainstorm.
Let's ask some questions!
Scriptwriter
Yosuke Kuroda
Scriptwriter Yosuke Kuroda:
Trigun / Battle Athletess Daiundoukai / Android Ana Maico 2010 / Tenchi Muyou! / Mahou Shoujo Pretty Sammy
Please tell us the difference
between the game and OVA.
First of all, I tried to combine the
game's originality with animation.
I mean,
even though similar pictures and characters are used, a game and a film are two different things.
So I drew a line in terms of how close it'd be to the game
without losing the excitement of film.
I hope everyone likes it.
What's there to see in Tokimeki Memorial OVA?
There's two parts. In the first half...
I was trying to describe the moment when...
the character's feelings turn
into love, in detail.
In the last half, I focused on the process,
in which she confesses her feelings to the boy.
Rather than making a mess,
I was hoping to describe...
the story in a slow, normal
transition of a girl's feelings...
until her confession,
after consultation with Konami.
Director
Hajime Kamegaki
Director Hajime Kamegaki:
Fushigi Yuugi / Ganbarist! Shun / Fushigi Yuugi Part 2 / B't X NEO / Sotsugyou M / Shonen Sunday Commercial
Have you ever played the game, Tokimeki Memorial?
I haven't yet played the game,
although I've already heard of it.
But considering things, I think I was lucky
not to have played it before this job.
If I were crazy about it at the time,
I couldn't have seen it objectively...
And would have made the
characters to my favorite types...
which would give nasty and
strange impressions to viewers.
From that point, I'll have fun
playing after I finish this job.
Please tell us about the differences
between the game and OVA.
This depends a lot on everyone's imagination.
I believe that this is not
driven by my image alone.
In that sense, animation is created by
many people who put their own feelings to it.
As such, without being influenced
by scenario writer Kuroda-kun,
I would want to find out my favorite girl.
Then if some of us get together the drama will develop naturally by expressing our opinions.
Who's your favorite character?
I was completely unaware but I've been
subjected to lots of information
and hot stuff about the characters by Kuroda-kun.
Apart from Fujisaki, my favorite among the girls,
since I like watching baseball,
I'd like to see a game with Nijino.
I'd be happy if it came true.
Character Designing Room
Character designer
Hideyuki Motohashi
Character designer Hideyuki Motohashi:
Fushigi Yuugi / Gambarist! Shun / Fushigi Yuugi Part 2 / Beat X NEO / Sotsugyou M
What is the essence of character design?
Since an animation relies on
the expression in the face...
I'm trying to give emphasis and
add highlights to the eyes and hair.
Even though it might be
different from the game...
I'm trying to appeal to those who
see things visually, in particular...
by creating characters who can tell
stories through their eyes and hair.
Who's your favorite character?
My favorite character, I mean, who I want
to draw, is Fujisaki Shiori, of course.
But honestly, Mikihara Megumi-san is my favorite
to draw because she has straight hair.
While I know every character has
their own impressive hair style,
my favorite is Mikihara Megumi-san
with straight hair.
Please send a short message to the fans.
As I find some new settings
to my surprise,
I'm happy if everyone is surprised
or sad in that sense as well.
While watching the video, you'll
find it's like a diary of your play.
I hope you remember each scene
and the sense of the situation.
And I'll be happy if you remember
your feelings of love.
I want to create scenes which make
you a little shy when you see them.
I've heard that the majority
of viewers are men.
So I want to create something which
makes me excited as well,
and makes me feel upbeat,
as if I were in the story!
What do you think?
It'll take some more time to complete the film, but it is already very exciting, isn't it?
Now then, I'll see you in the OVA!
You host, Fujisaki Shiori!