An interview with Shiho Kikuchi,
voice of Miharu Tatebayashi
When the girls from the game
come to life in animation,
What is your impression of the OVA?
I can't help but get super excited,
like "what it would be like?"
But when I come to the studio,
I forget everything!
When the characters appeared one by one,
there were cheers of “Waa! Waa!” during the recording session.
The impression I got was that they were all incredibly beautiful.
I remember the animators and director saying they paid attention to even a single strand of hair.
They really brought out
each character’s traits—
with beauty, elegance,
and a touch of sadness.
I think it was one of those moments that made me cry without meaning to.
It was an unhappy ending, wasn't it?
As for Tatebayashi, the ending is always like that.
Both in the CD drama and this OVA,
the ending is kind of sad.
I think Miharu-chan has a really strong sense of compassion.
So there’s this Miharu-chan who’s been watching over the person she likes, the protagonist, all along.
Rather than her own happiness,
she finds joy in someone else’s happiness...
In his happiness, and I think she’s the kind of girl who can truly feel content through that.
In a way, maybe she has a slightly passive or weak side because of that,
but at her core, I believe she’s incredibly strong.
You sang the insert song "Rain," didn't you?
When I heard there was going to be a recording,
I received the materials for the song and read the lyrics,
and also when I listened to the song,
I thought it was a bit different from the usual Tokimeki Memorial character songs.
It was more of a whispery voice kind of song, a sad, really sad kind of song.
I had heard that the song would be used in the OVA,
and I wondered what kind of scene it would appear in.
When the rainy scene started and the song played,
I thought, “Ah, that makes sense.”
Story-wise,
Miharu-chan has kind of an unhappy ending,
but the fact that she was given that song...
I think that in itself must mean she’s happy.
What were the past five years like
for Tatebayashi Miharu and Kikuchi Shiho?
When I first got the role,
her character description read something like “a girl who keeps watching the protagonist
from the shadows, undeterred by wind or rain.”
And the script had only about 10 pages of lines—
compared to everyone else, it was really, really little.
But when I was given the chance to sing “Journey Song” the other day,
I had a lot more lines and got to speak a lot.
So I feel like, in terms of Tatebayashi’s story,
her dialogue gradually increased over time.
While other characters confessed their feelings and moved their stories forward,
Miharu-chan still ends up with the same sad ending—she stays in the same place.
But I’m sure that emotionally, with every story she completes, she grows a little stronger.
Even though five years have passed, she hasn’t aged,
just kept looping through those three years.
So in that sense, I think I, Kikuchi Shiho,
have probably grown emotionally too.
It feels like the two of us, in totally different worlds, have been running in sync, side by side.
Having come this far and finished the OVA, that’s kind of how I feel.
Will we ever see you again?
(From a fan)
Your perspective and feelings toward Tokimeki Memorial,
compared to five years ago, have probably changed little by little, too.
This may be the end in form,
but I think the feelings of us, the cast, the staff who created it, and the players
should be carried forward into the next form, the next incarnation of it.
That all depends on how we feel about it.
So rather than thinking of this as the end,
let’s treat it as a turning point to find a new form.
I hope everyone will continue to support us with your feelings.
I’m looking forward to the day we meet again.
This was Kikuchi Shiho.
Bye-bye!
Translation: Perevodildo