Kirameki
High
Graduation
Ceremony
Goodbye
Class 3-A
of Kirameki High
Everything has a beginning and an ending.
A meeting is inevitably followed by a parting.
The eternal connection between two people...
Is that not a wonderful source of happiness?
Our Kirameki High School has a myth.
At the end of the field, there is an old tree.
There is a myth that if a girl confesses her love to a boy on graduation day under that tree,
the two will be able to live happily ever after...
5 Months Ago
Mom? Mom, aren't you there?
Yes, this is Fujisaki.
Do you believe in love at first sight?
Eh?
Fujisaki...?
Um... Yes, this is Fujisaki speaking...
Huh? Ah...
I'm sorry!
I think I got the wrong number.
Oh no! What am I going to do now?
Maybe a crosstalk happened?
But then...
No, I do think so!
And... Um...
I'm sorry! Really sorry!
Sorry.
Was it an important call?
No...
I mean, you could call it
important, to an extent...
But if you said it's unimportant,
that'd also be true.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to report to me.
I don't mind.
Actually...
I just wanted to hear that person's voice.
Even if it's just for a moment.
Then it must be your boyfriend.
No! You've misunderstood!
We're not a couple or anything...
I hope you get through to him.
Huh?
The person that you actually intended to call.
Yes.
Like it or not.
I wonder who was the first to say that
I'll be going now!
Okay! Be careful on the road!
My memorial runs through my heart
I'm going...
I comb my hair in front of the mirror today
Pink lipstick is sweet magic,
my very special cologne
Whispering, twinkling, heart pounding, and loving
I want only you to look at me
Take the Chance
Great finishing touches
Tell Your Heart
I've prepared myself
A wonderful feeling, carried by the breeze
Try Your Luck
My uniform ribbon
Tell Your Love
I tie it again
Today's the day I can say, "Love me please"
Take the Chance
Great finishing touches
Tell your heart
I've prepared myself
Throw Your Charm
A wonderful feeling, carried by the breeze
And then...
Try Your Luck
My uniform ribbon
Tell Your Love
I tie it again
Today's the day I can say, "Love me please"
Take the Chance
A premonition of excitement
Tell Your Heart
You come running
Throw Your Charm
I can feel my heart pounding
Because...
Try Your Luck
Take a deep breath
Tell Your Love
Be brave
And confidently say, "Love me, please"
Tokimeki Memorial
Wrong number?
Yes.
It was from a very curious girl.
She sounded very nervous on the phone.
It piqued my curiosity,
so we talked for a while.
Really?
Richard Bach
So you're into those
kinds of books, Fujisaki-san?
It's the first time I'm borrowing it.
I just thought it'd make
for a nice break from studying.
By that logic, I'm doing nothing
but taking breaks all the time.
Izumi
Mio
There are only three months
left until the exams.
Incredible, isn't it? Only a year ago,
we were still in the middle of our school trip.
What is it?
No, it just reminded me of that time
a boy from your class
got attacked by an animal on a school trip.
Oh? Ah... Right.
Are those rumors true?
Well, that's...
Perhaps I shouldn't disclose it
for the sake of that boy's reputation.
Fujisaki-san, I'd like you to read this
next time you want to take a break.
You had it with you all this time?
I received it as a present for my birthday.
This book must be important to you!
I can't accept it.
The gifter must've been
someone very dear to you.
No, I wouldn't necessarily say so...
It's just that we go to the library together, that's all.
All right, but only for a week.
Sure, be my guest.
What's the matter?
Hm? No, it's nothing.
Hurry up and get back to defense!
There's an opening on the right side!
All right!
Okay, Yumi, you can come out now.
Mari, get in!
Okay!
It's good to be a second-year...
They can just run around and romp happily,
without a worry in the world.
Passing the ball here and there...
I envy them.
That girl must be Hoshino of Class 2-C!
Damn, what a cutie pie she's become!
Take note, take note.
That hurt! What the hell?
I can't believe it!
You gotta decide whether you're here to take notes on the girls, study, or grumble, big bro!
Humph! As if you could ever understand
your innocent brother’s sorrows
as he faces the upcoming entrance exams.
Maybe I'd have been better off
with some club, too...
Compete in Inter-School Championships,
make a name for myself,
and get offers from famous universities.
That'd be a nice plan.
The only thing you've been pursuing seriously
in the past three years are women.
Not like it bore any fruit, though.
You're such a nasty little sister.
Couldn't you spare even a bit of sympathy
for your brother's life tribulations?
I'm not having it easy either, you know.
Is it that guy again?
What did he do this time?
It’s a secret.
Good! Go for it, Mari!
I'm sorry. I've been thinking a lot
about my future and that's what I've come to.
But I promise to still prepare the lunch
for everyone during the competitions.
Okay. Then I'll come to help when you do.
Other than that...
How is it going between you and Senpai?
In what sense?
Aren't you going out?
Yes... We were at the stadium the other day.
It was the decisive battle for the top spot.
He hit! He hit!
Don't let me down with the next one!
That's not what I mean!
We want to know if you've made
any progress with him.
Well, about that...
What, you haven't confessed to him yet?
You see...
This is an important time for him.
I don't want to bother him with such trifles.
For a girl, love is no trifle!
Still, I'll hold on to it
until the graduation ceremony.
Do you have anything
planned for the ceremony?
It's a secret.
If I tell you now, it'll lose its effect.
I don’t know what you have planned,
but I like where this is going.
Girls have guts, too. When the time comes,
hit him with it like a bolt of lightning.
Kiyokawa-san?
Wait a minute!
What are you planning to do now?
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity for you!
Please let me consider it a bit longer.
Tell her, "You only live once!"
You only live once, huh?
I've told you, Kiyokawa.
Modern Japanese Poetry Collection
Hello?
Oh, it's you, Megu?
I'm sorry, that's not what I meant.
Yes. Oh, I see.
Tomorrow after school?
Yes. Fine by me.
Okay. See you!
The "that person" in this sentence example
refers to Setsu-san, who is mentioned
in the third line from the beginning.
From that point on, the author will use the term
"that person" in all her writings.
This depicts both her desire to view the character of Setsu objectively
and the subjective feelings
she has about him.
In other words, we can interpret this as her deliberately trying
to distance herself from Setsu, even though her feelings for him
are clearly showing through in her writing.
Like sounds being woven together to form a melody,
like silk being sewn together to form a garment,
like white clouds in a blue sky,
like fish swimming in water,
like flowers blooming in the sunlight,
will I ever find someone
who'll stay by my side forever?
Just consider...
What is he like—the person by my side?
It's someone I want to be close with.
Through confronting and combining my thoughts,
I can become a better version of myself.
If that’s what you call "love"...
Why do I feel so collected here?
Is it because I enjoy swimming?
Here.
How'd you wound up here?
I saw you coming here, that's how...
Did you reject the offer?
I just don't know what to do.
I find self-fulfillment in sports,
but not in competitions.
Because the career of a pro swimmer is always short.
I'd like to become a swimmer
for a pro team.
But I don't know if I'll be able
to continue swimming after I turn 20.
Or even if I'll still like it.
Hm?
Hello... Good morning.
Katagiri-san?
Oh? You know each other?
Yeah, I've seen her work at the school cultural festival. But what brings you here?
You came here to learn to swim, didn't you?
Eh? Oh... I guess that's what drew me here... Yeah.
Well, since you're asking for it
so nicely, I'll do it.
Come.
W-Wait! Just a minute...
W-W-Wait, I'm not mentally prepared yet...
Come on.
It's that girl...
She doesn't stand a chance for sure.
Ah! Katagiri-san!
Help! Help me! Please! Somebody!
The water isn't that deep.
Yes, good! Keep it up!
Don't leave #4 free!
Yumi, you're up!
Okay!
No, you're just making splashes!
You won't make any progress
if you just keep floundering.
You're getting the hang of it.
30 seconds more.
Keep going! Fight...
Thank you, Shiori-chan.
For what?
You’ve helped me become
a slightly better person than I used to be.
Where'd that come from?
It was the same in our second year.
If you weren't there to encourage me,
I'd never have the guts to go out with a boy.
Megu...
Megu, what are you doing?
But, it’s too embarrassing...
I think I can do without it.
What are you saying?
You’ve been waiting for this moment—
gather your courage!
Look, couldn't you give it to him from me?
But that defeats the whole point of it.
I can come with you, but that's all.
No...
It's nothing.
You’ve helped me become
a slightly better person than I used to be.
I...
I'm sorry.
I'm not ready to go out with a boy.
I'm flattered that you feel this way towards me, though.
Why did I feel that way?
I'm going to bed. Don't forget
to turn off the appliances in the kitchen.
Okay!
Hello?
Hello.
I'm that no-name caller again.
Did you call the wrong number again?
I've made sure to dial up
the correct number this time.
How should I say this...
I felt like talking to you for a bit.
How peculiar.
I also felt that way towards you.
I'm glad.
Good morning, Ijuuin-kun!
Rei-sama, good morning!
Good morning!
It looks like it's going to be another fine day.
Geez... It's the most regular thing that happens every morning, yet they can't get enough of it.
Shiori-chan?
Oh?
Ah, I...
Why were you spacing out?
Feeling romantic out of season?
Oh, right... There's that new girl
in Class F—Koshiki—isn't she a bit curious?
I agree.
I wonder if she's in the tennis club.
Yeah, that's right.
During the game, she spotted some boy,
came over and said, "Hello... So you're back?"
And then...
Um... Something urgent
came up, so excuse me.
Ah, w-wait a minut—
I'm sure...
It was for something very important.
When writing a conditional sentence,
we usually use "were" instead of "was."
Okay, you can sit down.
So, when "if" is used
in the empathic construction,
such as "if it is something that, et cetera,"
the "something" part becomes accentuated.
Ah! Fujisaki-kun, did you take a liking
to someone in the back rows?
Please read from the third line on page 96.
Okay.
"The world is your exercise book,
the pages on which you can do your sums.
It is not reality,
although you can express
reality there if you wish.
You are also free to write nonsense
or lies or to tear the page."
Kagami-san, the same time as usual today?
I'll be about 30 minutes late.
Could you warn everyone else?
Certainly, Kagami-san.
Close the door.
I've prepared what you requested.
Come on, we've no time to waste!
Please, wait...
I didn't bring my swimsuit today!
I'm not gonna swim, sorry!
I'll lend you my spare one.
N-No way...!
Do your best, Katagiri-san!
Name:
Date of Birth:
Blood Type:
Height:
Kagami Mira. Born on November 15th.
Blood type O, 167 cm tall...
Name: Kagami Mira
Date of Birth: November 15, 1979
Blood Type: O
Height: 167 cm
Likes melons, hates sour plum.
Do you even need that kind of info?
It's just part of the job.
My fortune telling is not like
any of the unscientific stuff out there.
I analyze natural ripple effects
of DNA sequences through fractals.
It even accounts for fluctuations
depending on the location.
It's not entirely clear to me,
but I get the gist of it.
So what does it say?
The results are favorable.
There is an 87% chance that your fortunes
in love, marriage, and life will improve.
Or rather, things have been unusually bad for you up until now.
The remaining 13% are missing
due to insufficient information about the partner.
There's not much I can do
without even knowing his name.
I just wanted to check
hypothetically, that's all.
To think you could get so excited or upset
over something so trivial...
Someone like you can afford to take it easy.
Well, I didn't expect you to understand. Thank you.
I hear the voice of the rain
it's crying
In the shadow of love, it's crying
My slightly nervous heart
Name: Himoo Yuina
Date of Birth: July 7, 1979
Blood Type: A
Height: 161 cm
is healed by the steady flow of its voice
Name:
Date of Birth:
Blood Type:
Height:
What am I doing?
Everyday I'm in Dream
(I'm in the Rain)
Everyday I'm in Love
A rainy kiss melts on my wounded lips
A rainy kiss melts into my eternal smile
I should have brought an umbrella...
Whew! It's raining hard! I'm glad I didn't take
my umbrella home from my locker.
You can walk under mine if you want.
Oh?
I hear the song of the rain
I know, right? When reservations opened,
it became impossible to get through to them!
it's ringing
So I had to rope in some friends for help,
I hear the eternal flow of love
and lo and behold—I finally scored tickets to PRF’s concert!
it's ringing
And it's the 7th row from the front!
I couldn't stop bragging about it
at school today!
Coming in through the window,
After all, it's been a long time
since we've had a date.
this gentle song envelops the room
Ah... It seems I still can't stop going about it.
I'm sorry for not letting you speak.
Not at all. It's all fine.
Oh... Good to know.
Everyday I'm in Dream
(I'm in the Rain)
Everyday I'm in Love
Um... Can I ask what exactly
you liked about that person?
A kiss in the rain can wipe away
even the hurtful words
Nothing in particular.
Um... Let's see...
Let's be together forever
Maybe it's 'cause we enjoy
each other's company?
He's cool and stylish.
He also plays all kinds of sports.
Kiss in the rain
You could say he's just like
every other boy out there,
but a long time ago, we went on a date
to a terribly boring library.
And here's the strange part.
I enjoyed it!
That was when I realized,
"Yes, he must be that special someone."
Special?
Yep. My very special person.
Thanks for walking me home.
I scratch your back, you scratch mine.
Your phone is ringing.
Yes. Thanks!
See you!
Hello?
It's raining outside, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Did something happen?
No. Nothing. Nothing changed at all.
Have you confessed yet?
I just content myself looking at him.
That alone is enough for me to be happy.
I'm a bit envious.
Huh?
To think that you can care about someone that much...
As for me...
I don't know.
I don't know what to make
of my own feelings right now.
I have someone who makes me happy.
But I don't know whether the feelings
I have toward that person are real.
That's easy to figure out.
Think about when that person
is no longer with you.
But they're always there.
Just try to imagine it.
Would you be sad?
Would you want to cry?
Would you perhaps feel that something important has been lost?
When they're no longer there, huh?
You may hate that thought,
but if it's so painful you don't even want
to think about it, that feeling is true.
I know because it's the same with me!
If they disappear...
from my life?
Modern Japanese
Poetry Collection
Huh? How strange...
Why?
Why...?
Returning the book?
Yes.
All right, consider it done.
I'll put it back on the shelf later.
Thank you.
You're here as always.
Fujisaki-san?
Thank you.
It's a wonderful book.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I've noticed this one passage in the book
that you've underlined.
Yes, I really like that poem.
I'm not very strong physically
and a bit of a coward.
But as I was reading this poem, I came to realize
I needed to change that part of myself.
And then the things around me
will seem different too.
Including the person
who gave this book to you?
That's right.
I see...
Like sounds being woven together to form a melody,
like silk being sewn together to form a garment,
like white clouds in a blue sky,
like fish swimming in water,
like flowers blooming in the sunlight,
will I ever
find someone who'll stay by my side forever?
Just consider...
What is he like—the person by my side?
It's someone I want to be close with,
that person.
Through confronting
and combining my thoughts,
I can become a better version of myself.
If that’s what you call "love"...
Modern Japanese
Poetry Collection
Perhaps, I...
Perhaps I'm in love now.
She was... watching over me?
Really?
Oh, this one?
There's something written on it.
Huh?
Tanaka Mio
Fujisaki Shiori
What? What is it?
I love Shiori
A light that gently envelops my heart
Something's different from before
I can feel it overflowing
For some reason,
whenever I remember your smile,
the road and the people I pass by begin to shine too
(I'm so happy to be with you)
The diary of my palpitation
Ever since the day I found you,
all sorts of wonders,
all sorts of kindnesses began to take off
I feel like I'm spending
the same time as you
It's the little things like that that make me happy
Is this love?
The diary of my palpitation...
What you see?
Yes. This is Fujisaki.
No.
It's nothing.
Anyway, do you need something today?
Let's see...
Yes. Sounds good.
Yes. Got it.
Don't forget to come!
Okay, later.
Maybe I...
Maybe, after all...
Maybe I'm in love?
Goodbye
Class 3-A
of Kirameki High
Everything has a beginning and an ending.
A meeting is inevitably followed by a parting.
The eternal connection between two people...
Is that not a wonderful source of happiness?
Our Kirameki High School has a myth.
At the end of the field, there is an old tree.
There is a myth that if a girl confesses her love to a boy on graduation day under that tree,
the two will be able to live happily ever after...
Maybe I...
am in love, after all.
Like it or not.
I wonder who was the first to say that
My memorial runs through my heart
Tokimeki Memorial
I comb my hair in front of the mirror today
Aren't you going to confess to him?
Don't you know, Shiori-chan?
Our Kirameki High School has a myth.
Pink lipstick is sweet magic,
my very special cologne
So you have to hold out
until the graduation day.
Whispering, twinkling, heart pounding, and loving
She doesn't stand a chance...
Present for you! Will you accept it?
I want only you to look at me
I cannot get your image out of my head...
When I'm at home,
I can only think about you.
Take the Chance
Great finishing touches
Tell Your Heart
I've prepared myself
I can't get anything done.
A wonderful feeling, carried by the breeze
I still have things to do here.
I can't graduate and let it drag behind me.
Try Your Luck
My uniform ribbon
Tell Your Love
I'm only doing this as a charity
for the unpopular guys.
I tie it again
Today's the day I can say, "Love me please"
I let them have some good memories
of high school.
I'm not having it easy either, you know!
Take the Chance
That was when I realized.
Great finishing touches
'Yes, he is that very special someone."
Tell your heart
I've prepared myself
And then things around me
would start to seem different too.
Throw Your Charm
A wonderful feeling, carried by the breeze
It's about him again?
What did he do this time?
And then...
Try Your Luck
My uniform ribbon
Hm... How do I put it...
Tell Your Love
I don't know for sure,
but I hear they're dating.
I tie it again
Today's the day I can say,
Do you believe in love at first sight?
"Love me please"
I don't know.
Take the Chance
A premonition of excitement
I don't know if my feelings right now
Tell Your Heart
You come running
are real or not.
Throw Your Charm
I can feel my heart pounding
Because...
Try Your Luck
Take a deep breath
Tell Your Love
Be brave
Tokimeki Memorial
And confidently say, "Love me, please"
Pre-order now!
RAW
Original translation
Transcription
Cooperation
Translation check & TS
Quality check
WOWmd
Crossfade
instable200
Obscurerips
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies