Hey, can I really have it?
It's been ten years already...
Ah, dear me!
Our family heirloom is a clay figure.
You can ski too? Wonderful!
Thank you. What is this?
Thank you, I'm good.
Mesmerizing indeed.
You mean my dress?
I mean you.
Come on, you can't be serious!
I would know!
Everyone, thank you for coming to the Ijuuin Christmas party that we take great pride in.
Please forget the everyday routine
and enjoy yourselves to the fullest today.
Fujisaki Shiori         Ishikawa Satomi     Honda Megumi
Thank you for coming.
Please check your coat
at cloakroom over there.
Okay.
Please keep this tag until you leave.
This is good!
Really?
Would you like some?
Yes, thanks.
Please enjoy yourself.
We've opened hotel in Hawaii recently.
You should come visit next time.
Wow! It's so gorgeous!
You're right, quite extravagant.
Oh, I see! So that's how it was?
What?!
Male guests are required to wear a neck tie.
Make sure no more unwanted rabble
slips into the party.
If anything improper happens to our female guests, it’ll disgrace the Ijuuin family name.
Yes, I’ve already made
all the necessary arrangements.
The special response unit
is deployed outside.
I'm counting on you, Sotoi.
I'm sorry.
No, it was my own inattention...
Do I know her?
Who is she?
Since when have you become afraid of getting hurt?
Where did the courage to take a step forward go?
Believing has become a little harder than before
Now even warmth is slipping away—
are you just going to let it go?
But...
If I embrace those feelings
and gaze at you without looking away,
you are fabulous—
more than today, more than yesterday
Only when you get hurt really deeply,
you'll learn what the true kindness is
You'll learn to fly much farther
You can be proud of what you believed in,
even if you've lost it and can't get over it
Throw your chest confidently out
and start walking
Tokimeki Memorial
What did you do for the New Year's holidays?
I studied the whole time.
The closest thing I did to celebrating
was going to the shrine.
What?
Nothing at all!
Come on...
The school starts tomorrow.
At your school too?
Uh? Yeah...
Huh, I see.
I'll get to see him again.
Actually, ever since the school had already permitted it,
I'm thinking of starting an after-school activity.
An activity?
Ugh!
For god's sake, what are you doing?
Even if we're not in the same grade,
I'll be doing same things senpai does.
We're already sharing the hardships!
If you have the time for that,
why not provide emotional support instead?
Another third-year girl from senpai's class
is treating him to her bento.
That's my senpai, all right!
He's hot as fire!
Huh?! No way!
Himoo-san...
Who are you?
Come on now...
I'm Saotome Yoshio of Class A.
Saotome?
Ah, the informant?
Well, that's one way to put it.
Do you need something?
Not anything in particular...
Ah... Come to think of it, I heard you got a job offer from one of the leading companies.
Congratulations.
Lucky you...
All that's left for you
is to just wait until the graduation.
If you've nothing to do,
how about a date?
I'm not in the mood.
I still have things to do.
I can't graduate and let it drag behind me.
To think I’d have a third-year student
still going back and forth about her future…
So, have you decided?
Isn't there a job that you'd like to do?
There is, like a news anchor,
or an entertainment reporter.
A stylist is good too, or a designer...
Geez. The winter holidays ended so soon!
Spring holidays will come
in just two months, stay strong.
Classical Music Appreciation Club
Every Thursday afternoon
in the music room
Kirameki High School
Classical music appreciation session
Chopin's Piano Concerto No.2 in F Minor
The piece we just listened to
is Chopin's Piano Concerto No.2 in F minor.
This piece was written by Chopin
in collaboration with Konstancja Kładkowska,
a vocal student at the Warsaw Conservatory.
She was Chopin's first love.
But despite his enormous talent,
Chopin couldn't bring himself to confess to her.
In later years, it was said that she didn't even remember Chopin's name.
Ijuuin-kun?
I know I'm a bit late,
but do you mind me joining the session?
Ah... Well, I'm sorry,
but we're done for today.
We can't borrow the music room for too long.
Really? Well, that's a pity.
I know!
As a consolation, why don't I use
the Ijuuin limousine to drive you all home?
But we haven't done anything
to deserve that.
I'm sorry, I must go
to the cram school right now.
And I promised mom
to go shopping after school.
Shiori-kun, perhaps you also
have some errands to run after school?
Eh? No, I don't...
Then it's decided.
No! Not fair! Rei-sama!
Shiori-kun, why did you decide
to start that kind of after-school activity?
Our high school life
is nearing its completion.
Maybe it's not the most straightforward explanation,
but I wanted to do something
that would leave a memory.
Why not? Who knows, maybe that person
will also come to listen to it.
It was all I could do.
The company suits have just called.
If you don’t give them an answer today,
you might as well pretend
the offer never existed.
Cyclamen...
In the flower language, you mean shyness.
You're just like me...
Whew! To think I'd get to eat your bento!
Here, you need to keep your spirits high.
It is that obvious my spirits are low?
Yes, a bit.
My! That's really cute.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
This stuff totally doesn't suit me.
All I do is swimming,
so my body shape is like that of a boy.
Did he say something?
I know he cares for me.
I'm just...
A little, you know, insecure.
You're growing your hair long...
Yeah.
Ah, auntie? Hi! It's me, Ayako.
Uh-huh. Yes.
I see.
Uh-huh. No matter what?
Maybe he'll never come, after all...
Hey, keep it quiet back there!
You don't want to stay out
in this cold all day long, do you?
Hey, Shiori, did you know?
What?
That boy and Kagami from Class H
went on a date.
It seems they've got time to spare, even though the exams are right around the corner!
Yes, this is Fujisaki.
Ah... You answered so fast,
it caught me by surprise!
I wanted to say...
Something really good happened today.
What's wrong?
"Just watching...
Just watching him is good enough..."
Is that true?
I was thinking...
If I don't tell him...
about my feelings,
he might never notice.
But...
I won't find the courage for that.
I know I won't.
Yoshio-kun, can we talk?
Hey Yoshio! What did Fujisaki
say to you just now?
She asked for a phone number...
Yes, this is Kagami.
Um...
Who is calling?
Um... I'm...
Ah! It broke!
You broke it!
Oh god... Will you two stop!
Hey! Just stop for a minute!
You'll get hurt if you step on the pieces!
Don't you hear? You need to stop!
Ah...
Oh no, I'm sorry.
Hello? Hello?
Well, great job, you two! I already missed out
on a date because of you, and now this!
No...
I can't do it...
So what is it?
What did you call me here for?
Do you want to learn breaststroke next?
You're making me nervous.
A present for you.
Please accept it.
That's so sudden... Why?
Please...
O-Okay...
Keep up the good work, swimming.
This time, we're going to listen
to Beethoven's Piano Sonata No. 14.
"Moonlight" in C sharp minor.
This piece was dedicated to Countess Giulietta Guicciardi, who was Beethoven's piano teacher.
The title of this piece, Moonlight,
was not chosen in accordance with the composer's own vision,
but rather coined by the German critic...
Mira-kun, that classmate of mine...
What was his name...
Anyway, I don't know him well,
but I've heard you two are going out.
P-Please don't misunderstand...
It was merely a charity for an unpopular boy.
I wanted him to have
some nice memories of his high school days.
All right, then.
And now, let's get started.
Huh? Going abroad? Our Ayako?
Yes. It's something she's been considering for a long time.
She has an aunt living abroad,
so she's going to study in earnest now.
She's brave...
I couldn't do something like that.
If I get injured and can no longer swim,
I will have nothing left of my life.
Isn't that the same for everyone?
That flower is Lavender, right?
Yes, it's the birth flower
for my birthday, December 3rd.
In flower language, it's "hope."
Even though she always looks so untroubled...
Can't stop doing what I love?
University Entrance Exam Site
When you keep chasing what you once dreamed,
a cold, strong wind will blow to stop you
Staffroom
Goodbye.
Continuing to walk as you please is nice,
but you may feel lonely and want to cry along the way
So you've decided?
It seems I have it written
all over my face, huh?
Good luck. I'll keep cheering for you.
That being said,
all I can do is make bento for you...
But believe in yourself,
because it's what you decided, don't waver
I'll pass.
See, the world gets more wonderful
every time it opens up
After all, there must be someone else
that you need to cook them for.
If it's a dream you yearn for
so passionately, just give it a form
But I want to make them
for someone who's always doing her best.
Bonjour, bonsoir.
Oui, c'est ca. Je voudrais...
Be stronger, be more enduring
France, huh...
If you stop and waver,
just try to remember what it means to be honest
Rats! This time for sure!
Senpai likes... me!
Ah, there you are. It's me!
A bright new tomorrow is waiting for you
Ah, this? I bought a cell phone.
No one calls from public phones these days.
It's finally finished.
With this, I can conquer the world.
Anytime.
But...
Friends, although it was only for a short time,
thank you all for joining us
for all the listening sessions.
I planned this kind of after-school activity with graduation just around the corner
because I wanted to leave something behind
from my three years at this school.
I wanted to spend as much time as possible with people I did not yet knew personally,
even though we were in the same school.
And also...
Never mind.
Thank you ever so much.
Our graduation is just a week away.
And so, the following piece
will become our final listening session.
Mozart Piano Concerto No. 27.
This song is rumored to have been written for Magdalena Hofdemel,
who is believed to have been
Mozart's last mistress.
And now, please enjoy.
Employment notice
Just one week left, huh?
These three years really flew by.
But there's still one last important event
before we wrap up our high school days.
Event?
I wonder what is she doing there.
It's a bit embarrassing for me to talk about,
but I just couldn't get your image out of my head.
You didn't know, Shiori-chan?
There's a myth going around
our Kirameki High.
There is a myth that if a girl confesses her love to a boy on graduation day under that tree,
the two will be able to live happily ever after...
But if you tell others, it will lose its effect.
The myth of Kirameki High?
Yes. And that tree
is the one from the myth.
Graduation is in three days
You know... Actually, I've always...
I don't have the courage...
Modern Japanese
Poetry Collection
Forest
Gump
Melody
of Love
Rewind
Why...
Am I like this?
The low pressure front keeps moving eastward,
and the high pressure front
coming from the conflict is gaining strength.
The clouds will move eastward from Kanto,
so it's going to be sunny starting tomorrow.
However, it'll still be chilly tonight
and may turn to snow in some places.
Sis, what are you grinning at in the mirror?
Hey! Kids should already be in bed by now!
Sweet dreams!
G'night.
Good luck, sis.
Thank you.
The back...
of a boy...
Now then...
What do I do after I chop these up?
I'm sorry, Robo.
Hello?
Miss No-name Caller?
Yes...
You got me.
What's wrong?
What happened?
My love...
died.
I can understand why...
That person always had an eye
for another girl.
I knew it all along.
When I first met her at school,
I thought she was nice.
But for him, it was love at first sight.
But I didn't know how to approach him,
how to speak up.
So I decided to just take the plunge...
His shocked expression
is still vivid in my memory.
I would also often walk past him
so that he could remember my face.
I thought it was good enough
even if I don't tell him anything.
I thought just watching him
was good enough...
But, I was terribly wrong...
I couldn't stand just watching him
and then part forever.
So I mustered all of my courage today
and called him on the phone.
Walking down the avenue with that person...
I pictured it in my heart the whole time!
It was to become a wonderful memory.
It was meant...
It was meant to be a wonderful day!
Hello?
Have courage,
Fujisaki Shiori-san...
Eh?
Your feelings will surely reach him....
They will reach the person you love!
I've been bothering you for so long...
This will become the final call
of the no-name caller.
Ah, wait... Hey, wait a minute!
How do you know my name?
Do it with all the courage you can muster...
My feelings...
The feelings that he never noticed
are still growing ever-stronger.
Our time together,
the three years we spent here...
Hey, look! Do you remember this?
It's a mark from when we compared
our heights about ten years ago.
What a great sense of mystery...
I want to keep watching
the stars like this forever.
I've prepared a cake.
Would you come to my place?
I wonder if we look
like a couple right now.
I'm sorry! I just felt like
spooking you a bit there.
Pretty! It's a White Christmas!
If you want to know,
I just prayed for some courage.
I felt that giving you this at school
would be too embarrassing.
After all, I put my very special feelings
into this chocolate.
I've sought this CD for a long time.
I'll make sure to treasure it!
And today, the time has come for you
to graduate from this temple of knowledge.
Thank you for all the wonderful memories.
I'm lucky to have a childhood friend like you.
It's not true...
No...
Not just a childhood friend...
I don't want it to become just a memory...
Because...
Because!
I...
I...!
I'll tell him with all the courage I have...
how I'm feeling right now.
I'll tell him under the old tree from the myth!
About my love for him.
I'll tell him, the person I love.
I'm sorry for making you
come all the way here.
There's something I need
to tell you today, no matter what.
Actually, I've never dated a boy up until now...
But, that's not to say I'm disinterested.
I would really like to date a boy, if I could.
And I've even received
a few love letters in the past.
But...
For some reason,
I didn't feel like going out with them.
That's because...
Because you were by my side.
Up to now, I've always thought of you
as nothing but a childhood friend.
No...
I was just too scared
to reveal my true feelings to you.
Maybe that's what I thought...
But now,
now that we have to graduate...
Now that we must go our separate ways
and may never meet again,
I've finally realized what I feel.
I feel embarrassed and want to run away,
but I...
Don't want to stay just childhood friends.
I want to be the only girl...
that you look at.
So I'll muster my courage
and say it.
I love you.
I only love you
with all the love in the world.
Say, isn't it strange?
I should be really happy now,
but I can't stop crying.
Don't ever, ever let me go.
Today's topic: one last word.
Performing for you: Tatebayashi Miharu,
voiced by Shiho Kikuchi (菊池 志穂).
I guess I believe in love at [UwU]
I guess I believe in love at first sight!
Mikihara Megumi,
by Mikiko Kurihara (栗原 みきこ).
I don't wanna do it for another 30 seconds!
Mikiko.
Asahina Yuuko, Yoko Teppouzuka (鉄炮塚 葉子).
Thank you so much for everything.
Asahina-san will do her best from now on,
I'll also give it my best.
I hope you all stay well.
Kisaragi Mio, Akiko Sekine (関根 明子).
Thank you so much, everyone.
It was a very wonderful memorial.
- Akiko.
Himoo Yuina, Tomoko Naka (中 友子).
Oh man, it was fun!
Don't you agree?
It was so much fun!
I feel a little sad that I'm graduating.
Here's one last word from me:
Robo, go!
Tomoko.
Saotome Yumi, Kurin Yoshiki (よしき くりん).
Thank you so much for sticking with us all this time.
I'm sure that every ending
is also a new beginning.
It was a lot of fun, I agree.
A lot has happened.
Let's meet again somewhere.
So my last word is,
"Next is big brother!"
Right, right, thanks...
You forgot? Kurin! (Yoshiki)
Yeah, I did forget.
Saotome Yoshio, Yuuji Ueda (うえだ ゆうじ).
May you have a nightmare tonight...
Yuji!
Katagiri Ayako, Masayo Kawaguchi (川口 雅代).
And as for my last word, I just want to say I love you and I'm gonna miss you.
Good luck and goodbye.
You are my treasure forever.
Goodbye.
With love from New York, thank you for your hard work, everyone. Masayo.
Nijino Saki, Sachiko Sugawara (菅原 祥子).
Sugawara.
Yes. It was very fun.
It was a really long time,
enough for my hair to grow long again.
Thank you very much for sticking around!
I want to see everyone like this again.
I hope to see you in a year or two.
This was Sugawara Sachiko!
Ijuuin Rei, Narumi Tsunoda (津野田 なるみ).
How do you do, peasants!
Thank you very much for sticking around. Narumi.
Koshiki Yukari, Ayako Kurosaki (黒崎 彩子).
Really, really, really!
Thank you for a long, long, long time with us!
I've grown up to be a lot more responsible.
It's a lie!
Why's that?
Ayako.
Kiyokawa Nozomi, Ayako Sasaki (笹木 綾子).
During this year, my skirt just kept getting shorter and shorter.
It only got a little longer at the end,
when I had an operation, LOL.
Let's meet again somewhere. Ayako.
Kagami Mira, Rei Igarashi (五十嵐 麗).
Since this is the last time,
I thought I'd say my thanks to everyone.
Do you agree?
Is that okay?
Well then, everyone, it was really fun, wasn't it?
Everyone?
Yes, Kagami-san!
This was Rei.
Sorry, sorry.
Fujisaki Shiori, Mami Kingetsu (金月 真美).
I'm really grateful to all the different people I've got to meet.
It's been a very enjoyable few years.
And I ended up saying it too...
Yes, but really, I want to say this on behalf of all the cast and staff,
thank you very much for your support!
Please remember us again somewhere, sometime. Mami.
Strange glasses!
You didn't have to mention the glasses!
Like it or not.
I wonder who was the first to say that
My memorial runs through my heart
I comb my hair in front of the mirror today
Pink lipstick is sweet magic,
my very special cologne
Whispering, twinkling, heart pounding, and loving
I want only you to look at me
Take the Chance
Great finishing touches
Tell Your Heart
I've prepared myself
A wonderful feeling, carried by the breeze
Try Your Luck
My uniform ribbon
Tell Your Love
I tie it again
Today's the day I can say, "Love me please"
Tokimeki Memorial 2
RAW
Original translation
Transcription
Cooperation
Translation check & TS
Quality check
WOWmd
Crossfade
instable200
Obscurerips
Perevodildo
None