Uh, hello? Janice...?
Who the hell are you calling?
Huh? Oh, wrong number, sorry...
Shit...
Dammit, May! You always overdo it.
The possession of this firearm would complement your file nicely... Jonathan Washington.
Bitch! You're no cop, are you?
Larry Vincent, bounty hunter.
And I'm Minnie May!
Hope you'll behave from now on.
Hello. This is Gunsmith Cats.
What? Becky, what does that mean?
Washington was arrested for illegal drug possession...
but no substances were found on him.
But why try to run away so hard when you know
you'd likely be apprehended anyway?
That's the question.
Something doesn't add up.
Hey, Becky,
could you run a check on him once more?
Well, it'll cost you.
You bloodsucker...
I've got a customer. Later!
Welcome.
Looking for anything in particular?
I'd like to get some customizations done.
A police officer, Roy Coleman,
recommended you.
Certainly.
Could you write down your name and address?
Okay...
You really ought to be more careful!
Did you know you left a round in the chamber?
Sorry about that...
Is this okay?
Yes.
I'm guessing you're a police officer too.
You know this'll make your gun heavier, right?
It's for my personal collection.
I'm in the K-9 division, so I primarily use this guy.
Revolvers are nice, but I'd suggest
bringing that in for maintenance too.
Sounds like it's got some loose parts.
D-Does it?
Oh, that's my partner calling.
Also, if you'd maybe like to
get some dinner together on a weekend,
you can call my number anytime.
Thanks, but I think I'll just call you
when your gun is ready.
Give my regards to Roy.
A bulletproof heart, just like I heard.
See ya!
Come again!
Geez, it's no wonder you can't get a man.
I don't remember asking!
He's not asking to marry you, you know.
Shut up!
Welc—
Easy there! I come in peace.
William Collins, special agent with the ATF—
Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, and Firearms.
And what can we do for your Department of Everything Fun?
Our books are up to date.
Oh, no. That's not what I'm here for!
So what, then?
I'll get straight to the point.
I'd like your help on a little sting operation.
A little what?
Can we talk this over in the back room?
So, Jonathan Washington doesn't actually trade drugs, but he runs guns?
Yep. And the reason he was running away
was to sell enough of his stock to post his own bail.
And then I caught him
before he could do that?
So, why not let him escape again?
I'm afraid it's not that easy,
which brings me to why I'm here.
You want to make a deal with him
to find where he stashed his merchandise?
Correct.
Alas, we're operating
on a tight budget, but— huh?
Sorry, but we don't have much to discuss, then.
The exit is this way!
Ah, bummer.
I really didn't want to resort to a house search.
And just what are you implying?
Illegal possession of weapons
requiring a Class 3 license.
You don't have one?
And as for you, May Hopkins...
Illegal possession of explosives and violation of the Hazardous Materials Handling Act.
Fine... What do you want us to do?
If this goes through, we can get you licensed and knock $250 off the tax on each gun.
Well, I'm not asking for an immediate decision.
Please think it over.
Thanks for the coffee...
Oh, and one more thing...
Remember to lock your doors.
They just left the shop.
Roger. I'm ready.
It's all you now.
Roger.
What the hell? There's nothing to eat!
What are you talking about?
We have our dinner right here.
Don't be so picky.
I'm sick of Chinese takeout.
And I'm sick of the pizza you always get!
Don't slander it like that!
Hey, seriously.
What do we do about that ATF guy?
What choice do we have? If we don't
do what he wants, we'll both be in cuffs soon.
That doesn't sound like you.
Is there really nothing we can do?
Well, why don't you use some
of that feminine charm of yours?
Don't you have a thing for middle-aged men?
I think I'm still youngish, you know.
Larry!
Knock it off.
That guy has zero style.
Ken... love you...
Hey! This is just an ordinary house.
Are you sure they've got loads of guns?
I trust my source.
Okay, let's do this quick.
Thieves?
It's been a while...
It's the mother lode!
What did I tell you?
Wow!
They've got all sorts of variety!
Who the hell are the people living here?
Hey! Take a look at this bad boy!
There's enough here to start a war!
No question about that!
Three of them. I can handle that.
Hey! Are you gonna blow up the house?
I've prepared the smokeless ones, alright?
That's not the point.
You stay out of this.
Aww...
Hey!
The other room is filled with ammo.
Cool. That's just what I need.
Hey, are you really gonna load it right now?
I've always wanted to have one like this.
Shit!
Where'd he go?
Huh?
Wait! Don't go that way!
This is a no-parking zone.
What do you mean, "Stay out of this"?
Like I said, this is the ATF's private investigation.
Geez, what a mess!
That was a pretty slick arrest.
Almost like you set this all up.
Hm? Come on! Why would I?
Hmph... I don't buy it.
Still, what a splendid collection you have.
It'd be a real waste to
have to melt them all down.
Enough, already. We'll help.
Huh?
You will? That'd be great!
But on one condition.
You've gotta let me do it my way.
That means no tailing and no outside interference.
Not a problem!
So we've got a deal, then?
Spare me the pleasantries. May, let's go.
Ra... Larry!
Hm... Oh!
Oh, right...
It's only your panties.
You're never getting married anyway, right?
Shut up, you...
So, what brings you here?
Like I said,
I just want to buy your "toys".
First, you put me in jail, and now this?
Well, whatever...
I still need cash. Cough up some front money,
then we can talk about the details.
How much do you need?
Go ask the judge.
Oh, I gotcha.
I made a deal with Washington.
The exchange is to take place in three days.
He said he'd fax me the time and place later.
Well done. I was right to bring you in.
Spare me the flattery.
Just remember to make good on your promise.
Of course. I won't get in your way.
Somehow I'm not convinced.
And another thing...
We won't tail you. You have my word!
Anyways, I'm counting on you.
What?
Boss is calling.
Huh?
Oh geez, I was trying to keep this thing a secret,
but it seems it's been leaked already.
Yes, when it comes to this case... Yes.
Come in.
You called?
The three new agents we brought in are already dead without having made any real headway.
What's going on?
I'm trying here.
Right, so who're you sending this time?
Well... nobody.
Nobody? What about the investigation?!
Well, I have no conclusive evidence yet,
but it looks like there's a rat,
here, in our Illinois division.
You can't be serious!
Who is it?
Like I told you, I've got no evidence.
He would've been dealt with if I did.
R-Right, I see your point.
What?
You have a call from a state senator.
On it.
Hey, Bill!
Worst case, I'll go undercover myself.
Later!
I'm counting on you.
Yeah, I know.
Yes, I'm here! Black speaking.
Yes, with your help... Yes.
It sure is exhausting to be a big shot.
Why are you guys always doing this to me?!
You're nothing but trouble.
You always do things without talking to me!
What was that, Becky?
I asked, why'd you take such a stupid job?
I was worried,
so I arranged a great gig for you!
Look, I told you, we'll have license
and tax problems if we don't take this job.
So what?!
Larry, you got a fax.
Oh, Becky, what're you doing here?
Yeah, good question!
Because it seems my advice isn't worth squat here!
Now, now, don't be so salty.
I'll buy you dinner.
No Chinese takeout or pizza.
Hey, Larry!
Where the heck are you taking me?
All you have to do is stay in the car.
After this, I'll buy dinner, trust me.
And what do I do?
Nothing whatsoever.
What the hell?
Oh, I see. You're making me babysit May.
Bingo!
Hold up, Larry!
That's not what we...
Really...
Here I go.
Be careful.
Who's there?
Larry Vincent. I'm here to
buy from Jonathan Washington.
Come inside.
Thanks.
You're packing, right?
We'll hold onto them for you.
Sure, sure.
Slowly!
Sheesh...
Like that?
Give it to him.
What's next?
Any other weapons?
Yep, here you go!
Hey! Full body check!
Do what you need to.
Sorry! Just doing my job.
She's clean.
Hey.
Washington's upstairs.
You. Go with her.
Yes.
What a creepy bitch, dammit!
Who is it?
My, what interesting hobbies you have.
Oh, it's you. Glad you decided to come.
Of course I did!
I did pay your bail, after all.
By the way,
when do I get my guns back?
You'll get them back
as soon as you pass a little test.
Test?
Yeah. The boss won't let me
hear the end of it if I'm not careful enough.
What do I have to do?
Oh, it's nothing.
It won't be a bother.
This way.
Who's he?
Some special agent.
He was snooping around outside.
Luckily for us, the boss spotted him.
Looks like I'm famous.
Now I remember!
This is the same guy who blackmailed me into setting you up.
Tsk. That's what I thought.
Larry...
Sorry, but things won't go your way this time.
So, what's this test?
Here's his gun.
You want me to take care of him?
Business is built on trust.
Hmph!
Hey, what about the bullets?
You don't expect me
to club him to death, do you?
Oops! My bad.
Still, you can tell just by holding it.
That's what it means to be a pro here.
So much for that "trust"!
The boss just wants to be careful.
Killing an official will land you in a sea of trouble later.
By the way, do you really have the merchandise on you?
Of course!
I've got a few samples over here.
These come in handy when push comes to shove.
I'm looking for something more conventional.
Don't worry. We've got crates bursting with guns downstairs.
Really? Good to know.
Catch!
Freeze!
L-Let's talk this over.
This is what happens when you don't take a lady at her word.
You too!
All the lights went out!
Oh my... this looks pretty bad.
That's my cue.
Huh? May? How'd you get loose?
Don't!
May...
That was harsh, Larry.
You really shouldn't have deceived me.
Just paying you back for jumping the gun.
What were you doing here anyway?
I may have crap fashion sense,
but I can be useful.
I'm no Eliot Ness, but still.
Right... sure.
What do you know?
They don't trust you at all.
It's looking grim.
Too bad we can't grow wings and fly away.
Suck it up. I don't intend on becoming an angel anytime soon.
That's reassuring.
Well, bossman... shall we boogie?
What a reckless moron!
Over there!
Yikes!
Locked too?
Well then...
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
Larry!
Cover me!
You take care of yourself!
I'm pinned too...
Larry, you okay?
Larry!
I'm not one to gamble, but...
That bitch is a crack shot.
I was just aiming at the floor,
but I'm not complaining.
Larry, behind you!
Larry!
Come on...
Shit!
Larry?
Where are you? Larry!
May, look out!
Larry!
Idiot!
Die!
Bill!
See, I wasn't totally useless after all, was I?
Yeah, right, he says
after pulling that reckless stunt.
It wasn't my cleanest performance.
Bastards... We're not done yet!
But we are!
What?
No way...
I have nothing to do with this!
Yes, that's right. We caught them all.
Seriously, what's your problem?
You have no sense of severity whatsoever!
But if I hadn't shown up,
you'd be meeting St. Peter right about now!
I can take care of myself.
Oh, is that so?
Hey now, you two.
Don't even get us started!
Eh? What did you say?
It seems my ears are still a bit clogged.
You're impossible.
How insufferable can you be?
Ah, that's right.
Speaking of jerks, I've got one more little favor to ask. How about it?
Huh?!
You're joking...
With this gun-smuggling business dealt with,
we hoped to catch a break...
But Jonathan escaped once more,
and we're the ones in captivity now!
That Bill from the ATF isn't very trustworthy.
And to make matters worse,
there's this crazy Russian running around!
You'd better be extra careful.
That Russian's a real psycho!
Aah! Larry, help!
Ah! May!
The next episode of Gunsmith Cats!
Chapter 2: "Swing High."
Don't you underestimate my driving!