Yeah, we're about to load
them onto the truck now.
Yes, tomorrow, I guarantee it.
What's going on there at this hour?
Damn it...
Huh?
Hello.
Wha...
Goodbye.
Who'd use a weapon that you have to recover after every use?
Shut up, you idiot.
She doesn't understand a word of it anyway.
Hey, Major!
Is it true that Russian women will sleep with any American guy?
Dumbass!
Even ex-special forces operatives
will do anything for money.
So how much for a night in your bed, eh?
Cut it out already!
Yes?
What? Got it...
Ms. Radinov!
It looks like the boss
has another job for you.
For an additional fee, of course.
Another hit?
"Yes. Thank you for calling Gunsmith Cats.
We're unable to take
your call at this time.
Please leave a message
after the sound of the beep."
Say, what the hell were you thinking?
We’re the ones who busted you,
and now you're asking us to meet you out here?
It's not a very fitting place to take revenge, you know...
As far as we're concerned, your case is closed.
What do you hope to accomplish
by locking out the ATF guys?
Trust me... Gimme a sec...
Hey, are you listening to me?
Damn it, he cut the microphone!
Let's go!
Please! You gotta break me out of here!
Don't you understand what kind of place this is?
You're in an ATF safe house!
Washington, you won't
find a safer place anywhere.
I know too much about the organization.
I'm a sitting duck in here.
That's why the ATF stationed five guards to—
But those ATF agents aren't to be trusted!
Washington, time's up!
Open the door!
Get the spare key!
Right...
Washington! Open up!
Washington!
I know... Could you at least take this watch?
It's a Rolex.
All I'm asking of you is to give this to my daughter.
I have her address here.
Now hold on a second! Why should we...
This is the only thing I can do for her as a father.
Please, Larry!
Wait a second!
We're not done talking yet.
No, I've heard enough.
But...
Excuse me.
Ms. Larry...
I'm telling the truth.
You'll understand soon.
And when you do, I won't be around anymore.
He walked a slippery slope, and this is all he had left...
That's kinda sad, really.
Sheesh. You're too soft, May.
Why's that?
Because you took a job
that's not gonna pay a dime.
I didn't hear you raising any objections.
That's not the point.
By the way, May, have you
been practicing our new timings?
Huh? Yeah, I have.
I made it all the way to where we bust a move.
Wanna go over it?
Sure.
Ready?
Ah!
That punk bitch!
I won't forget that face!
Larry...
Damn it!
They dumped all this extra work on me.
At least it's good to kill time.
And now, the news.
Huh?
With the mayoral election coming up,
state senator Edward Heinz
pledged today to work with the ATF to completely eradicate illegal gun and drug trafficking.
We all know law-abiding citizens don't need these things.
I'm just trying to promote some common-sense solutions.
Where's the camera?
Ah.
Fellow citizens! I, Edward Heinz, promise you that,
together with George Black of the ATF...
Furthermore, to improve his reputation—
Boss never misses a PR opportunity.
Hey, are there any other visitors
scheduled for today?
No, not that I know of.
Hey Bill, what's going on... Huh?
Stop! I'm warning you!
Drop the gun!
W-Wait!
I know what can take down the organization.
Don't kill me!
My people will come—
Five agents down in one go!
It seems the rumors
of a rat in the ATF were true...
Hey, did you hear what happened to Bill?
What's that?
What's the meaning of this, Bill?
Don't tell me you're behind that.
B-Boss, what're you saying?
How could you even suggest that?
You're off the case now, Bill!
Sir! You don't really think
I'm part of this, do you?
Someone is trying to frame you,
and that's a fact.
Then you must let me stay!
Bill...
this isn't a battlefield.
Going alone won't win you any medals.
Understand?
Yes, sir...
Yes.
This is a good time.
Yes, you've seen what happened to the first target.
I've already checked the intel on the next two.
Gotta say, I'm impressed
the Americans have a woman that good.
Yes, I got it.
Heroin sells
for a very high price in Russia.
By the way, I've received
no intel on the fourth target.
I see... He definitely wouldn't expect his own partner to do him in.
Are you sure this is the place?
Yeah, that's what the note says.
Well, I guess we'd better go see.
I wonder how old his daughter is.
Around 10 or so, I guess.
Number 6. This is it.
Good eve—
Huh?
What do you want?
Nothing...
A fake address and a fake Rolex?
I wonder what he was really up to?
It's got to mean something.
That's not good enough, May.
You got us into this, so figure it out.
Now hold on, Larry!
You agreed to do it in the first place—
Yoink.
I was joking!
You're way too hot headed.
Hey, Larry, that's my pop.
Give it back!
Hey, Larry!
May... are you alright?
I'm done listening to you.
W-Well, in any case, it's pointless to keep thinking about this.
I guess we'd better drop it for now... right?
Working hard, gentlemen?
This is for you.
Uh... Well... I don't think I...
Spare us your flimsy excuses, Bill.
Our business with you is over.
If you've got time to bug our house, then you've got time to get us that license you promised!
This investigation isn't over yet, Larry.
Please, I can't do it without your help!
It's no use puffing out your chest now.
You're a fool if you think
we would ever trust you again!
Oh, that's cold.
Fine, you win. We're leaving.
Yes, sir.
Did you have enough time
to get it all set up, May?
Of course!
Piece of cake!
Naturally...
I'm ready here.
Roger.
I should have known...
Tsk.
The real question is what do these two things really mean.
A phone number?
No, not that...
It's not a bank account number,
maybe some sort of code?
Hey, did you notice anything strange
the day you caught Washington?
Huh?
We did it!
Yeah, our rhythm was perfect!
Are you two even listening to me?
Ah! Sorry.
But you might be right.
Maybe there was a clue...
He was browsing the internet!
He was? That's it!
I'll bet this is an internet
address and access code!
Hey... there's something carved in here!
Huh?
Look...
What's this number?
Of course!
Huh?
This is a secret code
for a site on the web!
Watch this.
First, we enter the first letter of each word in the address, plus the phone number.
That's it! That's the picture
Washington was looking at!
Bingo!
Now, we enter the number
on the back of the watch.
Nailed it!
That's incredible, Becky!
Hiding data in a porn site is a clever idea.
But what kind of data is this?
Wait a second.
Let me look at these exchange dates...
And now...
Ah...
All the weapons they're selling
were previously seized by the ATF!
This data could fetch you a fortune, Larry.
However...
We'll need evidence to support it, right?
Exactly.
May... ready to roll?
You bet!
Thanks as always!
H-Hey, wait!
Let me make some printouts first!
You print out there,
and I print out here, Miss Becky.
Bill!
How come you're still here at this hour?
Don't tell me you're still...
No way!
I'm sorting out my reports.
I've been putting them off for too long.
Alright, then...
But remember to
assist Frank in any way you can!
Understood?
Aye aye, sir!
Is this the right place?
The shipment should have arrived here last night.
Hey, let's do this tomorrow.
No way! We're already here!
Sorry, Becky, you'll have to stay here.
Of course.
I wouldn't come even if you asked me to.
Figures.
Pretty serious security for
a yacht club during the off-season.
It's a good thing we left Becky back in the car.
May...
Let's go.
Wow! We struck gold, Larry!
Hold it right there, you two...
The boss told us you'd be dropping by.
You two look pretty hot.
Turn around so we can get
a good look at you.
We'll make sure to play around with you before we kill you.
Hey, hurry it up!
It's her!
Hey, that was cutting it a bit close...
Bill! Not you again!
This sucks!
What the hell are you doing here?
But wasn't I helpful?
How should I know it's not another set-up?
Huh? Hey, now.
I happen to share your opinion
about the trustworthiness of the ATF.
You tapped into our computer,
didn't you?
You snake!
May?!
May!
Larry, get in!
I'll drive!
Hey, Larry! Take me with you! Larry!
Let's move!
May, get the message!
Larry!
Okay, time to bust a move!
That's her! Music... start!
One... Two... Three...
Get off of me!
You little bitch!
L-Larry, don't go crazy!
Tell that to her!
Oh no you don't!
Becky, can you see May?
Hold on... Huh...?!
Yikes!
That punk bitch!
She'll pay for this!
Becky, open the window!
Larry!
This ain't over yet!
Damn you!
One more verse.
Then you're mine!
Well, at least this makes it easier to shoot!
You're dead!
Bitch!
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Zero!
Oh... Shit!
Nice catch...
Really, guys! You're totally insane!
Larry! Look ahead!
May, just what did you do?
Boy, that was quick.
Larry...
We did it again, May!
That said...
Huh?
There's still more work to do before this case is closed.
Finally, it's time to get
back to business as usual.
I'll be going on a date with Ken...
Hey, you two!
You'd better not relax yet.
Radinov's still alive!
Eh?!
Ugh! I guess that sense of foreboding was for real.
We're in trouble, Larry!
This case goes deep.
The next episode of Gunsmith Cats!
Chapter 3: "High Speed Edge."
If Radinov wants a one-on-one duel,
that's what she's going to get!