The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
In October 1944, a landing fleet and convoy led by General MacArthur was gathered in the Leyte Gulf.
The Second Fleet, led by Vice Admiral Takeo Kurita, set sail from Borneo via Brunei Bay with 39 Japanese ships,
including the battleships Yamato, Musashino, Nagato, and the heavy cruiser Atago,
in order to destroy the American fleet.
This operation, called Sho-ichigo, is a desperate operation for the Japanese Navy, which has been cornered.
That is, the MTF of Vice Admiral Ozawa, whose flagship is the aircraft carrier Zuikaku,
advanced to the north of Luzon Island in the Philippines,
and the MTF of the American side was transferred from the south,
heading towards Leyte Gulf through the Surigao Strait.
The main force of the Kurita fleet runs through the San Bernardino Strait
and plunges into Leyte Gulf off the coast of Samar Island.
In addition, the Nishimura fleet was supposed to support the second fleet of Vice Admiral Shima.
Battle of Leyte Gulf (Part Two) (Episode 22)
However, this voyage was would meet with misfortune.
First, on October 23rd, the flagship Atago and the heavy cruiser Maya
were attacked by a submarine and sank at Palawan Suido.
Takao was also wrecked.
The Japanese cruiser is approaching.
Attack, only attack!
Next, on the 24th, the battleship Musashi was sunk by an air raid of 260 American attack aircraft in the Sibuyan Sea.
The heavy cruiser Myoko was also attacked.
Fire!
Stop the main cannon from shooting!
However, despite such a blow, the morale of the remaining 23 Japanese crews did not decline.
That is because it may be possible to bring about a decisive fleet battle
with the American Grand Fleet led by General Halsey.
It was dawn of the following day, the 25th, that they skillfully escaped from the San Bernardino Strait,
which is said to be a difficult place, and went to the coast of Samar Island overlooking Luzon Bay.
The Battle of Leyte Gulf, which was said to be a spectacular battle by the Japanese fleet, begins.
It's a quiet 50 km to Leyte.
It's totally empty.
It may have been effective to show that we turned back at Sibuyan.
What is the Ozawa fleet doing by the way? I haven't heard from them at all.
I will go to the operation room for a while.
Chief. It is a signal from Kumano.
#MISSING LINE
Found an enemy ship at 110 degrees.
Enemy ship?
Found enemy fleet, 125 degrees, distance 37,000.
Hey. There can't be an enemy fleet so close, Isn't it a mistake? Look closely
There it is. Ah
It's an enemy aircraft carrier. Thank you.
It was good then that we come this far.
Chief. We can take them.
If it is a convoy, attack the convoy, if it is a fleet, attack the fleet. Just do it.
Chief. Finally we can fight.
Idiot. Why are you crying?
It was a reasonable response.
They have been training hard for a fleet battle with the enemy,
but they could not bring about a decisive battle between fleets.
Moreover, for those who were ordered to attack the convoy, it was nice to be able to fight with the battleship Yamato.
It was the realization of the Japanese Navy's dream.
Full power, immediate standby.
Line 130. Fire direction 110 degrees.
However, this discovery was not only made by the Japanese side but also on the American side.
We are a shooting gallery for the Japanese.
Alright, launch all aircraft and evacuate.
Raise a smoke screen.
Alright, let me call for help.
Where is the closest fleet?
The 77th, fourth, and second units.
Hello.
Not yet?
No.
I want to fire.
Not yet!
I am firing.
I am firing!
Not yet, Chief.
Has the destroyer closed to range yet?
In Chief Kurita’s head, a tactic was drawn up in which a battleship and a cruiser would first
hit the deck of the enemy aircraft carrier, and then a destroyer would finish it with a torpedo.
He was waiting for the destroyer to be in the perfect position.
I'm shooting.
They're trying to escape. Please let me shoot.
Chief!
Yeah, start bombardment.
Fire!
1 minute and 7 seconds.
Yes!
The world's largest cannon on the battleship Yamato was fired in search of its first prey.
It takes one minute and seven seconds for a one and a half ton shell to reach the target.
Shell landing. First shell hit.
The giant guns fired all at once.
At this rate, its the same as facing a tank in a shirt.
Please come quickly!
Okay, don't panic. I won't abandon you. Don't get excited. Don't be fooled.
Amazing
What are you talking about. They are adjusting their fire.
It's a squall. This is the same as putting up a smoke screen.
If we can't see the target, they can't hit us.
It will stop soon.
Chief Kurita could still attack the US fleet that was within range.
However, the squall became a god of help for the US Navy and prolonged the naval battle.
During this time, the American side changed direction, widened their distance from the Kurita fleet,
and was able to bring their destroyers forward enough.
Its finally our time.
Look for the huge one first.
Ok. But the enemy's cannon Is ridiculously big.
It's too big. Even if it hits, it just penetrates and does not cause an explosion, it is rather easy.
Is it time to go?
Heavy cruiser ahead. Distance 18,000.
Alright, it's an assault!
The enemy cruiser is approaching.
Prepare to fire!
So America does have some brave guys.
Fire!
In this way, the battle off Samar has become turbulent.
Good. Now turn!
Now look for the next one.
Hit!
#MISSING LINE
Where is the next Japanese ship?
The enemy is good. It's a textbook torpedo attack.
That's true.
Torpedo spotted!
Full port!
Torpedo spotted.
Is it a pincer attack?
Proceed as we are.
They seem to be alive.
We can't steer to the right or left.
We have no choice but to go straight until the torpedoes run dry.
It's finally time to leave the battlefield.
Yamato was chased off by a torpedo and left the battlefield.
The aircraft carrier Gambier Bay was sunk along with the destroyer Samuel Roberts and Johnston.
Fanshaw Bay and Kalinin Bay and the few remaining ships were shot at but escaped.
Major General Sprague, who had been seeking help from the beginning, went higher up the command chain
and asked his Lieutenant General Kinkaid, who defended the Philippines, for help.
But Kinkaid was far from the battle.
While relieved to annihilate the Nishimura fleet,
an escort carrier in the bay was suddenly attacked by a Japanese fighter.
They are the Kamikaze corps of the Asahi and Kikusui corps that launched from Davao base that day.
The attack of the Kamikaze corps paralyzed Vice Admiral Kinkaid preventing him from going to Sprague's aid.
He asked Admiral Halsey to help the Sprague fleet.
General Halsey was far from the battle.
When Halsey, who said the carrier fleet was their main objective, was informed of the discovery of the Ozawa fleet,
he ignored the request for help from Vice Admiral Kinkaid and went north in search of the Ozawa MTF.
Thus, the Ozawa fleet, acting as a decoy, was brilliantly successful in distracting Halsey.
One light aircraft carrier on fire.
Sir, Halsey. I received another radio message.
Kinkaid's whining?
That is not the case. This is a message from General Nimitz in Guam.
Why from Nimitz? Please read it.
WHERE IS RPT WHERE IS TASK FORCE THIRTY FOUR RR
I'm fighting here.
THE WORLD WONDERS
What? The world wonders?
What is that saying? Does he think I'm doing a hula dance?
This bastard!
He wants you to help him.
However, Nimitz does not speak out from the sidelines.
What do you want to do?
Then, I would like to go help him a little.
What a shame. I was looking forward to seeing what kind of hand Ozawa would play this time.
Then, leaving the rest to General Mitscher, he went south with the fleet.
Chief. It's almost as planned.
Mr. Ugaki, I finally did it.
Yes. Finally Yamato's cannon was useful.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What was the result of the battle?
Sunk three or four ships, including the USS Enterprise, two cruisers, and one or two other aircraft carriers.
#MISSING LINE
After that, we must rush to Leyte Gulf before the enemy rescue team comes.
No, I'm actually thinking about that, but...
Thinking?
I think this is fine. I was allowed to do a decisive fleet battle that I had been waiting for. And I won.
Certainly this will change the result of the war.
If you rush into Leyte as is, their rescue fleet will come.
With that enemy as the last threat, our fleet may be wiped out.
As you say, we may be wiped out, but they have ordered us to enter Leyte Gulf.
I know that.
Is it okay to sink the entire Japanese fleet here or preserve what we can and protect Japan for as long as possible?
I'm the opposite. Isn't it just one more another push?
There is no information to go on.
What's going on with Ozawa?
Even though the Nishimura fleet was wiped out, there are no detailed reports on the enemy.
Where are the enemies?
What are our allies doing?
Certainly no information was gathered.
No. What's happening with the Ozawa fleet?
I think this is a fake message, it is from the enemy.
Halsey's plan text radio message: "I will go to the rescue in two hours."
Will they go to the rescue in two hours?
Yes. It is a tactic that they often use. We also do it.
We are in trouble.
At that time, they did not know that the Ozawa fleet lured Halsey and had played the role of decoy so well,
nor did they know that the Kamikaze corp's attack was successful.
It is better to rush in as we are.
That is why this strategy is meaningful.
But.
I don't think it's time for me.
Do we have any more information.
There is nothing more.
Is that so? There is nothing after all?
Good. Let's come about.
Yes.
Full starboard!
Captain. What are you doing? The enemy is over there.
Thus, before entering Leyte Gulf, the Kurita fleet suddenly turned around and pulled out.
The Japanese fleet is moving north and pulling out.
That's stupid.
It was rather the Combined Fleet's General Headquarters in Hiyoshidai that was surprised at their reversal
ahead of their entry into Leyte Gulf.
Immediately after receiving the news of the course change by the Kurita fleet, an encouraging radio message was sent.
Considering the damage of each fleet and their sailors, I think the enemy is in a more difficult situation than us.
From now on, you should proceed to the operation point regardless of sacrifice.
Radio message from the Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet.
However, there was no fleet that responded to this encouragement.
It is said that Chief Kurita’s decision to reverse in front of the enemy is a mystery
that will remain forever in the history of naval warfare.
but at that time, Lieutenant General Kurita’s mind was preoccupied with the idea of decisive fleet battle
and the possible results of that battle.
Lack of fuel, lack of information on enemies and allies, etc.
This teaches us that important decisions always require information,
and how the right information is gathered is a key factor in making a decision,
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS LINE 1
#CREDITS LINE 2
#CREDITS LINE 3
#CREDITS LINE 4
#CREDITS LINE 5
#CREDITS LINE 6
#CREDITS LINE 7
#CREDITS LINE 8
#CREDITS LINE 9
Operation Iwo Jima (Episode 23)
#CREDITS LINE 10
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2