The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
In April 1943, with the Americans having captured Guadalcanal,
the Japanese were fiercely defending against them advancing along the Solomon Islands.
lsoroku Yamamoto, Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet,
flew from the base on Truck Island to Rabaul on the front line for a front-line inspection.
Attention.
Salute.
You see. It's a Japanese radio message.
The Combat Intelligence Department, which belongs to the United States Pacific Fleet Command in Hawaii,
is located in a top secret basement that can only be used by the cryptanalysis team.
All the radio messages of the Japanese Navy received from various parts of the South Pacific are collected here,
and this electric cryptanalyzer was devised and developed by Major Thomas Dyer,
a leading expert in cryptographic analysis in the US.
It had been enhanced to the point where it could almost decipher the Japanese Navy's encrypted messages.
Hey, take a look.
What is this? It's not like a Japanese sentence.
I wonder if the machine broke.
Look at this.
I don't know. Call Major Dier right away. It's urgent.
Operation Vengeance (Episode 18)
Major Dier.
It is not a mechanical failure. The code of the Japanese Navy has changed.
Has it changed completely?
I don't know.
If so, this machine is no longer useful.
We have to make a new decipherer. How many months will that take?
It takes half a year.
However, cryptography does not always change completely.
Anyways, break this code.
Yes
Even if you stay up all night, you must break this code.
How much can the Navy do if it comes to war with the United States and Britain?
I am a soldier. If I am told to do it, let's do it.
For half a year or a year, we can plan as much as I want.
However, we cannot guarantee it after that.
Was it a dream?
That year is over.
Who is it?
I am sorry.
I woke up after dreaming. I want to go to the beach, is that okay?
Yes. I will be with you.
Chief, this one.
No,
this feels better.
I don't think it's the sea where the war is going on.
Have you been working in Rabaul all the time?
No. I was in Bougainville three months ago.
Oh. It's the front line.
How was it, over there?
Yes. The Bougainville Reserves are unfortunately poor.
Is Rabaul any good?
Yes
Thanks to being in Rabaul, I can see the Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet in this way.
Just relax.
Yes
Are you glad I come to Rabaul so much?
Yes. The Chief is the guardian deity of the Imperial Japanese Navy.
You are a god.
You exaggerate. I also drink alcohol and like gambling. Is there such a god?
That's why you're God. You are right next to us.
I feel sorry for the people in Bougainville because they can't worship God directly.
Bougainville.
How do you feel about carrying God?
I will have to pay for it. I'm happy.
I understand.
I solved it.
We don't have to stay up all night anymore.
The code was broken.
The Japanese Navy did not change the code.
They just changed the random number table a little.
All we have to do is tell that to the machine.
Then, that decryption machine can be used?
Of course.
I came to Rabaul. I have to go to Bougainville.
Bougainville is 500kms from here. It's dangerous.
The air superiority of this area is in our hands so far. It's okay.
However, the Japanese do not have complete air superiority.
I don't know when the enemy planes will appear.
Excuse me, but I think that the Commander-in-Chief should never leave the safe area.
When the Chief does that, then that will be when the Imperial Japanese Navy is destroyed.
This theory is exactly what you guys say.
But I want to go.
Yamamoto came all the way to Rabaul, but was it useful?
I can only make the soldiers guarding small islands around the Pacific think, "Hey, Yamamoto is here, lets do it well."
Yamamoto shows his face here, then the front line for the Japanese forces isn't so terrifying. I want them to think so.
Chief. I understand that.
Come out, come out.
Oh my goodness!
It's big news!
Connect to Lieutenant Colonel Layton. It's urgent.
Lieutenant Colonel Layton enter.
Could Yamamoto make such a stupid mistake?
Even if it’s a trap, it’s too good.
Just listen as you are.
Who is the one who wrote such a message?
Is there anyone who can describe the actions of the Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet in such detail?
It's like sending an invitation to the enemy,
Let the Chief know that I have flown from Bougainville.
Chief. Bougainville is absolutely okay as long as it is defended by me.
Please retrain from visiting.
It doesn't mean that I'll show up because I can't leave it to you
I understand, but why did you lay out that detailed schedule of the Chief's inspection?
What it this message is intercepted by the US?
Our code may have been broken, or they may not have been able to.
It is usually undecipherable.
I cannot lose great joy in the unlikely event.
Sir, can you believe this Japanese message?
This is the responsibility of Admiral Nimitz, Commander-in-Chief of the United States Pacific Fleet.
Come in.
This is a top secret message from Dutch Harbor in Alaska.
Let's read it.
On April 18th, Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet Yamamoto will visit the island on the front line.
6am, this must be Rabaul’s Japanese time.
Depart Rabaul with six escort aircraft Zero fighters. 8am. Arrive at Bougainville.
It matches exactly with the message from the Japanese from Hawaii.
We also caught this encrypted message in Alaska.
What was their intention in sending such a strong radio wave?
Is it a trap?
No, it's the result of confidence that the US can't break their code.
We were given very difficult homework.
You already have the data that I have handed out. Ask questions.
There are few escort planes for Mr. Yamamoto, but there are also Zero fighters in Bougainville.
We only have P-38s. No matter how close we are to Yamamoto, we can't fly to Bougainville.
Let me answer. Bougainville certainly has Zero fighters, So hit Mr. Yamamoto before he lands on Bougainville.
Major Mitchell, it's time to explain your plan.
If I can solve this homework, I will be the commander.
So here is my answer.
The target is Bougainville, about 600kms from our base.
The first thing is how to fly so that the enemy does not see us coming.
So, we fly at a low altitude just above the sea.
If Yamamoto, our key objective, does not fly as planned,
wouldn't it be possible to pass each other in the vast Pacific Ocean?
That's right. That is the most difficult point.
The distance from here to Bougainville is 600kms.
500kms from Rabaul, where Mr. Yamamoto is, to Bougainville.
There is a difference of 100kms.
There is only one place in the South Pacific where the two lines meet most effectively.
How to find that one point.
What is your answer?
There is only one.
Start one hour before Mr. Yamamoto and ambush him on the way.
Yamamoto is a man who always keeps his promises.
Does he really keep your promises? The attack on Pearl Harbor was a surprise.
No, that was a strategy to attack after the declaration of war.
At that time, the people at the Japanese embassy In Washington made a mistake and the time was off.
Yamamoto struck Pearl Harbor at the promised time without knowing war had not been declared.
Make a note of the final decision.
First proceed 133kms, 265 degrees directional. Speed 360kms, flight time 55 minutes, and so on.
Second, 144kms, 240 degrees orientation, 27 minutes.
Third, 200kms, 305 degrees orientation, 38 minutes.
If all goes well, we will definitely hit the enemy before 8 o'clock. That's all.
It's a wonderful answer to your homework, but Layton,
no country killed an enemy Commander-In-Chief like this during World-War I.
Mr. President, Yamamoto is was the planner for the undeclared attack on Pearl Harbor.
Don't worry. This is fair.
Please make a decision.
There are only two days left.
However, Yamamoto is a regrettable man to bury.
Chief. I will take the first plane.
Don't forget to have the commander on the first plane. I am the commander today.
Yeah...
The first plane has Chief Yamamoto, Major General Takada, and Deputy Secretary Fukusaki.
Staff Officer Ugaki and Aviation Staff Officer Muroi are on board the second aircraft.
The Japanese forces called this Mitsubishi G4 "Hamaki(sigar)",
and the US forces called it "Betty" or "Writer".
The equipment was made extremely light to extend its cruising range,
which meant that it was flammable when shot.
We lost one more. 16 aircraft left.
Whatever. If the enemy Yamato has a soul, there is also a Yankee soul here.
Even so, I should meet Gentleman Yamamoto soon.
Chief. 10 minutes before landing.
Oh. Really.
Then Chief. It's time to prepare for landing,
Are you ready?
Should I laugh when I meet the soldiers for the first time?
Or should I be dignified?
I wonder if I came a little too early.
That's it I'll use the radio.
Enemy plane found. 11 o'clock direction. Altitude 2000.
Send to all aircraft. Discovered Betty. Drop the spare tank.
It enemy aircraft.
Don't panic, the base is close.
It is an enemy aircraft!
Damn.
Protect the Chief.
Which one is Yamamoto on? Anyway, I can shoot both.
It's the soul of Pearl Harbor.
Are you okay?
Recover!
Betty
I did it!
Chief!
Chief, please hold on firmly.
Don't lose sight of the Chief's plane. It was attacked.
This is Mitchell. Message to all aircraft. Both Bettys fell.
We have served our purpose. Run away if you want a medal.
If I were on the first plane.
When a man who tried to avoid the war ironically has to take command of the battle, he fights like a lion.
He probably knew his destiny.
lsoroku Yamamoto's death is by no means a careless death. By dying, he believed in those who followed him.
This sad act taught us that in order to win the battle, we must know our enemies well.
Even today, the more accurate information you have, the better you can make the decisions to win.
The death of Isoroku Yamamoto eventually led to the setting sun of the Japanese Empire.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS 1
#CREDITS 2
#CREDITS 3
#CREDITS 4
#CREDITS 5
#CREDITS 6
#CREDITS 7
Battle of Tassafaronga (Episode 19)
#CREDITS 8
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2