The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
On March 16th, 1945, the fall of Iwo Jima created a foothold for the invasion of mainland Japan.
In order to further strengthen their invasion plan,
the Commander-in-Chief of the United States Fifth Fleet, General Spruance, was put in charge of this operation.
An order to capture Okinawa was issued.
Under his command was Lieutenant General Mitscher's high-speed aircraft carrier unit,
and a fleet led by a major general with 10 battleships, 9 heavy cruisers, and 23 destroyers.
In addition, under his command is a large unit of 1,317 ships, 1,727 carrier-based aircraft,
and 452,000 personnel, including a fleet led by Rawlings a Vice Admiral of the Royal Navy.
In contrast, the Japanese Combined Fleet Command was only the battleship Yamato, a few light cruisers,
and 10 destroyers.
That was all that remained of the Japanese Navy's proud combined fleet since Marshal Togo.
The End of the Coalition Fleet (Episode 24)
Meanwhile, the US began landings on Okinawa on April 1st, at 4:06 a.m.,
under the command of Vice Admiral Buckner of the 10th Army.
Hey it’s ridiculously quiet. Isn't there a Japanese army?
It's strange. I thought that they would fight on the beaches since the Japanese army is so good at that.
The Commander-in-Chief of the garrison, Lieutenant General Ushijima, was determined to carry out a defense in depth.
So he was waiting for the US military to move southward.
However, the Combined Fleet Command, which was angry with this passive approach,
issued a dispatch order to the second fleet under Yamato, who had been waiting off the coast of Mitajiri.
On April 6th, a strategy meeting for this sortie order was held on the Yamato.
Especially on this day, Chief of Staff Soka and Chief of Staff Mikami
from the Combined Fleet Command attended for encouragement.
As the Secretary has just explained, we will load enough fuel to go one way,
but I would like you to look at the documents you have regarding this strategy.
I have a question before starting the strategy meeting.
Please, Staff Officer Yamamoto
Thank you.
I have a question from the Combined Fleet Command today,
so I would like to ask you about what command intends to do.
Let's listen.
Yamamoto.
It's OK.
Of course, we are not dissatisfied with the special attack order itself.
However, the purpose of this order is unclear.
The order says to destroy enemy ships around Okinawa.
That is the purpose.
However, can you achieve that purpose?
It will be eight days to one week after the enemy landed.
Their air base will have been improved and the enemy air corps readied.
The US military will have a considerable numerical advantage.
We also estimate there to be 10 aircraft carriers nearby.
While the enemy is waiting, we are setting our time and course and rushing into their trap.
That's right.
Eight days is too little to be a decoy, We must attract the enemies here to squeeze the forces on land.
Only we will drown in this special attack, not headquarters.
That is not the case.
Is this just an idea from headquarters?
What?
I understand well. Maybe that's right
There was considerable disagreement within the Combined Fleet Command
about how Ito and Yamato are to be used now.
Fuel for only one way, no support aircraft.
Even if it is boasted as an unsinkable battleship this is still a messy strategy.
However, while understanding that, I want you to understand the circumstances
under which such a strategy must be used.
Would you like to have a drink after such a long time?
Okinawa is the biggest game. Losing Okinawa now is the same as deciding Japan's fate.
We can't win unless 100 million sacrifice themselves in a suicidal attack.
There will be various theories,
but now, we are just the forerunners of this 100 million suicidal attack.
The Commander-in-Chief of the combined Fleet, Toyoda, asked me to let Yamato's flowers bloom.
Do you want the flowers to bloom
Let's do it.
What?
If you are alive, do you go to eat Togakushi soba again?
I have to go.
Yes.
Sir.
Let me in.
Yes, please.
If you need something, I could visit from here.
Its been cleaned up. It has a nice face.
I feel at ease.
Have you smoked at all these last few days?
After all, I smoke about 100 a day.
So the ration alone is not enough.
It's an enemy's one.
Thank you.
Mr. Yamamoto,
was my decision to undertake this special attack wrong?
No,
you don't need to worry about that.
I heard that your family also volunteered for the kamikaze unit.
That's night.
But there is another purpose behind this.
Of course, as you say, we may be sunk on the way. But, I want to go to the coast of Okinawa and sink ourselves there.
In other words, I want to make us a floating battery and fire the world's largest 46 cm cannons again.
I also thought about this.
Let's get there somehow.
#MISSING LINE
Yes
The Second Fleet set out with a secret decision in response to HQ's idea.
Befitting a sortie that would remain in the records for a long time, Chief Ito's instruction was signaled.
God's body, now is the time to move.
The prosperity of the empire depends on this battle.
Struggle with each other, destroy all your enemies, and show your true potential as kamikaze.
By the time he passed the Bungo Channel, Yamato had already been spotted by an enemy submarine,
and there was something that reminded him of the difficulties ahead.
Around that time, General Spruance, Commander-in-Chief of the Okinawa Landing Corps,
was attacked by 400 Japanese Special Attack Units that took off from Kanoya and other bases.
He was overwhelmed by his obligations and command, and had a late dinner.
I'm sorry to interrupt you during your meal.
Davis, what do you want with me?
I have just finished.
We had a terrible day. Who knew there were such airplanes still in Japan.
I was also surprised.
The Kamikaze planes are a gift of Tokyo Rose.
At that time, the damage caused by the special attack aircraft was 3 destroyers, 1 LST,
and 2 ammunition ships sunk.
Along with the destruction of the light aircraft carrier San Jacinto, 15 destroyers, and 4 minesweepers.
Due to the turmoil, battleship North Carolina, light cruiser Burnett, two transport ships, and
one LST were damaged by friendly fire.
One transport ship was also damaged in a collision.
There is news that will make you happy.
What is it?
Your lover will make an appearance.
Lover?
Yamato ts finally coming out.
This is a report from the submarine Threadfin.
I see. Now that's a lover. How do I welcome her?
Let's go to the operation room.
Is this the only report on the Japanese fleet?
Yes, sir.
Then, there are two facts that can be drawn from this report.
One is when Yamato comes out.
The other is that the enemy forces are weak with just about 10 ships.
Yes, sir.
Then, Davis.
We will have one choice and one question.
In other words, how do we defeat Yamato?
The other question is where will Yamato go?
I understand the question of where Yamato will go, but how will we defeat it?
Like Musashi and Prince of Wales, by flooding them with aircraft or with a decisive fleet battle.
Naval battle?
According to this information, the enemy is naked with no air cover.
However, Yamato has the largest cannons in the world when it comes to naval battles.
But I will do that.
Since the Prince of Wales was sunk by airplane, a decisive fleet battle without airplanes is unthinkable.
Nevertheless, Spruance decided to fight with the old-fashioned surface fleet.
Why make that decision?
General Spruance's decision to engage in a naval battle as a way to meet Yamato was communicated to
Major General of the Attack Support Unit and Lieutenant General Mitscher of the carrier fleet.
That's stupid. The main force of the Navy is now the aircraft carrier unit.
Right?
Even so, since we are going to fight a naval battle, should the air force be responsible for only a light jab?
He has gotten too old.
Yes, sir.
The honor of defeating Yamato, the embodiment of the Japanese Navy, is naturally decided to be
the aircraft carrier unit, which is representative of the US Navy, and our 58 MTF.
Is there any other way?
Admiral, General Spruance is allowing us to make a jab.
Even if it is not an uppercut, if you do it quickly, you can bring down the opponent with just a jab.
You are right.
Alright, I understand. I will tell him.
From the Major General, it seems that everyone is celebrating and going up a lot.
They thanked you very much.
Yes, I was happy, it’s only natural.
Battleships should fight battleships.
No matter how much you support the landing party, if you hit only on land, our skills will dull.
38 years ago, when I graduated from the Annapolis Naval Academy and was in Japan on a diplomatic trip,
I was with Admiral Togo.
Not just me, we were all Navy soldiers, they were longing to meet him.
While there we learned Togo's strategy.
I saw Japanese sumo.
The naked fighters?
Yes. It is said that defeating the senior who taught them is to "Return the favor".
And the senior congratulates the juniors who beat them.
Is there such a thing?
I want to do this now. I want to give back to the respectable Japanese fleets raised by Togo.
Yamato was proceeding on a peaceful voyage without knowing that General Spruance
was waiting to meet him based on such a decision.
The clouds are thick today.
If they keep going like this, it will be much harder for the enemy to attack.
Enemy aircraft spotted!
Anti-aircraft combat, man your stations!
Enemy spotted. 31 degrees 22 minutes north latitude 129 degrees 14 minutes east longitude.
Yamato-class battleship one or two, 8 destroyers, course 300, speed 12 knots.
This is not a full-scale air raid.
Where does Yamato go if their course is 300?
Its not Okinawa.
Is it Sasebo?
Don't let it escape.
Can you catch up?
We can catch up with our airplanes, but our fleet can't.
Is it impossible?
Sir.
It's from Mr. Mitscher.
#MISSING LINE
Hello, Mark.
Hello, Ray.
Do you wanna fight a naval battle after all?
Mark, of course.
Is that so? The enemy seems to be headed in the direction of Sasebo, can you catch up?
Are we not able to catch up?
That's right.
At this time, Spruance was confused. But he has to make a decision.
If I miss my chance now, will I be able to meet Yamato again?
But even so, I don't want Yamato to be the prey of airplanes.
Hello, Hello, Ray, are you listening?
I want to sink the biggest ship in the world
Alright, then you can do it.
OK
Major General?
All right. Leave it as it is.
No matter how strong the mark is, it is impossible in today's weather.
The clouds are low and the visibility is 5 or 6 miles. It's impossible to fly. They can't attack.
The attacks of the 58th, first, 58th, third, fourth, and the MTF will start immediately.
It is 9:40 a.m. now.
If you launch at 10 o'clock, you will be in time for the enemy's lunch.
You guys will be uninvited guests. Then, don't go home until Yamato sinks.
I say it again. don't come home until Yamato sinks.
31 knots, Berg and 280 aircraft took off.
As General Spruance said, the attack wasn't easy.
It was like swimming in a stew.
Target spotted!
A large formation of enemies is approaching!
Man your stations!
335 degrees!
Next target, 250, 85 degrees!
Fire!
After all, I couldn't become a floating battery in Okinawa.
It seems that our decision was not kept secret.
You haven't smoked at all.
I refused to do so until we became floating battery.
Did you keep your decision secret?
April 7th, 2:23 p.m. 30 degrees 20 minutes north latitude, 128 degrees 4 minutes east longitude.
Yamato sank in the East China Sea, 200 nautical miles north of Lokunoshima, Kyushu, and 480 meters down.
Thus, the Japanese Navy Combined Fleet,
which boasted a brilliant tradition since Marshal Togo, has reached its decisive end here.
The Japanese Navy's dominance was swallowed up in the vortex of history.
At the same time, we can learn how terrifying a blind decision is,
and from the American side that there must be bold execution after the decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS LINE 1
#CREDITS LINE 2
#CREDITS LINE 3
#CREDITS LINE 4
#CREDITS LINE 5
#CREDITS LINE 6
#CREDITS LINE 7
#CREDITS LINE 8
Final Decision (Episode 25)
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2