The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Nakajima Ki-27 fighter.
This fighter boasted agile maneuverability, but its short range was its biggest drawback.
Therefore, since 1939, air operations personnel of the Imperial Headquarters Army have been
desperate for improvements to aircraft in preparation for modern warfare.
After many improvements and experiments,
a new naval aircraft with the same engine as the Zero-type fighter was born.
Two 12.7mm machine guns. A maximum speed of 515km/h and its biggest defect, its cruising range,
was solved by installing a falling auxiliary fuel tank under its wing.
This is the falcon fighter that the Japanese Army is proud to show the world.
Major Takeo Kato, the captain of the 64th Squadron, took the initiative in launching an intense training flight
in order to demonstrate the high performance of this falcon.
Kato's Falcon Squadron (Kato Hayabusa Sentotai) Episode 14
In December 1941, the 64th Squadron under the command of Major Kato first supported
a large fleet of landing parties on the Malay Peninsula under the command of Lieutenant General Tomoyuki Yamashita,
and flew from Phu Quoc Island In Indochina to Nakhon, Thailand.
After completing the mission, Kato Squadron proceeded further to Kota Bharau, Malaysia.
The advance was a divine work.
Our landing party continued its blitz operation and advanced to the Peran River on the Malay Peninsula.
However, if the bridge is destroyed by the enemy, the blitz to Singapore,
which is the purpose of the Malay Peninsula operation, will be delayed by three months.
Our Hayabusa Squadron will be on standby at the Allorster Base to prevent its sabotage.
If the enemy destroys the bridge, it will be by enemy planes from Kuala Lumpur.
However, my falcon squadron can't wait for the enemy to come out.
Go out first and crush the enemies in Kuala Lumpur.
This voluntary assignment.
Do you understand?
Yes
Hey, I'll take a picture
Sure!
♪ Kato Hayabusa Fighter Wing
The engine roars like thunder
The falcon conquers the edge of the clouds
The wings shining like the Hinomaru
The chest upon which draws the image of a red eagle,
It is the mark of our fighter.
Kuala Lumpur
Damn. Alright.
#Missing Line
I'll take you to hell with me.
Goodbye, Captain.
The Kuala Lumpur attack was a voluntary order by Major Kato,
but the action received a congratulatory telegram from the Southern Expeditionary Army's General Commander
as a flexible measure based on a calm judgment of the situation.
Hey, Tadayama, this photo I took became your last one.
Please wait.
I can't let you die alone.
On January 9th, the 64th Hayabusa Squadron, commanded by Major Kato, went further south and was based in Ipoh.
Sorties are made from this base to Singapore every day.
He succeeded in bombing Singapore Airlines with his allies and heavy bombers,
but he could not find a fight with the Hawker Hurricanes.
There was no decisive battle for Hayabusa.
On January 29th, Major Kato was about to take off to support the Singapore bombers
with several planes from Kota Bharu.
Is it still not fixed?
No. It needs a little more time.
I can't wait. I'll go ahead Omori.
You will catch up with us later.
Yes. I'm sure.
However, they couldn't find any friendly bombers to support, so they had to go home.
I'm late.
I have to catch up with the captain soon.
Ah. It's the bombing corps.
Where are the captains who should be supporting them?
Damn. If this happens, I'll deal with you all at once.
The captain is in a bad mood and does not speak.
Then, after all. He couldn't support them.
He doesn't even eat dinner.
It's Omori!
I engaged with one fighter.
So, how about the bombers on our side?
Two planes.
They were killed.
Please forgive me.
It's a lifelong mistake.
Captain, an emergency telegram came from the bombing squad that went to Singapore today.
Read it.
In the telegram, Captain Omori shot down two Hurricanes with one aircraft.
They thanked him for his brave support,
and it was noted that two of his friendly bombers were crash landed and all were safe.
Is that so? Are they all safe?
It was good.
Because of the success of the Japanese aviation unit, including the Kato Hayabusa combat corps,
the systematic challenges presented by the British army have almost disappeared.
And the Malay Peninsula capture unit under the command of Lieutenant General Tomoyuki Yamashita
approached Singapore one step further.
However, in the daily battles, the Kato Hayabusa fighting corps also suffered considerable casualties.
Around that time, the first parachute unit of the Japanese Army planned to occupy the oil fields of Palembang intact.
On February 10th, Major Kato rushed to the Cruz base alone. He visited the 3rd Squadron Commander.
Enemy troops are concentrated in Singapore.
Palembang should be captured before the fall of Singapore.
According to aerial photography, the enemy air base in Palembang is hidden in the jungle,
and has about 100 large and small aircraft gathered together.
In order to safely lower the parachute unit, you should first secure air superiority.
Please give that mission to my squad.
Your corps has lost a lot of strength in battle so far.
Support is almost impossible with its current strength.
Certainly some of the strength has been lost.
But,
its fighting spirit is enough.
I'm sure we will succeed.
Please let me do it.
Even if I say no, you won't listen.
Yes
Thus, the Kato Hayabusa Combat Team went further south in preparation for the Palembang Air Battle,
and made Kahan its forward base.
Our unit cooperates with the light bombing unit of the 3rd Flight Unit. Destroy the enemy planes in Palembang.
No matter what happens, you have to succeed.
For that purpose, I would like each person to do their best,
not to take credit for themselves, but to exert the power of the entire unit.
First, a raid on the British base in Palembang,
and on February 4th, the Hayabusa combat corps sortie to support the paratrooper units.
Their deadly success supported the successful occupation of Palembang.
The Hayabusa fighting corps had no time to breathe.
After Palembang, they moved to Chiang Mai, Thailand. Launching daily attacks on the Burmese Achab base.
They are tired
Let's all go.
I am ordering this unit to immediately hit and destroy the remaining enemies.
What? Are we still doing more?
The greatest purpose of combatants is to always be prepared to sortie, day or night.
Damn, even if I hit it, it will come out soon.
Around that time, Major Kato was given many letters of appreciation for his remarkable achievements
and was promoted to Lieutenant Colonel.
On May 21st, he pursued a British bomber over Chittagong, but lost sight of it.
Ah. Shimizu!
Shimizu, I'll definitely look for you. Wait for me.
Tomorrow afternoon, we will move to Tonggu base.
By then, be sure to find Lieutenant Shimizu.
Yes. Let the locals do their best to find him.
I'll leave it to you then.
Near noon on the 22nd, the Hayabusa Combat Team is ready to move to Longgu Base to destroy the Allied Air Forces.
They were waiting for Captain Kato's sortie order.
Captain. It's time to leave.
Let's wait a little longer.
The captain is late.
It's been two hours since the scheduled time.
Shimizu, please come back safely.
Captain. It's already time.
Yeah.
Captain
It's Shimizu! Shimizu is back!
It's an enemy plane
Damn!
Start me up!
Captain!
Damn, Shimizu's revenge.
#Missing Line
Captain!
Finally, the 64th Commander of the Hayabusa Combat Team, Lieutenant Colonel Takeo Kato,
has become a person who will never return, and went to the deep under the seabed of the Bay of Bengal.
May 22, 2:30 pm.
However, Lieutenant Colonel Kato was alive.
His indomitable Fighting spirit lived on in the hearts of his men.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS 1
#CREDITS 2
#CREDITS 3
#CREDITS 4
#CREDITS 5
#CREDITS 6
Rabaul Air Corps (Episode 15)
#CREDITS 7
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
pittman789