The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
In July 1944, due to the devastating defeat at the Battle of the Philippine Sea
and the annihilation of the Saipan garrison,
command of the sea in the western Pacific was completely transferred to the US military.
Then, in September of that year,
the Seventh Fleet, commanded by Commander-in-Chief MacArthur, rallied in Leyte Gulf, south of Luzon.
In order to meet this threat, the Japanese Combined Fleet launched Operation sho-ichigo.
All the remaining troops were gathered and started to advance into the Leyte area.
It was dawn on October 18th, 1944.
Japan's offense and defense depends on this battle.
However, there are more than 700 enemy ships that have attacked Leyte,
and their planes number 1000 at least.
On the other hand, the number of airplanes that can be dispatched by our 1st Air Force is less than 100.
Kurita fleet and Nishimura fleet are scheduled to advance toward Leyte from Brunei Bay, Borneo.
There are no escort planes for the Ozawa fleet,
which advances as a decoy over the northeastern sea of Manila from the aqueduct.
We are naked here.
In this emergency, the only operation of the 1st Air Fleet is to
hit each ship with a zero-type fighter loaded with a 250 kg bomb and make a desperate ramming attack.
I would like to hear your opinion on this.
I can't agree.
What is your reason?
The squad attempting to capture Lushun Port in the Russo-Japanese War was ordered to return by boat,
and the midget submarines in the attack on Pearl Harbor in Hawaii
should have returned if the surprise attack was successful.
That is why both Marshal Togo and Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto were allowed.
Chief, although there are records for forlorn hope squads in the history of war, there is no precedent for a suicide squad.
No matter how difficult the battlefield,
such a desperate corps that rams ships with both humans and bombs
will leave a stain on the 70-year tradition of the Japanese Navy.
As you say. This is an evil way that ignores the rules of war.
Chief.
There is no chance of winning this battle anymore. At the very least, we must inflict as much damage as possible,
defeating the enemy's fighting spirit, and creating an opportunity to end the war.
If we do not stop here,
if we do not end the war, our homeland, Japan, will be ash and the Japanese people will perish.
This is no longer a strategy.
It is a prayer of the people who long for peace. It's a long-cherished wish.
I will order this even if they curse me 100 years from now.
Because I believe that there is no other way to save Japan.
Chief, We will follow your orders.
Birth of The Kamikaze Unit (Episode 17)
Fighter crews, gather in the first room.
Attention!
The fighter corps is ready.
We have been ordered to organize a special attack corps.
A special attack is a desperate and deadly tactic in which a 250 kg bomb
is loaded into a zero-fighter and rams an enemy ship.
I will give you this paper now, so if you apply, write your name, and if you do not apply, leave it blank.
Put each in an envelope and have the officer bring them directly to me.
This will go to the non-commissioned officer then the senior non-commissioned officer.
No one knows except me if you're going to apply or not.
So if you can't apply for health reasons, family reasons, or any other reason, you will never have to worry about this.
Please submit it after careful consideration.
As a reminder, this attack will begin tomorrow.
Hey, what did you do?
That's right. Once I die, I won't die anymore. The earlier death won't make others take care.
Because a fool cannot be cured unless he dies. Should I go powerfully at once?
#MISSING TEXT
Captain Seki. Can I enter? This is Lieutenant Kuno.
Yes.
I brought a special one.
Would you like to have a drink?
Hmm, It's gorgeous. Where did you get this?
It is a gift from a fellow student from Singapore.
I'll get it.
Pray for each ether's luck.
It's finally time to come clean.
Captain Seki.
Can I say my true feelings?
Hmm, yes.
I do not agree with these ramming attacks.
What?
I think that Chief Onishi was thinking that these ramming attacks were to be done only once,
but once this tactic is implemented, It will not stop, and the Naval Air Corps as a result will suffer.
I am afraid that even if it is a volunteer system at the start, it will eventually become mandatory.
There is a good reason for you. But how do we stop it?
No, is there a way to regain the initiative in this fight, even if the ramming attacks are stopped now?
You really will miss your life.
Captain Seki
I didn't want to die either, until just about 20 minutes ago.
But now I have decided.
Lieutenant Kuno is volunteering for the special attack corps.
Why did you bring it?
It was because I made up my mind that I could say my true intentions.
This guy, you made me tell my true feeling as well.
How is it? How many applicants have gathered?
All are volunteers.
♪ Wakawashi no uta
♪ The seven button emblems of the passionate naval preparatory flight trainees
♪ are cherry blossoms and anchors
♪ Today we're flying above Xiapu...
Captain Seki, I'm here.
Come in.
Have a seat.
I will have one.
By the way, this is the first formation of the special attack corps,
but it is also the very time we have made a unit like this,
and it is difficult to select a commander.
I consulted with the staff in various ways.
How about you, can you accept it?
Please let me do it.
Is that so? You accept it?
At first, I thought that a person from a military academy should take command.
It's a matter of commanding the entire army. I'll leave it to you.
At 5 pm on October 20th, four of the special attack units formed at the Mabalacat base in the Philippines
and were escorted by four fighter aircraft
and returned to the base from Manila by Major Nakajima, the 201st flight commander.
He led the move to Cebu base.
In view of the current situation,
a ramming corps will be formed with 26 carrier-capable fighter aircraft under the command of the 201 Air Squadron.
They will be called the Kamikaze Special Attack Corps.
This attack corps is divided into four corps: Shikishima corps, Yamato corps, Asahi corps,
and Yamazakura corps, and the commander is the Navy Captain, Yukio Seki.
The mission of this attack corps is to destroy the enemy task force.
We hope that favorable results will come out before we have to attack units in Leyte gulf.
The Yamato Corps will move to Cebu Base on October 20th, and will carry out an attack from Cebu Base.
It's great.
I wonder if Lieutenant Kuno was from a music school.
No, I just imitated what my sister was learning.
I'm sorry.
You don't need to apologize.
Music and pilot suitability has been proven in medicine to have an important link.
It wouldn't be strange if a fighter pilot was also a piano master.
Sir, I have something to ask.
What is it Ensign Uemura?
Will I not be excluded from the special attack corps?
What do you mean?
Yes.
I'm a junior of Lieutenant Kuno and I'm right out of school,
and since my flight time is short, I was wondering if I might be excluded.
There are no marines or preparatory students in the selection of the kamikaze unit.
You have flown long enough.
Don't worry about it.
Play me another song.
Yes.
An enemy task force with six aircraft carriers, has been located at sea 60 nautical miles east of Suluan Island.
Good.
We will launch three special attacks and two direct attacks.
The commander of the special attack unit is Lieutenant Kuno. We are ready to start immediately.
Ah! A Grumman!
Remove the bombs from the special attack aircraft! Disperse the planes!
#MISSING LINES
Special attack aircraft, prepare to start.
Do not miss this chance to chase the enemy.
Immediately chase the enemy and show your strength!
Kamikaze corps, Yamato corps, start!
Thus, the first sortie of the Kamikaze corps was carried out.
However, on the way, due to bad weather,
the two planes returned without finding the enemy.
Only the commander, Lieutenant Kuno's plane, did not return.
Lieutenant Kuno did not return, either because he felt responsible for not finding the enemy,
or because of his silent resistance to the first ramming attack in history.
The Japanese Navy did not inform the public that he was the first sortie of the kamikaze corps.
The reason is still unknown,
perhaps because Lieutenant Kuno was a preparatory student, or that he had no spectacular results to show.
We have received a call from Shikishima Corps.
Enemy MTF has not been found yet.
Although their fuel is low, they are continuing the search.
It seems that the weather is bad
Three days until the Kurita fleet rushes into Leyte.
If you don't find the enemy aircraft carrier within three days, the operation will fail.
Please think of Seki.
He is desperately looking for it every day.
The Shikishima Corps, which started from the Mabalacat base,
searched for the American MTF and continued to fly every day,
but finally could not find it and had to turn back in vain.
I couldn't find them today either.
I'm sorry.
Is your body okay?
Lieutenant Kuno.
I'll definitely go, so please wait.
On the 26th, 0600,
the first attack corps encountered an enemy task force off the coast of Suluan Island and immediately engaged.
Prepare to launch the special attack corps.
I'm taking the place of 100 million people.
I wish you success today.
Kamikaze corps, Shikishima corps, start.
On October 25, at 7:25 am, the Kamikaze corps took off from the Mabalacat base, led by the commander, Captain Seki.
Prior to that, the Shikishima Corps, at 6:30 am on the 25th,
the Asahi Crops and the Yamazakura Corps departed from Mindanao Island and Davao Base.
Motoko. You looked at my face and laughed a lot.
You slept in my arms and we took a bath together.
When you grow up and want to know about me, ask your mother and your aunt Kayo about me.
I wanted to see you grow up and be happy, but if I die, I will never be sad.
When you grow up and want to see your father, come to Kudan.
Welcome. And if you think deeply in your heart, your father's face will surely come to your mind.
Your father always protects you, You should be kind and loved by others.
Read this letter when you grow up and start thinking about me.
To Motoko Uemura. From your father.
The Shikishima Corps has contacted us.
Ten Battleships, four to five cruisers, destroyers, and more than 30 other ships on the sea east of Samar Island.
More than 20 Grumman planes in the air moving north.
This is Shikishima Corps. 1040. City of Tacloban 85 degrees.
Discovered four aircraft carriers, cruisers, and six destroyers at 90 nautical miles. Attack starts immediately.
Message from the first fighter. The assault started.
The second fighter assault started. The third also goes to Sanbanki.
Thus, the Kamikaze corps was born.
And until the end of the war, more than 2,500 young people were scattered one after another.
I would like to say to the heroes of the Kamikaze Corps.
Thank you for fighting well.
Believing in the final victory, I apologized to my subordinates, the Kamikaze Corps and their families,
for failing to achieve that goal after making a suicidal bomb attack.
Those who make decisions need to be prepared to judge themselves.
Even in death.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS LINE 1
#CREDITS LINE 2
#CREDITS LINE 3
#CREDITS LINE 4
#CREDITS LINE 5
#CREDITS LINE 6
#CREDITS LINE 7
Operation Vengeance (Episode 18)
#CREDITS LINE 8
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
Ivan55