The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
On June 5, 1942, Japan was defeated in the Battle of Midway.
They lost four aircraft carriers: Kaga, Akagi, Soryu, and Hiryu,
as well as one heavy cruiser, 322 aircraft, and 3,500 soldiers.
On the other hand, the US military lost 150 aircraft and 300 soldiers, but one aircraft carrier: Yorktown was wrecked.
Yorktown was attacked twice by the Japanese, but only the engine was damaged and the hull was slightly scratched.
The submarine I-168, commanded by Captain Tanabe, must put an end to this Yorktown.
Five hours after receiving the order, 1-168 continued its run 150 nautical miles northeast of Midway.
But can they really meet their enemies in the vast ocean?
Radar was not heavily in use at that time. They can only rely on nautical charts, binoculars, and beliefs.
Submarine I-168 (Episode 12)
One black dot. It's like an aircraft carrier.
Like an aircraft carrier.
Captain. That is consistent with the reconnaissance aircraft report.
Stop. Prepare to dive.
Dive, hurry.
There are no waves at all.
Captain. The periscope will be discovered.
However, I'm grateful that the enemy stays in the direction of the sun.
Heaven's help.
No, voyage chief. Your calculation was correct.
How far is it between us and the enemy?
Yes. We can catch up in two hours.
Check the torpedoes again.
At that time, only the Japanese Navy used compressed oxygen to propel its torpedoes.
Max speed: 40 knots.
The range is 4000m and the amount of gunpowder it contains is 500kg.
It has the highest hit rate in the world.
And again, the submarine itself has many world-class features, including high-speed power at sea.
Its excellent performance, along with the German U-boat, shook each country.
How is it?
Captain, the weather is wonderful.
It's like a dream that there was such a fierce battle.
I am not asking about the weather, but the engine.
Yes, even according to the previous report.
Is it useless? But somehow we're back in Hawaii.
I can't stay in such a place.
Yes, the destroyers are toeing us right now.
Now, in our home country, they are doing their best to save an aircraft carrier.
However, for the time being, the remaining two ships, Enterprise and Hornet, must protect the Pacific Ocean.
To that end, I want to return Yorktown to the battlefield as soon as possible.
Fortunately there are no waves. Right now.
Captain, the wind has come out.
The wind has come out.
Good. Heaven's help.
Lower the periscope.
They are doing it. They are on the alert.
The enemy's vigilance is strict.
Don't make noise inside the ship.
Master of the voyage, their current location doesn't fit the calculation.
Is the enemy being swept away by the wind?
No, the enemy is moving.
You've come behind the enemy for a long time.
I'm sorry.
No, you don't have to apologize.
No matter how genius your navigation is, you can't get close to it exactly in a place like this.
It is dangerous to raise the periscope any further and approach.
Yorktown engines are off, so it’s Impossible to follow their sound.
Aren't the enemy destroyers making a sound?
Will you follow the sound of the destroyer?
Pass under the destroyer. You can't go through just one.
If you pass under the destroyer on the other side, you can surely catch the enemy.
It's too bold.
It’s a battō-jutsu in the dark.
let's go. Depth 45.
Captain
Is it okay?
A two-hour dive in the dark.
Depth 18. Raise the periscope.
It's perfect. We are on the right side of the enemy. Thank you. Master of the voyage.
However, 500 meters is too close. Keep a distance of 800 or 1000.
Captain
The knack of battō-jutsu is in time.
Did they stop all at once?
Seven destroyers at once.
We were discovered.
Let's shoot and run away.
What time is it now?
12:37.
It's lunch time.
The Americans have taken a break.
The enemy can hear it.
Ready to launch a torpedo.
Ready to launch.
Prepare
Shoot!
70 depth. hurry up.
37 seconds, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44,
We did it!
30 minutes have passed.
The enemy destroyer is moving, but not coming near.
The enemy destroyer is approaching straight on.
The enemy ship is passing directly above.
Enemy, depth charge launch, 2 shots
Full starboard
Enemy depth charges, 54 shots, 55
Turn on the emergency light.
Flooding!
Rear, flooded!
Flooding.
Everything is useless, both vertically and horizontally.
The battery is damaged.
Gas outflow
20 people in the back, move to the front.
Captain, depth exceeds 100m. This ship cannot exceed 75m.
Trust Japanese shipbuilding technology.
20 people in front, move to the back. 1 ton drainage.
Put on a gas mask.
Connect usable electricity.
How many hours will the battery last?
About 2 hours.
Officer, how much air remains?
40kg
Good. If you do your best for two hours, the sun will set.
The enemy will also run out of depth charges.
Captain, at your feet.
This is suffering from gas.
Was the mouse here?
It's auspicious.
Do you know I-170?
Is she the one sunk in Operation Hawaii?
When 170 departed, the mice on the ship disappeared steadily, and 170 didn't come back.
I know the story.
As you can see, our ship has not been abandoned by the mouse.
It will be absolutely okay. We will definitely be back in Japan.
Surgeon Chief, don't let this mouse die.
Yes. I will take responsibility for it.
Don't laugh. The air becomes muddy.
I-168 lost power. Not only did the propulsion motor stop, but it couldn't stay level.
When that happens, the air and seawater in the submarine's tanks begin to move on their own, and as a result,
the submarine either surfaces or sinks with a striking force.
However, there are enemies on the sea.
Also, it is not allowed to sink to the 4000m seabed.
I-168 managed to balance her ship and tried to save time. The battle between sinking and buoyancy continues.
By the way, based on this bitter experience of the I-186,
the Japanese Navy completely remodeled the battery of their submarines to make them shock-resistant.
The ship is floating up.
Move everyone forward.
Is human balance useless?
Captain. Let's prepare for what we should do.
Captain, prepare for suicide with torpedoes.
It is going up.
Captain, I'm sorry. We are floating up.
How many minutes have passed since the sound of the depth charges disappeared?
40 minutes.
Good.
Get ready to engage.
#Missing Line
Hurry up. Let's fight with all weapons.
Man your stations.
Enemy, three destroyers. 15,000m. They are moving away.
The enemy does not seem to be aware, because we are in the sun's glare.
They will soon find us.
Hurry up and get air and electricity.
Put out smoke.
Alright, hide it with smoke.
The enemy is back.
Hey, have you ever seen the captain's angry face?
That kind of person has luck. Do not worry.
How much air did you get?
About 70 kg.
Enemy, distance 5000 meters.
Make more smoke.
#Missing Line
We can use the motor. Is working.
Hurry up the battle.
Alright, we can run away.
I can't hear the sounds of the enemy destroyers.
What is it?
Just give this to the captain.
All the non-commissioned officers have gathered.
Captain
We wanted to thank you for something,
but I didn't have any words, so I brought this instead.
Thank you.
Captain. Have a drink.
No, let's go down and drink with everyone.
The captain hasn't eaten anything since last night.
Me? There was not enough training.
Master of the voyage.
It's beautiful.
#Missing Line
The captain of this submarine, who did not lose his mild-mannered personality,
encouraged his men, and achieved his goals together. He was always calm and bold.
Reliable decisions, especially in extreme conditions, cannot be made without this calm.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS 1
#CREDITS 2
#CREDITS 3
#CREDITS 4
#CREDITS 5
#CREDITS 6
#CREDITS 7
Battle of Savo Island (Episode 13)
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2