The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Prior to the start of the Pacific War, in October 1941,
a meeting to discuss the Southern Operations was held at the Army War College for several days.
Among the Southern Operations,
the leading role for the Philippine operation was the 14th Army
under the command of Lieutenant General Masaharu Homma,
to which the 5th Flight Group was assigned.
However, there was an important problem with the operation.
It was unclear if the US military would fight in the capital, Manila, or stay in the Bataan Peninsula.
The mission of the 14th Army is to destroy the major enemy bases in the Philippines.
That means the city of Manila.
I want the 14th Army's main force to land 10 day after the start of the war and occupy the city of Manila 35 days later.
However, the plan is that the 48th Division and the 5th Flight Group
will be diverted to Operation Java-Malayan after a pause.
I think that time will be a problem.
Is the purpose of the Philippine operation to capture the city of Manila or to destroy enemy troops?
I want to clarify it.
I think that the enemy is likely to escape to the Bataan Peninsula, as it did during the American-Spanish War.
Yes. If the enemy can escape to the Bataan Peninsula, it will be difficult to destroy.
Moreover, if the 48th Division and the 5th Flight Group were later pulled out by Operation Java-Malayan,
our troops would be thin.
The Bataan Peninsula is a natural fortress.
It would be difficult if they escaped.
I think we should also consider fighting in Bataan.
No, I don't think it's possible.
The enemy is mainly the militia, and MacArthur must be thinking of a defensive operation in Manila.
After the Philippine Operation, the Java Operation is planned.
Therefore, in order to send the 48th Division to Java,
#MISSING
If the enemy escapes to the Bataan Peninsula, I think it should be dealt with slowly later.
I understand.
On November 3rd, the Chief of Staff, General Sugiyama, submitted a draft of this operation.
First, the purpose of the operation: to destroy the enemy in the Philippines and destroy its main base.
Second operational purpose: The Army, in cooperation with the Navy, will land on Luzon and quickly capture Manila.
Isn't it necessary to write down what happens when the enemy escapes to the Bataan Peninsula?
The authority to make that decision is left to the commander of the 14th Army. I think you don't have to write it.
Battle of Bataan and Corregidor
On December 8th, the 11th Air Fleet's formation of Mitsubishi G4M Zero fighters,
informed by the successful surprise attack on Pearl Harbor,
ambushed the US Air Force bases in the Philippines: Clark Air Base and Iva.
It destroyed about 100 US planes waiting on the ground and the US Air force in the Philippines was destroyed in a day.
Subsequently, the main force under the command of the 14th Army Commander,
Lieutenant General Masaharu Homma, formed a convoy of 76 ships
and was escorted by the Third Fleet under the command of Vice Admiral Takahashi,
and went south into the southern waters.
As for the plan on the day of the landing, a successful landing is the first priority.
Its okay. The soldiers are enthusiastic and are competing for the first ride in Manila.
Morale is quite strong,
However, MacArthur must be fully prepared and waiting for us.
The problem is Bataan,
but we can think about it at that time.
No, sir, we have to take Manila all at once and not give the enemy time to escape.
The 14th Army's main force split into two and landed in the Lingayen Gulf on December 22nd,
and in Lamon Bay on December 24th.
From the south and north, they launched their march towards the City of Manila.
The Japanese army!
Turn back!
The US army could not fight against the tremendous advance of the Japanese army.
The enemy forces in the Central region are estimated to be 5 divisions, and 3 of them have already been devastated.
What is the situation of the enemy army in Manila?
I don't know the exact situation, but some of them have been hit hard.
So I wonder if the enemy is staying in Manila.
Although just a part of their force, enemies near Iba are retreating to the Bataan Peninsula.
Finally, are they going to stay on the Bataan Peninsula?
The advance of the Japanese army was narrowed down to Manila from the north and south,
and the fall of Manila seemed to be just a matter of time.
General Douglas MacArthur, commander of the United States Army Forces of the Far East,
is now faced with an important strategic decision.
Charge!
The advance of the Japanese army is faster than expected.
The enemy is supported by a powerful air force and equipped with a large number of tanks and field artillery.
All right. Make Manila an open city and withdraw all troops to the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor Island.
It's War Plan Orange.
Yeah. Move the military headquarters to Corregidor.
Defend here until the rescue army comes from our home country.
We can absolutely protect the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor.
However, if San Fernando, the entrance to the Bataan Peninsula, is captured, our withdrawal is impossible.
No quarter given.
Stop the Japanese here until the withdrawal is complete.
I will do it in honor of the US military.
Manila is declared an open city and General MacArthur plans to blow up the bridge at 6 AM on January 1st.
His entire army is ordered to withdrawal by then.
All US military facilities in Manila were burned down.
"Open City". In other words, a cloth was put on it to indicate that the city was defenseless,
and a truck full of soldiers, weapons, and ammunition passed by it in a hurry.
Sir, the enemy has escaped to the Bataan Peninsula.
The 48th Division Commander strongly advises us not to let the enemy escape to the Bataan Peninsula,
and to put Manila behind us.
Report from the reconnaissance aircraft.
Large units of enemies are retreating to the Bataan Peninsula one after another.
In addition, it seems that they are moving from the direction of Manila.
It's bad. There is no point in robbing Manila, which has become vacant.
No, the enemy is also desperately fighting back.
It will not easy to withdraw to the Bataan Peninsula.
No, it is a clear withdrawal. We should destroy the bridge, prevent their retreat, and hit the Luzon Plain all at once.
No, it may be a trap.
Sir.
The intention of the Imperial Headquarters is to defeat the enemy and quickly capture Manila.
48th Division must defeat their enemies and move towards Manila at once.
For some time, it was what was expected.
Lieutenant General Homma thought to disobey for a moment,
but kept the duty of all military personnel to obey the orders of his superiors.
and aimed at Manila as instructed by the Imperial Headquarters.
This allowed the US military to safely withdrew to the Bataan Peninsula.
On January 2nd, Manila fell and Japanese troops entered,
but this did not end the Philippine operation.
That's because most of the US troops stood on the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor Fortress.
In order to completely occupy and secure Manila City, it is necessary to secure Manila Bay.
In order to secure Manila Bay, the US troops on the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor Island must be conquered.
In other words, Bataan must fall.
Charge!
The Bataan Peninsula is 48km long and 24km wide.
The west and south were protected by cliffs, inaccessible from the sea,
and the entire peninsula was covered in jungle. It was a natural fortress.
Moreover, the number of US troops was more than 80,000.
It's okay. We wont be defeated for three years.
Charge!
The 48th Division was transferred to Operation Java as planned.
3000 soldiers of the 65th Brigade, under the command of Lieutenant General Nara,
landed on the Lingayen Gulf on January 1st.
They had no time to rest
and relied On an inaccurate 1 / 200,000 scale map to pursue enemies on the Bataan Peninsula.
The Japanese did not see General MacArthur's withdrawal from Bataan as a strategic retreat, but as a mere rout.
The Japanese troops underestimated the US troops who retreated to the Bataan Peninsula,
and were hit harder than expected.
On February 8th, Commander of the 14th Army, Lieutenant General Homma, gathered his staff members
and held a planning meeting On measures to carry out the operation.
We are now in a critical phase.
The question is whether to continue the attack or suspend it and rebuild our formations.
I would like to hear your opinions.
The attack should continue.
That is impossible.
With the current combat power, it will only be wiped out.
We can do it.
Until now, the operations have been left to each unit,
but from now on, command will be unified at military headquarters.
It we focus your attacks on the east and west coasts, you will always succeed.
Yeah. Attack is the best defense.
If we continue to attack even with a part of our forces
and replenish our troops in the meantime, we can go on the offensive.
However, the soldiers are exhausted and their damage is great.
It is better to take measures to wait for our troops to recover.
Opinions were divided into two camps, and there was a fierce controversy,
forcing the commander to make a decision.
On February 10th,
the commander made a decision and telegraphed the General Staff.
The attack was stopped.
The soldiers are over the limit of their physical strength.
I can't stand fighting like this anymore.
I dare to be ashamed as a military commander and ask for reinforcements in this section.
However, at the General Staff Headquarters.
What is the 14th Army doing? It's an army of shame. The attack should continue.
The problem is that the Southern operation is going well,
only the Philippines are not.
The Southern Expeditionary Army commander also wants an attack.
Isn't it necessary to write about the case when the enemy escapes to the Bataan Peninsula?
The authority to make that decision is left to the commander of the 14th Army, I think you don't have to write it.
It was the General Staff Headquarters who advocated the primary objective of capturing Manila,
and the Southern Expeditionary Army Command, who was in command.
But now the commander's decision hasn't changed.
A week later, Lieutenant General Homma telegraphed the commander of the Southern Expeditionary Army,
The message was still to stop the attack and ask for reinforcements.
The next day, the Southern Expeditionary Army command dismissed several staff members,
including the Chief of Staff of the 14th Army.
Several members of the General Staff Operations Division were newly incorporated into the 14th Army,
and an operation for a second total attack on the Bataan Peninsula was planned for.
A truck road was also built in the jungle.
30,000 reinforcements, mainly from the 4th Division, have also arrived.
The night before the second all out attack was a quiet one.
#POSSIBLY MISSING
Well-trained soldiers slept confidently and comfortably.
The following day, April 3rd, the second all out attack on the Bataan Peninsula began.
Charge!
On April 9th, the US military on the Bataan Peninsula was finally defeated.
The number of POWs was 70,000. Many were thin because of hunger and malaria.
All that remains is just to attack the enemy on Corregidor Island,
but that requires transporting 70,000 POWs rearwards.
Most of the POWs Are sick with malaria, or malnourished.
That's why, if we leave them alone as they are, they will be wiped out.
If we transport them to the rear, there are field hospitals.
I want you to set up a first aid station every few kilometers and deliver them.
However, the number of POWs is 70,000.
Collect as many trucks as possible.
Yes, I am doing it.
I leave it to you.
However, despite the commander's order, there were few Japanese trucks and it was difficult to procure them.
Therefore, the POWs had to walk 88km on the hot road.
Only 2,300 POWs died in the Bataan Death March, but this was far less than if they were left on the Bataan Peninsula.
However, the US still called this a "death march."
Already, General MacArthur had transferred command to Major General Wainwright
and had escaped from Corregidor Island to Australia.
The words "I shall return", which included a counterattack against the Philippines, made the Allied side excited.
Next to the Bataan Peninsula is Corregidor Island, but the US military was no longer willing to resist, and on May 6th
Corregidor Island also fell, and the Philippine campaign was completed here.
However, shortly afterwards, the commander of the 14th Army was transferred to a reserve role.
The commander obeyed the orders of the Imperial Headquarters and captured Manila.
Thinking of the hardships of his subordinates,
he abandoned his pride as a military commander and sought reinforcements.
He moved the Bataan prisoners to Corregidor to avoid useless deaths and injuries.
However,
the commander's weak decisions made on the harsh battlefield were seen as a fatal flaw in a commander.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
#CREDITS 1
#CREDITS 2
#CREDITS 3
#CREDITS 4
#CREDITS 5
#CREDITS 6
Submarine I-168
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2