Japan is the Kingdom of Gymnastics.
5 gold medals at the 18th Tokyo Olympics
6 gold medals at the 19th Mexico Olympics
5 gold medals at the 20th Munich Olympics
3 gold medals at the 23rd Los Angeles Olympics
Right now, our traditional gymnastics world
welcomes a new generation.
Shinji Morisue
This is the tale of a man who rose from nothing, blazing like a comet across the night sky
to carry Japan into the 21st century.
Fight!
Why?
Try your best, Fujimaki-kun!
How did I end up here?
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Ganbarist Shun
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
As much as it's unrealistic,
As much as it's going to hurt,
I found the courage to take the first step
'Cause I believed!
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
A dazzling miracle descends upon you
So spread your arms and catch it!
Episode
How Come?!
Tournament With Zero Practice!
See ya!
Heisei Middle School Entrance Ceremony
Yeah, tomorrow!
Fujimaki Shun
Ouch...
Whatever!
Um...
Higashi Denji
What is it?
N-No...
Heisei Gymnastics Club
Pretty sure this is the place...
Um...
Uchida Minoru
What is it?
I-Is this is the gymnastics club?
Yeah, that's us.
Then... I'd like to join!
Wh-What?
Shindo Yuichi
You're interested in our club?
Y-Yes! Class 1-B, Fujimaki Shun!
I want to win an Olympic gold medal.
G-Gold medal?
That's quite a statement to make.
Hm! You don't know what you're saying!
Looking down on gymnastics, are you?!
Easy now...
Anyway, come inside.
Thanks!
You're our first new member in years.
But are you sure? We're the men's gymnastics club, you know.
Excuse me?
Hey, first-year, got any
experience in gymnastics?
Not at all!
A-An absolute rookie?
Then maybe you were good with the horizontal bar?
No, I was completely helpless on it.
U-Um, what are you doing?
What are these muscles?!
You've no confidence in your strength?
I don't!
Know what a vault is?
I don't.
That's hopeless...
Higashi.
Got it!
Wh-What are you doing?
Gymnastics is about power!
It's about muscles.
Someone as feeble as you can never succeed in it!
Gymnastics is about brains.
Someone foolish enough to aim for a gold medal starting from zero is bound to fail!
H-Hey, Higashi, don’t you think personal motivation counts too?
Captain, just forget about that cretin.
B-But I really think gymnastics is about your spirit, your heart, Uchida.
Captain, gymnastics is about the appearance.
It's about looking cool.
Sanada Toshihiko
Sanada...
Huh?!
W-What's with that crutch?!
I sprained my leg.
It's no laughing matter!
We’ve got a team competition tomorrow!
We need four people to compete!
Welcome to the gymnastics club, newbie!
Fujimaki-kun, I have high hopes for your untapped potential.
Huh?
Urayasu District Gymnastics Preliminaries
You're a lucky guy!
You’ve barely been in the club for a day,
and we’re already letting you compete in a tournament!
Sorry, Fujimaki-kun.
We needed a fourth member
to simply be able to participate.
I swear I’ll give that cretin Sanada
a piece of my mind for that sprain!
Do your
best,
total
rookie!
Well, do your best now, Fujimaki-kun.
E-Even if I try to do my best,
what on earth am I to do?
What am I supposed to do here?
Raise your hand and reply!
Y-Yes!
What should I do?
What’s the matter?
Staring at the bar won’t get you to the Olympics!
Nothing will, if you don't know how to do it.
Please, Fujimaki-kun!
Just try something, doesn't matter what!
Oh... Whatever!
I'll try!
C-Can't reach it!
Really, what else did you expect?
That horizontal bar
is 2.6 meters off the ground!
Seriously?
Sorry, let me give you a lift.
Have you seen that number 26 just now?
He's a complete joke!
Is he from Heisei Middle School men's club?
Tsk. That's why I hate tournaments
Did you reach it?
Yes.
I'm letting go, then.
Hey, is he gonna start moving or what?
What's with that guy?
It's not a dangling competition!
Fujimaki-kun, you need to do something,
whether it’s a back hip circle or whatever!
Back hip circle... Back hip circle!
Back hip circle...!
Is he for real?
Can't even do back hip circle?
Why is he just swinging his legs like that?
He’s like a fish pulled from the water!
C-Come on, you two!
Stop laughing!
Fujimaki-kun is earnestly...
Uh... Huh? Wh-What's going on?
I-I'm swinging now!
C-Can't stop!
Here!
I'm gonna die now!
Way to go, Heisei Club!
Idiot...
It's no longer even laughable!
Just embarrassing.
F-Fujimaki-kun, strike the finishing pose...
Not like that!
You need to stand up on your feet!
That was great!
Keep up the good work!
He's embarrassed our club!
Just keep pretending we don't know him.
Don't come near us!
Still, you did your best, Fujimaki-kun.
Here, wipe your nosebleed.
O-Okay... Thanks.
Now then...
They’re about to announce the score.
Hm? Score?
Heisei Middle School
Huh? 10 points?
Shut up, dumbass!
Where are you seeing 10?!
That's 1 point! 1.0!
1.0?
Be grateful they've given you any points at all.
After all, everything you did was the kind of stuff they usually deduct points for.
Deduct?
Falling.
Double swing.
Then finally, standing on top of the bar.
That 1 point is a participation point
that everyone gets for simply showing up.
In other words,
it's the worst possible score.
Worst score?
What are you surprised about?
It's only natural!
Will you ever forgive me?
I’ve brought down the team’s total points with my terrible score!
Oh no...
No need to worry about it, Fujimaki-kun.
Captain!
You don't understand a thing, do you?
Huh?
Only the three best-performing members out of four contribute to the team's score.
1 team = 4 members
So your points don't count toward it.
They're cut off!
Well, that's also true,
so you don't have to worry.
Is that so?
You didn't really ruin our score!
Captain, there's nothing to worry about!
He can't even do the back hip circle,
but dares to talk about the gold medal!
They're right...
I’m here just to meet the required number of members.
Fujimaki-kun.
Huh?
Come on, don't lose your heart so soon.
Even the greatest athletes had to start from somewhere.
At first, I also watched the others' performances to learn from them.
The first step is learning by watching.
Now then...
Do your best!
Okay!
I'll do my best!
Oh!
Here comes the Heisei Women's team!
It’s Orikasa Reiko!
She’s irresistible every time I look at her!
Look, look!
They'll be practicing now!
Orikasa Reiko-san?
It's so...
It's so dreamy...
She is #7 in Japan
Huh?
She's a candidate for the Olympic team.
Olympic team?
Yes.
She's the Heisei Women's Gymnastics Club Captain.
Huh? She's from the same school as us?
Yeah.
Japan's representative...
Olympic team candidate...
And we're in the same school!
Okay, it's the floor performance next.
Fujimaki-kun!
Hey, we gotta go, Fujimaki-kun!
Aye-aye!
Heisei Club, please conclude your practice and start the performance.
Are you for real?! No extra points for these beautiful muscles?
There's no extra point for muscles.
What's the point appealing to your muscles?
Appeal to your technique if you have to!
Appeal?
In gymnastics, you have to present yourself appealingly to the judges.
Remember this, gymnastics is a battle against the judge.
I slipped up...
I've been wondering about it for a while now,
is that bell signaling for something?
Man, you really are a complete rookie!
Floor performance time is from 50 seconds to 70 seconds
That's first one signals that 50 seconds have passed.
That means he needs to finish his performance now.
Wow!
That's amazing Captain
You got 8.5!
You jumped so high there!
Easy now, 8.5 is nothing to make a fuss about.
Hey, it's your turn next.
Don't embarrass us like last time.
Got it!
You can count on me this time.
Oh? He sounds mighty confident.
What's he up to?
Um... Would it be possible to play a slow ballad during my performance?
Huh? Captain, the men have to perform without music?
Yes!
I see. So they only play music for girls?
Oh! There he is!
It's him!
That number 26 again!
Oh, he started running!
This is it!
Okay...
He tumbled!
Just threw himself!
It's not judo, you know!
Can't wait to see what he does next!
What now?
Calm down...
Calm down!
Does he...
Does he want to actually do something?
That jump...
I can do it too!
What?!
Ganbarist Shun
What on earth is that pose?!
He's like a heron!
No, like one of those Noh statues!
Even more embarrassing.
That's why I hate the tournaments.
Wh-What...
Is he...
Could it be...
that he's trying to imitate my stance earlier?
Hey, there's something
interesting on the floor.
Yeah, let's go check it out.
Remember!
Gymnastics is a battle against the judge!
Even with his ridiculously awkward posture,
he's been upholding it for so long?
Fujimaki-kun, what if...
What if you are...
An idiot.
Yeah, very much so.
A stance cannot be more than three seconds long.
If you keep holding it for longer,
they'll start deducting points instead.
Which means...
That guy is irredeemable...
Imbecile!
I guess they're right...
Nice!
Keep it up!
Clumsy statue!
Wh-Why? Why is he staring at me like that?
I won!
Is it the finish?
What is he going to do?
He keeps speeding up.
That's...
A simple...
Jump.
With one 360 turn.
Finished!
Fini          shed!
Nicely done!
It's the most fun ever!
He seriously thought that a landing like that would do!
That was one hella performance!
Captain, I did it!
Y-Yeah... Well done.
Right, the score...
1 point again...
1.3...
1.3?
Don't lose your spirits.
Everyone has to start...
Captain! I did it!
It's 1.3, no longer the lowest score!
Ah... What? So you're happy about it?
T-That's right, you showed just a fraction of technique there.
Yahoo!
He's a hopeless idiot.
Okay, time for the next event.
Hold on tight to your heart's burning excitement
Yes! Captain, what's next?
A vaulting horse.
A vaulting horse?
Embrace the endless future and never let go!
Remember vaulting over boxes
in grade school?
Vaulting horse is like the extension of that.
V-Vaulting over boxes?
Now, Fujimaki-kun, it's practice time.
You should try vaulting over it a few times too.
R-Right...
The vaulting horse is 120 cm tall
and 160 cm long.
Through all the sleepless nights I had to endure,
Well, just try not to get yourself killed.
I kept telling myself that I can't give up
Vaulting box...
As much as it's unrealistic,
What are you waiting for?
Get a move on! I need to use it later too!
As much as it's going to hurt,
The gymnastics rookie Fujimaki Shun,
long is the road to the gold medal.
Spread your arms and catch it!
After his first encounters with the horizontal bar and floor,
Shun is now about to face the vaulting horse.
Hey, why are you shivering so much, Shun?
With that attitude, how can you hope to ever win the Olympic gold medal?
Go, Ganbarist Shun!
My head revolves around the universe,
they say it's as pure as honey
"Will it work out or not?"
Doesn't really matter
A planet that revolves around with life on it
by an invisible power in imperceptible time
The love song of angels that I can still hear right here, in my naive grownup heart
When I was little, I feared the demon of darkness,
but now that I grew up, the love song of angels is still with me
Love song of angels, once you start hearing,
it'll stay with you even when you grow up—love song of angels!
Raw provider
Translation
WOWmd
Perevodildo
Next episode preview
It's no use. I just can't forget about what happened back then.
Really? You're training to vault over a horse out here?
Can you really call it training, then?
All right.
Come on, try to jump over me.
Next Gamba:
Oh No! The Terrifying Vaulting Horse Experience.
This technique was introduced by American athlete Gaylord.
Look closely, do you understand?
You let go of the bar, make a double turn and clutch it again!
Next time we'll see the Double Kovacs performed by the Atlanta Olympic team member Hatakeda!