Otake High School
How cruel! Where is he going like that?
A blooming flagrancy!
Oi, Yakuda.
Want some coffee?
Come on, a greeting for a transferred student...
How can you be such idiot!?
This guy sure is nervous.
Are you a moron?
Should I kick your ass?
(Shibai Taroka)
I still don't believe he can get Okajima.
I'd rather bet he drops dead on the first shot.
But this Yakuda is also a real deal.
Such tough face should cover an according character.
True.
He may be be experienced,
but so is Okajima.
In this school, such arrogance
will ruin him, just you wait!
We should find out, which one is stronger?
So far, Yakuda sure wins a face to face.
Pansy
Come on, lads, bloom and prosper, okay?
Daigo Yakuda, 16 yo!
Yakuda, here you are, finally!
I was looking for you everywhere.
It's the five ones,
trampled by your classmate.
Anyway, Kariya from the C-class wants to speak to you,
they're waiting for you behind the gymnasium.
I don't speak to no one.
If you don't go, it's fine.
Please return this to the washroom instead of me.
He totally doesn't look like a 16 years old...
Gotta go to the washroom anyway now.
Hey!
I have nothing to do with Kariya myself!
It's true, you have to believe me!
I was just persuaded to call you in, nothing aside that!
Don't kill me...
Where is the gymnasium?
Yes...
I got transferred just recently.
I don't know where the gymnasium yet.
Is that the problem?
It's yonder.
Much obliged.
He may not be as bad as his face appeals.
Who called me out here?
I did.
It was rude, my flowers got trampled.
Kariya Masataka, 16yo!
Bastard, you weren't too sweet
on my friend being polite either.
Shit...
Judging by face, he has already lost.
For no reason, you hit our man
and didn't say a word afterwards.
For no reason? Did this bastard
really tell you I had no reason for that?
I really love flowers, you know.
He pretends to like flowers?
Then bastard will have it for his funeral.
I see, that's how it is.
By the way, what's with your laces?
Then it's a quick victory.
Won't even have to fight you.
What a barbarian!
Students at this school have no respect
nor love for flowers in their hearts!
They look like they were already taken care of.
Someone else but the gardening club teacher
does it on holiday?
Manami Sera, 16yo!
Someone else but the teacher
spares time for it?
Such a thing does not belong to this school.
Listen!
I'm the only one to hold this school in my fist.
I'm Kariya Masataka. For today,
I forgive you due to being a transferred newbie.
But from now on,
I won't let you get away with it.
I need to go home.
Back off, Kariya!
Stop it! Stop, both of you!
You're on it again, Kariya...
Fuckin...
Stop I said!
Miyama
I need to go home.
Come on, teacher.
Don't you want to let go of me already?
It was just a friendly bros' conversation.
Didn't you see yourself?
Kariya! Fighting is strictly prohibited!
For how long are you planning to keep it this way?
Fighting? You must be joking. We were just
kickinspecting one another's martial arts styles.
I'm fond of inspecting things.
It makes me burn with enthusiasm.
Isn't that right?
Just inspecting one another's martial arts.
Right, people?
Being enthusiastic about research is great,
but you still should be reasonable, okay?
Before, I remember sudden blow,
like if something hit Okajima's valet.
Gotta think something bad happened.
What a hooey!
This could not be the case!
I'm sorry!
It wasn't on purpose!
I just stumbled!
What does he want?
He isn't gonna beat me up, right?
I'm completely fine.
It didn't hurt.
I'm really sorry!
My, what a surprise!
He didn't try to molest a woman?
But he had his tooth knocked out.
I don't get it at all!
Knock-knock on wood.
That guy, if you look up at him,
reminds me of my father, I wonder how old is he.
I managed to talk to Sera...
Lucky!
In addition...
To such a reason for happiness!
Infirmary
Stay still!
It's just a scratch, nothing serious.
Nothing?
Who was he? The guy.
One of our students?
High school students are almost adults...
Do you want something
from that guy?
You naughty boy!
Not in such place.
We can't!
If you go any further,
I'm afraid I won't be able to stop!
We can't.
Someone might come.
Well, what can I do if it's love?
Huh?
Didn't you hear something now?
What do you mean?
Whether it was of pain or of joy,
I heard a woman's cry now.
I haven't heard a thing.
You must have misheard.
Is that so?
So be it!
What's more important,
is it true what they say happened earlier?
What happened earlier?
Yakuda was beaten to the pulp like never before.
This one? True indeed. By the guy who claimed
to love flowers despite his most unfitting for it face.
It's him after all.
I still can't believe it somehow.
Did you say something?
Soliloquy.
After all, it was him who beat Okajima.
He was the only one able to tame Yakuda's iron fist.
Despite having a face like this,
he isn't a bad person at all!
Someone must be thinking of me quite hard.
Or maybe it's just a cold...
I wouldn't want that to happen.
It must be one of our students.
Hey, boy! Sorry to bother,
but won't you mind fetching this to the teachers' room?
Teacher forgot something at home you see,
need to return...
I don't need nothing...
We still have something to discuss.
What is this thing?
Let's step away for a bit.
How about later? The teacher asked me to bring
something to the teachers' room, I don't have "bits."
Bastard...
Didn't you hear what I said previously?
I can repeat it for you if you didn't hear.
Let us settle it now.
Earlier, I couldn't get this guy over with quickly,
thus he has made himself Okajima's rival.
Luckily, I'm not some demon.
I don't like carrying out the group lynching.
I'll treat you fair,
like the unaware of anything transfer student you are.
If you say you don't want to become my cugine,
I think I'll be fine with letting you leave.
I got you...
I see, a wise choice should I notice.
You can be a reasonable man
and a "don't judge a book by its cover" instance.
Also tell this guy,
he owes 10000 yen for the flowers ruined.
See now?
Regardless of face, he still pees his pants.
People are never what they appear to be.
Well, even if it COincides he COmes to us later,
he'd COllect a few new bumps, right, Kariya-san?
Good morning!
Morning!
Yakuda?
What's all of a sudden?
Manami, what on the world happened?
So womanly!
Should I take a canned coffee for you, Kariya-san?
In that case, I also want a melon bun!
Got you!
Even if it's a shortcut to the way out,
such is unacceptable.
It's not a reason to trample the beauty!
How can be those guys be so ruthless?
What a deplorable situation!
Do you even mind where are you walking?
I recall telling you I love flowers already.
Don't you still get it!?
The guy smacks them all up!
So easily!
Oi, Yakuda!
So you were serious about loving flowers?
I thought you claimed to love flowers
only as a mean to avoid the fight!
So you're the guy who loves to watch the Sakura blossom.
I like it too! Such is my character!
Um, excuse me?
I never noticed you exhibit such a liking, Boss.
Isn't it great?
Teachers' Room.
The flowers were delivered safe and sound...
To teacher
No, it's still too early to rejoice.
Things can't go smooth with that guy.
To teacher
You'll pay for making me deliver the flowers
with a constant expectation of something fearful.
What will he say?
A little advice on flowers:
Teacher, you expose them
to a bit too much water and sunlight.
Saintpaulia is vulnerable to the direct sunlight.
From Yakuda Daigo.
If it won't bother you,
do you mind sharing one sprout with me later?
Is this...
Have you heard what they say
about our recent transfer student?
Transfer student...
You mean that year 1 class B Yakuda?
Right, right! They say, right this morning,
he knocked out 10 of our students all of a sudden!
Seems like we had
some outstanding transfer this time.
Even we, teaching staff, no matter how old he is,
should be feared of a child like this.
I can't believe I ended up
asking the favour of a thug!
She has such a fine body!
Manami, we'll go ahead.
God damn it...
I can't hold myself any longer.
It's Kariya...
Why would class C Kariya come all the way here?
What are you looking at, morons?
Starting today, I'm also this class' student.
Let's do our best in studies, Yakuda.
Oi! I expect you all to take care of me too.
Hey, what's the matter?
Has something happened?
What's the meaning of this?
My, it's class C Kariya here.
What for?
Since we're to warm up now,
how about some soccer?
Hey, aren't you a silver-haired man's brother?
What do you mean?
I have no idea of such a man.
It means little to me without a name.
Call him by name.
What?
You have a piece of cloth torn out here.
Take it off. This should be fixed.
I don't give a shit!
If it hurts your feelings, just shove them...
Shouldn't rely on the parents only.
You!
Where the fuck are you going!?
And what're you looking at, dimwits!?
Huh?
I'm certain, at this time, the year 1 class B is having
the physical education. Or is it in a cold season?
This and that, things are getting overcomplicated!
Maybe, I should see the doctor for once?
This Yakuda bastard made a sweet face at first
but uprose against you after all.
Bullshit about the cloth hole was a fucking lie!
It seems, he tries his best
to mock and disgrace Kariya-san.
He wants to scare Kariya-san away.
But he's just the sucker who hits from behind.
Things can be settled not through fight alone.
Only a man of many talents can be a warrior.
But it's also well known that at war
the safety is in numbers.
From now on we're also gonna be rising in numbers.
It's always better to have some warriors guarding you.
And it also must be the allegiant warriors,
committed to me from the heart.
But this jackass Yakuda...
He is who he is.
But he'll become a guy to die for my prosper.
Let him love flowers all he wants.
He is but an ugly weirdo now.
His fighting skills are more important.
The Story of Great Pure Love
Yakuda!
You really helped me out this morning.
Thank you. This is the one you wanted
to borrow from me, Saintpaulia flower.
Good thing I left that notice for you.
Gardening teacher and Yakuda
talk horticulture stuff!
Yakuda is moving right here!
Is something there?
Looks like he accidentally grabbed some green along.
Seen this money? It must have been
a token of appreciation for safety.
Gardening teacher bribed him with this money,
no doubt about it!
It can't be!
The bodyguards also require a fee,
especially the ones looking yakuza-like!
Teachers' Room
None of the teachers here?
That's a shame.
Don't lose your money anymore.
10,000 yen
Oh! Thank you, Yakuda.
Excuse me?
Yakuda, weren't you the one
who protected the flowerbed?
And besides, when it got trampled,
you bothered to fix and water it.
You're kind, aren't you, Yakuda?
The flowers always make me feel better.
I just need to be gentle to them,
and then, when I'm stressed,
their beauty relieves me.
Indeed.
A gospel truth!
Turns out, Yakuda, despite the face, you can be romantic!
I'm sorry! I said it doesn't suit your face,
should've kept that to myself.
Don't know
what's got into me...
What's going on?
Why do Sera hangs out around this guy?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because Sera is a gardening club member!
She must be very brave to do so!
Talking to such guy with a complete composure!
That's it!
I've read a book about something like this.
Remember Yakuda is bodyguarding that man?
He started doing it
as a mean to approach Sera easily!
It can't be!
His aim is Sera's voluptuous body only!
The bust is 85, the waist is 56, hips - 83!
How's that?
You know Sera's three sizes?
They say girls these days prefer exceptional guys.
What if he starts dating her?
Is Yakuda exceptional?
Is this for me?
Yeah.
Thanks a lot!
He even ribboned it!
I hope Sera knows what Saintpaulia
stands for in the flowers' language.
Should I better write or say it?
Shock...
Sera-san with such a guy.
Hey, cheer up, will ya?
Isn't it time we go home?
If we hang out here any longer,
the watchman drives us out.
Hey! What are you doing?
The after-school activities time is over!
I'm waiting for my friends here.
Hurry up and head home!
What?
Has someone yelled now?
Hey, Saburo...
Gymnasium storeroom
Is someone there? Hey!
What on Earth happened here?
Sera-san!
Why...
What's the matter?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Stop, not so fast, mongrel!
What did you do to her!?
What else?
I was surprised to notice a mouse in the dark.
Mouse?
Nothing aside that.
He also assaults women now!
And of all people he picked Sera-san!
Unforgivable! Absolutely unforgivable!
Sera has?
Wait, Yakuda beat her up?
Yesterday after-school
in the gymnasium storeroom.
How terrifying!
What will happen to me now?
You will be alright.
The teacher rushed there at once,
but didn't make it in time to prevent it.
Unforgivable!
Absolutely unforgivable!
Oi!
I want to know,
who was running near the gymnasium yesterday.
What's the matter with you bright and early?
Nobody seems to have any idea, huh?
Though I clearly saw you doing it yesterday.
What's this about?
You approach us and start accusing guys
though they know nothing. Don't they?
Right.
No idea what're you talking about.
It was not Yakuda's doing?
He simply heard my cry
and came to help me.
Then who is the culprit?
I don't know.
It was pitch dark and I couldn't see him.
It happened so abruptly.
But if it wasn't Yakuda,
can you explain why he was watching you sob?
That's right!
So fearsome!
Hitomi, I already said you have nothing to fear.
So, Manami?
In any way, it was totally not Yakuda.
Please, I forgot it already.
Let's not speak about it anymore, okay?
Guys could not hold on even for a minute...
His strength is transcendent.
What's even the deal with you all?
He disposed of you 10 times easier than before!
Yakuda!
What happened to flowers?
Nothing to worry about.
I replanted them to another place.
Stand still, I'll check your eye.
It hurts!
Hey! This Yakuda is doing something to her again!
Hurts!
Isn't he trying to make her kiss him forcibly?
I knew he was actually evil all the way
but I couldn't tell the truth beforehand! Manami...
What should we do?
At this rate, Manami
will be pumped and dumped, tattered!
Once he is done with Manami's body,
he'll come for mine...
You will be totally safe, you hear me!?
Hurts!
I didn't notice I stepped on you.
So sorry...
What now?
Is your eye better now?
Yakuda's eyedrops did me great.
He made Sera cry too!
But what a cute pouch you have here!
Did someone gift it to you?
I made it myself.
Because of my appearance,
women always consider me a threat.
I learned to care for myself
no worse than a woman would.
Yakuda?
In contrast, you are kind, aren't you?
I recall you had a brawl with Kariya the other day.
He may look arrogant,
but in reality he is a good boy too.
Therefore, do you mind getting along with him?
I think, if you look closely on it,
you have a pretty refined face!
Later.
Whoa, lil' sis, lil' sis!
Sis!?
What?
Damn it! This Yakuda is a jerk!
We just need a small handicap against him!
Look! Just look at it, Okajima!
Yakuda and doctor Miyama are cooing there!
What do they do?
Just chattering.
"Say nothing,
let me do just one bang, and we're over."
I was right after all!
Where is he going to bang her I wonder?
Of all the women,
he decided to lay his hands on Kariya's woman.
With this guy,
it just keeps getting better!
Hey! You sure we should let Kariya know?
While I'm at that, track down those two,
and I'll make sure to amuse you!
That's what we do!
You were more gentle at first!
Infirmary
What a swift bastard!
They have already started.
Amazing!
Yakuda! It feels so good!
Great...
- Deeper!
- They really are doing it!
What!?
Doctor Miyama and Yakuda do sex!?
Are you fucking sure!?
No... No room for doubt. Doctor Miyama
was moaning with such pleasure there...
Yakuda, fucker!!
I'm serious, Yakuda.
You're so good at massage!
Thanks to it,
my back pain has gone into thin air!
I'm an anma massage pro.
The neighbouring old lady often had back problems.
May I ask you to ever come again?
Sure. I can take care of you anytime.
Asshole... He seized the preemptive punch chance,
means I'll mince him with particular cruelty.
Hey! What imbecile would leave
a block weighing ton in a place like this?
Alright! I will do it now!
I have to do it now!
I might have no next chance to do it!
Give way, give way!
Move aside!
What's with these guys?
Can't they show some discipline in a campus at least?
What if those guys are Kariya's cugines,
avenging him being smashed?
What are they up to then?
The usual way!
They probably seek to group lynch Yakuda.
Isn't such litigation means cowardice?
For a Yakuza like Yakuda, serves him right.
Fight fire with fire they say.
Shit...
He had me unconscious.
Yakuda, you bastard, not this time!
This guy Yakuda...
Even if he begs for mercy sobbingly, it's too late.
I already have a mind to show him a true fear.
Actually, with this guy's face,
his crying face would resemble
an infant punished for misbehaviour.
That sonofabitch...
I'm growing tired of all this fighting...
Even received 2 to 3 punches this time.
It's bad for the skin as delicate as mine!
That's where my first aid kit comes in handy.
If I apply my favourite
character Band-Aid, it'd be fine.
I've had enough of your petty revolts.
Today I put you down for good, Yakuda!
Men should care for each other's condition.
Shut the fuck up, asshole!
You had no reason to do that!
You are a treacherous man, Yakuda!
Oh, really?
In this case I will encounter you!
Clingy jerk!
Now you got me ignited.
What!? I can't hear from here!
Asshole, die!
Damn bastard... Die, will ya!?
No way in hell!
We have an emergency, Principal!
Nice putt!
The terrible situation is taking place!
What is taking place, gardening teacher?
Please, get yourself together and explain.
Vice-principal, I didn't know you are also here.
But that's even better.
A moment ago, at the schoolyard,
Kariya and the transferred Yakuda
have started a serious brawl!
Oh... Means that rogue Kariya and the Mobster Face
finally get people's attention, so we could transfer them.
What a happy-go-lucky approach!
So how is it?
Is the fight in Kariya's favour?
No, I'd rather say it's an even battle.
This only grows more entertaining.
I'm glad to see lively students in our school!
But at this rate, the conflict is not resolved
until one of the parties is knocked out.
The battles can also be wholesome!
Isn't it one of the citizenship education doctrines?
Those boys are versed in fighting,
trading punches until one's death is not about them.
Besides, for the worst-case scenario, we have him.
Allow me to introduce. I invited this discipline
enforcer here as our insurance for the next time.
Teacher Nishinari.
Teacher Nishinari has the 4th Dan in Judo
and the 8th Dan in Karate.
During his college days, an amateur wrestling champion.
Truly, a man of valour.
From now on, none of our children would be able to brush us off by pulling a grimace like they used to before.
I'll do my best to meet your expectations.
Wonderful!
Shit!
I can't know - perhaps, in Osaka you were the top gun,
but here I'm the only top gun!
Have to say just one thing.
You are quite tough, lil' bro.
I'm Kariya!
Don't you dare to call me brother.
You can consider it a boast,
but you can't defeat me.
Will ya ever shut up, jackass!?
Wait a second!
Giving up already?
Guys like you are always all mouth and no trousers.
No way, just a temporary armistice.
Take a look at this.
What're you doing?
Need a reconstruction to go on.
Yakuda and Kariya,
you shouldn't fight any longer!
Sera! Step away! Run! It's dangerous!
Sera!
Is she alive?
Notice board: Year 1 class C - Kariya Masataka expelled.
Year 1 class B - Daigo Yakuda, suspended for an indefinite period.
We succeeded no matter what. Everything
was resolved smoothly and the most pleasant way.
Delinquents' chief is rid of. "Block Reconstructor to go on"
is also successfully made away with.
And thanks to teacher Nishinari,
the campus is also subdued quiet.
More than ever, our institution
is a perfect fee-paying school now.
Indeed, Principal!
Instead of trampling the flowerbeds,
everyone is trying to win Nishinari's favour now.
That is just splendid! Because if it goes on,
we may apply for funding soon.
Sure enough, this funding
ought to be of a significant kind.
A ratio no lower than of rivals'.
Hey now! What's going on?
You aren't one of our students anymore!
Get lost!
Cut the crap!
You are but pigs wearing a fake loving smile skin.
Before you step into trouble,
I suggest you retreat.
Principal's new watchdog can fuck off.
What's the matter?
With such punches, you won't even hurt me!
Out of breath already?
If you try to punch,
then hit like this!
Girl's friends
What? They got Kariya done?
Kariya was hospitalized with his right leg broken.
We have no one else to rely on, but you, Yakuda!
Kariya himself admitted so too.
Even if someone tells me to, I can't...
Yakuda!
Sera? Has your injury healed already?
Yes. What's more important, Yakuda,
do your best, okay?
What do you mean?
They impute you with crushing
the gardening club flowerbeds.
On the contrary,
you should visit the principal and explain!
Didn't you hear it from Ryota?
Why should I do that?
Because Yakuda turned out
to be precisely the kind of man that I anticipated.
And which, exactly?
May I try to clarify? Yakuda surely is one manly fellow,
in the sense that he is a kind-hearted justice devotee.
The manliest man of all men! An ideal type for Sera,
or so they say... That was a little redundant...
You've had plenty of time
to learn to watch your tongue!
Alright, you go watch me through the window then.
Cause I will take care of it.
And whoever gets in my way
will be whipped 'till the last one!
Someone has to bear a martyr role...
But does such simple-mindedness
really attracts women?
Go, go, Yakuda!
Principal's
Stop it!
You can't enter without permission!
- Learn to knock! To knock...
- Piss off!
Was not suspending me as a "Block Reconstructor
to go on" enough for punishments?
What are you talking about?
Leave the office please!
You may have deceived common folk,
but I'm a deceiver myself.
I know you're knee-deep in hassle,
bullish and with a pitch-black soul.
The Boss treated you like the precious flower earlier.
Go home before he regretted it.
To him, I am no other essence
than King Kong himself.
Even though my friends admire my modesty,
I might as well hit back damn good.
Your petty revenge is not happening!
Careful!
My precious sake is wasted!
It's too dangerous in here!
My money!
Money...
This big mouth guy is sure a roly-poly.
I think I fell asleep.
What!?
What's with this guy?
Pops, your feeble strength
belongs to the nursing home.
Asshole!!
While my real strength
was not yet exposed to you.
Finishing blow!!
How about this? Is the taste of my righteous
full-power fist thrust to your liking?
So-so, it at least resembles a gun now.
Now it's my turn.
Please!
Notice board: former principal Honda (rogue),
former vice-principal Sakurai (bandit) (thief)
both dishonourably discharged for self-enrichment on behalf of the city.
Year 1 class B Daigo Yakuda,
year 1 class C Kariya Masataka,
both aforementioned reinstated in school.
This is our best flowering in my whole life.
What a joy!
Gardening teacher,
I truly am happy about this as well.
The commemorative photo is almost here.
Yakuda is not present?
- I'll go fetch him.
- No, you should be here!
Manami, I love you...
Won't refuse even if everyone finds out?
No refusing.
I love you after all.
Yakuda!
But in such a place!
His sleeping face is so cute too!
I wonder, what kind of dream
you might be seeing, Yakuda.
What, 'tis but a dream?
How unfortunate,
it felt so real...
Still, the white snake is a good omen.
Could it be of a prophetic dream?
It somehow made me want to take a piss now.
The restroom is afar,
maybe do it right here?
Wait, don't look!
Otake High School
Yuu!
Listen, what's going on? Yakuda right now
was trying to strangle Manami with a line.
But soon as I noticed, he fled this way.
You should be careful walking alone.
This time he retreated only because I came in.
Wait a minute.
I know Yakuda couldn't have been doing it, you'll see.
You shouldn't, Manami!
Yakuda! Are you here?
He isn't here...
Must have escaped through the window.
Yuu must have misunderstood.
Yakuda is really not a bad person at all.
Even if you say so,
I can't trust this man after what I've seen.
Well, it's fine.
With time, you'll grow believing it.
Instead, how was it?
You Sunday date.
It was fun.
I never regretted going.
I'm sure you'll make a fine couple!
You both know to give and take.
But well, so far I've been taking only.
I also had no chance to give yet.
I get you since our three sizes are almost the same.
Talk to you later then.
Date, huh?
I'm jealous!
Manami.
Hitomi and Keiko!
Is that Ijima over there?
Manami, aren't you afraid
of getting too close with Ijima?
Did she say something?
Like what?
Everyone knows that girl is dating yakuza.
He acts quiet towards Ijima only.
And it seems she is fooled by that.
So we are worried
that you might follow the similar model.
Manami, don't fall for the same bluff.
Yakuza are always what they look like.
What do you want?
Today you told Sera you're virtually her sister.
That you two have nearly the same sizes.
I have just a small favour to ask, so please listen.
I need to take measurements of the sister's body sizes.
What are you doing to my woman?
What's with this guy?
Are we doubles?
He acts quiet towards Ijima only.
And it seems she is fooled by that.
Tatsuya!
He sure have some guts.
Courting a yakuza's woman with a peacock look.
If willing to play with a schoolgirl,
you should get Ministry of Education approval first, Pops.
Yakuzas don't give a shit about it, bastard!
Arrogant brat!
Now you've got me mad!
Tatsuya!
Hey, wait I said!
- Wait, so what do you think about my offer?
- NO!!
Hey. Hey, come on. Hey!
What do I do now?
Fainted before I could do any explanation.
Oh well, at least I can peacefully
take measurements of the sizes now.
Stop it!
If you abuse her, bastard,
I swear, I'll kill you!
You have to stop...
I'm begging you!
You got it all wrong.
I'm just assessing her body sizes.
My beloved woman have sizes similar to your woman's,
and I was planning to gift her a sweater, that's all.
I had no coercion in mind,
but she didn't listen when I said so straight.
Also, Pops, I don't want a burden
of being branded selfish by you.
One's imagination is often deceptive.
You should know by now.
2 months later
He also told me
he quit the gang he belonged to before.
Being defeated by Yakuda,
he saw he should change his life.
Yakuda fought him too?
To fight a yakuza, he surely has to be one big stubborn,
not knowing when to stop.
Apparently, he fought fiercely.
Your class is lucky to have such a bodyguard.
But losing to a high school student
must have been a shock.
How much more will they walk together?
I can't give her my knitted sweater in front of others.
Yakuda was just trying
to protect her from a yakuza!
You can't know.
Maybe he planned to attack her.
What a charming sweater!
Indeed!
Wanna buy it? Manami, didn't you say
you want a sweater of that kind?
Though it's adorable,
I already have 4 white sweaters.
I definitely wanted a different colour this year.
The sweater that Yak-kun was kneading
past the last 2 months was white, precisely.
Pops!
You are exactly the one I needed now.
Got a small favour to ask.
There's a problem with this sweater.
I assume such never happened before,
but can you present it to your girlfriend?
Several days later
My! What a lovely sweater!
A present from boyfriend!
Nice, nice!
When you don't wear it, may I lend it?
It seems Manami greatly fancied
the sweater knitted by Yakuda after all.
However, the Angel remained deaf
to Yak-kun's pleas.