Girl's Friends
He is reading a shōjo manga!
What was that?
Not actually very polite.
Even though I read it,
women totally don't understand me.
Bastard! Yakuda, come out now!
Come out and face me!
Let's just crush his lovely passion then!
Yakuda!
Better come out soon!
Girl's Friends
You! Stop it now!
Here you are, Yakuda!
What the hell are you doing?!
Don't you see there are flowers?
This whole garden is now good for nothing!
You there, who ordered this?
I'll get him crushed!
What happened?
You woke up just yet?
Guess I'm the one you were asking about,
I directed this.
You don't wanna mess with us, the Dracula Team.
Wet your pants, didn't you?
OK then, don't cry if I accidentally kill you!
- Will you ever fuck off!?
- What?
I'm fed the fuck up!
Your fighting is totally
not something to be respected.
Asshole... Get him, people!
Fuck off I said!
Should I kick your ass?
(Shibai Taroka) Episode 2
Otake High School
Fine arts class
Three elements system.
Twas like yesterday!
What happened? Report.
Well, you see...
New special uniform
and band emblem design need your approval.
What's your impression of this model?
You didn't have to go through the trouble
of showing it to me.
I entrusted this whole thing to you.
Then, you fancy it?
By the way, Kariya...
What?
Are you doing fine over here?
You couldn't take part
when the gang fought Dracula.
And when the time came to form a new team,
you were also out of touch.
Nothing to worry about.
Even if I drop out of some action,
don't we still have hundreds of replacements?
Since Kariya says so,
I must obediently submit his command.
One more!
Where is the fine arts club?
Fine arts club?
You see...
This design was drawn by our school's guys,
who are not actually good with pencil you know.
So I thought of drawing the local guys to drawing.
What a remarkable ardour.
You betcha!
Anything for Kariya's reborn team!
Upon defeating the Golden Bat and Dracula,
the team is bound to become legendary!
Fine arts class
Oh my... Gotta piss, gotta piss... Mwahahaha!
What is it?
Did he kiss his own painting?
This is...!
Yours?
I'm sorry!
Did you draw this one?
I didn't!
Then I should meet the guy who did!
It's crazy!
Everything else here is no match to this!
Have something against that drawing?
Did you draw this one?
No, I was drawing Luo Guanzhong.
Yeah... right.
That's just what I thought.
You know, actually, after seeing your art, I was
wondering if you could redraw this symbol mark.
What do you say?
How about fee?
Compensation for materials!
10,000 yen!
Alright!
That's the tough guy I've heard so much about.
I guess he'll make me pay it fully even if I die...
Then in a week,
I'll meet you here about the same time.
Sure!
Lucky. An order for painting.
- Uhm... Back then, weren't you drawing Sera?
- Why you...
You saw it?
Yes!
Really-really saw?
So well I could almost smell her hair!
I see.
A week later
I hope that Yankee draws well enough.
Greetings, Nakamoto-san!
Well isn't it Kiyama?
What a fine place to meet you.
I'm here because I needed to call Kariya out.
But why are you here, Kiyama?
Aren't you a former Dracula renegade?
Yes...
Wasn't that guy a Dracula officer?
Yeah, no doubt he was one.
Dracula eighth leader Nakamoto.
It seems Kariya knew this guy before.
Think he'd become the ninth leader?
Then it's the retiring officer,
what's the point of coming otherwise?
Dracula officer might as well
have come to collect tribute.
Isn't it time for the next term payment?
Yeah, messing with Yakuza is dangerous.
Let's have a word, Kariya.
The bastard told us
something about you, a fishy one.
That you're leaving our team
to create a new, your own team.
You're turning your back on Dracula,
did we get that right?
So what do you say?
Aren't you thinking of breaking the bonds
and overthrowing us with another group?
You're planning to do it with this month's tribute,
that's what we were told. Correct?
Haven't you forget how the founder leader
almost killed you last time?
Don't you really think you're strong enough
to become any worthy group founder yourself?
I won't lose to you, not this time!
What?
Even outnumbered by such bastards!
Aren't you afraid at all?
It's your last chance to apologize!
You're not getting away with it!
Hey, you shouldn't chase him!
It's fine. I can cripple the brat alone.
Where the fuck did you go? Shit...
Where in the world might that guy be?
He's still supposed to pay me 10,000 yen
for painting. I'm worried...
What the hell are you doing here!?
What do you want?
I was waiting for you in the fine arts class.
You were supposed to collect
the symbol mark design for your group today.
Sorry, I got intercepted.
What's this all about?
Have you really asked the guy about it?
No, it's just...
Let me see it too, bro.
Then you'll pay on his behalf.
The hell ya talking about?
Don't you know who we are, damn Yankee?
No, I don't...
We are goddamn Dracula
hereditary leaders may I introduce!
Old man, your breath stinks.
My skin is too delicate for it.
I don't want your gross liquids on it.
Don't you ever dare to come back
intimidating me into not founding the group!
Damn arrogant mongrel!
Sooner of later,
I'd have faced them anyway.
For a man like Kariya,
creating a legend of himself,
this is a necessary step
to becoming the Kanto's number one!
It's either them or us!
It's Yakuda!
What is he doing here...
He defeated all the gangsters alone.
Yakuda, is your strength bound by any limits?
I have your compensation for trouble.
Look, I got it. There.
Australian Outcast Gang
What the!?
No, no, it's splendid.
You don't seem very impressed.
No, it's just a bit too nice.
It didn't look that way.
Rather like trembling with fear.
Did I really make you think so?
It's not yet even close to the end.
The real battle begins from now on!
Otake High School
Hey, Sera!
My, it's Yakuda!
I wanted to give this.
To me?
What might it be?
Wow, and you even ribboned it!
Is that me?
Beautiful!
Did Yakuda draw this himself?
That will be the token of my love.
Today I begin building relationships.
Any woman will melt with such a gesture.
Yakuda, thank you!
I still have a lot of work ahead...
A few days later
Suddenly occupied the home economics classroom...
Yakuda, what whim is on your mind this time?
Isn't Kariya acting strange these days?
Yeah, something is bugging him.
He's like this since the last Dracula officer visit.
It was coming for a while.
Things finally heat up.
Um, Kariya-san...
You see, some gentlemen
are willing to see you by our gateway.
What!?
Who!? What kind of guys?
I couldn't hear their names!
Menacing ones!?
Just a pair of guys in sunglasses looking strong!
So they finally came.
The gang sent their bouncers.
Kariya-san! Kariya-san!
You are not coming along!
Sure...
What happened?
Such a bloodthirst...
I believe Dracula hereditary leaders
are not exactly the merciful type of guys?
Were they all really defeated
by a single high school student?
I'd rather believe the opposite.
So this kid must be incredibly strong!
Hey, cut the defeatism!
This Kariya is not a threat!
It's just a 16yo brat!
He defeated 4 men at once. I don't happen
to know many 16-years-olds of that kind.
- This way, I can't help being tensed.
- Hey, what's the matter?
It's just a pathetic bloke,
and we're Yakuza may I remind!
How do you think,
what kind of bastard is this coward?
I've heard about him in Osaka.
Even if I tell, you'll hardly believe it anyway.
Guess those two are here for me.
The founder leader must be in there.
To get to the founder leader,
I mustn't get stuck with the small fry.
"I love Manami."
I wonder if she'll understand.
This bastard Yakuda...
He's never there when you need him!
It's done!
My hand-made message is completed!
The home economics classroom!
What is wrong with this guy?
Where might Yakuda be now?
Found him!
Come on. Is it jammed again?
Hurts, hurts, hurts!!!
Kariya?
Sorry I didn't see you, are you okay?
I'll be fine! What's more important - gentlemen you
defeated before demand a rematch at the gateway!
No way!
Please deal with them just once more!
Damn bastard...
Asshole, I know you did it intentionally!
There he is!
It's the man, bros!
Is he really a high school student?
It's Yakuda! Why did I have a feeling
it'll happen to be this pest...
Did you want me to kick your asses again?
What...
Back down, back down!
Remember what I told you about this fearless man?
We should withdraw!
I'll go explain to Inamura-san!
We absolutely should not confront him!
Inamura-san. Inamura-san!
I know what a pest this guy can be.
Kariya is okay, but not his bodyguard.
I see. The fact that Kariya
has made some powerful friends
is only natural since he decided
to revolt against me.
Wery well.
I wonder how strong the kid
you're so afraid of really is.
It's time I find it out for myself, on my grounds.
It's cookies!
Baked with excellent precision.
That child is really capable of such deeds...
It smells so good too!
Yakuda is a wellspring of unexpected talents!
Yakuda must be in love!
But can this be...
Don't come closer!
I hate dogs!
What have I done. Such a present ruined!
I'm so sorry, Yakuda.
Leave me alone already!
Yakuda's love message cookie
has been destroyed so brutally.
Even the Angel of Love
declared the situation hopeless.
I have no idea what to do.
Damn...
If I don't hurry up,
Inamura will be defeated by Yakuda instead.
I must be the one to beat Inamura!
While he beats up everyone else.
Otherwise, the legend about me
won't have me in it!
Do you see now
what I told you about this bull?
Inamura-san, don't get deceived by that cute apron
worn by a devil! Please retreat!
Boy, your whole appearance
makes quite a disparate picture.
What do you want, pops?
I'm the Dracula founder, Inamura.
What does it have to do with me?
You seem to have messed up
our precious hereditary leaders.
Those idiots had what was coming to them,
they attacked me on sight!
He is even more dangerous than I heard!
Listen here, boy.
As a man of a certain reputation,
I can't let such an incident slip through fingers.
What's wrong?
Can't even dodge this kind of blunt punch?
The rumours about you are exaggerated!
You interrupted such a splendid view...
Now I'm locked and loaded to fight you!
Wait! This one is my opponent!
Kariya...
Those guys came here
in order to fight me only.
I'll deal with the founder leader myself!
After all, I was the one who started this fire!
But soon this fire returns to you,
burning you out for good.
How do you like the flame
you ignited now, Kariya?
Cut the bullshit! The flame is just enough
for a bastard like you, Inamura!
Sorry then, but this time I'm merciless.
Spare me your excuses.
I'll pay back the borrowed time a hundredfold.
Very well!
Asshole!
I see. You've become much swifter, Kariya.
Holy shit! Inamura's offence
is much more restrained now!
Apparently, even Inamura
has to be cautious against such a guy.
You sure Inamura will be fine?
He should be fine.
A few new face scratches are inevitable.
Kariya...
You dared to turn against me, but your show-off
fighting is not something I can't handle!
I thought I'd need to save that idiot again.
Well, at least I can finally tend
to Manami's cookies.
I have an ill feeling about this...
Now it's fishy...
Damn...
Son of a bitch!
Come back here, you shit!
Come back here!
Shit...
I caught you, so it's my turn now.
Sorry, but the child's play is over.
Think the battle is done?
It's not yet clear enough!
Despite the appearance,
he's a virtuous kid.
That's right!
I hope he'll join our household club.
*Glance*
What's the matter with you now? Has seeing my face
scared you enough to faint on the spot?
Come on.
It's dead! I knew it!
Those cookies were poisoned after all!
What? Yakuda has made poisoned cookies?
Staff room
And he killed the dog with it?
Yes! And I'm sure he is going to skin it next!
I got in this myself, so I don't care what you say.
Just gotta overcome it!
This time no apologies will help you,
hope you understand,
Kariya!
I have to win... this fight.
Yakuda, I'm in this shitty state because of you!
Yakuda!
Hey, Sera.
How can I help?
What is it?
Haven't you come here alone?
Please...
It's bad! Kariya's in trouble!
What might've happened to Kariya?
He was messed up badly!
Won't you go and take a look?
Why should I...
Kariya you say?
Dipshit!
Your speed is in decline already.
This is turning bad...
And I'm also crippled!
He hit it!
You there! Get the guy in the car.
I hope you can handle one half-dead bastard.
Behind! Behind, behind!
It wasn't fine after all.
No wonder this guy posed no challenge at all.
Yakuda...
Stop right there!
Who said you can take him away?
The showdown is over.
Enough already.
So how does it allow you to pick him up?
That's right, I can't let you go whatsoever.
We have our own showdown to settle.
Sorry, not now. Kariya needs treatment, pops.
You'll have to wait until then.
What...
Besides, in my shape, I can fight 200 guys in a row,
easily winning every single one of the bouts, pops.
What!? You brat!
Ryouta...
I'll get help.
Please!
Leave it to me!
Through my limbs, I will finally get an idea
of what kind of man are you.
You better be more of a fighter
than this Kariya pussy!
I hope Inamura won't regret
speaking this way.
Inamura has never heard of Yakuda's past.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have been so eager to fight!
I'm not done yet!
Inamura-san, we should retreat! It's cops!
Shit! You're damn lucky this time!
Yakuda! Are you okay?
Hey, Sera.
You were worried about me, didn't you?
This fella will be fine.
On the other hand, Kariya could use some bandage.
Infirmary
Here. This is fine now.
I'm done, Yakuda.
Yakuda! You denigrated Kariya's name!
What are you talking?
You wouldn't have made it here if not for Yakuda!
This redundant medicine
is nothing to be glad about!
It's because of him my hand is like this!
If not... If not for this handicap,
I might've already become a legend by now!
Infirmary
- Hurts! It hurts so bad!
- There's nothing to yell about.
- Yakuda! Once it restores, you're done for!
- Sit still just for a moment!
I'll kill him!
Osaka, 6 years ago
Year 4 Class C
Naughty boy!
What happened to you?
Are you even alive?
Yo, a schoolboy!
Yeah?
Won't you step away with me for a bit?
Step away towards those guys.
What's the deal with the toddler?
He'll be the one!
My first subject for mugging!
Dumbass, does he look like he is worthy of shit?
Don't you see he's in elementary school at best?
But he is strong enough.
Hey, stop right there!
I said wait, damn brat!
First, you're gonna show this brother
if you're any strong.
Oh, so we have a 4th grader here?
Year 4 Class C
Daigo Yakuda
You don't look like someone I'd like to fight.
Bastard, it was not an offer!
I can't be hanging around here the whole day!
I'm in a hurry.
Even six years ago, when Yakuda was
just an elementary school 4th grader,
Devotion
he was already the tough Yankee he is now.
Even then, after engaging in a fight,
nine high school students
were all crushed in a matter of 5 minutes.
But what about your fate?
Were you in that number as well?
Has my own brother also found himself powerless
along with the small fish?
Once you're acquainted with him,
you'll also feel feeble!
Listen! A legend or whatever else,
it's all the fucking same to me!
- Still, if you...
- Silence!
You just got fooled by the bastard's ugly mug
along with the others.
From what I saw before, he might have some power,
but nothing to be afraid of.
You haven't really seen any of his power yet!
Please hear me out! This terrible legend
still misses an even bloodier ending!
Where may it be?
The sophisticated string figure
the teacher gave me...
On the second thought,
fighting was a bad idea.
What else?
You're a real deal, boy.
Big bro is deeply impressed!
What is it?
I see now you're a polite child.
Why don't we replace foes with toys?
Moron! Do you want to fucking die!?
No, that kid pushed me here.
I'm sowwy!
The string for figures didn't break,
and now I could resume solving it with both hands.
That guy...
It was Yakuda! The boy who rejected my peace
treaty and almost killed me the next moment!
Osawa,
I don't know who kicked your asses back then,
but this ain't enough for one to come into legend.
The legendary part about it is that he almost
killed me when I was a high school student!
Three span bridge.
Tokyo Tower.
Butterfly.
Amazing!
You're so good at it!
Hey, hey, will you teach me that one?
Sure.
I wonder what terrible stuff he really intends
to convey with those string figures.
True indeed!
I should also be wary.
You don't have to worry about it.
What are you trying to say?
I got it! Hey, you think this is good?
You're a quick learner.
It's so strange to see you
being good at such things, Yakuda.
Nothing special. I've been enthusiastic
about string figures ever since the fourth grade.
May it be it was Yakuda's first childhood love?
Don't be foolish.
Why is that?
A few days later
What? Inamura again?
During your fight,
he couldn't protect his group honour.
On the other hand,
it'll prevent future trouble.
Do I really have to steal from him
in plain sight?
I need it to make Inamura
fight Yakuda once again...
Osawa!
Yes?
For how long should we wait? Hurry up!
Sure!
If we get to make Yakuda disengaged enough,
there might be no need for us to flee.
This might be our chance to rewrite the legend.
He arrived!
You! Get out!
We can't finish our fight through the window!
Finish it? You might not like the way
it is bound to end. Very well.
My punches can hit you even in a decent distance.
Haven't you still understood?
Besides, you seem to be
a matter of importance to my affiliates...
So you're just plain bad after all.
Don't ease off after receiving my light jab only!
With such strokes,
you stand no chance against Kariya.
His abilities are disparate to this.
To prove it, I must first even your conditions.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Wha' is it?
What, have I overdid it a little?
Just what do we have here? Yakuza are always
so noble in image, but wearing tattered clothes!
A man is never taken seriously looking like this.
Alright, I'll stitch it up.
What are they thinking? Isn't it clear
such pants were not designed for fighting?
For God's sake, spare me! I'm not one
of those bloody faggots! Please spare me!
You sure this place is fine?
Thanks, man.
Sure... Uh, Kariya-san,
which hospital is the next one?
The second one.
In Kyoto at the same time.
- Got it. See you.
- Hey, Kiyama...
Yes?
About this new team
special operation suit...
Until my injury is healed, and I fight Inamura
once again, you better not show up around.
You'll crush him then, no doubt about it.
I'll wait until the fight,
to see the power passing into other hands.
Besides, I've already decided to leave too
if Kariya-san loses. Have no worries!
Do you see now his true strength
of a goddamn battering ram?
Anyway, we'd better head to the hospital.
There might be a fracture.
There is no... ouch!
Why, isn't it Kariya...
So we can fight on equal terms now, huh?
What do you mean?
There's no point concealing it. The reason
why I lost before was in this stupid handicap.
Which means I have a good reason
not to fight you now.
It implies no fucking reason!
With the same handicap, you've no right to lose!
Why don't we try and see?
Where may this idiot be now?
Now's the best time for them to fight anew
since their injuries provide equal handicap.
When everyone is so busy,
it's the best chance for me.
Hey, wasn't it Manami just now?
Exactly. But what's more important,
was it Yakuda?
It's a paramount matter now!
Infirmary
Ah! It hurts!
Just swallow it.
It'll turn for better soon.
It sounds like treatment,
but Manami's kinda strange.
What will happen to me?
You'll be alright, I tell you.
I'm sorry, actually.
I was also looking the other way.
What cute knees she has too.
It happened so quick.
Sure no one saw you carrying me?
I don't think so.
So Yakuda knocked me out,
but he also rushed me to the infirmary.
Band-aid?
You spared one for me?
At moments like this,
the school nurse is never there.
Say, do you always have
such a band-aid with you?
Yeah, you never know when you get hurt,
better to be prepared.
Yakuda, thank you!
What is this?
It's too cute to use!
With this Yakuda's face... Such an inappropriate
face... He'll never cease to amaze me!
Her shoulders tremble.
Manami is crying!
He hit him!
Looks strong...
Feel that? Hope you understand now.
Didn't you think it would hurt less?
Asshole, do you really hope
to defeat me in this condition?
On my short call, 200 soldiers will make
their way here. Didn't you forget, Kariya!?
Soldiers, subdued by brute force only.
Call them to witness your miserable defeat!
Think they'll remain your subordinates after?
Your bluff won't save you!
The legend of you expires today.
The rest is up to my mercy.
Adieu!
Come to think of it, that injury of Inamura...
Who in the world could...?
Ahchoo goddammit!
I should visit the hospital today.
But first, where can this guy be...
Yakuda's feeling of guilt vented out by itself,
without satisfaction.
Hey, I'm a little broke here.
Lend me some, will ya?
We'll make sure to return it the other day.
Do it quicker, dimwits!
Who threw it!?
Right here. I just lent you a can,
why don't you deposit it for money instead?
Bitch, what's your problem?
You...
Now you'll pay for this!
Let me go I said!
Manami! What's the matter?
Hurry up, hurry!
Though we were rescued,
I can't flee like this.
Get off me, goddammit!
Cool!
All turned out weaklings.
Shame on you, punks!
Amazing! She got rid of them in no time!
Thanks a lot!
I was happy to help,
but by any chance, can you lend me some?
I forgot my wallet it seems.
I was supposed to meet a person here,
but now I can't even return home.
Okay...
Here you go.
Sorry to trouble.
Can you write down your name and address?
Sure!
Say, aren't you from the Otake school?
That is our school, yes.
Then, don't you also
happen to know Yakuda Daigo?
I'm a classmate of his.
Just as I thought.
Guess this band-aid is also Daigo's merit?
Do you know him too?
Ever since I was in Osaka.
Here. My name and address.
Great!
I'll make sure to return every penny!
What a beautiful one.
And she addresses Daigo by his name only.
What kind of relationship they have?
Manami, are you a dummy?
You've lost the money after all.
Why didn't you run away?
What's got into Manami then, I wonder.
Yeah... It's a shame.
No way to return them now.
But luckily it's just 1000 yen.
Hey... Isn't it Yakuda?
That one, over there.
Who'd think you'll transfer into this city school?
I was much surprised.
It's a relief.
It's money!
She forgot no wallet!
Yakuda must be blackmailing her
into robbing other people!
What is this?
For tooth prosthetics. An exact amount.
I feel obliged to do at least this much.
Don't talk nonsense! No need.
Our master insisted on sending this to you.
Besides, if not for Daigo,
who knows where two of us would've been now.
Let us just thank you once more.
I was fine with simply doing it for you.
Though I won that fight,
it would be selfish to accept.
I can't take it.
Daigo...
What is this wound?
Were you fighting somebody again?
Not at all!
Just tripped over.
Scratched when falling, huh?
Lemme see.
Careful, Daigo!
Look! How shameless!
Peeping under her skirt in public!
Wait... Whatever you're up to, stop!
I'm totally fine, Daigo! Come on, Daigo!
You'll be less embarrassed here. Your stockings
won't let me treat the wound, take it off.
It hurts! Can you be more gentle?
Hurts! Come on!
Incredible boldness!
And so suddenly!
It's good, isn't it?
Yakuda already has a girlfriend.
Still...
Oh no! What was I thinking, idiot!
- I hate everyone!
- Was it because of the money lost,
- or because of Yakuda's girlfriend,
- What do I do?
- Manami's heart was shaking wildly.
- I'm an idiot!
In any case, Manami was restless.
The following day
Hey, hey, Manami, are you listening?
Hope you understand now
you shouldn't hang out with Yakuda.
That's right! You'll only get yourself messed
like that woman.
But I wonder why would such a beauty
agree to become Yakuda's woman.
It's only possible if she was forced
to become his woman!
Who was forced
to become whose woman you say?
Good afternoon!
Can't help noticing
your company is so superstitious.
Here!
Who'd have thought that was the case!
People often get him wrong. Yesterday he simply
gave me the same band-aid as the one you have.
See?
Although, at first, I also thought he had something
lewd in mind, especially with this mini.
I must have blushed!
So far, Daigo and I are just friends,
connected by unrequited love.
It seems Daigo
doesn't think of us as a duo at all.
What's the long face?
Let's drink!
You catch up with me too!
Sure you'll be fine?
I can't stand it without drinking.
He is so insensitive to women.
Unbelievable... Did he dump you?
I just became resigned to loving him.
And mayhaps you also do?
Me?
Impossible!
Are you sure you will be okay?
I'm phine, hic!
I won't get drunk
on just a few mugs of beer!
Can't we do better than that?
Please! You reek of alcohol!
What's wrong?
Not feeling well after all?
We might need some help.
Go!
It's serious!
We'll finally repay you for yesterday.
This time we took trouble to greet you well.
What a pity it's not gonna happen.
Retreat now,
before I doubled your humiliation.
What!?
Your intimidation won't help!
Out of my way!
Team, about time we call for backup!
Understood! Just you wait, ass!
Everyone!
That bitch is here again!
Who'd think!
Our best forces are already here?
Those guys are at your service!
Don't you dare to run, cunt!
She is making a run for it! Hurry up!
Run, run!
She's not getting away!
Yakuda!
A pansy in such a place. :)
Who the fuck...
I am... Now... Yes, yes... Now... Not looking.
Cornered now.
Just you wait. We're to have a lotta fun
with you now. Like this!
That cheeky babe...
Enough already. Stop it.
Okay, Aokura-san!
Be reasonable. The art of hunting
is in preserving the prey's body intact.
Especially when it's just one woman.
Why don't we get along instead, sis?
With you!?
I don't mind the refuse.
In fact, it's even better.
Nice, nice! Totally nice!
A man and a woman become one while doing it!
It's SEX!~
You must've tried it.
But how many times in public?
For me, sex with you is... Eh?
It's...
How'd you end up in such a place?
Daigo!
Shit...
Are you okay?
Fucker!
Whaddya wahn?
Be careful, this one is strong.
Asshole, you'll regret messing up with Aokura!
I don't know no Aokura.
Asshole!
Aokura-san defeated!?
It's bullshit! I don't believe it!
It's my fault, Daigo.
An eye for an eye.
The snowball of revenge
keeps engendering new fights.
Don't blame yourself.
If I hadn't come, the circle'd become even worse.
By the way, how did you know?
A passing birdie directed me here.
She did? Say, Daigo,
Sera Manami - what kind of girl is she?
Oh my... How do you know her?
Doesn't matter.
But isn't she a cute girl?
I think she's your type of girl.
Mind giving her a chance?
- Don't be silly.
- Where are you going?
- To piss!
Here you are, finally!
Huh, wasn't Yakuda with you?
Away for a moment.
The flower of love is just starting to bloom.
This won't be a legend of a fighter,
but a new kind of legend about a true love.
And I can't think of a better hero
for one than you, Daigo.
I friggin pissed my clothes!
I zipped the foreskin! Again!
Shouldn't have been pissing here!