Your wife's cheating on you,
and you're gonna do nothing about it?
You should just finish with her,
quickly and decisively!
All right...
Not that kind of quick finish.
Quickshot Theater
Written by Iwatani Tenho
Anime: Quickshot Theater!
Mom, have you seen my school uniform?
I sent it for cleaning.
What's wrong?
It's summer vacation, isn't it?
I need to wear it even when I go out on holidays. It's the school rules.
It seems she needs her uniform
even during vacation, dear.
Why?
Quickshot Family
Quickshot Family!
Part 2.
Masao, are you awake?
Dad, what are you doing
at this time of night?
I'm reading a book.
Then how about you read it in your room?!
Part 3.
Younger
Sister
RENTAL DVDs
<ADULT SECTION>
College
Coeds
RENTAL DVDs
<ADULT SECTION>
Masturbation
College
Coeds
RENTAL DVDs
<ADULT SECTION>
Masturbation
RENTAL DVDs
<ADULT SECTION>
Masturbation
College
Coeds
Younger
Sister
Th-That's my daughter...
Hold on.
What if it's someone else,
even if they look alike?
Yoko.
Do you know Kashiwagi Mayako?
I do. She's a JAV actress, right?
People at school often say we look alike.
Once I realized it wasn't her,
it wasn't fun anymore.
Part 4.
Ah, Mom? I'm staying over
at my friend's house today.
Again?
We need to punish her a little.
Dear, how did you punish her?
Phew...
I'm wearing her panties right now.
Part 5.
Have you seen my glasses?
You've forgotten them somewhere again?
After eating my lunch,
I was watching TV under the kotatsu...
Ah, I know.
Found them!
Part 6.
Can you go wake up your dad?
Sure!
Daddy! Wake up!
Mom! Something's happened!
Dad's gone, and all that's left is his willy!
Huh?!
Kyaa!
What are
you doing
there?
Huh?
Just reading
the paper.
Why?
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
An incident? I'm on lunch break!
I'll send someone there when I'm done.
A woman's corpse?!
An 80-year-old grandma?
Quickshot Police
Quickshot Police!
Part 2.
So? Seen any movement?
Nothing so far.
The neighbor isn't home?
Right.
Let me see.
No, sir.
Part 3.
MORGUE
It's my daughter.
That can't be right.
Want me to call him my son
after he's turned into a woman?
Part 4!
Set the hostage free!
I'll be your hostage in her place!
That woman, Yoshii Megumi-san,
is supposed to have an operation tomorrow.
Don't try to trick me
with that bullshit, you nitwit!
She has an appointment for breast enhancement surgery at ten!
Why would I need that, you nitwit?!
Part 5!
Dammit, we let her escape?
It's still warm.
Aluminum Foil
Probably not enough for foil steaming.
Part 6!
Try sketching the face
of the robber now.
Did you see his face?
Hm... Still not quite right.
No, I think he had somewhat thicker lips.
And his eyes... make them narrower.
Yes, like that.
Ah, and make the nose more piggish.
Right...
Was he wearing pantyhose on his head?
Yeah, he was!
Leave me
alone!
Your panties
are wedged
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
What?
May we please pee here?
Of course not!
This is my front garden!
May we please pee here?
Sure, go ahead.
Fiddlesticks!
Quickshot on Third Street
Quickshot on Third Street!
Part 2.
Part 3.
Tonoko, Fujito.
Bus
All right!
Part 4.
I had an unobstructed view of that exhibitionist's "instrument"!
What was it like?
It was abnormally large
and covered in warts.
It's my husband.
Part 5.
Is that where you fell from?
Hey, the lady drying her underwear
on the second floor!
Don't drop your weird things on the street!
Part 6.
Walking around with a wife
who looks like my daughter is awesome!
Walking around with a daughter
who looks like my wife is abominable!
Huh?
There!
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
Who the hell made this tea?!
It's full of eyelashes and nose hair!
Ah...
S-So sorry!
Goddammit!
Who the hell made this tea?
There's pubic hair in it!
Goddammit.
Quickshot Company
Quickshot Company!
Part 2.
Tch. It's from work.
Huh? The section chief isn't there?
Then who's calling?
No, not really. Nothing.
Huh?
Really?
I-I see.
Give me an hour, then.
No, 30 minutes.
I'm in Shinjuku.
It's a woman.
Part 3.
What do you think?
What the hell is this?!
Even an elementary school student would...
Power harassment.
...have a bigger chest.
Now that's sexual harassment!
Part 4.
That's a very good idea.
It's your idea.
When working overtime alone,
you did it too, didn't you?
Part 5!
Please take this to my desk.
I need to take a jog to the top floor.
It seems Manager Tanaka has been to 30 marriage meetings, all unsuccessful,
yet he hasn't lost his spirit!
Yeah, he's going strong.
Manager Tanaka!
Doctor,
please
examine me
already!
Isn't that
what I'm
doing now?
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
Woohoo!
Your boobs are huge!
What size are they?
Reception
Are they the real thing or silicone?
Yamamoto-san!
The Yamamoto-san who's here for phimosis surgery is next!
Examining
Room
Quickshot Hospital
Quickshot Hospital!
Part 2.
Your wife is on the cusp
of life and death right now.
We need something
to pull her soul our way.
All right...
Noriko!
Look, it's your favorite food.
Grab it!
Noriko!
There's only death that way!
Come back!
Come, come.
Part 3.
Please don't do it in my hospital room.
Part 4!
It's okay now.
She'll regain consciousness in a few hours.
Is that so?
That's a relief.
Can the two of us be alone
for a few minutes?
Yes. Of course.
You meant me?!
Yes.
Part 5.
I can't remember. I just can't!
Get over it already.
No, sister, you don't understand the pain
of not being able to remember!
I think he lost his memory.
He can't remember the last time he had sex.
Since it was probably more than ten years ago, no wonder!
Doctor,
please
examine me
already!
Didn't I say
that I'm already
doing it?
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
Carrot.
Corn.
Red pepper.
You can even tell the color?
Quickshot Couple
Quickshot Couple!
Part 2!
I'm sorry. I was too quick.
I see. Boys care a great deal about that, right?
Maybe I should praise him now
to make it easier on him.
Tanaka-kun, you were very good.
With pulling out the tissues just now.
Swish! Swish!
Part 3.
You're an animal!
Part 4.
There are women who shriek "Cute!"
about anything they see.
I really hate that.
I must be careful.
In
His
Room
In
His
Room
In
His
Room
In
His
Room
In
His
Room
In
His
Room
Ah, cu—
Got anything gruesome?
Part 5.
Pasta
His is just the right thickness
for a bundle of pasta.
Yeah!
At your
service!
I'll serve you!
Quickshot Theater
Anime...
Quickshot Theater!
Stare...
Quickshot Train
Quickshot Train!
Part 2.
Hey, lady.
I want to molest you.
Oh... Well...
Could you pass it on to that girl?
Part 3.
Please.
I'll sit there, I think.
Part 4.
Oh... No-no-no-no!
Part 5.
Are you in that much of a hurry
to get rid of me?!
Boss,
your chest
hair...
Huh.
Oh yeah.
You like
it?
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
Hanzo!
Sir?
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
sec-
onds
or
less
Hanzo...
Sir?
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
1.5
sec-
onds
if
he's
fast
You're quicker to come
while I'm doing this.
Quickshot Historical Drama
Quickshot Historical Drama!
Part 2.
If you can't pay back your debt,
I'll have to take something from you.
Then, t-take my daughter.
What?
We need to make another
before he changes his mind!
Part 3.
There you are!
Oh? It looks like she can play
with me as an equal now.
There you are!
It looks like eight years of my training
have come to fruition.
You're already 16, after all.
I feel so weird!
Part 4!
Okay, then I'll be "it" in the next round.
Yay!
Is everyone ready?
Not yet!
Ready now!
All right...
I almost blew my cover!
Part 5!
Kaede, what are you playing at?
Did you call, my lord?
Huh? You're over there?
Has this hole always been here?
Oh jeez!
Part 6!
It looks just like a woman's receptacle.
Now I really wanna do it!
Oh no, oh no.
What am I thinking?
If I hold it
for too long,
I'll get
cystitis
Fourth
Quickshotmaru
Quickshot Theater
Anime: Quickshot Theater.
A nice smell on a crowded train
A gentle push from behind
I was so shocked I felt like I was falling apart
But when I turned around, I saw a fat, bearded old man
Groping and rubbing, quickshot
Ha! Quickshot
A sexy office lady asked me
What I was planning to do tonight
I replied with a smile, "Nothing!"
So she asked, "Would you please work overtime?"
Hey! Groping and rubbing, quickshot
Ha! Quickshot
She texted me to say
That she had cleaned her room
I was so happy, but when I got there
She'd only lined up her secret sex toys
Groping and rubbing, quickshot
Ha! Quickshot
In an erotic magazine, I use my fingers to hide
The bras and panties of the girls in bikinis
I fantasize and get excited
Stop!
But when I raise my eyes, my mom is there
What's that?
Groping and rubbing, quickshot
Ha! Quickshot
Ha! Ha! Quickshot!
The end!
The End
Translation & Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair,
Paul Germoni, Uchuu
anonymous