Feature-length animated film commemorating 60 years since the end of the war
It happened more than 60 years ago,
when I was trying to survive in the depths of grief
Fishing Rods Workshop
Original Work
Ebina Kayoko
Fishing Rods Workshop
after losing my parents,
my many brothers, and my friends.
Narration
Yoshinaga Sayuri
Stop it, Kisaburo.
You're just lying to scare me, right?
The fabric and pattern are high quality.
It's a splendid kimono.
It's a memento of my mother.
All I want is for the world to become a place
where children can live freely and peacefully.
Ki-Kisaburo?
Kayoko's voice
Ueto Aya
Kayoko?
I wanted to see you, Kisaburo!
Kicchan!
Don't die, Kisaburo!
The lotus flower blooms quietly
Kisaburo!
"Renka"
(Lotus Flower)
Hayashi Asuka
Toshiba EMI
Lyrics
Music
Ebina Kayoko - Tanimura Shinji
Tanimura Shinji
The meaning of the pale pink of this flower
Look, you've got so much snow on you.
I just bought it from that black market.
I want to become a singing wind
It's still warm.
Eating gives you energy to move on.
So eat while it's still hot. Here you go.
It's warm!
Why did I even come home?!
What was I fighting for?
Here.
Thank you.
I won't let go of my dream either!
I won't give up on it.
A wish for peace
we want to convey to you.
Tomorrow Will Be Better!
~ Half a Sweet Potato ~