Thank you very much to everyone
who is going to watch this movie now.
This is me from sixty years ago,
a really cute Kayo-chan.
She puts the current me to shame.
This movie...
Its main point is to depict parental love,
but it will also tell you about the cruelty
and wastefulness of war.
I hope there will never be a war again.
In the last war, I lost my parents, my siblings, and my grandmother: six people in all.
I became a war orphan.
But even as an orphan, I lived on with all I had.
I think it was the love of my parents
and my siblings that allowed me to do that.
In tough times, sad times, and painful times,
I always remembered my parents.
"You're a cheerful, resilient,
and strong girl, so you'll be fine."
These reassuring words of my mother
would come back to me.
I also remember my youngest brother calling out to me "Sis, sis!"
And so, the bad things in life
didn't seem so bad anymore.
"Let's live a bright, lively, and energetic life, smiling."
Those words from my mother always reassured me.
I think a parent's love is a precious thing.
And if watching this film makes you think,
"It's incredible how strong children can be,"
that'd make me so, so happy.
War is an infinitely foolish, cruel, and wasteful enterprise. That's what I wanted to convey.
Please watch it, everyone.