This film depicts the love of parents...
Feature-length animated film commemorating
60 years since the end of the war
Tomorrow Will Be Better!
~ Half a Sweet Potato ~
Kayoko's voice
Ueto Aya
and the brutality and wastefulness of war,
Original Work
Ebina Kayoko
in the hope that wars will never happen again.
I won't let go of my dream either!
I won't give up on it.
Original Work
Ebina Kayoko
Suddenly, the flames engulfed everyone.
Kayoko's voice
Ueto Aya
You're lying just to scare me, right?
It's warm!
Feature-length animated film commemorating
60 years since the end of the war
Tomorrow Will Be Better!
~ Half a Sweet Potato ~
I won't let go of my dream either!
I won't give up on it.