We welcome the cast and staff.
~ Half a Sweet Potato ~
Tomorrow Will Be Better!
Stage greeting at the premiere
March 7, 2005, Hibiya Public Hall
Please give them a big round of applause!
First, the original author of this work.
Please welcome Ebina Kayoko-san!
Original Work
Ebina Kayoko
I think she played her role well and beautifully with her voice,
making Kayoko into a really believable character.
Kayo-chan, voiced by her,
is really cute and loveable.
She is adorable.
I'd like the young people
to know about the destructive
March 10th air raid too.
I'm glad I could do it through media,
so I'm most grateful to be able
to participate in the creation of this.
Well, I voiced Kayoko-san. I am Ueto Aya.
Voice of Nakane Kayoko
Ueto Aya
Well, this is the second time
I've been given such a major role.
I tried my best to express
Kayoko's soft and gentle voice.
And well, I strove for that effect,
when you're sucked straight into the screen.
And I hope you won't find
the pace of this film uneven.
When I looked at the finished product, I found myself
criticizing my acting quite a lot. It was stressful.
And you thought so too. Right? Right? Yes.
So, this was Kayoko.
Well, before I actually looked into
Half a Sweet Potato, what it's about...
Theme song lyrics and music
Tanimura Shinji
I met with Ebina-san
and her daughter Yasuha-chan.
And it made me realize it's about enduring hardships with a pure heart.
So I tried to match that theme as best I could.
So I wrote this music with the poem Ebina's mother wrote in mind.
Before watching this movie, when I learned I was going to sing the theme song, I hesitated a lot.
Theme song performance
Hayashi Asuka
I wondered, "What feelings should I put into it?
How do I go about it?"
I've had my grandma tell me
a lot of stories about the war.
Also, before this, I watched
the film Who's Left Behind.
After all, I've been watching that film
at home since I was little.
So I've watched it once more, diligently,
to see if there was something I'd missed.
Because no matter how many times I watch it
or how many times I listen to it,
it really touches my heart, and I can't stop crying.
Chairman of the Production Committee
Miyake Kunihide
Hello, everyone. My name is Miyake, and I am the chairman of the Production Committee.
I'm not really a big shot in the movie industry,
but Ayabe from Route Pictures, far in the back, has been my friend for many years.
It was around October 2003 when he said
he definitely wanted to adapt
Half a Sweet Potato into a movie.
So the president was very invested in it.
After all, if we don't release it now, the next anniversary will be in ten years—the 70th one.
And there'd be very few people who'd actually lived through it.
We realized this is our last chance to express our respect. I felt that too, so we all worked hard.
And I'm glad to have worked on this.
Yes, thank you very much. And I really think that everyone's thoughts are with Ebina-san today.
Chief Director
Nakada Shinichi
I hope everyone enjoys it today.
That would make me really happy. Thank you.
This movie, or rather the original work, moved
the 2.5 million people who read it, not just us.
Executive Producer
Ayabe Masanori
So we wanted even more people to learn
about this story. This was what motivated us.
And now, today, please enjoy this premier showing of Tomorrow Will Be Better.
Thank you very much.
What did you think of the film?
When I first watched it,
I felt relieved.
Even though, in a way, it made me relive once again all those painful, grueling experiences.
But it also made me glad I'm alive.
I survived to fight another day.
It reinforced my belief that you only live once,
and I'm really glad to be alive right now.
I also have a big brother
who is just two years older than me.
What did playing Kayoko feel like?
And well, while listening to this anime's voices...
While watching this anime, I couldn't help comparing Kisaburo to my real-life older brother.
At first, I just looked at the screen for a moment
and almost burst into tears.
But soon I got used to how it looks,
to watching it, and to the voices in it.
I think this story is really about family love,
which is the most important thing ever.
And in that regard, I think it's best for as many people as possible to see it,
and maybe start cherishing family love more.
That would make me very happy.
That's how I felt about this movie.
We really wanted to convey Ebina-san's feelings
as a Great Tokyo Air Raid survivor.
Message to Everyone
Tokyo was no more,
but she didn't give in to despair, and she also tried to inspire others not to lose heart.
I'm sure you'll also feel that way
after you've watched it.
As a storyteller, I would like as many people as possible to watch it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
So as we celebrate the screening of the movie today,
we'd like to present the staff with some gifts.
Please welcome the Hayashiya family!
On this day, the entire Hayashiya clan came to congratulate them.
Please accept these flowers.
Thank you very much!
Photo Session
Yes, and that concludes today's stage greeting from the staff!
A round of applause, please! Thank you!