We live peacefully and trouble-free
under this shining sky.
But even at this very moment,
countless wars are being waged across the Earth.
Many children lose their fathers and mothers,
siblings and friends.
They are forced to live in sadness.
More than 60 years ago,
Japan was nowhere near as prosperous as it is now.
Still, the grownups were working
with all their might,
and the children were playing
and learning enthusiastically.
Still, the black shadow of war
was creeping up quietly, even on such simple lives.
Tomorrow Will Be Better!
~ Half a Sweet Potato ~
Numazu, Navy Ministry Official Residence
March 10th, 1945
Dad, Mom, thanks for writing me a letter!
I'm also keeping my chin up.
It's been five months already
since I evacuated to Numazu.
Mt. Kanukiyama's all dressed up for winter now.
The other day, we trained with naginatas at school.
I'm not good at exercising.
But the naginata is the only weapon I'm good with.
In case the enemy manages
to land in mainland Japan,
Nakane!
this will be our only way to repel them,
so everyone is working hard.
Then there are field trips every other day
for physical training.
Whenever I pass by the Yanagihara Shrine,
I'm reminded of the Gentoku-Inari temple fair at the foot
of the Sannohashi Bridge in Honjo, Tatekawa.
Okay, there you go.
Not bad. It's beautiful, Kayoko!
Seriously?
Sure. It's a yukata, after all.
That doesn't count, coming from Dad.
Here you go.
Your purse. I'll put it in here.
Thanks, Mom.
I'm off!
Take care!
I know!
Dammit!
Too bad, but you have to knock the target off the shelf.
Hey!
Kisaburo!
Looking at ground cherries?
Yeah. Which one should I choose?
How much did you get from Mom?
Let me...
And...
Five sen!
I see... Five sen, and that's it, huh?
Well, it'll do!
Ah... Kisaburo!
For a ground cherry,
two sen is enough.
I'll borrow the rest.
Kisaburo!
I'll bring you something good, you'll see!
Stupid, stupid Kisaburo!
Kayoko, what's wrong?
Takejiro, Tadakichi!
Wh-What? What's wrong, Kayoko?
It's Kisaburo... Kisaburo!
Tsk. Why won't it fall if I hit it?
Is there some device holding it?
Hey kid, do you know where you
should be aiming at with such a big toy?
Where should I be aiming?
Try to aim for the upper part of the target.
Kisaburo...
Kisaburo's trying to win that doll for Kayoko.
That guy has his good sides too.
This time I'll knock it off for sure!
Good luck, Kisaburo!
Kayoko?
Leave it to me.
Oh no...
Come on, you!
Ah! Kisaburo!
What'd I tell you?
Kayo-chan!
Auntie?
Shizue, we gotta hurry!
B-29s are incoming!
Okay.
Kayo-chan, hurry up!
Okay!
It's at Kanukiyama! Don't get lost!
They're here!
Where are they going?
From the direction,
probably Yokohama or Tokyo.
Dad, Mom...
Fishing Rods Workshop
Dad! Mom!
Quick!
Hurry up, everyone!
Hey, is everyone there?
Quick! Quick!
We're coming!
Kisaburo, Chuwa Elementary!
Got it!
Mom!
C'mon, hurry!
I can't abandon this house!
Mother!
Yoshi-san, run away without me.
D-Don't dawdle!
The fire will engulf this place soon!
Dad... Mom!
Hey, there are more!
That's one hell of an air raid!
Will Tokyo survive it?
God, please, please keep everyone safe.
Quick, quick!
I know!
Kayo-chan, don't worry.
I'm sure everyone is safe.
Numazu
Shizue! Shizue!
Yes?
Since that day, Kayo-chan has been climbing
Mt. Kanukiyama every day to look at the Tokyo sky.
Kayo-chan.
Kisaburo!
Kayoko...
Kayoko!
You're alive! Thank God!
I'm so glad, Kisaburo!
Kisaburo, where's Dad and Mom,
and everyone else?
Kisaburo?
Dad, Mom, and the others...
They all... all...
Died.
Dad!
Mom!
It all happened in a flash.
Suddenly, the flames engulfed everyone.
Stop it, Kisaburo.
You're lying just to scare me, right?
You're a cheerful and likeable girl,
so you'll be okay.
Kayoko!
Sister!
Everyone... Everyone...
Kisaburo...
Listen, Kayoko, you'll have to live
with Auntie Shizue for a while longer.
What about you?
I'm going back to Tokyo for now.
Then I'll come with you!
You can't! Who knows if Tokyo
will get hit by another air raid.
No way! I wanna go with you!
Kayoko, listen, we're on our own now, okay?
No Dad, no Mom, no other brothers.
If I let anything at all happen to you as well...
B-But...
Calm down. I promise I'll come for you one day.
Kisaburo...
Kayoko, listen to Auntie and be well.
Kisaburo!
Kayoko?
Kayoko...
Kisaburo...
When the capital city of Tokyo was hit
by the Great Tokyo Air Raid on March 10th, 1945,
about 40% of the city was destroyed.
Over 120,000 people lost their lives.
One million people became refugees.
In the midst of this scorched earth,
people welcomed the end of the war on August 15.
Nakano Station, Tokyo
Kisaburo, how are you?
Since our last meeting, I moved to Anamizu
in Ishikawa Prefecture together with Auntie Shizue.
The people at Anamizu are very welcoming,
and I had a good time living here.
But after discussing it with Aunt Shizue and
Aunt Kazue, I've decided to go back to Tokyo.
I look forward to seeing you again.
Are you on your own?
Come.
I'm sorry.
I hardly have anything to eat, even for myself.
I'm sorry. I have to go now.
It's here!
Ozawa
Kisaburo, I'm home!
Kayoko?
Kayoko? Kayoko!
Yuri-chan, long time no see.
You're late, aren't you?
Shizue's telegram said
you'd come during the day.
My train was late.
I also got a little lost in Nakano.
Um... Where's Kisaburo?
Kisaburo left us.
It's been about a week already.
No way... But I wrote him a postcard
and said to wait until I come!
Your big brother got into
a big fight with Mom! And then...
Yuriko!
Don't talk unless you're asked!
So... Where did he go?
He just left without telling me anything.
I wouldn't know.
Well, Kisaburo can take care of himself,
but Shizue asked me to look after you.
You'll live with us for the time being.
But you know... It's the times.
We're living a tough life, barely scraping by.
You're gonna have to work too.
Yes. I'll make sure to make myself useful.
Thanks for having me!
Kayoko is gonna stay with us! Yay!
Let's not waste any time
and start preparing for dinner, then.
Okay.
I'll help too!
Ready.
Welcome back!
Oh?
Kayo-chan, you're here?
Yes, I'll be living with you from today on.
Sure, sure.
Did you conclude the deal?
Yeah, we sold it for a high price, and the place is nice too, so the other party was happy.
I see.
Yuriko, a snack for you.
Wow! Sweet potato snacks!
Hey, Kayoko!
That's quite unnecessary, Yuriko.
You can eat them all yourself.
We'll have dinner soon.
That's more than enough for Kayoko.
Thank you, Yuri-chan.
I'm already full.
Can I have another bowl?
There's no more!
Thank you for the meal!
It was tasty.
What's tasty about it?
Are you being funny?
Just a couple of rice grains
on chopped vegetable leaves.
How could that be tasty?
I'm sorry.
In the shaded wood, among the beech trees boughs,
things stir and rustle and murmur.
The flames flicker, the glow dances round colored forms, round foil and stone.
It is the gypsies who throng there
with flashing eyes and waving hair,
Kisaburo.
I am now living with our aunt at Nakano.
suckled alongside the sacred Nile,
bronzed by Spain's southern heat.
I'm going to school too.
But...
I'm always starving.
Auntie doesn't even give me lunch.
What are you writing, Kayoko?
A letter to Kisaburo.
Did you finally find him?
But when I write these,
I feel like I'll be able to meet him sooner.
This girl isn't right in the head.
Who's gonna write a letter
they'll never be able to send?
Welcome back, Dad!
Welcome back.
Yeah.
That's right!
Kayo-chan, you know Gen-san,
who used to live near your father's shop, right?
Yes, from the Sumiya family.
Yeah.
I ran into him on the train on my way home.
Gen-san said he's met Kisaburo.
Here.
It seems he was wandering
around the black market in Asakusa.
He was?
Uncle, where in Asakusa?
I think... I think he said it was the black market
behind Hyotan Pond.
I'm going there right now!
Kayo-chan?
Kayoko, once you're done here,
start preparing dinner.
Kisaburo...
Would you like a flower?
Flower, anyone?
Hey, Georgie!
Let's go-go!
Get back here, you brats!
You're not getting away!
Stop, you!
Come on, come close, it's cheap!
Our goods are the cheapest!
Just try and compare us to others!
Hey, mister! How about some chocolates
as a gift for your child?
Only 80 yen for two cans! It's a steal!
Kicchan!
What's wrong, Noboru?
I-It's the union guys!
What?
Here today?
You punks keep changing places every day.
You've got some nerve, you pricks!
What makes you think
you can do business on others' turf?
We do business wherever!
What's it to you?!
That's not how we do things
around here, you see.
Wanna come and have a talk with us?
Kicchan!
It'll be fine, don't worry.
Come!
Come on, start walking!
Move it, you brat!
Hurry up!
What's your problem?
Shut up and walk!
What's that? They're just a bunch of kids!
Do you guys have parents?
It doesn't matter.
We all were orphaned by the March air raid!
I see.
If you brats wanna do business in this ward, you'll sell the union's goods and give us our cut. Thirty percent.
Th-Thirty percent now?!
That's ridiculous...
That's how all the groups in the city operate.
Have you heard?
The new era of freedom and peace starts now.
You guys can also start making great profits with us and grow up into great adults, right?
Great adults?
Are you kidding me?!
What kind of great adult is that?!
What the fuck?!
It's all your fault. Grown-ups selfishly
started a war, then selfishly lost it!
We didn't choose to become war orphans!
What was that?!
You fucking stuck-up punk!
Now it's our turn to do things the way we want!
We're not gonna listen to you!
You fuckhead, I'll show you how to...
But you see, I can't make
an exception for you alone.
Wait for me!
Shimamoto!
Tacchan!
Oh, I see...
Shimamoto, so these kids
were following your command?
It's not all that outrageous.
Well, I suppose I'm the one
who stands in for their parents.
Boss, will you let them go home
after hearing me out?
What?!
Very well.
I also thought you and I need
to have a talk. A long one.
Kisaburo, take everyone and get out of here.
But...
Forget about me, hurry up!
Will Tacchan be okay?
This place isn't safe either, is it?
After they're done with Tacchan,
they'll come here, and...
Quit shivering over everything!
Aren't you men?!
That's right! Tacchan is strong,
so he'll make short work of those yakuza!
Right, Kicchan?
Yeah, that's true.
Tacchan!
Hey!
Thank God!
They didn't hurt you?
Hey guys, don't worry anymore.
I've reached an agreement with the union.
We can trade the same way we did before.
Really?
Nice!
See, people?
Tacchan had us covered.
You didn't have to worry.
Right, right!
Tacchan...
Kisaburo, can we talk?
I made a deal with them.
A deal?
If I leave, they promised
to leave everyone alone.
So I guess we'll have to part ways for a while.
Tacchan?
I used to be with the union too.
But their methods were too forceful and dirty.
I got fed up with it and fled the union.
They've been gunning for me ever since.
So...
If I stay here with you any longer,
you'll all get caught in the crossfire.
But we all depend on you!
Without you around, we'll all be lost!
Besides, I have no way
to procure goods like you do!
What are we gonna be selling
on the black market, then?
Sell your own products.
Something the other stores don't have.
Our own products?
Kisaburo, take care of everyone for me.
Tacchan...
I'm home.
Did you see Kisaburo?
No, I couldn't find him.
I see. You're late, so there's no dinner for you.
Okay.
Kisaburo...
Huh? Shop for produce?
Yeah. I've had this splitting headache since morning. I can't even stand up!
Take the backpack over there.
There are some items in there. Ask around if anyone would like to exchange them for rice or vegetables.
Can you do it?
Excuse me?
Yes?
Um...
I just wanted to ask if you maybe
have some rice or vegetables to spare?
No can do.
I wish I could help you,
but we're just as strapped for food.
Is that so?
Excuse me!
Yes?
Um, do you have some...
I'm tired.
How about I help you?
Thanks, sweetie!
It's nothing.
No, really, you saved me there! Thank you.
No, I should be thanking you!
You even treated me to such a delicacy!
Did you come here to shop for produce?
Ah... Yes.
Show me what you got there.
Okay.
Oh, that's quite an impressive item!
The fabric and pattern are high quality.
It's a splendid kimono.
It's a memento of my mother.
It must be important to you.
Are you sure you want to sell it?
Yes.
And you need rice and vegetables for it, right?
Here you go.
I'd give you a lot more for this
if we had more to spare.
No, it's all right.
Thank you very much.
That kimono was my mom's favorite.
Why did Auntie sell it?
But thanks to that kimono...
Thank you, Mom.
It's a crackdown!
Run!
Move it!
Hurry up!
Don't push!
Please don't take it away!
If you take this away, you'll be condemning
a family of five to starve!
The government doesn't give us any food
and only increases the intensity of crackdowns!
Are you telling us to starve to death?!
This way!
E-Excuse me?
Don't just dilly-dally! Run!
Ah, wait!
Stop!
These damn brats are fast!
They're not here!
How about there?
Nothing here.
Dammit, where'd they go?
Where could they be?
We lost them somehow.
Um...
What?
No, thank you very much.
You went to buy food?
Yes.
Same here.
What's wrong?
Damn it!
They're crushed!
Eggs?
Out here, people have to bust their asses
just to scrape together enough food to survive!
And they're cracking down on them?!
These cops are demons!
Th-They'll see you!
Um...
I don't have any eggs, but I could share
some rice or vegetables with you.
It was for Mitsue...
My little sister.
She was hit in the March air raid.
She's been bedridden ever since.
We had a doctor check her out, and he said
she needs to eat something nutritious.
Um...
Thanks, but...
I have enough rice and vegetables here.
How old is your little sister?
Probably a year or two older than you.
I see.
I hope she gets well soon.
Yeah.
It's just the times.
You'd better watch your step too.
Bye.
Thank you!
So, who was that boy?
I didn't know him.
But he was very kind to me.
Yummy!
That's true. I don't remember
the last time I've eaten white rice.
Um...
Auntie.
What?
Refill!
Sure.
What was it, Kayoko?
Ah? No, never mind. It's nothing.
What a weird child.
Mom, you remember that kimono
that you gave to your sister?
Thanks to that kimono, we could eat
some white rice for the first time in a while.
It was very tasty!
Thank you, Mom.
The Golden Mask appears!
With his white cape fluttering,
the Golden Mask cuts a dashing appearance
and goes straight to face the bad guys
and save the children!
Ah! Kayoko, look!
Does it suit me?
Why, it's lovely!
Such a pretty kimono!
That was my favorite kimono.
Kayoko, we're going out for a bit.
Look after the house, won't you?
Mom's kimono...
That's right, it's your mother's
kimono and sash.
Does it look strange on me?
But... why?
Your mother gave it to me for safekeeping
before the March air raid.
She said I can use it
however I want if I need it.
Is that true?
What? You're doubting me?
Are you implying I stole it?!
No...
You were foisted on us, you know!
And this is the attitude we get in return?!
I-I'm sorry!
Let's go!
Mom...
Who's left behind?
Kayoko, come home for dinner!
Okay!
I'm home, Dad.
I'm home, Mom.
Welcome back, Kayoko.
That's right...
Wouldn't it be nice
if Kisaburo inherited father's trade?
Kisaburo will make fishing rods, and I'll help out!
And then...
We'd be able to live here again... Kisaburo and me!
Yes, yes, that'd be perfect!
Here's the entrance.
Here's the workshop.
And then...
Dad, Mom, I'm sure Kisaburo and I
will live here again.
Yeah.
Great-grandfather...
Whoa!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Are you okay?
Okay!
Oh, wonderful!
Japanese Buddha statue!
Oh, Buddha statue!
Stop! Please stop.
Nakano! Nakano!
I need to get off!
Please let me get off!
Young lady is getting off!
Getting off!
Bye!
Kisaburo, I found something peculiar
in the ruins of father's shop today.
The bronze statue of our great-grandfather,
the founder of the family trade,
that Father would pray to
every day before starting work.
If Auntie finds it,
she'll make a fuss again.
Kisaburo!
S-Sorry, I mistook you for someone else.
That was scary!
That way!
I'll go here!
It's a smuggler hunt!
Run!
Stop it!
Easy now!
The hell do you want?!
Let me go, you idiot!
Stop struggling!
What did I do?!
Not so fast!
Let go! Let go!
Assholes!
I-I'm not doing anything!
Kayo-chan?
Uncle...
Kayoko! Girls aren't supposed to wander around
the black market all day long! Have some shame!
You're lucky my husband was there.
Otherwise, you'd've been taken in by the police!
I can't imagine how embarrassing
that would've been to me!
Promise not to set foot
in the black market ever again!
Never again, you hear?
Kayoko! Answer me!
Y-Yes!
With this child, I can't...
Kisaburo, I won't stop coming here,
no matter how many times Auntie tells me off.
Because I need to find you.
'Sup.
Looking for your brother?
Yes. I heard that he works
in a black market in Asakusa.
The black market is a big place.
There are more shops here
than you can shake a stick at.
What's your brother selling?
I don't know...
Where's his shop?
Is he alone or in a group?
I don't know...
Well then, you can't hope to find him
if you don't know anything.
I'm sorry...
Get back here, you pig!
Sorry, some urgent matter came up.
When I'm back, we'll look
for your brother together!
Okay!
Ah, right, what's the name?
I'm Nakane Kayoko!
Your brother's!
Ah! It's... Ki!
Kisaburo!
Kisaburo?
Do you know him?
Please wait there for a bit.
I think I know someone like that.
Okay!
If you don't want to end up in a gutter,
spit out where your friends are.
You're playing dirty!
That's not what you promised us!
Promised?
Really? What kind of promise?
Tacchan said the union will leave us alone!
That means we can trade
wherever we want in Asakusa!
Dumbass! Did you really think
that kind of promise would last forever?
The crackdowns are becoming
commonplace these days.
We don't need some rookie like you
getting yourself nabbed in Asakusa.
Because after that, the cops
will go after the union directly!
Long story short, we can't have you guys
doing business here from now on.
Are you trying to destroy us
to protect yourselves?!
Our hands are tied.
That's just how the world is these days.
Old habits sure die hard, don't they?
What?!
Shimamoto!
Tacchan!
It's people like you, the adults,
who lost Japan the war!
You cocksucker!
Come now, it's nutritious!
Steaming hot clam soup—
your vitality for tomorrow!
Hot off the boil, fresh clam soup.
Get it while it's steaming!
Oh? With clams?
That's rare.
We got up early in the morning
and collected them ourselves!
Hey, mister, we also got carp here!
Miso soup with carp. This one's also fresh!
Hurry up before it's sold out!
Kicchan.
Shinji? What is it?
Got a minute?
What?
Tacchan!
Hey, Kisaburo.
Guess I'm back in Asakusa.
What's that wound?
The union guys got me.
The union is seriously determined
to destroy us now!
Rats! How cowardly can they really be?
Then, does it mean we'll have to join the union
if we want to keep doing business here?
Don't make me laugh!
We've always been doing it
however we want.
So we'll keep doing it the same way!
Damn right! Dumbass rules dreamed up by clueless adults are pure horseshit!
Exactly! We'll keep doing it same as before!
Yeah!
Kisaburo,
you've got good stuff going in your store.
Clam soup and carp soup... You won't find stuff like that in other stores.
We tried what you told us to do and it worked.
We get up early every morning
and go collect them together!
I see. Impressive stuff.
You found stuff that the union
doesn't trade in and secured a supply.
Kisaburo, that was a really good idea.
Kicchan is amazing!
He can make those rods
for catching fish so easily!
And fishing with his rods is a piece of piss!
I see. You're all doing your best,
aren't you? Keep it up!
Kisaburo, keep looking
after everyone for me, won't you?
Tacchan...
Ah, shoot!
I completely forgot!
Say, Kisaburo, you got a little sister?
Think she said it was Kayoko or something...
Kayoko?
Kayoko...
Kicchan!
Kicchan, did you find your sister?
She wasn't there.
Pour one for me too.
Sure!
At once!
Kisaburo, do you know where Kayo-chan lives?
Probably with our aunt in Nakano.
In Tokyo, she has nowhere else to stay.
Then go there and see her.
No, I quarreled with my aunt
and ran away from home.
And we don't exactly have it easy here, either.
Kisaburo...
Here's your soup!
Oh! Thanks.
My little sister was the only person I had left.
But she died in the hospital a week ago.
I couldn't see her when she died,
but the nurse told me later...
She'd been calling out to me
until the moment she died.
I'm home. Sorry I'm late!
Where have you been this late?!
Don't tell me you went
to the black market again!
Uh, I'll start preparing dinner now.
Yuriko-chan, can you help me?
Yes!
Can you go to the well
and fetch some water in this?
Sure!
Kisaburo...
Here it goes, Kayoko!
Dad!
Playing badminton?
Yeah! Kayoko is so good!
I see. Don't lose, then.
Okay.
Here it comes, Kayoko!
All right.
Sorry, Kayoko!
It's all right.
Here you are.
Is it true? Are you sure?
Yeah. I've just met with the prospective buyer,
and he was quite satisfied.
You think he's gonna buy it?
Most probably.
Listen, you make sure that buyer
doesn't slip through your fingers, no way!
After all, the site of their shop is the absolute best spot in that neighborhood.
It can fetch us a small fortune, for sure!
Yeah, I know.
Still, we're lucky to find a buyer for it so soon.
Yeah, you're right. Good call grabbing the deed
and the land register ahead of time.
It...
It can't be!
Kayoko!
They'll sell father's shop...
Father's shop!
It's here...
This land...
Dad...
Mom!
They'll build a new house
and someone else will live here!
Not me, not Kisaburo!
Goodbye, Yuri-chan.
Great Grandpa, please stay in here
for a little longer, okay?
I'll make sure to come for you later.
Kisaburo, I left our Auntie in Nakano.
I won't set foot in their house ever again.
Kisaburo,
our father's shop is in grave danger now.
I really need to see you soon.
It's a fight!
A fight?
A fight?!
It's near Hyotan Pond!
Hurry up!
Kisaburo! We told you to get fucking lost.
What didn't you understand?!
Do you think you own all of Asakusa?!
Anyone should be able to trade here freely!
Excuse me, please let me pass.
You fuckhead!
Just stop acting up!
Fuck you!
Kisaburo?
Get back here, you cockroach!
Out of our way!
Kisaburo...
Ain't catching me that easily!
Ki-Kisaburo?
Kayoko?
Kisaburo!
Kayoko!
Kisaburo... I wanted to see you, Kisaburo!
Don't cry, Kayoko.
I'm here. I'm here now.
Found him! Over there!
Stop!
Shit! Let's go, Kayoko!
Don't let him get away!
Kayoko, are you okay?
I'm... I'm not okay!
You've run well, sport.
We should be safe here.
No...
Kayoko, this is our base of operations.
Our hideout.
"Our"?
I live here with some friends
I met in the black market.
They're all nice guys.
It seems you've made quite a few friends.
Yeah.
Right!
I've been writing letters to you!
Letters?
I wrote a whole bunch!
Here. Your mail from Kayoko.
That's true! You've wrote so many!
I couldn't help it. Writing letters to you
was the most fun I had in Nakano!
Kayoko...
Here. Will you accept them?
But now that we've met in person,
there's no need for letters.
Doesn't matter. Just accept them.
You're a weird one...
Did they send you to trade for food too?
Yes. But trading for food was a lot of fun.
I got to meet many different people.
Oh no, I forgot something very important!
Look, someone else might snatch up
the land where Dad's shop used to be!
I see. But there's nothing we can do.
I refuse to give it up!
That place is full of memories
of Mom, Dad, and my other brothers!
I don't want to see them disappear!
Kayoko...
Hey, Kisaburo, I think I've had
this really good idea.
You and I will work hard and buy that land back.
And then you'll take over Dad's shop.
You'll make a great fishing rod artisan,
and I'll help out in the shop.
Right? Right? Doesn't that sound great?
I'm sure that's what our dad and mom
in heaven would want!
Kayoko, it's not possible now.
What do you mean? Why?
I have these guys now.
I can't just leave them to their fate.
But brother...
Didn't you say you'd come and take me with you?
Yeah, I'll come for you.
I'll work as hard as I can,
save up some money, and come for you.
But it's impossible right now.
Please understand.
That's so...
So long...
Just a little longer!
It may be hard, but please bear with it
and live with Auntie in Nakano. Okay, Kayoko?
Kisaburo...
Kicchan! I've prepared
some rice porridge inside.
So, Kayoko? Is it good?
Y-Yeah...
Of course it is! It was me
who did the seasoning! I'm Tecchan!
Hello.
I'm Noboru.
Hi.
Shigeo.
I'm Shinji.
Kicchan is always looking after me.
Not after you in particular.
I'm Aiko. Nice to meet you.
Hi.
And that over there...
We've known each other
for a while now. Right, Kayo-chan?
Yeah.
Oh, is that so?
Are you all living here under the same roof?
Yeah. We're like family.
We've got sleeping quarters
on the second floor.
We all sleep there in a huddle.
Oh? On the second floor?
Hey, you've no idea how loud Shinji's snore is!
It's so noisy we can't get any sleep!
I snore?
Yeah, you do.
But I'll still take it over Tecchan's bed-wetting.
Wh-When did I ever wet the bed?!
You just did yesterday.
No, I didn't!
Yes, you did!
I didn't...
You really are like one big family.
We all lost our families in the air raid.
We don't have anyone else left.
That's why we all cling to life,
trying our best to support and help each other out.
Why not let Kayo-chan
live here with Kisaburo too?
Really?
That's a no-go.
Kayoko still has a place she can call home.
But I like it more here.
That's right! Stay with us, sister Kayo!
You can sleep next to me.
Okay.
Kayoko doesn't know
how to do business in the black market.
Then I'll just stay here all day,
cooking and doing the laundry…
No means no!
Kisaburo...
Why?
Why not?
An earthquake!
It's the union thugs!
Hey, brats! Hurry and come out.
We know you're in there!
You guys...
That's what you get for repeatedly
ignoring sound advice.
You're getting your just desserts.
What do you know about justice?!
Your own made-up logic
is no reason for us to leave Asakusa!
You don't want to do it the easy way, huh?
Then prepare for a world of hurt!
Kicchan!
They're serious this time!
Kayoko, you leave through
the back door and go home.
No! I don't want to run!
Let's all escape together!
That won't be possible.
This here is our home.
B-But...
Kayoko, I don't want to expose you to unnecessary danger. Go home!
Shinji, take everyone and run upstairs!
Let's go, guys!
Tacchan, can you move?
No, I don't think so.
I see. Kayoko!
Tacchan, look after Kayoko.
O-Okay. I got you.
Kisaburo?
Stay here with Tacchan, and don't move.
How'd you like that?!
Fuckers!
Guys! Grab onto it!
Shit!
Brother... No... It's dangerous!
Kisaburo is fighting with all he's got.
To protect the friends who look up to him,
he doesn't back down from danger.
He's ready to risk everything.
That's the kind of guy Kisaburo is!
Brother...
You motherfucker...
Watch out!
Kicchan!
Pull out!
Kisaburo!
No! Don't die, Kisaburo! Kisaburo!
Kayoko...
Kisaburo?
Kayoko, I was saved, thanks to you.
Your letters took the hit instead of me.
Thank God.
Kicchan is immortal!
That's why he's our general!
Sorry I made you worry, people.
Kisaburo, you idiot!
Kayoko...
Kisaburo...
Tacchan.
We've pushed them back today somehow,
but they'll definitely come again soon.
They can come all they want!
That's right! We'll never give in to them!
Yeah.
We've got Kicchan and Tacchan on our side!
How could we ever lose?!
Is everyone okay?
Tacchan.
Kisaburo.
Kayoko, you should return to Auntie.
I can't do that.
I've already said my goodbyes to them.
Just apologize. They'll let you in again.
I can't do that!
I don't wanna go anywhere else now!
I want to stay with you!
That's not gonna work. You can't.
Why?
Why?!
You're so cruel, Kisaburo!
Didn't you promise we'd live together?
Please!
I know it may be hard,
but you must return to Auntie.
And forget about me from now on!
If you follow me around,
it'll end badly for you!
How can you...
Kisaburo, you idiot!
Idiot!
Subway platform
Asakusa Station
Dad, Mom, I had hoped
I'd get to live here with Kisaburo.
But it seems it wasn't meant to be.
Father's shop is gonna end up
in someone else's hands.
I'm sorry, Dad, Mom.
You're a cheerful, resilient, and strong girl...
Mom, I've been trying my best.
But I'm tired.
I'm afraid that if this continues,
I might follow after you.
Kayoko, don't talk like that!
When you're sad,
everyone else gets sad too!
Cheer up, Kayoko!
What's the matter?
You're gonna freeze like that.
Look, you've got so much snow on you.
It's cold!
I just bought it from that black market.
It's still warm.
Here.
What? Don't want any?
You look down.
And the first step to feeling better
is to eat something.
Eating gives you energy to move on.
So eat while it's still hot. Here you go.
It's warm!
What about you?
Eat up. Don't worry about me.
But...
Here.
Thanks.
Everything and everyone went up in flames.
I was in Northern China when the war ended.
I barely escaped back to Japan with my life.
I was on the verge of death many times.
But every time I despaired, I remembered.
My child's smile.
All I wanted was to see that smile once again.
That thought was what carried me back to Japan.
But by the time I finally got back, all that was left
of our house was a pile of ashes.
No one from my family survived it.
They all died.
Why did I even come home?!
What was I fighting for?
Amulet
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Mister?
Thank you, young lady.
You cried for them with me.
Thank you.
At least that made my return worthwhile.
Mister, you mustn't give up.
Everybody here keeps looking
for their family day after day.
You have to keep searching!
I'm sure they survived!
I'm sure your wife and child are alive.
You're right. You're right...
Yes. I won't let go of my dream either!
I won't give up on it.
So please keep searching for them.
Yes, I won't give up. I'll keep searching.
Then cheer up, mister!
You too, young lady.
Yeah!
Kayoko?
Kisaburo!
All over the world, more and more children are going through the same fate as Kayoko.
They're all trying desperately to live the peaceful life of their dreams, carrying an infinite love for others in their hearts.
All I wish for is for the world to become a place
where such children can live freely and peacefully.
The lotus flower bloomed, overflowing with feelings.
The pale pink flowers bloomed; their dew is like tears.
Time passes, people go by, the tall buildings long for the sky.
They all go about their day, forgetting the sensitive heart.
I want to become the wind, the open heart.
The meaning of the pale pink of this flower...
I want to become a singing wind...
The wind that passed through the alleys
of downtown on that day
carries the smiles of my father and mother from long ago.
It's not bitter, it's not sad,
it's just happy to be alive.
Don't people really live in the sensitive heart?
The lotus flower blooms quietly.
The meaning of the pale pink of this flower...
I want to become a singing wind...
The lotus flower will continue to bloom tomorrow,
entrusted with feelings I can't hide.
It will just continue to bloom without anyone noticing!
I want to become the wind, the sensitive heart.
The meaning of the pale pink of this flower...
I want to become a singing wind...
I want to become a singing wind.
Translation & Timing
Editing
Typesetting & QC
QC
Encoding
Presented by
Perevoldildo
Paul Geromini
Collectr
Uchuu
anonymous
Orphan Fansubs