Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Queen's Cup 90 finals
were postponed due to the rain.
The Jean Ryder vs Oka Hiromi match
was rescheduled to 1 pm of the following day.
Welcome.
Your room was empty,
so headed here.
I'd like a cafe au lait.
As you wish.
Yesterday evening,
I've been to Madame Butterfly's house.
I'm not sure if I should confide it to you
until Hiromi's finals are over,
but it seems Madame Butterfly is retiring.
Your cafe au lait.
Episode 12
I'm back!
My match is at 1 pm tomorrow
and waiting in the hotel is no fun.
I'll have plenty of time to make it there tomorrow.
Besides...
Besides?
If I don't sleep this night in my own bed,
I won't get any sleep.
I also missed mom's cooking!
Besides...
It's just 4 o'clock.
You did well, all the way to the finals.
I recorded every TV broadcast of you.
Thanks!
A salmon pot will do just well! How about it?
Huh?
I'll take a little walk outside.
Is salmon pot okay?
Yes!
This is Katsura.
Can I speak to Ms. Oka?
Did Hiromi leave the hotel
without Mr. Katsura's permission?
No, I'm... Making sure she made it there.
That's all I needed to know.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
Reika, Oka's here.
Reika?
Oka came to see you,
waiting in the living room.
I wish her the best of luck in tomorrow's finals.
Please tell her so.
I'm terribly sorry, Oka.
Reika is taking a little nap.
She deserves some rest now.
Oka! Oka!
Oka!
Todo...
Todo!
Oka, I went to the venue
but today's match was postponed.
You weren't in the hotel,
so I headed to your home.
Madame Butterfly retires?
Is it confirmed?
I went to her to confirm it.
But then she didn't wish to meet me.
However, last night,
when Midorikawa managed to see her,
as she was sitting there,
exhausted and in tears:
"Forgive me.
I cannot play tennis anymore."
To all inquiries of Chairman Ryuzaki, her father,
she just hung her head in sorrow.
It troubles me so much!
It is all so wrong.
With this on my mind,
I cannot play tennis...
I was aspiring to her.
I could only climb this far
because I thought Madame Butterfly is waiting here.
I don't care what happens in finals tomorrow.
If Madame Butterfly quits tennis,
it ends for me as well!
Do you remember us sitting in this restaurant?
Just like today,
it was pouring rain.
I thought I either become a pro or quit tennis.
I was completely lost.
And then, while drinking that burning-hot coffee
here with you, I could make up my mind.
"I will try my best no matter what."
This restaurant, which is nothing but commonplace,
became a starting point for me.
That was how I thought of it then.
So even if I fail,
I won't lose my spirits.
I'll just come to this restaurant once again.
Perhaps, that day it won't rain anymore.
There's also no telling if you'll come here with me.
Chances are, this whole restaurant
won't be present by that time.
But I'm fine with that too.
I was sitting here with you, it was raining,
the coffee was burning-hot - that's the only truth for me.
That was when I mustered the courage to go forward.
A wonderful decision, it seemed to me.
Because... Because I knew
that even if I fail, I won't lose everything,
and that if I come here,
you will equip me with courage once again, surely.
I wonder where Madame Butterfly's restaurant is, though.
Right now she is desperately trying to recall this place.
All alone, certain that at such a moment,
not a soul would show up at her special place.
Once Madame Butterfly returns there,
she'll need time to think it over.
She'll come back to the light, surely.
Until then, Oka, we have to just wait patiently.
Unfortunately, there's nothing else we can do.
Honestly!
You dumped away my training plan just to come here!
Fortunate of you, Todo!
Without rain postponement, you'd never see the match.
Lucky!
Remind me to teach you some pro responsibility!
Oka, it's time.
Get on the court.
Well, let's go, Hiromi.
Okay? The time has come.
Just one more push, Oka.
There's no retreating from the final round.
Forget about Madame B until the match's conclusion.
Listen, Oka.
Those who kept winning and could advance into the final stage
are obliged to fight for those who got eliminated along the way.
Midorikawa, Broir, Morita, Ling, and of course Ryuzaki.
Those who lost remain on the court,
represented by your fierce fight.
Do you mean to say you forgot them?
No, I remember them all, still lucidly.
Stand up then!
Stand on the court!
And show everyone your ultimate fight!
Reika!
We should leave shortly for the Colosseum.
Are you ready to go out?
I'm sorry, father.
Today I...
Rightly so.
That's even better!
Whatever was there, it's over.
Father, you are not going to Colosseum?
It appears today I'm staying indoors as well.
But you cannot do that!
You are the Association Chairman.
You have a major task of awarding the Cup to the champion!
Anyone can replace me in this role.
Father...
But today, on such an important day,
nobody can replace me as your father.
If you are staying indoors for an entire day,
I think I should too.
If I can do anything for you, I must do it.
That's how it should be and how I want it.
Father.
Hiromi might very well become the champion.
You are the only one
who can award the Champion Cup to her.
Have you not looked forward to that day since long ago?
Don't you always say that the Japanese Tennis Association
places its hopes in Oka?
And when that dream is about to be fulfilled, you turn away?
From Hiromi...
Can I tell you just one thing, Reika?
Yes.
This defeat was essential for you, Reika.
Thanks to it, you can now move on and grow,
break the chains!
I hope you forgive me for what I'm to say
because I see it appropriate.
Congratulations!
Let us go, father.
Let's go to the Colosseum together.
No. It's fine if you want to stay.
I should go. I want to go!
Reika!
Hiromi is doing her best, so I must see it.
I want... I want to see it with my own eyes!
Daigo...
I got you, Munakata.
Daigo, do it for me...
I got you perfectly.
Trust me to make it all OK, Munakata.
Oka keeps her service-game. The score is tied.
From the very first set, her offense is fierce!
A gain again!
Oka's return ace!
Since when did Oka
learn to hit such a ball?
Jean Ryder, #7 in world rankings,
is much paler in the face now!
Honey, tea.
Okay...
Tea!
Okay.
Ryder approaches the net!
What kind of attack?
She hits!
Daigo, human beings touch and communicate
in a variety of different forms.
Through a variety of different approaches.
I once met Oka through the tennis approach.
Whether Oka likes it or not, there's no escaping the major premise
of me being the coach and Oka being the player.
That's why I am responsible for sacrificing
her entire priceless youth to a greater cause of tennis.
I got what you mean, Munakata.
I got it all.
Still, the limit of tennis...
The limit to which I can teach her tennis is already near.
What does it mean to be a true player...
What does it mean to be a true coach?
Munakata...
No!
Goddamn!
What a hot temper.
Is that even worth of world's #7?
Unknown Oka Hiromi turned out formidable.
It's a shock for her!
Todo, that would suffice for me.
Madame Butterfly,
thank you so much for everything.
Coach Katsura,
today, I'm not fighting here alone.
I was never fighting here alone, and I see it now!
I'd never manage to make it this far doing my best alone.
I realized it suddenly while hitting the ball!
All this time I have been the most ordinary child.
An ordinary child, who happened to be playing this big match.
Unbelievable, isn't it?
I don't believe it either.
But what I know for sure is, it were Coach Katsura
and Madame Butterfly, Todo and Maki, Chairman Ryuzaki,
Chiba and Ozaki, and finally...
Finally, Coach Munakata.
It's thanks to all of them.
That is what I truly believe right now.
Next one is tie-break!
Under a twelve-point system,
the first player to score 7 points wins this set!
Well done, Oka! You scored 7 points!
The first set is rightfully yours!
One more set. If Oka's sustains this vigor for just one more set,
her premier Queen Title will no longer a dream!
Go for it, Oka! Till the end!
I wanted to hit those balls like Hiromi does it.
What?
3 against 0.
Oka lead!
It's a match point!
Oka is currently just one point away from victory!
Ryder has no room for a fault!
Half a step onward more!
Champion - Oka Hiromi!
Excuse me, but did you want to show something
to me and Oka?
And this...
On his last day, or maybe a day or two before that
Munakata Jin
he wrote me this, his final letter.
Go ahead and read.
I wanted to show it to you for its contents.
Daigo. Still, teaching her tennis...
The limit to which I can teach her tennis is already closing in.
To be a true player, to be a true coach, what does it mean?
I spend the little time I have left, pondering.
What will Oka need when she eventually becomes stronger,
mastering everything she will ever need for her tennis?
Perhaps, it won't be neither me, nor you, Daigo.
It's because we ourselves
are walking just a bit ahead of Oka.
Therefore, what Oka will really need by then
is a mate who could share her walk,
worries, grief and finally, joy, in the equal parts.
To whom she could bestow not just tennis, but everything else
as well... Faith. Whom she could put her faith in.
I believe, that person would be Oka's true coach.
Daigo, I entrust Oka to your command.
So when the time comes for you to pass this baton to another,
I also want you to pick a person whom you can entrust her to.
Because for someone as incapable as me,
Oka is too amazing.
Todo.
Yes?
In a year... No, even in half a year, after Oka completes
her transition to pro, her path will become even more rugged.
Will you be ready by then
to accept this baton from me?
I cannot know what lies ahead, but until then, I will make every effort to become a person capable enough to accept it.
I don't need any send-offs, you know.
I'm not a child anymore.
If I need you while you travel through America again,
how do I contact you?
I'll be paying you a call each time my address changes.
Well, that's fine by me then.
Why do you ask, though?
I was thinking,
maybe I should go to America too.
Maybe I'll have more luck
getting a Pro Qualification there.
What do you think?
Great! Definitely! That's a great idea!
I'm starting over.
Can't hear you...
Oka.
Yes?
This time, to celebrate your triumph,
I want to give you some kind of present.
Can you tell me what you'd like?
I can not.
Why so?
Because now I have everything I would ever want.
Oka!
15-0!
The end
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings messed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Thank you for watching.
I was happy to translate and compile this release for you.
Yours truly, Perevodildo.