On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Come in.
This is video taken
from the first Kanto Tournament match.
It was a wonderful victory.
I'm here to celebrate the win,
and when I see this,
I notice you've done unsurprisingly well.
She's definitely maturing steadily.
The movement of her legs are fantastic.
It's not a stretch to think she was born talented.
I'm curious to see how much more she can grow.
As you say,
it's true that she's talented at running.
But…
But... what did you mean to say?
But because of that,
Oka Hiromi can't take the next step.
Episode 18
Fight the Black Spy!
As expected from Madame Butterfly!
No one could return a ball like that from her.
What about our Hiromi now?
Hiromi's doing well too.
She manages to chase down those balls.
Madame Butterfly-Hiromi combination is the best!
This upcoming Kanto Tournament
is a guaranteed win.
I wonder.
What? Are you saying that Madame Butterfly
and Hiromi can't win?
Kanto Tournament is a battleground for teams
that conquered their way through.
It's the ultimate challenge,
with Madame Butterfly or without her.
You mean that Hiromi is the problem?
Look yourself, Aikawa.
Oh no!
It's true that Oka runs very well.
She has the legs to somehow chase down any ball.
But for that reason
the ball she returns to the opponent is always easy.
It must look miserable to Madame Butterfly.
Tell this to Oka for me.
With only swift legs, you cannot play tennis.
Albeit Coach Munakata will probably say it too.
What's that? As if she knows everything.
You just came to spy on Hiromi.
A peeping spy!
I'm tired…
You sure worked up a sweat.
Oka runs so well!
There's no way I could chase that kind of ball.
I've got a bit of confidence
with these fast legs of mine.
Oka!
Yes?
With only swift legs, you cannot play tennis.
Hey Hiromi, listen!
"Pass this to Oka from me.
With only swift legs, you cannot play tennis."
Like that!
Midorikawa said it, too?
Did anyone else say that already?
Coach.
Coach did?
"Oka, with only swift legs,
you cannot play tennis," like this?
Yeah.
I see. Then Lady Orchid wasn't a spy,
in this case, it was rather an advice.
And I said bad things to her, I feel awful.
But she said it so bluntly and with such certainty.
I see, that's how it was.
That means I should figure it out by myself.
"You should be searching on your own
for what you need to do."
That's what Coach's eyes were saying.
"You need to search on your own."
Coach's eyes said you need to search on your own?
But you know,
there's only a week left until the next match.
If you don't figure what to do by then,
what are you going to do?
If it comes to that I've lost.
I don't like that!
Me neither.
I don't want to lose,
and so I have to do something.
Hiromi…
Will you help me?
Of course!
I'll do whatever I can!
All right, let's practice!
Right now?
Let's go!
Wait, Hiromi!
You can't do it with fast legs alone.
Something else is necessary.
Practice, it's practice!
In my state, I mustn't think of anything else.
Well then, let's do our best!
Let's always do!
Here I go, Hiromi!
Okay!
Maki, give me a ball that's harder to return!
I'm sorry.
Maki, give me a ball that's closer to the line
and is more difficult for me to return.
Maki? Maki, what's wrong all of a sudden?
I'm pathetic!
I can't ever give the ball that you asked for!
I'm sorry I asked for something so impossible.
That was my fault.
No, it's just that I'm so useless!
Should I be your opponent?
I think I'm better than that girl.
Who are you?
But I have a condition.
Tomorrow we play a match right here.
A match of an official type.
I accept.
Hiromi!
All right then, tomorrow,
same time, same place.
This is bad, Hiromi.
You agreed to a match without knowing who they are
or where they are from.
The regulations say
you can't play in unapproved matches.
If you break the regulations,
the tennis club will expel you!
Is it really worth it?
It is.
Hiromi, think about it,
it might just be that…
they're spies from the enemy team
of upcoming Kanto Tournament.
Yes, that's it. That must be it.
Or else there would be no way
that she would be here at the right time and place.
Even if I would break the regulations…
Even if the opponent is a spy…
Coach, you'll have to forgive me.
Right now, I can't find any alternatives.
Hiromi…
You cannot play tennis with just your legs.
That must be it.
I'm always running relentlessly, but…
Madame Butterfly, for some reason,
doesn't have to run that much.
Why… Why… Why can it be so with me?
Regardless, I want an opponent right now.
I don't care if she's a spy or whatever!
Goemon?
You're going to be my opponent?
That's very kind of you, but I'll pass.
Ah, I got sleepy.
Good night!
Thank you, Maki!
Hiromi, what are you doing tonight?
Going, of course!
Oka!
Don't slack off over there!
Okay!
Later.
She's really going to do it, good grace.
If only I was better
and could provide Hiromi with a worthy opponent.
I can't even discuss this with Coach Munakata
or Madame Butterfly.
Oka Hiromi of Nishi High will go against us
of Ohara High at the oncoming Kanto Tournament.
I heard that she was selected
despite her abilities being completely unknown.
In order to beat Nishi High,
we've got to target Oka Hiromi.
Oka Hiromi we promise
that we will defeat you by any cost!
Aim for the Ace!
Oka Hiromi.
Nishi High's coach is training her devoutly.
She earned a legendary rookie title already.
We'll see how much fun she'll be.
There she is, Oka Hiromi!
I've been waiting.
I'm ready!
Same on my part.
Come on!
Here I go!
Let's do this!
Hiromi! Wait!
Maki!
Midorikawa, and Otowa too…
I'm Kaga High's Midorikawa Ranko.
I don't know who you are or where you're from,
but to scrimmage at this time and place,
what's the meaning of this?
No, I'm the one who requested it.
And... I know Nishi High Tennis Club regulations.
But I would like to practice more,
so I'll have a better chance.
So... That's why.
It's fine, Oka, you don't have to get so worked up.
But I just wanted to ask these fellows
what purpose they're here for.
More importantly I'm not here to stop this match.
If you're going to play a match,
I would prefer you both to do so properly.
Listen closely.
I will take full responsibility for this match.
But in return, you should play it under my orders.
Is that fine with you, mysterious pair?
Yeah.
Oka, it's fine with you, as well?
Yes.
Okay, it's been decided.
The match will be a doubles.
Three set match.
Doubles?
Otowa!
Oka, I'm not as perfect as Madame Butterfly,
but think of this as a doubles with her
and do your best!
Okay!
I see. Everyone is doing this all for my sake.
I see. All right! I have to do my best!
Best of three set match! Play!
15-0!
30-0!
Those girls in black are going full steam.
40-0!
Just as I thought.
She won't be able to keep up with my power ball
any time soon.
She's just aiming at me.
It's frustrating, but I don't have any kind
of special abilities to pose a proper response.
But please, aim at me more!
That will be my ultimate practice!
Otowa, when did she?
She managed to reach the ball easily.
The ball that was aimed at me.
Oka!
It's your turn to serve next. Got it?
Yes.
"With just swift legs, you cannot play tennis."
"With swift legs only, you cannot play tennis."
"With only swift legs, you cannot play tennis."
That's right… "With only swift legs,
you cannot play tennis."
I try my best and chase after the ball,
but it'll always be returned!
What should I do?
What to do?
But…
But I must do my best right now!
I must do my best!
Out! Double fault.
0-15!
Seems like her serve is still lacking.
15-All!
30-15!
What kind of girl is that?
I have never seen a serve that fast.
But her control is all over the place!
I can't tell if she's skilled or inept.
All right, here it comes!
Otowa runs nowhere near as much as I do.
But why is Otowa able to get to the ball
faster than I can? Why?
With only swift legs,
you shouldn't play tennis, I know that.
I know that.
But. But…
But I must go after it somehow!
Go after it and receive it!
Otowa isn't around!
Oka!
It's impossible!
I can't get to it!
I'm just futilely chasing after the ball.
Otowa's breathing
is unnoticeable compared to mine.
It's light! Quiet like she's asleep!
Otowa knows where the ball will go in advance.
She goes to that place in advance.
All I'm doing is chasing the ball itself.
Only the ball itself.
But Otowa is just waiting the ball instead.
What allows her to wait for the ball?
What?
How can she tell where the ball is going to go?
How? How can she tell?
The place where the ball will go next…
Maybe this means, I have to learn to read the ball?
Read the ball…
That's right! Read it!
I hit it now, then opponent returns it to my left.
Otowa hits it and the opponent…
It's empty!
That was close!
All right, this time around I'll read it!
The opponent returns.
I'll hit it.
Opponent chases ball to the right.
She will aim for Otowa's mark next.
That means that the back is empty!
I see! If Otowa returns it,
the other opponent will aim for the back!
The opponent will hit it,
then Otowa will return it.
The other one will hit it.
Here it comes!
It went to the place I figured!
Oka!
What a girl, she's able to receive even such a course.
I will leave this ball to Otowa at the back.
So I can safely go to the front!
Otowa returned it.
The opponents will have to advance.
When did she...
I should now aim at opponent's back
that's completely empty!
Game set!
Oka-Otowa team wins!
You did it, Oka.
That'll do just fine. It will.
Oka!
Hiromi!
I read it! I managed to read the ball's path!
Jin, just as I expected of a player
you're putting your whole soul into raising.
With this Oka has risen to a new level.
So? You think there is any need
for further scrimmages?
Doesn't seem necessary to me,
Ohara High gang.
Your purpose here has been fulfilled.
You've just witnessed a slice
of Oka Hiromi's full strength.
Now, go back home.
We'll see you at the Kanto Tournament.
Along with your school's team of real players.
We did it! They turned around
and ran with their tails between their legs!
Serves you right!
I don't know if you're skilled or inept,
thought there's definitely something about you.
But with our captain's technique,
it's still a whole bunch of nothing.
At the Kanto Tournament,
we must find Oka Hiromi's weak spot.
Kanto Tournament looks promising.
We'll make you see Ohara High's real strength!
They left. They left, Hiromi!
Hiromi?
I'm grateful to those girls regardless.
If they hadn't been there,
I couldn't have played this match.
Otowa, you've served your purpose right?
Yes.
Well then, shall we get going?
See you, Oka.
Excuse me…
Midorikawa, Otowa, thank you very much!
I understand clearly now.
Tennis is not only dependent on your legs.
What Midorikawa and Coach Munakata
were trying to say is
you cannot just blindly chase after the ball.
Read the ball and go
where the ball is going to land before it happens.
Midorikawa, Otowa, thank you very much!
To Be Continued
It's finally doubles semifinals.
A girl suddenly appears on the court Hiromi is using.
It's Kawamura Yumi from Ohara High, who is to appear in the competition.
Kawamura left mysterious advice to Hiromi and headed off.
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"The Bloodstained Return from Crisis!"
After hearing the mysterious advice, Hiromi's soul violently trembles.
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo