I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
New York! New York! New York!
We got to use the entire first day for recreation!
I can't wait to see the Statue Of Liberty!
I want to go through every sightseeing course
in my guidebook!
But I'm so excited.
After all, seeing it yourself
is nothing like hearing about it!
And not just seeing...
I have trod my first, yet so historically important
for my life, step on the American soil.
I just regret Coach is not here with us now.
Coach Munakata,
get discharged soon.
Please reunite with us again.
Mourning
Episode 3
Overseas tour without Coach
Ahoy, Maki!
Are you doing well?
Finally, my New York life starts!
I hope back in Japan,
Mr. Sun is benevolent to everyone as well.
Anyhow, the prime unusual thing about here
is how tremendously king size everything is!
People and cities alike.
Even the hotel we've stopped in is...
Guess what, 80 floors high!
Someone like Maki would probably go "Kyaaa!" and faint
by just looking down from the window.
Now then, our team of young Japanese players
from this hotel on New York's 8th avenue,
has to attend tennis court every day
as a part of our practice.
After all, in this tour we'll compete
not just with players from America,
but from Britain, France, and Australia as well.
For each of participating young player teams,
this is their first trial of strength.
Tournament format matches
are synthesized with practice.
This time Hiromi is surely giving it her best!
Well then, later!
Hey, it must be Bianca from France.
Still in high school, on All-France's Open,
she made it to the final selection.
Mighty players who'd qualify effortlessly as a pro
are all over the place.
How much tension!
Oka?
Yes?
One set. Will you do me this honor?
Yes!
Hey, Todo, should we probably start too?
Three-set as usual?
Unlimited deathmatch!
You really are into it!
Miss Oka?
Yes?
There's a person seeking to meet you.
Could you come to the clubhouse for a bit?
Warmest greetings, Miss Hiromi.
You know who he is, Oka?
Yes.
Well, I often see him in magazines.
A famous Australian tennis coach...
Right, it is Mister Reynolds.
Nice to meet you, Ms. Hiromi.
Very glad, Mr. Reynolds!
It goes without saying, Reynolds family includes
a bunch of young players from Australia -
Angie Reynolds
and of course, Eddy Reynolds.
He became famous for bringing up those siblings
not just as a father would, but as a coach as well.
This time as well, Angie and Eddy keep him company,
participating as a part of Australian team.
However, Mr. Reynolds resigned as Australian team's coach
today, with proposition to become your coach.
Well, I already have my own regular coach. So...
Coach Munakata isn't it?
Hiromi's coach.
However, you see, he's not here.
He is in Japan now.
But Coach Munakata will soon join us too. Therefore...
Oka.
It was actually Coach Munakata
who put forward this idea.
Because he's coming late,
he asked Mr. Reynolds to coach you until then.
You may not be aware of that, but Mr. Reynolds has been Munakata's pal ever since they were players themselves.
Coach Munakata's request?
I'm sorry, Mister Reynolds.
I didn't...
So is it OK now, Ms. Hiromi?
Yes! Well then, until Coach Munakata joins us,
please take care of me!
OK! Let's both do our best.
Chairman Ryuzaki...
Please hear out my proposition.
Because I think Munakata
would have proposed it too.
What is it?
Munakata's death... For some while,
I want you to conceal that fact.
She is now left to walk a long road
all alone and away from home.
At such a moment, what may happen,
should that fact come to light?
I don't think anyone can say for certain.
Besides, Oka should now
carry forth that tennis Munakata entrusted her with.
It's now more than ever important for her
to keep going undisturbed through that tour.
Therefore, at least until Oka Hiromi returns to Japan,
I want you to hold that fact in!
I understand it perfectly, Daigo.
I will do everything I can.
It won't leak to any mass-media. I'll see to it.
Thank you kindly.
Even by going to New York, I won't help you one bit.
I understand that much.
And yet, Oka, even if I can't be of any service to you,
I just want to be by your side.
If the worst case scenario hits you after all,
at least I would be there to say a word of consolation.
No, Hiromi!
Watch the ball more closely!
Okay!
In just three years of tennis, such a play...
Such power!
And that fighting spirit.
Did Munakata really have to leave behind such a miracle?
Such a fervor for ball...
Not just for Munakata, but for the tennis of the world,
we cannot let her passion burn out!
I'm going, Hiromi!
Okay!
Coach!
That's right, Oka!
Muster all the strength you believe you have
and hit that ball!
Okay!
Nice, Hiromi!
Splendid!
And not just for practice,
but for an actual match too!
This is not about techniques, but the spirit!
Don't forget your personality and engrave it!
On the ball! The ball!
Okay...
Yes, Mr. Reynolds has been attached to Oka as coach.
Yes, it's all alright.
With exception of Mr. Reynolds,
I haven't told anyone about Coach Munakata.
Yes. I understand.
Who's there?
Todo.
Come in.
If you excuse me.
What's the matter?
Manager, don't you think it's strange?
What do you mean?
One week... No, even if he arrives 2 weeks late,
all 3 previous years, he has been raising Oka himself.
You think Coach Munakata would suddenly entrust
a player so important to him to some other coach like that?
What are you trying to say?
I can't quite grasp your point.
Because I know what times Coach Munakata and Oka
been through together,
what sufferings endured,
what walls climbed over, I'm saying that!
No chance! For him to willingly entrust Oka
to a coach other than himself in this way...
Never before there has been a chance for such a thing!
If the things are really this way, then... Then!
You are overthinking, Todo.
Nothing particular happened.
In Japan, nothing changed either.
You are the Japan's team captain,
and it's unbecoming of captain to panic like that.
Actually, I overheard what you said just before.
Your call to management in Japan.
"I haven't told about Coach Munakata
to anyone except Mr. Reynolds."
What was the meaning of this?
Let me know the truth, please!
Todo, you'll have to believe me.
There's nothing.
If you excuse me.
Oy! There you are!
My, only you bothered to come greet me?
I'm so lonesome!
Ozaki wanted to come too.
I assured him I'd manage alone...
Then locked in his room just in case!
Hey, hey, hurry up
and show me the way to hotel already.
Ain't we both a bit starvey?
What is it you wanted to talk about?
When did Coach pass away?
Idiot, Munakata is still undergoing
a thorough checkup.
Chiba!
We are friends, aren't we?!
Can't you tell me frankly?
I don't... anything...
I know the truth about his condition!
His true condition, I know!
You...
Spit it out, Chiba...
Clearly and straightforwardly!
Chiba, please!
His farewell words are
"Oka, aim for the ace!"
January 15, at 6:37 pm.
As your plane was taking off from Japanese soil,
he took his last breath.
First round matchups finally arrived.
Along with you, players from 4 more countries
take part in this tournament.
The underlying idea is not to promote inter-country rivalry spirit or team cohesion spirit.
Instead, developing players' techniques case by case
is the main objective.
We want you to learn the most you can
from fighting foreign players.
For Japanese Tennis Association, these matches will serve
a gauge of Japan's level of ability.
In addition, those matches should lay foundation
for determining our objectives hereafter.
I wish you all a fair wind.
Oka Hiromi (JP)
Maria Young (US)
Maria Young?
Maria Young...
The most prominent pupil of Lady King,
said to be a world-class genius player!
Maria Young will fight me...
Oka, I was 6 when I first clasped the racket.
Since then and to this day,
my dad is my only coach.
On dad's recommendation, I worked
with countless amazing coaches of outstanding abilities.
However, with every new coach I met,
I couldn't help coming to the same conclusion.
Although these days he can no longer teach me
a single thing about techniques or theory, dad is still...
to me, the only possible coach.
You're not the only one feeling this way -
oceans away from her coach, alone in America.
Keep up the good work and don't lose the spirits.
You do, and so will I.
Okay.
Hey, don't pull that bitter face when looking at her.
The two of us have to remain strong no matter what!
I know.
I'm sorry, Madame.
But I just cannot be as strong as you...
I'm uneasy, and I don't know how to help it.
I'm letting Coach Reynolds down,
but I just can't focus on the practice.
Coach, please come sooner!
Coach! Coach Munakata!
Coach, is your health getting better?
I learned today that in the first round of tournament,
I'm getting put up against Maria Young.
But Coach, without you here...
Let's see... In Japan, it should be very early morning.
It feels a bit awkward to dial the hospital now.
Maria Young?
From the get-go, you're put up
against such a mighty target! Well, aren't you lucky?
Ding-dong! Maki, you think so too?
To tell you the truth, I bet Coach
will be even more than me delighted to get this!
Speaking of, how is Coach?
Coach?
I don't know much myself,
but I heard he is getting discharged any day now.
Really? Finally!
Then, you know when Coach departs?
Maki... Hey, Maki, you listening?
Very soon, they say.
Hiromi, international calls are expensive,
so I'm hanging up now.
Just keep doing your best!
Because I'll be rooting for you firmly!
Hanging up now!
Hiromi...
Do your best, Hiromi...
Your best!
What was that?
Weirdo Maki.
I'm never calling you again in that case!
Gonna go have a run!
Todo!
Oka.
Thought I'd go run to sleep better.
And I had the same thought as Todo.
Really having a hard time falling asleep.
I guess it's jet lag...
Wanna run together?
Yes! With pleasure.
Do your best against Maria Young.
Sure.
No matter how far away,
Munakata never stops watching over you.
Haven't it always been this way?
Yes!
Don't go easy on her, Oka.
With all might!
Okay!
Alright. How about we run to Central Park and back?
Sure.
Stay strong, Oka. Strong!
Sorry I'm coming so late, Papa, bro.
It's really late, Angie.
I thought you aren't coming at all.
How can I miss such a thing?
For her sake, Papa even resigned as our coach.
It's Hiromi Oka's match.
We'll see what resistance can she put up
against Maria Young.
I can't miss it, by all means!
Isn't that so, Papa?
The best of the three set match!
Oka's service. Play!
15-0.
Service ace!
Spectacular!
What a fast ball!
I throw open the door to my heart because we're starting
Nice serve there, Oka!
Keep it up!
Have been hobbling in zigzags but it's about time I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew, youth is always an eventful season!
30-0.
Look closely at her moves,
then hit where it hurts!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
40-0.
Step boldly ahead and hit!
But your answer has passed me by, wind is carrying it away!
Game! 1-0, Oka!
Amazing! It's a love-game!
Oka...
It's my endless dreaming still fresh in my memory
It's like stepping on a marsh countless times to find a solid path
Right... Right!
It's my endless dreaming, so I keep on walking
Towards the blessed season of me and you
It's almost unbelievable, Papa!
This match is so one-sided!
Maybe Maria is out of form?
No, wrong.
It's Hiromi's form that is so fearsome.
To the point of nullifying Maria's power!
For some reason, I have this sensation - my body is so light,
I can move exactly the way Coach taught me.
This sensation of pure and unobstructed perception...
A player endowed with outstanding potential
suddenly hits her prime form one of these days,
making progress by leaps and bounds.
Certainly, for Hiromi, that time is right now.
However... The higher peaks she reaches while here,
when she finds out about Munakata's death,
the more bottomless will be her despair of a player!
40-15!
It's match point now!
I am... I am going to lose?
The Great Maria Young is losing this so pitifully?
No, that cannot be true.
Right, I must be seeing a bad dream.
Bad dream!
That's the only way...
The only way I'd ever lose!
Game set!
Match won by Hiromi Oka.
Won...
I just...
Won it, Coach!
Jin, you used to always have Oka on your mind.
Leave it to me to make it OK.
Whichever hell Oka Hiromi lands into after this,
I will... I will make sure...
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I am Aikawa Maki.
It's terrible, everyone finds out about Coach Munakata!
Madame Butterfly and Ozaki too...
Hiromi is the only one to remain ignorant.
Despite that, she's knitting
a muffler for Coach, our Hiromi!
But until the tour is over,
Hiromi must not, by all means, find out!
Don't lose, Hiromi!
Everybody's rooting for you!
Next episode:
New York Melancholy