I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Japan's Junior Championship
First set! Game count: 6-2 for Oka!
However close...
No matter how close the liaison of hearts is,
even if the two travel the same road,
struggling through it hand in hand.
Eventually, one of them will be left behind.
Even if a long unseen way still lies ahead.
When that happens, one must walk the rest of the way
completely by himself.
If such predestination is true for us as well,
then I'm certainly the one quitting the journey first.
What words should I bequeath to her?
What feelings should I confess?
How should I best spend the little time I have left?
Daigo.
I accepted this predestination long ago.
So I was supposed to be fully prepared for its arrival.
And yet...
And yet, I keep...
I still keep
chasing her smile time after time,
in occasional blankness of my mind.
Since I discovered Oka Hiromi, and we became traveling companions, 3 years have passed.
Every single moment
has been flooded with thousands of thoughts.
Every single glimpse of light
has been a blessing from the eternal sun.
And so I thought I would meet
the oncoming parting fully prepared.
But the time for that parting is already imminent.
Therefore, friend...
I want to meet you again!
Episode 1
The promise of one and only best friend
Go for it, Hiromi!
It's already apparent, isn't it, Jin?
A new champion is being born as we speak.
Are you happy?
Don't say nonsense.
She'll be a champion, but after you and Madame B. went to university this year, it's a trivial High School Champion.
"Had we participated, she'd win regardless."
So says the inscription on that frown.
You should express your emotions frankly
every once in a while.
Advantage: Oka!
She did it!
Game count: 6-2, 6-4.
Set count: 2-0 for Oka!
There's more, Hiromi!
Have you seen this morning's sports news?
Haven't seen it yet.
"Women tennis world hope has been born.
New champion of Japanese juniors, Oka Hiromi.
3rd year at Prefectural Nishi High.
Munakata-Oka teacher-student combo is unstoppable!"
Are you listening, Hiromi?
I am listless...
"The rate of Oka's growth in tennis
deserves a special notion.
She was a complete novice
when Coach Munakata discovered her.
Less than 3 years passed
since she first played tennis.
Therefore, in addition to Oka's natural predisposition,
the specialists credit Coach Munakata
with astonishing adaptability."
That's exactly what they wrote!
What time is it now?
Almost 9 o'clock.
How about we go to movies in the afternoon?
Have an irregular holiday!
9 o'clock!?
You don't have to yell, Hiromi.
I'm late to the meeting!
At 9 in Madame Butterfly's mansion!
Chairman Ryuzaki summoned me there!
On occasion of All-Japan junior championship
conclusion yesterday,
Tennis Association Board
came up with a following resolution:
With young players
from universities and high schools as the core,
we will compose a team of 8 men and 8 women
for a tour to America.
Everyone present has been selected
to represent Nishi High.
Tour to America?
Although Todo, Ozaki and finally, my daughter Reika
all have already graduated from Nishi High this year,
you were enlisted as Munakata's disciples,
who is a coach in charge of this tour's team.
It was also meant to strengthen your teamwork,
so I want you to assist Munakata in every way possible.
Departure is January 15th.
Ain't much time left.
Therefore, I have prepared
a practice schedule for everyone. Oka.
Okay.
Todo.
Ozaki.
Okay.
Ryuzaki.
Among others from Kanto region is Horiki Saeko.
And of course, Midorikawa Ranko.
What an incredible selection of members!
It appears, even the Association can become really earnest,
when it comes to nurturing the youth.
America was chosen as the best place
to get the taste of genuine power tennis in the wild.
Perhaps, it was Coach Munakata's design all along.
...For Oka's sake.
Huh, Todo?
Hey, take it easy, Chiba.
No need to stir it up.
No, I didn't mean to.
On the contrary, I think it's an amazing decision.
Oka Hiromi and Munakata Jin - the dream those two
envisioned may soon come true in front of our eyes.
Coach is paving the way
for player to fight with all her might.
Player returns the favor
by trusting coach unquestioningly.
When Munakata discovered Oka and her dispositions,
I wonder if he trained her not just physically and mentally
for tennis, but also spiritually for their common journey.
"By trusting her partner unquestioningly,
Oka returns the favor..."
Player and coach are just a person and a person
at the end of the day.
A man and a woman, if you will.
Moreover, marvelous man and woman.
Wake up: 6 AM.
Roadwork: 8 kilometers.
Every 2 kilometers, five 50-meter dashes.
Swing - 500 times!
Okay!
Then, at 10, come to Nishi High court.
Every day until the plane,
Ryuzaki Reika will be your opponent.
Madame Butterfly?
My practice opponent?
Not a practice, but a real match!
At least one match per day.
Put up a profound battle,
as if the life is on the line.
Life?
That's right.
Mine and yours.
Winter holidays are for going to mall,
not the sports center!
Eve is coming, Christmas is almost here already!
Say, say, Hiromi,
what will you wear for the party?
Party?
No way! Hiromi, we've settled on celebrating your victory
with a grandiose party! Didn't you forget?
I see. Then, maybe that special stadium jumper.
No hint of charm!
Maki, what about you?
Mickey Mouse jean jacket!
The best of three set match.
Ryuzaki's service. Play!
Let's do it, Madame Butterfly.
Those two aren't joking.
Out!
Was close...
That receive...
I have never seen it before.
When did she learn to pull off that sort of hit?
What takes us a year to master,
she goes through in a course of a month.
She and coach Munakata.
Why you don't eat, Hiromi?
It'll become soggy.
I need to go make a quick call.
Whom to? Where to? Hey!
Well... With life on the line,
I lost.
I'm sorry. I took one set, but that's about it.
What about winning tomorrow?
The day after tomorrow?
The day after that?
What about "in a week?"
By that time, perhaps I can...
That means, the life is not yet lost.
I was busy with Association business today.
But tomorrow I'm coming to Nishi High.
See you.
Hiromi, what's the matter?
Reika, I guess you picked up
that 1000 swings practice again?
Yes, because Oka also works hard.
Daigo, hurry up so I could introduce you to Oka.
While I still have enough strength.
Daigo...
Good morning, Jin. You awake?
Jin?
Ranko, is that you?
What's the matter?
My, thank goodness.
Reply quicker next time.
I'm worried you know.
Say, did you really visit hospital
on the day of appointment?
When I get to America,
I won't be able to wake you up every morning like this.
Don't say nonsense, I'm going there too.
No way. You shouldn't exert yourself.
I know, because I track your physical condition
by the tone of your voice every morn.
I didn't ask you to bother.
Starting tomorrow, don't come.
You, too, need extensive training for the tour.
Are you trying to strip me of this privilege?
The privilege of being your sister.
We may have had different mothers,
we may have been brought up separately,
but I'm still your sister.
Are you going out?
I'll give you a ride.
Nishi High, I guess?
If you strip me off this privilege,
I'll disclose it to everyone. The truth about your health.
Ranko...
Just kidding.
Poor joke. Sorry.
But jokes aside, I sometimes wonder,
wouldn't it be better for you this way.
Whenever I give it a thought,
I can't help worrying ever so much about you.
Coach, this rally has been going like that
for 5 minutes already.
Neither is willing to give up that one point.
Oh no!
0-15!
Hold it! Hold that count!
Trivial mistakes, like the one just now,
should not affect this match's count!
In this game, only when any side
scores a hard-won ace, add points.
Power vs. power, technique vs. technique -
in this clash, every point is a feat.
I forbid you to rely on opponent's good or bad luck
in finishing this match.
Oka.
Yes?
Your trivial mistake in particular
is caused by a flawed basic technique
due to lack of career, like that of Ryuzaki.
For every trivial mistake made,
make a lap around sports ground after the match.
Okay.
Coach...
Oka.
Yes?
It's your service now.
Okay!
Coach, once again, I lost to Madame Butterfly.
However, today I managed to bring it to tie break
and lost in a close match.
One week later - I'm not sure.
But before we leave for America,
I'll definitely win. Definitely.
So for the moment,
my happiness is boundless,
with such an amazing mentor by my side.
Did you know? After every match, Madame Butterfly
also does laps around the sports ground along with me.
For the number of her mistakes.
And I'm just so happy!
I must do my best, tomorrow too!
Alright, everyone!
Listen closely starting now.
Nishi High tennis club,
along with the alumni association,
will piggyback on tonight's Christmas party
to get festive on two occasions at once!
First being the birth of All-Japan's juniors
new champion!
Oka Hiromi's flight into the world!
Thank you. Thank you.
Finally, the second one is
this time's tour to America members selection
final approval!
And now, let me introduce those members.
Todo Takayuki.
Although still university's 1st year, swift enough
to already be Kanto university students champion!
Ozaki Yu!
You may know him
as Nishi High's male team ex-captain.
Embarrassed himself
by being #2 among Kanto students this year.
Next year, he promised to break Todo's leg
to emerge as the ultimate winner!
Ryuzaki Reika.
As a Nishi High student,
held a record of 143 consecutive victories!
Presently, as a Saint Maria Women's College student,
keeps mounting that record.
With this superb play,
she truly is Madame Butterfly!
Okay, one more spot!
Collateral new star,
Oka Hiromi. Do your best!
Glad to have your support!
Miss Oka! V-sign, V-sign!
V...
Won't do, more expression!
V!
I think, I'll also withdraw my part-time savings
to follow everyone to America shortly after.
As a Nishi High's journalism club old boy,
for those supposed to carry Japan's tennis
on their shoulders from now on,
whichever country life hurls them in,
I want to document it.
Oh, by the way. Hiromi, here.
Merry Christmas!
I almost forgot too.
Jingle Bells!
Here.
How sumptuous!
I even get 2!
Wait, this one's not for you.
How mystifying.
If not me, then a boy!
Something like a wallet? Mystifying!
Who, who, who??
Somewho...
I see.
He didn't bother to come tonight.
Though the club sent him official invitation!
Unbelievable.
It was also his adorable disciple's victory party!
Oi, Munakata! That's haughty!
A snow...
A day off from practice?
They gave us a furlough just for today.
So, what are you up to?
Conversational English.
I thought I should do at least that.
Maki, you?
From under kotatsu, succumbing to winter gluttony
with gaufre, rice crackers and shortcakes!
Nice to meet you.
Hello!
Excuse me...
Excuse me?
Excuse me!
My, welcome.
Been a long time, yes?
Well...
You already have some guest?
Yes. Jin's ancient friend came to see him.
Then, I'll come back another time.
Is it Oka?
Yes!
Come on in, we're waiting.
I introduce: Nishi High's Oka Hiromi.
Well... You can call me just Oka.
Sorry for popping in unannounced.
And... I will have my leave soon enough.
Name's Katsura. Katsura Daigo.
A monk?
Yes, a real monk.
Somehow, Coach Munakata's bosom friend
ended up being a devoted head-shaven monk.
You talked to him?
He made me drink.
Made you drink?
Just a bit.
We drank while observing the snowfall.
First time meeting a monk?
Yes.
Though they're called monks,
underneath the bare skull, it's but an ordinary person.
However, they also usually drink
just a bit too much sake.
You in particular.
It was the first time ever I saw coach Munakata
laughing so blissfully while telling stories.
Laughing? Our coach?
Guffawing at the top of his lungs.
I got to see her, at last.
The one you bet it all on,
the hidden gem you entrust to me fully.
By exchanging letters with you,
I thought I'd find out everything I need to know about Oka.
But seeing her in person still was a shock.
What an unthinkable kind of player.
But more than anything...
fortunate and terrifying at the same time
is that she's still clueless about the truth.
But she'll find out now, one way or another.
It'll become complicated from now on.
Shall we go to sleep?
It's getting late.
Hey, it's fine.
I can get my futon myself.
Jin!
Don't raise voice...
It's finally here...
How many weeks left?
At least... At least, give me just enough time
to send them off undisturbed.
Jin!
Daigo, do it for me.
Take care of it for me.
Jin, I devoted these last 5 years fully
to keeping that one promise to you!
I'd do everything in my power regardless!
Listen, Daigo.
What we're trying to pull off...
It's a... It's a challenge
that would take a miracle to overcome!
I know it. I know it all, Jin.
Oka!
Todo?
Good morning!
I heard, coach Munakata
got hospitalized last night.
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I'm Aikawa Maki, Hiromi's friend.
That Demon Coach Munakata got hospitalized.
What will become of Hiromi,
who cares so much for Coach?
Just as she's about to embark on a tour to America!
I wonder if Coach cares about Hiromi at least a bit!
Though, admittedly, this Coach's hospitalization
is kinda worrying...
Next episode:
Oka, aim for the ace!
Look forward to it!