I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
I can see it,
Todo is in agony now.
It's been two weeks
since Coach Munakata passed away.
Of the entire tour team,
Todo is the only one aware of that.
Todo tries his best to not cave in
under the huge pressure of this news, fighting ferociously.
But in tournament, he lacks his usual grandeur,
struggling hard even against trifling opponents.
In 1st and 2nd rounds,
he managed to win somehow.
But in his current state of mind,
even getting into the Best 8 would take a miracle.
Mr. Katsura, the decisive measures you took
upon Coach Munakata's death
are subject to my deep admiration these days.
By postponing the announcement
of Coach Munakata's death until the end of this tour,
you helped to conceal it from everyone,
and from Oka in particular.
Finally, by entrusting Oka to a famous Australian coach, Mr. Reynolds, you allowed us to fulfill this tour's purpose.
Have no worries.
Naturally, Oka, along with Madame Butterfly and Ozaki,
still has no idea about this death.
Ozaki took the 3rd round effortlessly,
with his natural doggedness.
Madame Butterfly secured herself the place
in A-block's Best 8 among other foreign players.
Her power is dazzling.
As for Oka, Mr. Reynolds keeps her shaped up by packing her between-matches time tightly with intensive training.
She advanced all the way
to B-block quarterfinals.
Episode 4
New York Melancholy
Now, now...
I wonder if I should be doing this by myself.
Coach's style is approximately that of a foreigner,
so the size should match, I think.
Not quite that.
Wrong, all wrong!
What souvenir should I get for Coach?
Nothing is strikingly good here.
You never managed to decide
on a souvenir for Coach, didn't you?
Yeah...
But... How do you know
I was looking for a souvenir for Coach?
I can understand that much.
Later, when you're free,
come to my room, okay?
Angie Reynolds.
Matchups for quarter-finals
have been announced.
So I came here to inform you personally.
I'm the one you'll be playing against.
Although dad is delirious about coaching you for now,
once I defeat you, dad will certainly come to his senses.
Therefore, whatever it takes,
I am going to defeat you, girl.
Oka.
Yes?
Make sure to come to your match with Angie
thoroughly prepared.
Not only Coach Reynolds has always been
Angie's coach only, he is also her father.
Yet Mr. Reynolds favored you over his daughter.
Imagine Coach Munakata
favoring someone else over you.
Moreover, you get to play a match against that person,
Oka, how do you think you'd react?
Such a thing, I...
Cannot even fathom!
In this match, your opponent
is nothing like anyone you faced before.
Okay.
On the TV, our Japan's team roster
is the hottest topic it seems!
The two of us are also receiving
some special attention.
I see.
With that in mind,
what in the world happened in today's match?
For you, to yield one set to such an opponent...
I was a bit out of shape.
All's well that ends well, I guess,
but you really had us nervous for a moment there!
I did my best.
You aren't sick somehow, are you?
You think a sick man would do a roadwork like that
immediately after the match?
It seems Coach Munakata's condition was serious.
If Oka finds out, she'll probably be discouraged.
Perhaps, this guy also worries about her,
so he's out of tune himself.
That's it. That must be it.
I can't think of any other cause.
Coach Munakata is no longer with us.
But I can't tell anyone, not even you, about it.
You have to forgive me, Ozaki.
Madame Butterfly...
She might have some news about it.
Yes. I see.
Everyone is learning diligently, father.
Foreigners are mostly fine players too.
Spurred by Oka's vigor,
the entire team is fighting hard to win now!
Father? You've been acting strange lately.
Father?
Is something wrong back home?
You don't mind
sharing your bad mood it with me, do you?
Reika, I think we've had this kind of talk before.
The one directly responsible for Oka Hiromi's birth
as a tennis player, Ryuzaki Reika, it is you!
So I always asked you to be a good mentor for Oka,
both in game and in life.
Yes, I remember it well.
It helps to uphold my own confidence as well.
While Coach Munakata devotes his life fully to Oka,
I take pride in being a direct cause for her birth.
Yes, Munakata devoted to her the rest of his life,
but to Oka Hiromi's tennis, you effectively were the mother.
Father, just now,
why did you put it this way?
Devoted the rest of his life?
Reika, I have faith in you.
I have faith in you.
No way...
I have my faith in you!
I thought Coach's detailed checkup
just takes longer than it should...
Father, just when I called you the other day...
About such a thing...
And Hiromi...
I can't believe he left Hiromi behind...
This can't be...
Munakata... Jin.
Crap... I was so inconsiderate...
What have I done!
I'm doing my best.
Todo, we're supposed to be friends.
Why... Why didn't you tell me a word?!
What a dimwit.
What a dimwit!
Todo and Madame Butterfly
are closer to Oka than anyone!
They both will probably end up
spiraling into desperation, along with Oka.
I have to...
I have to stand fast for them!
Ms. Ryuzaki, this is Oka.
Hiromi...
Just a moment!
I have to stay strong.
After all, it will hurt her more than anyone else.
You understand?
Hiromi must not notice a single thing off!
Come in!
Well, excuse me...
What is it, Oka?
Well... About that...
I wanted to ask you
to teach me knitting wool yarn, you see.
I figured I should make a hand-knit muffler
as a souvenir for Coach Munakata.
So I bought this wool yarn in the supermarket.
I will show Demon Coach, I am perfectly capable
of doing this kind of girly things as well!
He'd drop his jaw amazed, I imagine.
And... Just basics is enough.
Just one simple way to knit.
I understand, Oka. Perfectly.
This Oka Hiromi is no prowessless lass, Coach!
This lesson you'll remember for good!
Should I really be doing this now?
I'm playing quarter-finals tomorrow.
Angie Reynolds.
My tomorrow's opponent, Coach.
A mighty contender.
But tonight, Coach,
knitting this muffler is my first priority!
Hiromi!
When doing a passing shot,
try to hit behind my back!
Okay!
Apply more power!
Received!
Nailed it!
A stunning passing shot!
Just an ordinary ball to her,
it hits bullseye of my blind spot!
Without a single clue of her true power,
she hits such a ball casually!
Man named Munakata that brought this girl up
treasured her for good reason.
Papa!
Angie.
Papa, you know,
I'm playing a match this afternoon.
An important one, quarterfinals!
Can you give me the usual
before-the-match intense training?
I think my backhand receive hitting point
became too loose lately.
Angie, at the moment,
I'm busy coaching Oka.
With Papa's help,
I'll fasten it back in place at once!
Leave the court.
I'm helping Oka practice now.
I heard you.
Angie!
It's all right!
I will always love my Papa no matter what!
Come on!
Let's resume it.
Okay!
Make sure to remember well the ball course
of our today's rally.
Those would be Angie's crown ball courses
for today's showdown.
Those passing shots from earlier may yield you initiative
in the match, if you persist in hitting them thoughtfully.
But why?
Why are you confiding Angie's crown ball to me?
You are Angie's...
And she is my daughter.
It's because I love her. She is an apple of my eye
that I don't stop caring about at all times.
But all this treatment
she only receives as my daughter.
I think, Munakata favored you
over his sister Midorikawa Ranko, didn't he?
Well, why can't I favor you as well
over my daughter Angie?
One can choose from a variety of roads
to put his life on the line.
But while traveling the chosen road,
you have to make sacrifices to let your soul grow.
It is always the right course of action.
Therefore, when the time comes
to choose a road companion,
you shouldn't favor anyone
merely on the grounds of being your offspring or sibling.
Although putting that into practice
is seldom a simple task.
Hiromi, you must know it better than anyone.
With boundless love
and readiness to traverse the edge of the world,
there was a man who chose you as a companion
to share both good and bad times,
Munakata Jin,
who will forever stay by your side.
And so, your cause
should be aided with all seriousness.
Can you now see why I'm here?
Yes, coach.
Munakata Jin
Like the old times, today
we exchange hits until we drop dead?
Yeah!
Brother...
Brother!
Me and Munakata
talked about many different things.
There was but a single time this pouty man
livened up when telling me about this one girl.
"It's actually a secret,
but turns out I've got quite a lovely little sister."
That man, who looked like sulkiness was his trademark,
suddenly became so gleeful while talking about her:
"For now, we can't play together yet.
But one day, when I start doing tennis just for fun,
I want to team up with my sister and play in pairs."
As only child in family,
I was a wee bit jealous.
This... He wanted this...
But...
But now...
He's gone!
The best of three set match.
Reynolds' service. Play!
Papa taught Reynolds family tennis to me personally.
There's no way it loses to a player
who plays tennis for less than 3 years of her life.
This one's mine!
We'll see about that!
15-0.
Impressive!
Whatever it takes,
with this, I'll make Papa return!
Angie, I like that determination.
By clashing with the right opponent,
you were able to find this determination in you!
Angie moves even better than usual.
30-0.
This is authentic power tennis!
Oka, are you not one bit jealous
of Todo's or Ozaki's male tennis?
Of that Todo's power?
All right!
Get this!
What I taught her just this morning,
Hiromi have mastered already.
What a child, Christ's sake!
Oka's moves became much sharper suddenly.
She regained her composure.
Hiromi!
This shouldn't be possible!
Advantage: Oka!
Oka, aim for the ace!
Okay, Coach!
Game set.
Match won by... Oka!
Won...
Coach Munakata...
With every Oka's victory,
the return day draws closer.
When I think of Oka finding out the truth, I...
Todo, I'm going to practice.
You coming along?
You mustn't lose your own match.
If befalls on us now to stand strong for her.
Ozaki, you...
Excuse me.
I will also join them for practice.
I see. Everyone knows at this point?
Everyone is trying earnestly
to act the most open way about it.
Mr. Munakata, you must be the happiest man ever
to have such wonderful students.
Hiromi, I have lost.
But don't forget, next time Papa coaches me again,
he'll warn me about your weak points as well.
I have faith in it.
Papa will definitely return to me in the end.
Nice play, Hiromi.
Thank you, Angie.
Coach, I defeated Angie Reynolds today,
the prominent contender!
I never thought I'd make it this far -
into semifinals!
Coach, it's a shame you're missing all of this.
But when I return home with it,
you'll receive the most detailed record.
And then I'll wrap this muffler around your neck!
My knitting may be imperfect,
but it's full of boundless love!
You understand, Munakata Jin?
Completed!
Cheeeeers!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I'm Aikawa Maki.
Coach, Hiromi is coming back at last!
And with a silver medal from finals!
She sure is in for a big shock,
to find out Coach Munakata is no more.
I'm scared. The moment Hiromi finds out
will be dreadful.
And who in the world is going to deliver to Hiromi
the news of such magnitude?
Next episode:
The Diary Left Behind