Video by Pachinko      Subs by Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Goodbye.
Never say Goodbye!
Okay.
Take care.
You too, Todo.
A scorching sun, a violent wind, and my burnt out heart
became heralds of autumn, inevitably reclaiming its rights.
It was only later when I started to understand
this summer was nothing special in the first place.
The Tokyo Cup is Just a week away now, right?
Making any progress?
Little by little.
Todo is so lucky to have left.
Still no idea when is he coming home?
I don't know...
Episode 4
Todo, I want to see you.....
I don't know through what, but he somehow knew for sure
she will come to see him off.
Even when the flight was minutes away, Todo was unwilling to leave his cafe seat.
He was waiting for her.
He knew Oka is coming.
Come to think of it, she was in Coach Katsura's temple
when Todo trained there.
When was the first time you noticed it?
Had I not known about Oka and Todo for sure,
it would still be the most natural thing.
Ever since her appearance at Nishi High,
Oka was growing fond of Todo.
Todo was also not indifferent to Oka's presence.
Oka is 19, Todo is 21.
Each one of them has each one's respective moral standards.
Whenever you grow affectionate or loving for a person,
no third party is allowed to interfere.
Still, how come that both for Todo and Oka
the prime moments of their lives are now?
What's left is to watch from outside.
Don't tell me, you had feelings for Oka yourself?
So ardent, I almost got burned.
So undisclosed, I never dared to say a word.
But now we can just watch at them.
So... He has not been it touch yet?
Can't be any other way with that fellow.
I only coaxed him to promise coming in touch once a week.
At the moment, preliminary matches for the right to enter
the US Open Championship are held in New York.
He should be taking part in those.
Wait, though.
Those preliminaries were supposed to end two days ago.
Then he certainly succeeded in preliminaries
and is probably busy preparing for real matches.
Madame Butterfly doesn't seem to know.
About those two.
I'll go for a swim.
Alright, that's better!
Then, this time try returning exactly to the line!
Okay!
Apply more drive to the ball!
Your shortcoming is in the way you step!
Okay!
About 10 days have passed since then.
How have you been doing?
Was New York a welcoming place?
Finally... Are you doing fine?
I think, it's about time you finally come in touch with me,
I get more agitated by a day.
I'm sure, you will prefer to bless me with a letter
over anyone else.
I look forward to it.
Because this will give me Todo's address in New York.
And as soon as I know it,
I will write you letters every single day!
As the Tokyo Cup is approaching,
my special practices get tougher too.
But I will still find time to write to you every day.
Perhaps, there won't be a whole lot of things to write about.
But my heart only really trembles while I'm composing those.
Seriously...
What are you thinking about?
40-0.
Oka, rainy days won't cease in New York. Oka...
International call, please.
To New York, 211...
I tried to get in touch with New York by phone.
You found out what Todo's phone number is?
Not with him.
A correspondent from my university lives there.
He also knows Todo well,
so I asked if he has heard anything.
Is that you, master? Chiba speaks.
Happy to hear from you.
There was this one match,
ended 2 days ago...
Hiromi!
Yes?
Hiromi, there's a letter for you.
Okay!
An airmail. From New York!
Hiromi? I'll leave it down here!
Thanks!
Oka,
are you doing fine?
The rainy days seem to never cease in New York.
I got myself a small apartment
along one of the rivers near Central Park.
The building is old,
but the area is quiet and peaceful.
First, before I describe to you the events of the recent days,
thank you for coming to see me in the airport.
Too bad we didn't have time to talk unhurriedly over dinner.
But I'm still happy to have seen you.
The figure of you looking desperately for me
in this huge airport lobby will forever remain in my memory.
Is has become the most precious gem for me.
Well then.
By the time you receive this letter
the outcome of my first match in America
will probably be already published.
Of course, I will positively win this match
and will then be on my way to the next goal.
I hope you do your best in the coming Tokyo Cup as well.
The next letter should follow soon enough. Until then...
Last ten!
Okay...
Aight! Last one!
What happened?
Your moves are a lot sharper than usual.
They radiate some kind of delight.
No, there's nothing...
What a truly eccentric buddy you are.
Of all the disparate athletes I've seen,
not a single one could manifest their state of mind
in the play as lucidly as you do.
But there really is nothing to affect me!
I'm not happier than usual...
Munakata struggled, trying to erase that habit off your hands.
Excuse me, did you just say...
Munakata was...
Munakata Jin was probably
wary of this more than anything.
Athletes whose play depends on the state of their mind
can play like true geniuses while they're happy,
but when they feel bad, they play like beginners.
Oka.
Whatever wonderful things are happening to you now,
put them aside.
Put aside?
Exactly.
Hiromi?
Yes?
Ozaki and Chiba are here today.
I came to ask if you would like to dine with us.
Sure! With pleasure.
Chiba, Ozaki,
that Chinese restaurant was really something.
Thanks for the treat!
Nevermind. Ozaki's idea. Every once in a while
we should somehow materialize our support.
Since I had to miss the Tokyo Cup myself,
I will at least encourage the rest of Nishi High - you two.
Shouldn't you also encourage Todo in New York?
Actually, it was Todo who I wanted to talk about.
A summary returned from my New York acquaintance.
Todo's first match:
6-1, 6-2, 6-0.
A shutout victory. I had no doubt Todo...
No. Todo has been crushed miserably.
It was raining on the court,
so only about fifty spectators attended.
His opponent was the rising pro
placed 300th in the rankings.
But Todo's arms and legs seemed to have failed him.
The match was a preliminary for preliminary.
But for Japan Open Champion Todo, the wall behind which
is the world turned out to be too thick and high.
I didn't want to believe it.
But the facts I have attest to this.
What is in this fellow Todo's head now?
And how should we think of this?
He is a seasoned player. He still has options.
He is used to challenges.
Even if he goes down once or twice,
it does not mean he lost everything.
The final one point...
Until it's scored, victory is possible.
So he unleashes his fighting spirit,
chasing the ball further.
However, the moment the match is declared finished,
he has to leave the court meekly.
And even if it makes him spill a big involuntary tear, he leaves.
Say, what you asserted a few days ago...
You said Todo who has been playing tennis since infancy
has already passed his peak.
And that by turning a pro now
he will never be able to stand on the top.
But standing on the top is exactly what Todo aims at...
And now it is all happening
in precise accordance to your words.
I don't want you to get me wrong, Hiromi.
In fact, I was just... I was just speaking on my account.
I was sure that for Todo
it would be no different than for me.
But it does not mean he should give up surmounting that wall
by turning pro and challenging the world.
After all, he is tenfold more courageous than I am.
Don't worry.
He'll figure something out.
It's not about winning or losing,
but rather him tackling whatever is tormenting him.
Tackling it...
That's right. He embarked on this path
not for anyone else, but for himself.
Nothing would offend him more right now
than sympathy and pity.
I will say just one thing.
Your today's opponent is younger than you.
A second-year high school student.
In consequence of her junior success, this match will become
her first ever in a major All-Japan tournament.
Oka Hiromi
-vs-
Sekiguchi Namiko
That alone would make her
capitalize frantically on your every fault.
You should by no means lose your spirit.
Let your guard down and she'll attack with everything at once.
Okay.
Oka!
Coach, I'm sorry. I do my utmost to keep my spirits high,
but it just keeps getting worse!
This morning I received the second letter from Todo.
Todo composed it when his first major match in America
was already concluded.
However, in that letter he didn't write a word
about this devastating game.
It's so frustrating. He could just say,
"I'll do my best next time!" and I'd be perfectly carefree!
But instead, all he wrote was how much he cares about me.
Oka, how are you doing?
By the time you receive this letter,
your Tokyo Cup matches will surely be in full swing.
It's as though I'm seeing you
running around the court with my own eyes.
I still remember your powerful serve,
your springy killer smash.
Finally, those incredible aces
that always make you smile when scored.
Game! One game to three.
Sekiguchi lead.
Finally, Oka,
I'm sure you will triumph brilliantly.
Therefore I expect a delighted reply from you.
Well then, Oka.
The autumn comes rushing to New York.
In a blink of an eye, Central Park lost all of its greenery,
and the wind has become cold.
In just two more weeks, I believe, the falling leaves
will start dancing their way to the ground. Until then, see you.
That one last point.
Until it is scored, the victory is possible.
So he unleashes his fighting spirit,
chasing the ball further.
However, the moment the match is declared over,
as he stands there stock-still on the court, involuntarily...
However,
at that moment, as he stands on the court stock-still,
he spills a big involuntary tear, I believe.
Seven games to five. Two games to six.
Love game to six. Two sets to one.
Hiromi
Sekiguchi
Match won by Sekiguchi!
What happened, Hiromi?
It was supposed to be an easy game.
Oka, I was hoping to fight through this tournament
alongside with you.
I'm sorry.
What is the matter?
Something makes my body so heavy
I can hardly move it.
Is that so? Get better then. I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Coach, well, I...
You are still allowed to enter the second round.
This championship uses
the double-elimination rule.
Six days after the first round defeat,
the loser is allowed to play a repechage match.
Make sure that in the repechage match
you don't lose miserably like today.
Only then I'll listen to your excuses.
What would offend him most of all now
is other's sympathy and pity.
The autumn is coming to New York at a rapid pace.
The greenery of Central Park
lost its color in a blink of an eye.
The wind has suddenly become so cold.
In just two more weeks, I'm sure...
the falling leaves
will start dancing their way to the ground.
This is wrong.
It's not about sympathy and pity.
That's not how it should be!
Not this way!
This is wrong, Todo.
I want to see you...
I so much want to see Todo!
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
Everything went wrong!
Although Hiromi was admitted to the repechage match,
she told Coach Katsura she won't play it!
In response, Coach Katsura blurted on Hiromi:
"You should make a decision
of what matters to you the most right now!'
What will you do, Hiromi?
You want to go to New York to see Todo?
Coming soon: "No turning back now."