On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
40-15!
Break point serve!
Come on, Hiromi, would you hurry up!
The first match's already started!
I know, I know!
But I just ran all the way from the station!
What was that?
It's your own fault for not waking up earlier!
I wake up early!
But this morning my alarm clock...
No excuses. I waited for you
for half an hour at the entrance.
Honestly! You're late to every match!
Today's the semifinal.
Come on, hurry up and get changed!
Okay!
You're Oka Hiromi from Nishi High?
Yes!
I'm your today's opponent, Kawamura from Ohara High.
And I want you to pass a message to Madame Butterfly.
To Madame Butterfly?
Listen up. Tell her that I, Kawamura Yumi,
definitely haven't forgotten what happened a year ago.
"What happened a year ago?"
That's right, one year ago.
You got that?
The Bloodstained Return From Crisis
Episode 19
Today is the semifinal!
Don't worry! We'll win big today too!
But I hear the pair from Ohara High
is undefeated!
It'll be fine! We have Madame Butterfly.
We've got to do our best.
The first match of the semifinal has now ended.
Players from Nishi and Ohara, taking part
in the second match, please gather on the court.
Oka, are you ready?
Yep. Just one more shoe and I'm done.
Ryuzaki.
Yes?
This is your second match as a new pair.
Lead Oka and play however you want.
I'm not saying a thing today.
Okay.
We'll be cheering for you!
Do your best!
Do your best, Madame Butterfly!
Hiromi, hang in there!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
There's something strange
about Madame Butterfly today.
That's right!
Let's go.
Excuse me.
I was just asked to give you a message, by Kawamura from Ohara High.
It was a strange message.
Yeah, right, she said that she,
"Definitely hasn't forgotten the one year ago."
That's how it was.
The sky looks a little weird today.
Maybe we'll get some rain.
Here comes our school's great pair, at last.
What's that?
Some pro tennis antics.
What a gaudy outfit!
Those eyes are filled with hatred and resentment.
The eyes of that Kawamura
when she looks at Madame Butterfly.
I see.
One year ago.
That's it! One year ago something...
Something happened between these two.
Best-of-three set match.
Nishi High's Ryuzaki-Oka team vs.
Ohara High's Kawamura-Okazaki team.
Nishi High Ryuzaki's service.
Play!
Oh no!
Love-15!
Sorry!
It's strange. Madame Butterfly
somehow doesn't seem very lively.
That can't be right.
Not during such a big match.
Is it my imagination?
My chance!
I've got it!
Shot to the empty right corner!
15-All!
I did it! Quite the smart play
if I do say so myself.
This makes up for my earlier mistake.
What's with those two?
It's like a test of endurance.
No, what's more strange here
is the way they strike the ball.
The way things are going,
this will never end.
Attack the open line!
30-15!
I got it, got it.
You play tennis like a little sleazy thief.
Who taught you this?
Do you think Madame Butterfly will be happy
if you pull tricks like that?
Those eyes… That's right,
she was like this earlier too.
When I noticed the gap in our opponents' defense
and went for the ace in the right corner too.
Madame Butterfly, I…
Oka, I'd like you to do as I say
without another word.
I don't want you to aim
for the lines and corners anymore.
For this match, send the ball
straight back at your opponent.
That's all.
Now, get in position.
Okay.
Hiromi, I'm sorry for dragging you into this too.
Oh no!
30-All!
It's strange, Madame Butterfly
is making major mistakes.
Nishi
Ohara
This is no good.
At this rate, the opponents will take the first set!
Hiromi, do your best!
Oh, my.
It finally started.
If this keeps up we'll lose, no doubt about it.
We'll lose completely.
Madame Butterfly, why no corners?
Why can't we aim for it or the lines now?
Aim for the Ace!
First set: 6-0 for Ohara High!
6 to 0.
To think they'd suffer a straight loss like this.
Ryuzaki, I let you decide how to handle today's match,
but I didn't mean you can decide to lose it!
I know that.
Your attention please.
It has been decided that due to the starting rain,
the second set of current match will be delayed
until the weather possibly gets better.
Players from Nishi and Ohara schools, please return
to your change rooms and wait for our decision.
Hiromi! Hiromi!
What was that?
That first set was awful!
And Madame Butterfly too!
Losing 6 to 0, it's just too terrible!
Hiromi, what are you doing?
Maki, you idiot!
We haven't lost yet!
They've only taken the first set!
But!
Aikawa, it's just as Oka says.
Come on, let's get a seat over there.
Okay.
Ms. Ryuzaki, I did just like you told me.
Madame Butterfly, I stopped aiming
for the opponents corners and lines.
But why? Why did I have to do that?
Hiromi, I'll tell you now.
I didn't plan to tell this to anyone…
But now that I got you involved,
there's no longer any choice.
It was one year ago
at the Kanto Regional Junior Championship.
The singles quarterfinal.
Ohara's Kawamura was a technician
who could contend for first place in Kanto.
Skillfully controlling the ball left and right.
It was a tough battle.
But if I won, it would be my 42nd victory in a row.
A new record in high school girls' tennis at the time.
I couldn't lose, no matter what.
But, with deuce after deuce
she finally took the match point.
And then… And then!
If that ball lands inside the line, I've lost.
The ball was out.
I managed to escape the crisis.
Thinking that, I waited for the referee's call.
But at that moment he had lost sight of the ball.
The linesmen had too.
I don't know by what trick of fate,
but everyone had missed that moment.
In situations like this in tennis, in the spirit of fair play,
it's common to ask the players.
So, the referee asked me
since I had been closest to the ball.
Whether it was out or safe.
I was the only one who had seen it.
Kawamura shouldn't have been able
to see it with me in the way.
Everyone waited for my answer only.
So I answered.
It was out!
The ball crossed the line.
I just said things as they were.
I gave the answer which was to my advantage.
But I swear on my pride as one who has played tennis
since she was a child, that it was no lie.
In the end, having gotten my rhythm back,
the match ended with me winning.
In high spirits, I went to shake her hand.
Next time I meet you on the court,
I definitely won't aim for the lines.
I want us both to fight fair and square
in the center of the court.
Don't you forget it!
Her eyes said, "That ball was safe!"
Her whole frustrated posture conveyed that.
It must have been quite a shock for her.
She changed quite a bit since then.
Rumors say, no matter what sort of match it is,
she stopped hitting balls at the corners altogether.
For a technician like her,
how hard must it have been
to go through matches without attacking the corners?
And now, today.
Having come through that hardship, she stands before me.
Are you telling me to shoot for the lines and corners
against a girl like her?
Maybe, if I had said "The ball was safe," back then,
it would have been better for both of us.
Although it'd be more painful.
I was making nothing but mistakes.
I was about to lose that major match.
No, the ball was out.
I believe you, Madame Butterfly.
You definitely weren't wrong!
That's why I think,
I want us to win this match!
Madame Butterfly, I think we can win
fair and square in center court!
Oka…
Nishi High and Ohara High players,
we will now resume the match.
Please gather on the court.
We lost the first set,
but we can still win this match!
After all, the fact Madame Butterfly shared her pain with me means that…
That she...
She believes in me now!
If I think of that, we can win!
I have to grit my teeth and do my best to win!
Not aiming for lines anymore!
I'll fight them head on,
face to face!
15-Love!
She said her name was Oka Hiromi?
What a brat!
You surprised me!
That's some will power you've got.
Of course! I have Madame Butterfly as my senior!
NIshI
Ohara
You're doing great!
Just a bit more and they'll take the second set!
It's totally different from the first set.
That's right! That's the way, Hiromi!
Madame Butterfly!
Something must have happened
between them in the change room.
Second set: 6-3 for Nishi High!
Ohara
Nishi
Oh no!
40-30!
Match point, Ryuzaki-Oka!
All right! They're on the match point!
Hiromi, hang in there!
One more point and you win!
On the court, everyone is alone, all alone.
My love and my pain
There!
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips.
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Out!
Game set!
Set count: 2-1 for Nishi High's Ryuzaki-Oka!
They did it!
Next up is the finals! The finals!
That ball was certainly out.
I totally lost this time.
Seeing Oka's fighting spirit today…
It's made me feel embarrassed
that I was so caught up on what happened a year ago.
You shouldn't...
Well, Ryuzaki, see you again.
Kawamura…
To Be Continued
With the final match of the
Kanto Junior Championship drawing near…
Hiromi naturally puts a lot more effort into her training.
And on the tennis court glistening in the light of the dawning sun Hiromi sees…
Todo training hard all by himself.
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"Rally in the Morning Sun"
As Hiromi tries to return Todo's powerful serves
her heart shines like the dawning sun!
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo