Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
I'm home!
I returned home!
Wait though.
I'm still feeling kinda feeble.
I'm home, dad, mom...
I'm sorry for making you worry.
First, I should unearth myself out of all this plotting.
Mom will surely start wailing.
Dad will flip out instantly.
He has every reason after all.
Instead, I can just come back,
drop a hi and head upstairs immediately.
Observe for a while, bide my time.
It's here!
Still...
Whichever the way I choose,
I remain guilty.
I wasn't even close to Karuizawa.
I went to New York overseas!
"I'm back..."
I should just walk right in without thinking.
It's my home after all. The home where my mom and dad are!
I'm back!
I'm back, Goemon.
Welcome back.
We're glad you're back!
Here, your tea.
Or would you prefer coffee?
No, tea is fine.
Wait a little longer for supper, will you?
Dad, mom.
I must have caused you a worry...
Honey, the bath!
Would you mind preparing a bath?
That's right! Bath is the best conclusion to a trip!
Episode 8
The final
repechage Match... !
Good morning.
What's that supposed to be?
It's wine!
A souvenir from New York for you.
And... it is delicious. Must be.
Also, starting tomorrow,
I will return to my practices!
I'm so sorry for being such a nuisance!
If it wasn't for you being a woman,
I'd give you a blow to deform your skull.
Come inside, we need to talk.
Okay!
An international women tennis tournament
will be held next month.
Most of the participants are soon-to-be pro.
Only two amateurs from Japan will participate -
Ryuzaki and you, Oka.
Coach...
That is, if this time you're willing to compete.
I'll do it! I'll compete!
Then, for today, you're free to go.
I will go there.
Let me participate, please.
Oka, take a sip too.
No.
Now I see.
You really are back.
Welcome back.
I was waiting.
I'm home!
I have so much to ask you about.
What is that gross giggling about?
Good Lord, you just returned to Japan,
but already have the game scheduled?
Hiromi, you sure is an eager beaver.
It's nothing! Tell you what,
I'm fired up about tennis now!
I figured you seem all brightened up!
Great, great! Hiromi is doing great!
Quit it!
So, so, how did everything go between you and Todo?
I demand a report with ins and outs!
Todo is doing just well.
The report is over!
Why is that so stingy?
Make it two, pops.
Just a moment!
But at least, I could reach the depths of Todo's heart
for the first time, in America.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure how to put it, but somehow it feels
like we're connected even when far away.
It feels like Todo is somewhere around.
Like a Red String? Naughty girl!
Speaking of that, I almost forgot!
Here, for you.
A souvenir.
You've been looking after me on so many occasions.
My, my, how most sudden!
Can I open it?
Sure thing!
What a spicy souvenir!
Which may only mean you've made up your mind
for something resolute, have you?
Cut it out!
I'm curious!
We have everything prepared,
Coach Katsura.
Thank you.
Oka is also to arrive here any minute.
Come.
This way please.
Hiromi has returned from New York?
I came back home the night before yesterday. And
- I sincerely...
- Did you make it?
You're admitted to this match, right?
Tell me that you have it sorted.
That you made it in time.
Well...
Thank God. Had you missed it,
I'd have no idea what to do next.
Now come on in.
Coach Katsura is already waiting.
Actually, Ms. Ryuzaki, I am... I am...
Be my guest. Now.
She is a guest player from America.
Gene Ryder, 17.
One of this tournament's favorites.
The Queen's Cup tennis tournament
will become her first public appearance this year.
So far, all the most promising players
are from overseas.
She is among the players
currently enjoying the whole world's close attention.
In addition to her innate springiness,
she also possesses the "Hungry Spirit," which is rare these days.
This type of players engages more of their reserved resources,
the stronger their opponent gets.
Gene Ryder - don't forget.
Finally, there is one more.
Spaniard Marchesa Broir, 14 years old.
The runner-up of last year Australia's Open Championship.
Young but an adroit player,
that doesn't play around.
Both parents are former pro-players.
Those skills were cultivated in her from infancy.
A player of first-class strength.
Her instantaneous strength and reflexes
are considered prodigious.
This video will make a great help
for the next month's tournament.
I want you to nail it well into your head, Oka.
Okay!
We're sorry for having to trouble you with this.
No, as soon as I lay my hand on a material like this,
I'll show it to you as well.
It's in my interest for both Oka and Reika to see it.
Todo has already embarked on a transfer to pro,
but he'll still have to struggle for a while.
While Ozaki effectively deserted the battlefield!
The Japanese tennis world
is in a steep decline right now!
The two of you here are clearly capable of turning the tide.
You can muster a new life in it by showing a magnificent play!
I'm not the only one believing in it.
Can you believe it, dear?
What?
Our girl went abroad all alone
and returned here all alone.
So what?
What do you mean "so what?"
She's already 19, after all.
No, she's still just 19.
There is one time proven
colleague of mine.
What about this gentleman?
He is a tennis club coach,
specialized in teaching male university students.
Since last week, this man
conducts a two-week training course in his camp.
If you are still committed to the cause,
I can arrange your participation in it, as an exception.
How about it?
It's a male only camp,
so you can't weep over how hard it is.
I agree!
Coach, please let me participate.
I want it, I agree!
Alright.
- Fight!
- Fight.
You! Quit muttering to yourself!
I can't hear you!
- Os!
- Os.
Yamakura!
Back to duty, ya hear me!?
That's totally him.
Oi, Daigo! Who'd think!
And what a cutie you have here too!
You there!
No staring 'round!
Glad you could make it.
Yeah, I'm happy to see you too.
I am Coach's colleague.
I am Oka.
Very pleased to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you from Daigo.
You must be used to harsh male practices,
so don't expect a special treatment.
Okay.
I won't get a single word in this.
Obey colleague's command unquestioningly.
Okay!
Todo, are you doing fine?
For the moment, to prepare for my next game,
I moved to a remote training camp.
I am alone among all the male players of this camp.
Alright, that's enough!
Hundred sit-ups now!
1! 2! 3! 4!
5!
6! 7! 8!
I'm constantly reminded how much I'm different,
as physical strength is above all here.
Every day, as soon as the practice is over,
I collapse worn-out.
I often wonder, how is Todo doing.
Be it down in New York,
be it in Boston. Perhaps, those endless thoughts
are what lets me carry on doing my best.
Whenever there's no training, I contemplate
the soundless and spacious scenery of Tateshina.
Imagining that Todo is also here.
Sure you want to go this far, Daigo?
Yes, it's decided.
The sooner we start, the better.
But still...
Worries aside. Moreover, make sure to pick
the most undaunted guy on your side.
Here, thank you for waiting.
Everyone!
Listen to me for a second now!
Our training program
is entering the middle stage.
To maintain the spirit of competition,
we play training matches now!
The bouts will be three-set matches.
But you should still do your best, as in an official game!
Okay!
Then, I'm announcing the upcoming matchups.
The first match of the first day - Takagi vs. Takeyuchi.
The second game.
Fujisaki vs. Mano.
The third game.
Naito vs. Oka.
Hey...
Don't fret. If you fail this interclass practice,
I'm signing you out of Queen's Cup.
Thanks for the meal!
Ma'am, thanks for the meal,
it was great!
Lucky you, Naito.
Beating a woman is not a luck but a misfortune.
Coach!
It's no use, Coach! I don't stand a single chance.
The opponent is a male!
I'm ready for any training you deem adequate,
and I'm full of determination! But...
If I lose today, I'm missing the Queen's Cup tournament!
This is nonsense!
How can I...
The hell is that whining?
Retreating again!?
You've already thrown away the first match,
then betrayed everyone by running away from a repechage match.
Don't tell me you already forgot it.
Consider today's game
to be your last and ultimate repechage match.
However mighty the opponent is!
This is your best ever chance to prove everyone
you are capable of meeting expectations!
And for this, you have to first
meet my expectations splendidly.
For you, who have once dumped tennis away,
the victory in today's match will decide everything!
To stand on the start line again, it's essential!
Only the victory?
What if I lose after all?
Then for Munakata, me and Oka Hiromi everything is over.
It's as simple as that.
Match - Fujisaki!
Next, we move on
to the third match of the day!
Oka
Naito
The best of three set match!
Service: Oka!
Naito!
Don't forget, it's fragile!
Too bad he ain't as kind fella as I am!
Fault!
Now, pull yourself together, Hiromi.
I have no right to lose.
Whatever the cost!
30-0!
Because if I'm defeated, everything is over!
For my tennis...
40-0!
Aight, love-game, here I go.
Damn it!
No... It's but a luck.
First set: 6-0, Naito!
What are you doing?
Why make a mess of a secured match?
Are you not ashamed yourself,
considering who raised you?
It's not over yet!
Not for my tennis.
A place like this...
A match like this...
Would never end my path halfway!
Is this for real?
How can that be happening?
Set: Oka!
Set count: 1-all.
Maybe playing against a guy
would have been more of a luck...
Is she really a woman?
Deuce!
At such a moment, they have a deuce!
It's painful... It's excruciating.
But I still can't lose here!
Whatever the cost, I can't afford a defeat!
Advantage: Oka!
Game set!
And won by Oka!
No need to worry, colleague.
She'll be alright. That's just the way Oka is getting used
to the court again. Let leave her here for a while.
This girl now... This very minute,
she has been excused to return on the court again.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
We're venturing on the Queen's Cup '90 court!
What a surprise!
Even Midorikawa is participating!
Her Cannon Serve was revived as a southpaw!
Hiromi, do your best too.
This time you don't have the luxury
of losing even once.
Get yourselves together.
Everyone is watching on you!
Coach Katsura even makes you
use your brand new shot!
Next time:
"Queen's Cup '90 Begins!"