Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
4-1.
Broir lead.
So far, Marchesa Broir clobbers Ryuzaki,
leaving her no chances.
The 14 years old prodigy
twists the Queen of Japanese Amateurs around the finger!
Episode 11
It won't fly, anymore...
What about Todo?
That fellow is returning later.
He has his own matches
scheduled throughout January.
Need to maintain the training pace.
Oka is keeping herself busy here.
Wherever they go,
they always root for each other.
Todo sure matured, hasn't he?
Nope. I barely managed to deter him
and shove back into the hotel.
Living the role, aren't you, Sadist Manager?
Demon, if anything.
Sure, sure, Demon Manager!
While we're at it, will you drop by my place now?
Yeah. That's pretty much what I returned for.
Queen's Cup '90
Third Round
Quarterfinals
Round three. Oka played with Natasha Dollis.
Clobbered her with 6-3 and 6-4.
But this match was much rougher...
Madame Butterfly?
Yes. First match of the third round.
Marchesa Broir vs. Ryuzaki Reika.
In first set, Broir secured a huge lead of 5-1,
forcing Madame Butterfly to metamorphose.
Metamorphose?
Yes. Not a trace was left
of Madame Butterfly's usual lofty play!
It was inconceivable, Chiba!
You could never tell the girl in front of you
was Madame Butterfly,
the one titled the Supreme Queen
for her fierce offense and brilliant footwork!
Throwing the pride away,
she stuck to the baseline.
In other words,
she ceased any offense towards the opponent.
Switched to the receive-only strategy.
Whatever chances she had before,
she never locked herself from going forward.
She kept forbearing and receiving Broir's serves
from the baseline, all the way back.
Like a novice facing a seasoned opponent.
It was as though she said,
"I am not yet adept enough to go offensive!"
Desperately staying clear from mistakes.
Her focus was on receive, receive and receive only!
After that and till the end of the game,
she never dared to attack even once.
It was perhaps the first time ever
anyone saw such a match from Madame Butterfly.
However, it yielded a magnificent result.
In Madame Butterfly's battle of attrition,
the composure of callow Broir crumbled soon.
Against an opponent that refuses to step forward, her attacks became reckless and grueling, wrecking Broir's pace completely.
Time after time, she was making careless mistakes,
ultimately ruining herself.
Out! 7-5, 6-3.
Match won by Ryuzaki.
Ryuzaki managed to win!
Now she advances to semifinals!
A win is a win.
However, in order to achieve it,
Madame Butterfly had to stop being Madame Butterfly.
But she won after all!
This stratagem cannot be a universal solution!
I don't want Madame Butterfly
to ever again play a match like this!
Ozaki.
Didn't Madame Butterfly say, she'd prefer to stay an amateur for the rest of her life, to keep playing her own tennis?
Didn't Madame Butterfly choose this
to remain Madame Butterfly, regardless of winning and losing?
She can still keep winning,
if such is Madame Butterfly's destiny.
That's the point - she can't!
There will always be some fresh power that'd defeat her!
Not even among the pro!
But fatal to her, so particular about winning!
Ozaki!
Ozaki.
Worst of all is that she realizes it herself.
You went through such privations for it, Madame Butterfly.
Ozaki.
Now then...
Here, right here.
Yes?
Guess who's here!
Welcome!
Are you really letting me stay?
I don't have a match tomorrow,
and it's no fun enjoying such a beautiful night view alone.
The semifinals are here, at last?
At last, as the grand final is approaching, we announce matchups for Queen's Cup '90 semifinals, held the day after tomorrow.
Ling Kowon (China) vs. Oka Hiromi (Park Hill Affiliate)
Jean Ryder (America) vs. Reika Ryuzaki (Park Hill Affiliate)
Hey, hey, what kind of player is this Ling Kowon?
Madame Butterfly is now facing
the tournament's number one favourite Ryder?
Jean Ryder              Reika Ryuzaki
Madame Butterfly wins,
and Hiromi also wins!
To make the final dream showdown come true!
What is that, long faces?
Hey, hey, take a quick look here!
Cool, isn't it?
I learned this one just recently.
Say, Maki.
Madame Butterfly won today, right?
Oh yes, she did!
Although she won, it feels off.
Feels so off.
Ms. Ryuzaki!
Congratulations on your advance to semifinals...
I will also...
Thank you, Hiromi.
You too do your best in semifinals, okay?
She must have been crying.
Why so?
Why would a winner do that?
I don't know.
But... But this was the first time
I saw Madame Butterfly so lonely.
Yes. You're through to the Sealine Hotel.
You want to speak to Mr. Katsura Daigo?
Unfortunately, Mr. Katsura
suddenly checked out at 6 pm today.
Although tomorrow night
we expect him to check back in.
I wonder where are you going, Reika?
I don't want to ever again
find myself in a match like today's.
That is why I will make sure to show you a brilliant match
with Jean Ryder the day after tomorrow, father.
Reika...
What's the matter?
How did Madame B. wander in here, of all people?
If Hiromi can do it,
there is no way that I cannot.
When receiving the inbound ball,
she returns it in the lowest point.
I know she has been trained by the special plan
to acquire this technique ever since Coach Munakata's time.
I want to use it too.
I want to carry on his legacy too.
I cannot do that.
It will ruin your own tennis.
Perhaps, it is already ruined.
Ever since this tournament's first round,
when Hiromi first showed me her brilliant wield of this technique.
After that, day by day, Hiromi was asserting
her superiority over me, steadily widening that gap between us.
When I'm asleep, when I'm awake,
and even when I'm holding the racket in the middle of a match,
those thoughts keep haunting me,
while she becomes less and less visible.
Please say it, Coach Katsura.
That you will do everything you can to help me defeat Jean Ryder, so that in the finals I could stand on the same court as Hiromi.
Because if my tennis career ends here,
I want it to be due to facing a mighty opponent like Oka Hiromi!
It's only if I lose to her,
that I could leave with no regrets!
One more step forward, Madame B!
Even now, you still hold back your step.
You never made more than one step from the line!
Take this line that you made up yourself to sit on
and make a huge step away from it!
You think you can pick it up in just a night or two?
For over 20 years, you've been believing
in this line you made up!
Until you forgo it, there can be no progress!
We're not getting anywhere at this rate!
Are you serious?
Even if it's just one night,
I have to put a 20 years' worth in it alone!
You are delirious!
No!
Since when do you let illusions take over you?
30-15.
Oka is in good shape. In the semifinal match against Ling Kowon,
Oka scores one return ace after another!
Ever since she entered this tournament,
Oka's strength never ceases to amaze!
After analyzing Oka's matches in second and third round,
I finally understood.
Compared to how she played before,
she advanced significantly.
Care to elaborate?
I'd say it's the receiving point.
Receiving point?
Yes. I never noticed until I looked closer.
Compared to other players, her timing for sending an inbound ball
back to the opponent is a few split-seconds earlier.
Well, it's a bit tricky to explain
without technical intricacies.
Some split-seconds, or about 10 to 20 cm closer to the ground
than the rest of the players - that's where she receives the ball.
And what does it mean?
It means such a timing in tennis is beyond common sense.
It's hard to believe,
but the more I look, the more I see it.
How unusual.
Oka was clearly not playing like this before.
How dare you omit reporting such a thing to America!
I wanted you to see it yourself in practice first. Both you and Todo.
You'd never believe something like this is happening otherwise.
Oka is advancing to finals, without a doubt.
I'd say, it won't take more than 10 more minutes.
Excuse me, is she asleep?
We came home just this morning.
I think she hasn't slept a wink
since the day before yesterday.
How peculiar to see her losing composure.
Midorikawa, this child has always been acting that way.
Not every time to this extent,
but always this way.
Although she would never disclose it in front of public,
this child endured more suffering and hard labor than anyone.
"It'd be better if she never discovered tennis,"
I had such thoughts numerous times.
Rosy, affectionate and frolic, making everyone laugh,
just the kind of child she was before all of this.
It's not so. Perhaps, it's not tennis,
but something else that drives her.
I'm sure she worked harder than anyone,
and suffered accordingly. But that's why...
That's why, don't you think your daughter
is a marvelous person?
Midorikawa.
I will be watching,
each of her first-grade strokes.
Please tell her just that.
Great work, Oka!
You advance to finals!
Really! She is so cool!
Nice play!
Keep it up!
Well done!
Coach, I...
Let me see your hand.
Okay.
Show it!
Just a couple of blisters burst.
But nothing serious!
An injured hand must be disinfected immediately.
Okay.
You already came this far.
Keep up the good work.
And now, let's proceed
to the second match of semifinals.
Reika, it's time.
Wake up Reika.
Hiromi did win her match, father?
Yes. 6-1 and 6-2.
She fought spectacularly and advanced to finals.
I should do my best too, in that case.
Best of three set match.
Service play: Ryder!
Ryder seizes the initiative at once,
she is this tournament's final Big Card.
Tournament's number one favourite, Jean Ryder vs.
the Queen of Japanese Amateur Tennis, Ryuzaki.
The winner of this game
will then play with Oka in the finals.
30-0.
A certain difference in power is apparent.
Ryder is #7 in world rankings.
Her winning a major Japanese tournament would be no surprise,
as she is still a rising player.
I see. Her temper is nothing like Broir's.
A true seasoned pro!
All right...
I have to do it.
Give up, Madame B!
You'll never be able to hit like that.
Even if you manage to perform it once or twice during training,
it'll never work in actual match!
Listen well! I'm saying that you'll never surpass Oka,
not because your techniques are inferior.
If we speak techniques,
yours are probably a level or two higher.
But that... That's precisely why you'll never surpass her.
Your muscle memory bounds you to your own techniques
and is certain to always hit the brakes in your heart.
Too anxious about failure, you can't muster the courage
for half a step more, hitting the brakes instead.
You constantly retrospect, and the better your tennis is honed,
the more you worry about failing.
Just like many outstanding players, you accustomed your body to playing tennis on reflexes in order to eliminate mistakes.
You get it now, Madame B?
Munakata picked the untrained Oka
and instead of eliminating mistakes,
made her the only one to take half a step forward!
He dedicated the whole teaching process to it.
Everything. Even what was left of his life.
He dedicated everything to it.
That is why Oka was able to do it
and you will never be able to do it.
No, Coach Katsura.
I will still give it a try.
It is indispensable right now to find the courage
for that one step forward, further than I had ever gone.
Not just for me standing here, on this court,
but for my entire future!
Courage!
I could do it before.
I managed it so many times during practice!
Courage!
My courage!
He gives it to me...
Did it!
Madame Butterfly...
has lost?
6-1, 6-0.
Set count: 2 against 0.
Match won by Ryder.
She lost!
Madame Butterfly has lost!
Maybe it's better if I go away?
Reika, you have a guest.
Father.
What, dear?
I'm sorry.
Reika cannot fly anymore.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
I'm Aikawa Maki!
It's Queen's Cup '90 finals!
But this all feels somehow unbelievable -
Hiromi's opponent is sadly not Madame Butterfly.
I'm so worried about her.
After all, it's thanks to Madame Butterfly,
Hiromi could make it this far.
Don't be mourning about that, Hiromi.
You're still here. Still here, you are!
And you should definitely win!
Closing episode: "FINAL STAGE."