Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
The New York - Boston express bus
is carrying me through the night.
Dear Maki, for the moment, I am heading to Boston.
There, I'll see Todo taking part in preliminaries
for getting into the US Pro Circuit.
But there's one more person.
Entrained by Todo's burning enthusiasm,
Midorikawa Ranko now follows us
to become a preliminaries challenger as well.
We should arrive to Boston tomorrow morning.
Both Todo and Midorikawa,
along with the rest of the passengers, are having a sound sleep.
On this nocturnal highway,
I believe, no one else except bus driver and me
is staring into that darkness.
I can't get to sleep.
For some reason,
I can't sleep at all, Maki.
Todo and Midorikawa embarked this bus
because they have own, clearly defined goals.
Comparing myself to them, I can't help asking,
what on Earth am I going to Boston for?
Those thoughts deprive me of sleep.
I could finally meet Todo, as I so craved to.
And I should, by all means, be happy to be riding the same bus now.
Say, Maki. Maki?
I'm not doing something wrong, do I?
I am not making a mistake?
Episode 7
Boston
Todo just threw his luggage into the room
and went out for a roadwork at once.
He is really fired about about that fight.
My, what a morning!
Midorikawa, do you mind if I have a little nap?
Sure. It's just me who has to wake up early.
The preliminaries are coming.
I'll go find us a permanent court for practices.
Sign the contract and stuff.
When it's time for breakfast,
I'll wake you up.
Sorry for the trouble...
No wonder you couldn't sleep in that cramped bus!
In that case, I take your word for it
and have just a little more...
Here.
Thank you...
Here you go.
Thanks.
I want to give this one to you.
You didn't bring along a racket, did you?
I'm giving you my spare one.
But...
I need an opponent. Won't you refuse me a match
for the first time in a while?
Sure!
Why are you in New York?
I don't know.
What a surprise.
I'm sorry.
Didn't see that coming.
I'm sorry. But I just so much
wanted to see you, no matter what.
Oka...
How most unexpected!
One could never tell you turned southpaw just recently!
It's no good. When I was playing with my right,
the power was times more.
That is not true! Your serve, your forehand
and your ball drive are no inferior.
Instead of tending to me, what about you?
I don't have a single clue regarding what kind of stuff
is going on in Japan right now.
But shouldn't autumn tennis season be in full swing now?
Yes...
So instead of making the best of your youth,
you are wasting your time training here with me.
Don't you think something's just a bit off here?
It's fine, I don't expect you to answer.
Everyone has their own different reasons.
Everyone has the right
to do whatever they please and how they want it.
It’s not for me to accuse others of being self-indulgent.
But this one time
it seems you're really under quite a pressure.
No matter how much pain you experience along the way,
you should never use it as an excuse to give yourself an advantage.
Should never use it to hamper others.
Instead, you should give this advantage to others.
I have always adhered to that tenet.
Give advantage to a partner and wait patiently.
Patiently.
Although eventually my partner left for elsewhere.
Advantage...
Not bad, Oka!
That's a great ball!
Got it! Thanks a lot!
Alright...
Nice!
At such moments...
At moments like this, I wish the time would stop!
Our hotel is about 5 kilo away.
Why won't we conclude the training
with a scenic Tour de Boston?
I agree.
Let's ride!
Count me in!
The first to arrive gets $1.
But the other two pay for the winner's dinner.
Well, I'll just get a dessert with coffee.
That's a positive okay!
Okay, well then!
Oka!
Alright...
Hey, you! That was a head start! Wait!
It's just the three of us, Maki.
Still I'm so exceedingly happy, Maki!
Somehow it feels that after that,
I will never forget the wonderful moments of today!
A bicycle ride.
A man I love.
A city in the dusk.
I can just forget about everything
and YELL my lungs out in delight!
I'm so glad Maki.
I am so glad to have finally seen Todo!
Thank you, Maki. Truly so.
I know! That's it, Oka.
You should also apply!
For preliminaries. You and me still have enough time
to make entry in doubles together.
Well... But...
Together we can put the local yellow pros to flight!
Well? Isn't it a fine idea? Don't you think?
We both happened to be in America.
Isn't it a great chance?
But think again. I was not planning to stay here for long.
I have a lot of loose ends...
What's the issue? Money? A hotel?
Well I'll gladly sort it out for you!
Slow down a bit there, player Midorikawa.
What now?
Oka's full-time hot-tempered Coach Mr. Katsura,
is waiting for her back home.
Therefore, such matters
are not to be decided solely on Oka's volition.
I'll call him! Trust me.
We'll reach a compromise.
Have no worries! If Munakata's sister is in charge,
even his heart will bend.
Keep in mind I know Daigo ever since I was in high school.
Plus the stuff Jin told about him,
he's like the back of my hand!
You've had enough of this.
Why, no!
It didn't feel like I drank that much...
However fine your idea is,
it can't be incarnated.
Once Oka takes part in this tournament,
her amateur qualification is gone.
After returning to Japan,
Oka could no longer play in amateur events.
Then it's not about Mr. Katsura only.
Madame Butterfly is also likely to be upset.
Tennis will be tennis. Pro or amateur -
no diffeence, whassoewhaa...
Midorikawa, are you feeling well?
Don't say nonsenth. Chattering like this with you two
will not tire me one bit in eternithee.
If ye excuse me,
I'll be heading to the room now.
Please take your time.
Have a good night.
- Goodnight!
- Good... night.
Oka...
Yes?
I am sincerely happy
that I was able to meet you.
To tell you the truth, until yesterday
I felt like I'm on the bottom.
But now I got myself together
and will do my best.
Okay.
Please tell me, how is it going for you.
You've been doing fine, haven't you?
Yes, I have been doing fine.
For real?
For real.
Without a hitch?
Yes. Without a hitch.
I see. That's all I need to know then.
Yes.
Good morning! Are you awake? It's Todo!
Come in, it's open!
Big news, big news!
Wait... Where's Oka?
Taking a morning shower. Why?
Well... I'm not sure how to put it,
but Mr. Sayama called me from New York.
This evening our friend Chiba
is to arrive to Boston.
Chiba is coming.
What do I do?
Questionable things I don't want Todo to know
happened back in Japan.
Hey! Oka!
We're here, here!
Didn't hear.
Is something wrong, Oka?
No, nothing is.
It's just a little cold here.
Chiba!
Todo!
Doing fine, Todo?
Yeah. But first, how come?
Why are you here?
Well... This and that.
Midorikawa!
Been a long time.
Yeah, when Mr. Sayama reported meeting Midorikawa,
I was utterly amazed!
Not only reborn as a southpaw
but also determined to transfer to pro!
I have always been an impulsive shopper.
It was Todo who became a catalyst.
I never gave it much of a thought.
Oka!
Good evening.
Oka, you should not get up just yet!
What's the matter?
Well, she just has a little fever.
The rain caught us by surprise during practice.
First thing in the morning we'll go to the hospital.
She is burning like a bonfire.
That's a dismal to know...
Then, if you excuse us, we'll head back to the room.
See you tomorrow, Chiba.
Sure. Okay!
Oka, don't exert yourself.
Okay.
The Tokyo Cup was
gracefully won by Madame Butterfly.
I see. Reckon she's working as hard as always.
Well, how is Oka doing then?
She didn't tell you?
Yes. She didn't want to talk
about anything related to the court.
Although she seems to be most troublefree every single day,
to tell you the truth, I'm kinda worried.
It appears, Oka had to go through impossible to get here now.
If Oka decided not to tell you,
then I shouldn't either.
I see.
But I believe, she's doing it for your own good.
It all started because you never reported back to us
that you lost your first match here.
And it's not about Oka alone. For me, Ozaki and Madame Butterfly
it caused unnecessary worries as well.
I'm sorry.
You have to accept responsibility for making Oka worried
buy living through this anxiety yourself.
Spit it out.
Oka was eliminated from Tokyo Cup by a rookie in the first round.
Moreover, she refused the repechage match in order to go see you.
Can you imagine such a thing?
However difficult it was before,
she never gave up a match before even trying.
I'm not trying to blame everything on you.
But this turned into nothing but minuses for both of you.
It's just deplorable.
It's deplorable, Todo.
Maki, I spent the next three days
recovering motionless.
Then, on the day of Todo's match,
I could finally go out.
First round, first set.
Takayuki Todo versus Ed Kartrite.
Service play - Todo.
I had no other chance to talk to Todo,
as I spent the last few days sleeping mostly.
But on that day, Todo's determination to win this match
was in the air, as if he was channeling it to audience somehow.
It was almost as if I was playing this match myself.
As if I was swinging the racket myself.
This was the first time I experienced such a feeling.
15-0.
30-0.
40-0.
Compared to his New York matches,
he looks more spirited now.
It seems Todo finally decided to live up
to his Japan Open champion title.
However, the opponent is also a player,
who won the East Coast Amateur Championship twice.
40-15!
Their abilities are about the same.
Victory and defeat are equally probable in this match.
However, Todo is good at handling the ball.
No matter if he wins or loses,
we won't see him weeping over his helplessness from now on.
Mr. Sayama!
Deuce!
Advantage: Todo!
This was your first victory in America.
Accept my congratulations!
No...
In the second round, in the third round, and of course,
even in the final round, keep doing your best!
Thank you, I will do my best.
I think... I think, tomorrow
I'm coming back to Japan.
I'm sorry. I know I came to America without warning.
And I'm sure, I caused a lot of nuisance for you.
Oka...
However, having that said,
I still have one more request.
Whether you win or lose,
tell me about it in letters!
Especially when you lose.
And you too.
Okay.
This way I can have no worries
even when you're away.
Okay.
I figured we should celebrate
Todo's first victory in America.
And if Midorikawa performs just as great
in women matches tomorrow,
how many more champagnes will I drink while here?
You can never tell!
Don't expect much on my side.
It's still more of a try-out.
No way! Todo said the other day,
your southpaw ball is even sharper!
He really did?
Why don't we wait a little longer?
For those two.
Of course, even if for eternity.
But still, Oka...
I'm the only one here who should apologize.
I was the one who hampered you first.
Even after I said that I love you.
You regret saying it?
No. That's not the way for me.
Then, this time,
let me take this little advantage of you.
Advantage, Oka.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
Finally, finally, you're back home!
Hiromi, welcome back.
And thanks for beautiful souvenirs for me!
But upon returning, you're engaged again.
The tough university coach takes you under his authority.
Even Coach Katsura wasn't always that harsh.
But you still must fight, Hiromi.
The Queen's Cup is coming, and you should be triumphal on it!
Triumphal! Right, Hiromi?
Next time: "The Final Repechage Match."