I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Be not intimidated, Oka.
You cannot alter the life's ways,
neither the death's ones.
Oka,
don't try to forget,
keep it before your eyes.
As a reminder that Munakata's death is now a fact,
keep it at all times within sight!
Then get up and go!
Wherever. Wherever!
Episode 8
Battle-Scarred Court
This is the place.
This court has not been in use
for a long time now.
With proper maintenance,
it can still do us service.
Yes.
Nishi Medical University Hospital
I heard that from medical staff.
The way you recovered so soon from all those injuries
was likely due to doing a lot of sports.
It's thanks to tennis.
Drop it!
Don't tell me about tennis!
While you were transported to intensive care
on a wheeled bed,
can you remember what you said?
You articulated it quite lucidly:
Racket... My racket...
It has to be a lie!
I'd never... I'd never do that.
While you yourself were unconscious,
your heart spoke...
Your whole being, even while standing
on the brink of death, only sought tennis.
Drop that now!
I could only do that because I had an older brother,
I had Jin, always by my side, always looking after me.
But no more!
Without Jin on the court,
how can I play tennis any longer?
Oka, move your elbows!
Aim with more precision.
Hammer the vision of your target
deep into your head!
Okay!
Toss and don't take eyes off it!
You're scatterbrained!
Get up!
My body won't move like I want it to.
It rusted to the point of being terrifying.
I don't mind if you look quietly.
Just don't be a distraction.
Sure, I understand.
So that's how it is?
You resumed the practice?
Listen, Munakata.
One way or another, Oka began to move on.
Devastated by the sorrow of losing you
and engulfed by the eternal darkness, Oka
got herself together
to get up and start moving on.
You can grab a racket and hit the ball,
but that won't solve anything. Won't ease your pain.
Perfectly aware of that, Oka
is giving tennis another try nevertheless.
This moment is crucial, Munakata.
Hereafter, we will be advancing
by leaps and bounds.
I will once again show Oka
the path to greatness.
To the powerful, great tennis.
Detach from the line!
Raise the speed!
Have you really defeated
Maria Young and Belle with that kind of play?
It's too soon just yet...
My body is still struggling
to move the way it used to.
I spent a month without hitting a single ball.
I arranged a match,
in a week from now.
Opponent is a first year at Nishi High tennis club,
junior to you male team player.
Therefore, you won't have
any right to lose.
But that's impossible!
My roadwork and my serve are still lacking...
Week from now.
You have until then to put your body into shape.
But...
I settled on that schedule already.
You'll have to make do with that.
Now,
aim at me and hit with all your heart!
Show me the serve
that won you a silver medal!
Spin around more!
Okay!
Deep into the mountains,
there's a small abandoned court.
Oka trains like a devil there,
and Katsura trains her like a devil.
Oka's eyes were attached to Katsura,
while following his command in her movements.
After all, Oka is one of a kind player.
With this kind of special training,
reverting to her former shape is a matter of time, I believe.
But it seems, Oka's opponent
is a pretty serious player too.
Yet he's just a first year.
Still, in the second year of middle school,
he even won a title as a junior player.
I'd say he a rather good player.
Really?
Chiba, you don't get it.
Oka's form is still nowhere near
that of her peak times.
Go away.
I didn't want to see you.
I didn't want to see anyone.
My only wish is to see you
standing proudly on the court once again.
Stop coming here.
And go away.
Go away!
Go away I said!
Here, it's rightfully yours.
Oka returned to court already.
In three days, she is playing a practice match
on Nishi High courts.
Oka, get on the baseline!
Today it's a serve-receive special practice.
High time I show you Power Tennis first-hand.
Let's see if you can handle my serve.
Okay!
To receive this ball, scoring a return ace,
only Munakata had the power.
Get up, Oka!
Concentrate more on the ball!
Goddamnit!
What is this impossible ball?
At least once... I want to handle it!
No way...
Not wasting any time, Hiromi?
Maki! Of all places! How come?
I have been eating dust all the way here,
so I figured I can join in.
You should!
Thank you!
Tomorrow you have a match at Nishi High?
So once the match is over, Hiromi,
you won't need to inhabit this temple for any longer.
Don't tell me, you haven't heard yet?
Are you serious?
Well, Katsura called me out to help you
sort out your luggage, so I guess I am.
What's the matter?
Excuse me, tomorrow, do I...
I'm returning you to family not because I think
you have finished regaining your footing.
Your mental state still fluctuates,
and I don't think you can stand on your own yet.
But at any rate, we're past the crisis.
For some time now, you have not been blurting out
nonsense like "I want to die."
Which testifies to the fact of Munakata's death
starting to take root in your mind, little by little.
Good enough for me.
As long as one can devote his life
unreservedly to something,
and also exercise some self-awareness of that,
in spite of agony, in spite of misery,
he can go on living.
For you, to discover tennis
was the grandest blessing.
As well, as getting discovered by Munakata.
Some years ago,
two middle schools waged a deadly feud.
Come at me!
Two schools sharing one neighborhood always
become one another's bone in the throat.
And so, two middle schools fought constantly,
with neither ever emerging decisively victorious.
One day, to bring it to the conclusion,
their bosses clashed one-on-one.
Though still in middle school,
both those bosses were already 175 cm tall.
Both just turned 15.
Ignorant of any discretion.
It escalated rapidly into a bloodbath.
Even the watching bunches were impressed
and backed away in fear.
Still, neither would willingly
admit himself beaten.
They kept on struggling
until both collapsed, exhausted.
Gimme a break!
On this occasion, two middle schools later became close
as though they were sister schools.
In some while, one of the bosses
enrolled in the high school of his choice.
Due to liking tennis before,
he wanted to join the appropriate club.
Tennis club
Where suddenly,
he stumbled upon the other boss.
That was how I reunited with Munakata Jin.
You mean you've known Coach Munakata
for over 12 years?
Since that time, Munakata,
with passion, in everyone's eyes bordering madness,
devoted his life to tennis.
What in the world happened to Munakata
to make him so devoted to tennis?
Munakata initiated me
into the intricacies of his family affairs.
Betrayed in love,
with wounds too deep to heal,
his poor mother met an untimely demise.
Munakata got exposed very early
to the harshness of reality.
That was probably why,
by the time I first met him, Munakata,
still a middle school student, already had a detached and disappointed look in his eyes, like someone fed up with life.
He drank sake, smoked tobacco,
picked up fights with whoever it was.
Even I myself
was a bit aghast at this demeanor.
Yet Munakata was rescued from this state
when he discovered tennis.
However, fate's ways can get truly cruel.
Just as he escaped his misfortunes
and could finally see the light in tennis...
Bone marrow leukemia.
A death sentence.
And then, just some 27 years old, he died.
Even in such a short lifetime,
he has seen hell not once but twice.
Twice.
Moreover, he spent bulk of that period
writhing in agony.
Oka, coming across you changed everything.
To confine his life in a box with "ill fate examples" label
and bury it in the dirt of pitiful memories is the simplest.
But I cannot take that way.
That one little ember spared by my best friend's ill fate -
I want to carry on fanning its flame.
Please help me, Oka.
Everything he ever did now lives in you.
But should this burden ever turn out too unbearable for you,
from now on, you can tell me at once.
Then, this instant,
I will give up altogether.
Best of three set match!
Service - Ishijima. Play!
15-0.
Right hand is going numb...
30-0.
Oka, what are you doing?
Get up at once!
Okay!
What is going on?
It's like I reverted to a complete novice again!
Like I never played any tennis whatsoever.
Though opponent is a man,
he's just a first year!
Hiromi!
Fight!
What's the matter, Chiba?
You haven't taken a single shot this match.
Shut up, will ya.
So many consecutive love-games. It's too hard for her!
Hiromi needs more time to recover!
Right, Ms. Ryuzaki?
Hiromi...
Double fault!
Game - Ishijima. 4-0.
In this match, I still scored nothing,
not one point!
Damn it all!
Yes! Good! That's the way! Keep it up!
15-0.
Well... It's probably none of my business,
but Oka's condition is still poor, isn't it?
- If so, shouldn't we wrap this match up...
- I will be fine.
Nothing is decided yet.
No way I'm withdrawing!
Alright, into position!
Do it for me, Oka.
My whole life
I put inside your burning soul.
6-0 and 6-0 then?
Eventually, Oka never managed
to score even one mere point.
Her usual shape is still miles away.
Well, one way or another,
Oka is out on the court again.
We should go celebrate this,
right, Todo?
What's the matter with you two?
Alright, alright, I know! I'm paying today!
I had no doubt you'd show up.
Should I give you a lift to the hospital?
Are you planning to bid your time here forever, Oka?
Aikawa is waiting, you know.
I put in my every effort...
For the first time,
I was putting so much effort in tennis.
Still, I didn't take a single game,
didn't score a mere one point.
So what?
"Everything he did now lives in me."
That's what you told me last night.
Yeah, I did.
And then you also said, "Should this burden turn out too unbearable, tell me anytime.
I will then give up altogether."
Exactly so.
Are you implying
the burden has become too unbearable today?
I want to give up!
And for you to give up on me!
If I keep on getting vanquished like in today's match,
however hard I try,
I will just let down
both Coach Munakata and Mr. Katsura!
Though I really love tennis
and try as hard as I can,
still, however painful it is to admit, I'm not talented enough
even to make Coach Munakata's dream come true!
It has only become clear to me today!
I couldn't even score a paltry one point!
For how long are you planning to grunt out some hooey?
Enough already.
Now! Change at once
and return to your goddamn home!
Okay!
Tomorrow morning you have a roadwork.
Don't you forget!
Okay!
At ease!
I'm a bit envious of Oka.
After this, her growth would be tremendous.
Perhaps. A sound and thorough defeat like that
often avails one to the road of tremendous growth.
Even while losing game after game,
she was spectacular in her persistence.
They are the most terrifying to me -
players of Oka's type.
Unlike conceited posers
who can't lose just because of their imaginary pride.
That's right,
I'm someone who can't afford to lose.
Neither to Hiromi, nor to you.
Oh well.
I guess, I'd better get back on my feet sooner, too.
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
Aikawa Maki here.
Though Mr. Katsura went through a lot of trouble
to get appointed as Hiromi's exclusive coach,
Hiromi still refuses to enlist for All-Japan's Open.
Even after Madame Butterfly
and Midorikawa announced they entry.
It's not the time to get the morbs!
Especially when Midorikawa
challenges Madame Butterfly to a practice match!
Hiromi, if you dawdle,
you risk getting left behind!
Next time: Rivals