On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Oh, what a wonderful day!
Perfect for winning the finals.
How are you feeling?
Locked and loaded.
Then, as the leader of your cheering squad,
I, Aikawa Maki, have a request.
Show us all a confident victory.
All right. Oka Hiromi hereby vows to do her best
together with Madame Butterfly.
Thus ensuring us a confident victory in finals.
Perfect. Straight to the match then! Let's go!
All right, I'm not losing, even if it's a race!
Episode 21
Close Call! The Doubles Finals
Yes.
Ryuzaki what?
Yes!
Yes, I understand.
Coach, has something happened to Madame Butterfly?
She had her arm injured in a car accident.
That can't be...
The hospital cannot say more
until they do a thorough inspection.
At any rate, she's not playing today's match.
But what do we do about the finals, then?
It starts in just 30 minutes!
Madame Butterfly is injured...
Injured! How can that be...
Madame Butterfly getting injured...
This is something I don't want to believe!
It's a lie! It's all a lie!
Coach, the match begins in just five minutes.
What will you do?
Can't be helped. We renounce.
Then...
Madame Butterfly!
- Madame Butterfly!
How are you, Madame Butterfly?
The match will begin soon, Oka.
Are you ready?
Yes...
But Madame Butterfly...
I'm all right. It's just a minor scratch.
Ryuzaki.
Today's match is canceled.
If you're worried about my injury, it's fine now.
Oka, let's go.
Coach!
Oka.
Will you be able to cover for Ryuzaki?
Yes!
Good, then go!
Okay!
Nishi High's Ryuzaki-Oka team vs.
Wakatake High's Tsuji-Sato team.
Wow, here come the finals at last!
Do your best, Madame Butterfly and Oka.
Hey, Ozaki, look at Madame Butterfly's arm!
Madame Butterfly's injured.
How did it happen?
Sato, look there,
at Ryuzaki Reika.
See that bandage around her arm?
She got injured somehow.
Then if we focus our attacks on her...
We have a good chance to win.
I won't let that happen. This kind of minor injury
would never be enough to make me lose.
I can do this as well! Just you watch!
I'll vanquish them!
Hiromi, do your best
while covering Madame Butterfly's part!
Oka, with your plays, one by one,
you will decide the outcome of this match.
The best-of-three set match!
Nishi High's service. Play!
Just watch!
It's out!
Fault!
All right, this time...
Double fault!
0-15!
Oh no!
I'm sorry.
It's alright, Oka.
Keep calm and play the usual way.
Okay!
I should be the one encouraging you,
but you end up encouraging me...
Okay, this time I won't miss!
I have to return it...
15-All!
We underestimated Ryuzaki!
We can't let our guard down!
Normally, Madame Butterfly would have sent that ball
sharply into the opponent's court.
This arm injury is taking its toll.
My arm!
I can't raise it!
Oka is giving it her best. Trying to fill every breach
in Madame Butterfly's defense.
There!
What an incredible spirit!
Even injured, Madame Butterfly
performs just as brilliantly!
I can't submit to losing too!
There!
Deuce!
Two more points...
We just need to score two more, by any cost...
Nishi High
Wakatake High
Deuce!
It's bad. Dragging this match out
is dangerous for Madame Butterfly.
We have to take this set no matter what!
Hiromi, it's out!
Advantage: Ryuzaki-Oka!
Okay, only one more point.
The opponent is injured!
We can't lose!
Get this!
First set! 9-7 for Nishi High!
They did it!
Hiromi's side has taken the lead!
Are you all right, Madame Butterfly?
Don't worry. We won the first set
thanks to you covering my part.
No, It's not like that.
Anyways, please look after your injury.
I'll remain unabated in doing my best.
Did you see Ryuzaki just now?
We completely crippled her in the first set.
But Oka Hiromi is still covering for her.
That's where we start winning this.
She'll be worn out soon enough.
When that happens,
we'll launch our counter-attack!
I see. Nishi High will destroy itself
during the second set.
This match has to be settled in the second set.
We can't jeopardize Madame Butterfly's arm even more.
All right, I'll show them!
Second set! Wakatake High's service. Play!
15-0!
30-0!
At this rate they won't last to the end.
As long as I'm still here,
you won't lay a finger on Madame Butterfly!
Hiromi, it's enough already.
Ruining yourself like this for my sake.
I don't want to see you doing this!
This is nothing! Nothing, I say! Compared to
Madame Butterfly's injury this is...
Madame Butterfly!
I can take this!
Regardless of what happens to my arm!
How do you like this?
What are you doing, Madame Butterfly?
Your injury!
I'm fine, Hiromi.
Don't forget we're playing doubles.
Dammit!
We got this set!
It's bad! Even Madame Butterfly
is falling for the opponent's trap!
I know it's a trap.
But if by striking this ball I will save Oka Hiromi,
I will fain take this bait!
Second set: 6-2 for Wakatake High!
Can you continue playing the match?
Yes, we—
I can continue playing, but...
But there's also Madame Butterfly. Madame Butterfly...
Can you continue?
Of course I will continue!
Struggle or not, this is already over.
Victory is plainly ours.
Get this!
You're at your limit already, Oka!
If only I could swap places with you...
I'd relieve you at once!
Good job, you two.
You've done well to come this far.
But right now you're too handicapped.
Don't push yourselves and return to your own pace.
It's out of question right now.
Should this injury tear my arm asunder,
I still can't let go of my racket!
Even in this state,
Madame Butterfly is still fighting so hard.
Meanwhile, I'm starting to lose!
I don't want it to happen!
I don't want to lose to Madame Butterfly!
Game count: 4-1.
She won't be getting back up soon.
I... I can't anymore...
Oka!
Stand up!
Hey, Todo!
Oka! Stand up!
You have to stand up!
Todo...
Come on, Oka, stand up
and pick up the racket again.
But... I can't stand...
No, you can.
You have spirit to do it.
Now, stand back up and keep fighting!
In this space between you and the racket,
your entire youth is confined!
Now, stand and walk!
Walk through your tennis youth
alongside with me!
Todo... I understand.
Good.
Look. Hiromi picked up the racket.
Oka...
I can't believe it.
Where does she take that will to fight from?
Madame Butterfly, I... I...
Good job standing back up, Oka.
Madame Butterfly,
I absolutely don't want to lose!
Then there's no choice but to play to the end!
I will... to the end...
To the very end, I will do my best!
Match point for Ryuzaki-Oka!
This is the end.
Our battle will be decided here.
Ridiculous. How can this be?
For someone beaten to a pulp just a moment ago,
to stand up like this again...
Fine! If that's the case,
our Murderous Smash should become the last resort!
Got you!
There!
Now, here comes the ball you cannot return!
Let's see that fighting spirit of yours
in its true colors!
You'll see how I hit it!
Missed!
Hit it! I gotta hit!
I put my whole heart in this ball!
How dare you!
6-1!
Set count: 2-1 for Ryuzaki-Oka!
Hiromi!
Oka!
Hiromi, thank you.
Madame Butterfly!
Hiromi! You won! You won!
Well done, both of you.
Congratulations!
With this victory, Nishi High's
new super combination is by all means born.
Oka and Madame Butterfly
have done really well to come this far, Todo.
Let's go.
Thank you, Todo.
It's because of you that we were able to win!
Thank you so much!
To Be Continued
As the day of Captain Hoshino's
send-off match draws near,
Otowa Kyoko asks Coach Munakata
to let her form a pair with Hiromi.
Then gives Hiromi a note
with all of Hiromi's weak points written in detail.
What exactly is Kyoko expecting her to do?
The whistle is blown on the match between the Hoshino-Ochou and Kyoko-Hiromi teams.
Look forward to it on the next Aim for the Ace:
"No Need for Tears at the Graduation Match"
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo