Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Finally, it's round two.
My opponent is the Spaniard Marchesa Broir.
I'm sure, Jin,
I have to defeat her, by all means.
This way, no later than in the next, third round,
I will play with Madame Butterfly.
And then, if I keep winning and winning,
I will make it to the finals.
In that case, do you believe
I'll have a chance to play with Hiromi?
In any case, I'm not in Hiromi's block,
so to make it happen, she must also keep winning.
Odd to see you here, Ranko.
It's a day before his death anniversary.
It's because I have a match tomorrow.
I see. Against Broir, is it?
Yes.
Go there in a relaxed posture.
The opponent is 14th in world rankings.
She may exploit your habitual manner
of boring your way through on full power, and destroy you.
But if you wait patiently in a relaxed manner,
a chance might arise.
She's just a 14 year old brat.
A puffed up dummy!
That might be so,
if we speak outside court.
I understand your confidence,
but I want you to acknowledge reality first.
What if I win?
What if I still win?
Then wish anything and I will grant it.
Want me to say it?
Will you let me see Jin?
Silly.
Let me see him.
See him!
Could one bring the dead back to life by winning in tennis,
I'd be standing on the court myself for a long time now.
Episode 10
Challenger,
Ranko!
I understand what Hiromi and Coach Katsura are trying to pull,
what they are thinking about.
Countless famous players
attempted to utilize this kind of play, but failed.
Reika, you are questioning your own tennis now,
so I have to exhort you from proceeding.
Despite being theoretically possible,
on an actual court such a play is considered prospectless.
Still Hiromi succeeded in the first round
using it against Morita, a pro.
Reika... For the first time in years
I miss the sounds of Chopin's Mazurka.
Her posture is lower than anyone's.
She steps into the ball further than anyone.
When handling the inbound ball,
she receives it lower than anyone!
When a ball is being returned from such a low spot,
the opponent is never in the position for receiving,
effectively warranting a return ace.
Not everyone is capable of such a play.
That's how Katsura put it:
"Allowing Oka to pick up such a play
was Munakata's original design all along."
In other words, the rookie Oka
was a blank canvas with no inclinations or habits.
To enable such play for her in the future,
he aligned trainings accordingly.
By observing her, you'll merely get it with your head,
not actually learn to use such a play yourself.
Hiromi can handle it, because it is her.
Is that what you want to say?
It was by a collective attainment of Oka, Munakata,
and finally Katsura Daigo. That's what I mean.
Wow, for real?
Checking in the hotel tomorrow?
The venue is far.
Most of the players were crammed into that hotel as well.
Cool. You mind if I drop in as well?
I want to try their "Space Battle" at least once!
Don't get me wrong,
but I'll be tending to matters of life and death!
You'll win, Hiromi.
Second round will be a piece of cake!
And judging by your first round,
even a gold is no longer a dream!
Shall we go play "Space Battle" if you win?
I think we totally should!
Nice shot!
This time you'll perform brilliantly, right?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's round 3 at best. Best 8 is my goal.
No, still, something was different the last time.
Burning for love and burning for tennis,
Oka Hiromi is being torn apa-pa-pa-pa-part!
You jester!
Wanna get ice cream?
Okay!
It may sound trite,
but I'll be waiting for you in the round 3.
but some #14 in rankings is not a threat to me.
Right!
Attagirl!
Then, I'll be back in no time.
The tourney favorite, Marchesa Broir,
makes appearance in 5th match of 2nd round!
14th in world rankings,
14 year old fairy of the court.
This would be her first play
in front of Japan's tennis fans.
Her adversary - Midorikawa Ranko, who is making a spectacular comeback as a southpaw, thus overcoming her right wrist injury.
After her thrilling victory in first round,
she is not stopping in the round two!
Service: Midorikawa.
Damn it!
0-15.
Todo.
Midorikawa fought in the most sublime way
in her match that day.
It was so extraordinary, I can do naught
but dedicate the next letter to this match alone.
That's how much I was moved by this astounding match.
Queen's Cup.
The 5th match of the 2nd round.
Midorikawa's play that day strengthened me more
than any of the countless matches I've seen before.
It stunned me to the core.
Midorikawa's play effused such a fighting spirit,
as if it was a fight to the death.
I will tell you everything how I saw and felt it.
At first, Broir was dominating the match,
imposing her own pace. Forehand,
backhand, serve. Whichever one she hit,
her perfect shots were always reaching Midorikawa's court.
Midorikawa was helpless, as though idling.
Eventually, her feebleness turned into despair,
and though I was just watching, even I clearly empathized it.
The Prodigy Broir lives up to her title!
She constantly keeps Power Hitter Midorikawa
completely at bay!
And this is Broir's famous coaching staff.
10 men in total. They are not just concerned about her play.
A doctor and a lawyer also accompany her at all times.
And additional standby team of tutors in hotel.
Impressive, isn't it?
And now it's challenger Ryder!
The most prominent favorite along with Broir.
Jean Ryder came here
to settle the scores with her rival Broir!
15-0.
30-0.
First set, sixth game.
Midorikawa never managed to break the Broir's service-game.
Eventually,
she was defeated 6-0.
Lost the first set dismally.
And then she entered the second set with that burden.
It appears that all I did up until now
was just fooling around vainly, Jin. I should give it a try...
I'm a little scared,
but there's a good chance it plays out well.
It's fine, right?
Then...
It's settled.
Are you an idiot, Ranko?
Todo...
Todo, Midorikawa was playing with her right again.
Doctors prohibited even holding the racket with her right,
leave alone playing tennis!
For the first time in life
I saw someone playing tennis so unbound and frolic.
Her eyes were glowing.
She really is an idiot.
To mitigate her inferiority,
she changed the hand holding racket,
rendering all the right hand recovery effort wasted.
This is the actual Ranko's right hand comeback.
Her eternal dream fulfilled.
Why couldn't you wait more?
Just six more months... Year at most!
She has to win this match, certainly.
If she doesn't win this match,
she can't fulfill her dream of fighting Madame Butterfly.
Silly. After a whole year,
Ranko should be targeting not Madame B, but you.
In second set, Midorikawa
is giving Broir a run for her money!
Midorikawa took the bull by the horns in second set
by holding racket with her right!
14th in rankings,
Broir is fighting her on even grounds!
As a right-handed player, she can employ
even more of her strength, which is as natural as it can get.
But worrying at the same time.
Care to explain?
Her right hand injury was not
of a neglectable kind, as far as I know.
15-40.
In second set Midorikawa
has reached the set point already!
She was blown away with 6-0 in the first set,
but using this new momentum, she turned the tables!
Damn it.
It's starting to grow a little numb.
It's just this one point, Todo.
This one point can be Midorikawa's shortcut
right into the final set.
Midorikawa!
That's how she always is.
Ranko's recklessness lost that match for her.
Yet one thing was different this time.
She showed us a spectacular fight.
Impelled by that spirit of rivalry, Ranko could drop the mask
and show us an ultimate play up until the ultimate one point.
Broir is facing a match point!
If Midorikawa wants to stay in the saddle,
she can by no means screw that serve!
No one has ever worked there that hard.
That's what top-notch players do, Oka.
By working hard there,
they secure themselves a triumph.
It's a pity that Ranko never was a top-notch.
My room is #28 above you.
If you need anything, find me there. See you.
Then I
don't want to ever become the top-notch!
Forehand, huh?
Naturally, I'd drop the ball with it.
However, backhand is much simpler.
My plan was to aim for her vulnerable spots,
but I couldn't put enough force in the ball.
Don't underestimate her just because she's 14 year old.
In this match she played like a tennis super-veteran
with decades of experience.
That's not the matter now. What about your right hand?
What was the doctor's diagnosis?
If she raises a Lob, try reaching for the net, then knock it down.
You'll always return it straight to the baseline.
Midorikawa...
Fast serve is her favorite. Three kinds of it.
Midorikawa!
When I tried shooting a rotating ball,
it invariably ended up in the net.
Keep your long legs straight
and return to the edge of sideline.
Her footwork is perfect to the left, right and up,
but she is still clumsy in moving back and forth.
When you pinch her, she's wide open.
Backhand, backhand, backhand, forehand.
It's her basic rhythm for groundstrokes.
You need to interrupt it first.
Midorikawa, you'll see,
I'm winning the third round by all means!
A shame indeed,
but Midorikawa lost to Broir after all.
But Oka cleared the second round confidently.
Finally, the third round, quarterfinals begin today.
Right! The very first match is
Madame Butterfly vs. Marchesa Broir!
By the way, how's the situation on your side?
Todo doing well?
I appreciate your concern about my right hand.
I do it all the time.
I don't mind starting all over from zero again.
Unlike you, my type is especially good
at starting anything all over again.
You swore to yourself you'd never lose. Are you sure?
As people say, you should never say never.
Because what if one day you lose after all?
I never gave it a thought.
I am sure. I will keep on winning for you as well.
Well said.
Really pleased to hear that!
That's what I hate the most
and also adore about you.
But I'd certainly lose it either way,
if I have to rely on my right hand only.
Take care, will you?
Out.
Hey, show your nerve, messy!
Try harder, Ms. Amateur!
Cheeky brat.
Did Broir just say something
to Madame Butterfly?
This is her strategy.
She's verbally confronting Madame B.
to piss her off.
She shows her contempt for Madame B.
Look.
Those groundstrokes.
Broir intentionally returns the ball
to Madame B's favorite spots.
It’s like she’s assessing Ochou’s strength.
Perhaps, she wants to find out if Madame B.
is as seasoned amateur as she heard.
She doesn't know what kind of amateur
Madame Butterfly is, right?
She remained an amateur on her own volition,
but the one of incredible earnestness!
Please show it to her, Madame Butterfly.
Show you strength and techniques to her,
#14 in world rankings!
Received!
Losing? Me?
Whom to?
To that 14 years old child?
Inconceivable.
That is just inconceivable!
That's not how it's supposed be.
I am Ryuzaki Reika.
If I am getting deposed,
then this is my final match!
I have already parted with playing tennis for myself.
But that time's not now.
I can't quit tennis just yet!
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings messed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
I'm Aikawa Maki.
The Queen's Cup quarter-finals became even hotter!
Madame Butterfly's opponent is the one who defeated Midorikawa, that girl Marchesa Broir!
After fighting exceedingly hard,
Madame Butterfly managed to avenge Midorikawa!
Nothing less from Madame Butterfly!
But is someone else feeling not right today?
To advance to the final and meet Hiromi there,
you have to fight well, Madame Butterfly!
Next time:
"It won't fly, anymore..."