On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Hey, what's going on?
Tennis club is holding a send-off match.
My, how wonderful!
We'll see Madame Butterfly's play!
Yeah, wonderful.
Hiromi, have you heard
what would happen this Saturday?
They'll gather Nishi High's best members
for a send-off match!
Yes, I heard.
The third years will graduate soon, after all.
But the thing is, "Nishi High's best members" are
Captain, right? Madame Butterfly, right?
Oka Hiromi, right?
But there should be one more person.
Would it be Aoi, Otowa, or, perhaps, Hiromi...
Hiromi, isn't that Otowa?
Surgeon Narita Mitsuo M.D.
Hours: 9:00 AM - 6:00 PM
It really is Otowa!
It is.
Otowa!
Well, about the send-off match.
Yes, I've heard.
I'm looking forward to the doubles
between the best members.
So do I.
Well, see you then.
- Excuse us.
- Goodbye.
The send-off match, then?
Why did you ignore it
until it worsened to this extent?
I thought I told you not to strain it so much.
Starting tomorrow, give it a total rest, okay?
If this gets any worse, you won't just lose your
beloved tennis, but your entire right arm movability.
You may lose the ability to move your right arm.
The send-off match. The send-off match!
Episode 22
No Need for Tears
at the Graduation Match!
Break!
I feel strong at today's practice.
Because playing the send-off match
depends on it!
Don't worry, Aoi.
You'll surely be among members.
Oh, I wonder.
Hey, the send-off match will be doubles, right?
Yes, I think so.
- And the teams are...
- No clue, but I'm excited.
It's a pity we should part already.
Can't be helped.
One way or another, we'd have to.
Captain, take care of the rest.
Okay!
I wish they'd announce members and teams sooner!
I'm all revved up!
Your excitement won't help, Maki.
I guess you're right.
Coach!
What is it, Otowa?
Could you let me take part
in the send-off match on Saturday?
Also, please, let me pair up with Oka.
Yesterday, I went to the hospital.
It appears soon enough
my right hand won't even be able to hold a racket.
This match may very well become my last one.
Coach, my right hand
recently went numb amidst practice.
Yes, it started around the day that the victory party
was held at Mr. Ryuzaki's house.
I decided I would quit the tennis
and turned in my letter of resignation.
But you returned that letter to me then
and said me this:
Otowa.
Otowa, make some good friends.
Friends you can share your happiness with,
someone to entrust your dreams to.
Because if you do,
the youth inside you will double its span.
No, it will become everlasting.
Losing the ability to move your hand
will mean nothing.
Do you understand?
Everlasting youth...
Friends I can entrust my dreams to.
Entrust my dreams...
That was when I decided it!
The one I'll entrust my dreams to will be Oka!
Please, let me pair with Oka
during the send-off match!
I want to spend my last match
being a good partner for Oka!
Alright, I understand.
Give it all you've got!
Thank you!
Oh no! Oh no!
We'll be late again!
If we don't hurry, we'll miss the announcement
of Saturday's doubles match members!
Now, I'll announce the teams and members
of Saturday's send-off match.
The Ryuzaki-Hoshino team will face
Otowa-Oka team in this match.
With Otowa...
Ah, what a misfortune,
to go up against Madame Butterfly and the captain!
Hiromi, you're unlucky.
Aikawa! Do you have something to ask?
No! I don't have anything!
All right, then we start the day's practice!
Hoshino, do me this final favor.
Okay!
What? Oka's pairing up with Otowa?
Yeah, it was just announced.
How will those two cope?
Can they even be a pair?
That's a good question. Up until now, there certainly
has been a lot between Otowa and Oka.
They have long been rivals
for playing in official matches.
I wonder why Coach chose Otowa this time.
I'm sorry for calling you out here, Oka.
You see, there was something
I absolutely had to give you.
What is it?
In this notebook, I've accounted down
all the weaknesses in your play.
If I let you read this, this will make my notes
three to four times more valuable.
But why are you giving this to me?
I want you to give me a promise,
Oka.
Promise me you will do your best
in Saturday's send-off match!
Yes, even if we hold this match just to send-off
Captain I'll to do my best nevertheless!
That's a relief to hear.
Let's make sure to win, okay?
But...
Otowa.
What a surprise!
She investigated my weaknesses so thoroughly!
Almost like she made this notebook
for me personally.
But why did Otowa take all those notes?
Oh, what's the matter Goemon?
So unused to seeing me sitting at my desk?
My, you just wanted to play.
Very well.
Oh, right!
I should check the things
written in those notes tomorrow!
What are you doing?
Just keep quiet and come with me!
Tell me what for or I won't go! Tell me!
For this.
Hiromi! You want me to do your homework now?
No way! I'm going home!
Oh no, you don't.
Take a good look.
What?
Otowa was watching my play
and summarized it in notes here.
Otowa did?
It's just as I thought,
Otowa slandered Hiromi in every way!
Jumping to conclusions again, Maki.
Why so? Didn't she write
all those awful things about you here?
But until we test it out,
we can't know if it's just a slander.
You also have a point there.
But is this what you called me out for?
Yes! Do you finally understand?
In that case, the sooner the better!
All right!
Here I go!
Okay!
There!
It's true!
Hiromi, what's wrong now?
It's all true!
Just like how Otowa wrote it in her notes!
It was a slander after all?
Volleys are supposed to be blocked,
but I try to strike them back.
Even things I had no clue about
didn't escape Otowa's keen eye.
Hey, what's wrong?
Maki, this time throw the ball as low as you can!
Got it. Here it comes!
There!
My hips really are stiff.
I'm scared to trip and never twist them.
Now you can see yourself that my notes were no lies,
to the very last letter, Oka.
Maki, alternate left and right now!
Okay!
I never realized there were so many flaws in my play!
Here it comes! There!
There!
Keep on trying, Oka.
Look, Madame Butterfly is here.
- Hey, isn't it Otowa?
- It is.
It'll be interesting to see how well
the newly formed Oka-Otowa pair fares.
Yeah, this might be hard for them.
But I believe Coach arranged this match
with some design in mind.
Is that what you wanted, Otowa?
Is this it?
Otowa, the notebook you gave me earlier
was of great help, thanks a lot for it.
Let's do our best today, then.
Okay!
I expect all of you to show an earnest play.
Play this match
for juniors you're leaving behind.
Okay, start!
Best of three set match!
Hoshino-Ryuzaki team vs.
Otowa-Oka team!
Madame Butterfly, make it count!
Captain, go ahead!
Hiromi, if you lose,
I'm not treating you to hamburgers!
Otowa's service! Play!
I'm starting, Oka!
Okay!
0-15!
Don't forget the notes, Oka!
No good!
Though I practiced to eradicate the flaws,
I forgot everything in an actual match!
Be wary of notes, Oka!
Okay!
There!
15-All!
Kyoko's quite lively
for her first match in awhile.
But Captain and Madame Butterfly
are still far-far ahead.
15-30!
It's one-sided now.
Ryuzaki-Hoshino team
makes this a perfect send-off match.
Still I'd like Oka to try her best for a little more.
I'm sorry about that.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I can already see you gradually improving.
Oka, don't you worry about points. Just play
to the best of your ability and I'll cover the rest.
Okay!
Now!
Game count: 6-4 for Ryuzaki-Hoshino side.
Something happened, Otowa?!
Don't mind it. What's more important, I'm sorry
for letting them take the first set.
Well done, well done.
Here, Hiromi's towel.
Thank you.
And... yours.
Thanks.
Hiromi, it's okay if you lose.
It's just a send-off match so take it easy, easy.
Aikawa!
Even if it's just to see someone off,
a match is a match!
Well, I suppose you're right...
You put all your might in the match
to have no regrets about it.
What else can one do, Aikawa?
Something is at stake... Otowa definitely
has something at stake in this match.
Something...
Second set. Hoshino's service. Play!
Ryuzaki-Hoshino: 6
Otowa-Oka: 4
15-0!
Otowa suddenly moves a lot stiffer
since the beginning of this set!
Timeout!
Timeout!!
I'm suspending the match.
Otowa, let's have a word.
Okay!
What is he doing suspending a match like that?
What's the matter with Otowa?
Her moves were indeed awkward.
Do you still want to continue, Otowa?
I paired you with Oka like you requested,
but I don't think your hand can take any more.
It's enough.
But, Coach...
I understand how you feel.
But what will become of your hand
if the match goes on like this?
Forget tennis, it won't even hold a pencil.
Her hand?
Coach, please let me continue!
This is my final match, after all!
Her final match?!
Even if my hand stops obeying me,
I will, for Oka's sake...
Um, Coach, is there something wrong
with Otowa's hand?
Coach!
I'm sorry. I didn't want you, my partner,
to worry about it.
My right hand is on the verge of collapsing.
I won't be able to play any more tennis now.
How can that be...
Don't worry, Oka.
Of course, it was painful to find out
I can't play any more tennis.
At some point, I wished I was dead.
I thought it'd be better if I quit tennis at once.
But... But you see, Oka,
seeing you try so hard I just couldn't do that.
I made up my mind
to entrust my dream to you.
Therefore, in the little time I have
before this hand becomes totally useless,
- I want to give you all the momentum I can.
- I see... So those notes too...
That's why... That is why, should this match ruin my hand completely, I won't feel in the least sorry.
If it moves your tennis any further,
even by a single step, then... Then I'll take it.
Do your best.
And finally, let me see...
Let me see that one dream of mine fulfilled.
Otowa...
Please do it.
Sure!
Okay, Otowa.
Everyone's waiting.
Let's resume the match.
Hoshino's service. Play!
Will we do our best, Oka?
Yes!
Alright, I'm full of determination!
15-30.
Hey, Ozaki, this turned into quite a fierce match.
Even on Kanto Tournament we didn't see such hits.
Also, look! Otowa-Oka team is taking the lead!
Otowa makes this such an incredible fight!
I have to put out my best as well!
Otowa!
- Hang in there, Otowa!
- Otowa, are you alright?
Now you have no regrets, do you?
Yes.
All right...
Game set!
Although she masterfully obfuscated it from you,
Otowa's hand can't take any more.
Thus, even if unresolved,
the send-off match ends here.
Otowa.
Thank you.
Oka, from now on, play on my behalf too, will you?
Okay!
Otowa.
I'm sorry, Captain, Madame Butterfly,
your send-off match...
What are you saying?
I'm the happiest graduate ever!
With such dependable and earnest club members,
I can graduate with peace of mind.
Thank you for providing me
such a great final match, Oka, Otowa!
Thank you, Captain.
Otowa, it's just as Captain says.
It was a good match.
Coach!
Don't cry, Otowa.
It's unbecoming of you,
as a tennis club manager from now on.
Ryuzaki, Oka, is that all right?
- Yes.
I'll try my hardest too!
Even more so than before!
Because... Because now I'm obliged to play tennis
both for myself and for Otowa!
To Be Continued
A joint training camp is held for the southern Kanto region to select the junior team members.
Seventeen players, including Hiromi, are in attendance.
As well as Midorikawa Ranko of Kaga High,
Kawamura Yumi of Ohara High,
or Tsujima Sato of Wakatake High. All the powerful opponents Hiromi once played against.
With those girls in front of her Hiromi's soul burns with a new fighting spirit.
Look forward to it on the next Aim for the Ace:
"Hit it! This one ball"
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo