I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
I should open the curtains.
January 15th
Plane to US
Oka, aim for the ace!
January 15th
Plane to US
Oka, aim for the ace!
Episode 6
Goodbye, Coach
Hiromi...
I'm going out for a training.
Late into the last night, Hiromi experienced it
for the first time. Losing someone so important to her.
Oka, I'll be by your side until the end of times.
Meeting you was the grandest blessing of my life.
Jin, wake up. It's morning.
You know, Jin,
I think I came up with a good idea.
Day after day,
I will be thinking about Jin only.
All the fun times, along with sad times...
I won't be doing anything else at all.
Just drifting endlessly through my recollections of Jin.
One year, two years, three years...
All of them!
Until I die!
Yes, I'm doing that.
I decided.
I'm trembling in excitement.
I think if I don't act this way,
I will hardly be happy ever again.
It seems, at all times,
this is the only thing the two of us cannot part with.
This teaching is deep-seated.
You're through to Oka family.
Ms. Maki?
We are so grateful for your concern.
How is Hiromi? About that...
Off for a training?
I swear, this girl Hiromi...
Is she really that insensitive?
Let's call it a day here, Oka.
I guess, you too
want to be left alone for a while.
Left alone?
Alone...
Hiromi!
Howdy, howdy!
I knew you'd be here!
Been looking for you.
I thought because of jet lag,
you'd still have a big head.
And then I'm told you're off for a training!
Old habits die hard, Maki.
Even if I don't have a mood for it,
my body carries me to the training regardless.
It really does?
It does, does!
So, till tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
See you later.
Later!
I know!
Hey, Maki, how about we have fun today?
I was so-o-o preoccupied with this,
I never got a day off to have fun.
So now I need a lot of fun to offset it!
All right...
Then, at the hamburger shop
next to the park at 10!
Alright, time to change the attire for once!
Later then. Bye!
Bye!
Hiromi...
Welcome back, Hiromi.
How was the training?
Refreshing to the heart and soul!
Really? That's a relief.
And now, I'm washing my face.
Hiromi?
Tomorrow, the mourning for Mr. Munakata is held.
I know.
Friends are for times like this.
While she is with me, I won't let a hint of sadness
into Hiromi's mind.
"Face is smiling while heart is crying."
At any rate, I must engulf Hiromi in buoyancy,
much like a sea would.
Maki!
Kept you waiting?
No...
Here, have you seen this?
This? Or this?
My, what a stadium jumper!
That's right, that's right.
Stumbled upon this in New York.
Cool, cool!
You haven't touched your hamburger yet?
Mind if I do?
What's your deal, Hiromi?
You didn't get to eat your breakfast?
I've eaten in plenty,
but for some unknown reason my stomach is growling.
Was planning to get full of authentic ones in America,
but never got a day off.
Ended up returning to eating usual Japanese hamburgers
before a chance presented itself.
Yes. That's right. Yes.
Wipe your tears.
It's unseemly.
Thank you.
This way, it's unclear who is comforting who.
Maki, get yourself together!
Oh right, right.
Hey, Maki!
Yes?
How about amusement park?
Let's party!
I approve! Was thinking about that too.
I approve the party!
Did it, you did it!
You little one!
This is perfect! So cool!
Coach Munakata!
Hiromi, what did you say?
Hiromi... Hey, what's wrong, Hiromi? Hiromi!
Yes, she has been like that.
Thank you again for your concern.
Yes, is that all?
I understand. Thanks for your time,
I won't bother you more.
What did they tell you?
After she returned from her "jaunt for fun,"
they never heard a word from her.
Just rushed into her room
and never came out even for a meal.
I guess, it's no use calling her out after all.
Yes...
Let's go there with just four of us.
Sorry for intrusion.
We are Nishi High graduates.
Munakata
We are really sorry to have come unannounced.
But we absolutely needed to present Coach
with homecoming report before the mourning.
No, no. It's good you decided to pay us a visit.
Jin would no doubt had been happy with it too.
You probably never heard of it,
but our daughter got married when she was 18.
A few years later, she returned to this house,
carrying baby Jin.
But before long, she fell ill and perished.
And now, our sweet grandson Jin also followed her,
outrunning us both.
Now we're just an aged pair,
left alone in this big house.
Yet even so, we can keep on living.
Because we have hope,
we can move on from today to tomorrow.
Besides, we now have Daigo here.
We have all of you.
We have a player named Oka Hiromi!
What Jin left behind...
The product of life Jin's spent in this house
is this spectacular linkage of souls he left behind!
It encourages us to live on.
Compared to my 84 years long life, Jin's life of 27 years
is in no way inferior, but in many aspects, surpasses it!
However, in those 27 years,
that flew by in a blink of an eye,
even if for a short instant, even if for a split second,
did he act like a spoiled child? Indulged himself?
Was negligent to details?
Forgave himself anything of that?
Squandered the time away
in meaningless distractions?
I'm talking about all those little trifles,
everyone cannot imagine his life without.
Therefore, I can't help wondering
if there was ever an actual moment,
when he thought to himself
"I'm so glad to be alive!"
This kid's 27 years that ran out so abruptly
will resound with heartbreaking thoughts
in everything and everyone he left behind.
I'll answer the phone.
It must be on the matter
of tomorrow's mourning ceremony.
Indeed, Mr. Daigo goes to a lot of trouble
to look after us in place of Jin.
He hardly ever spills a single word about himself.
But there's something else
I want you all to keep in mind.
While Jin and Daigo were rivals in tennis,
in usual life they were each other's one and only best friend.
That state of affairs remains unaltered even now,
when Jin is no more.
Those two were both
knocked down by a sudden tragedy five years ago.
Marrow leukemia.
And also quite advanced at that.
The diagnosis gave him
no more than 3 more years to live.
Naturally, he retired from playing.
That kid, fortuneless ever since childhood,
has been thrown further down the stairs.
Truly, the God has not been tender in his mischief.
Yet this kid managed to move on even from that.
When I made up my mind to become a coach,
Daigo and I made a promise between us:
When I come across a player worth putting my life into,
Daigo would back me by nurturing this player further on.
But immediately after that, Daigo's response actions
had everyone around them no less dumbfounded.
No wonder - that same day,
he discarded tennis and gone missing.
It was only later that we found out - as a monk
practicing asceticism, he cloistered himself in Eihei Temple.
Eihei Temple?
That school of Buddhism,
with the most severe precepts?
Yes, thanks for all your trouble.
After that, Daigo never came down the mountain
for three years.
And then it was the time
when I came across you, Oka.
Still buried in the ground,
your brilliance was not yet noticeable to a naked eye.
But I could see it, Oka - to me, you were unmistakably
the most important thing ever,
shining like the craziest diamond already.
It's the same for everyone.
Step by step, we use up
the little time allotted to us.
Whether you realize it or not.
Whether you focus on it or not.
The end is coming inevitably.
Therefore, the real question is, in this allotted time, what to look for, in what direction to step forward?
We can but admire the lofty ideals
Coach aligned himself with.
There was no telling if a player
worth betting his everything on exists,
yet Coach Munakata put his life
into unearthing one.
While Mr. Katsura put his life to ascetic practices,
cloistering himself in Eihei to safeguard best friend's will.
What an overwhelming resolve.
Yet this ideal is still only half-achieved.
Since this player by the name of Oka Hiromi
proved to exist.
But the harsh reality is,
Coach Munakata is no longer alive.
Truly harsh, merciless and unwavering reality.
What now? Their ideal is still nowhere near
being achieved in reality.
I there anything we can do about it!?
Coach?
You'll get drenched, Coach!
It's all right.
But it may harm your health.
Doesn't matter anymore.
I'm completely free at last.
I can tell you no more than that.
But... Coach?
Where are you going now?
No more than that.
Coach!
I will forever stay by your side.
Please wait! Coach!
Meeting you was the grandest blessing.
Coach... Please wait! Coach!
Coach! Coach!!
Today, I have to be very careful
to not burst into tears before Hiromi.
Munakata Family Mourning Ceremony
Hiromi. Hiromi, it's your turn.
Coach, look what I've got.
This medal...
I won as a runner-up.
A word... Just one word...
Please tell me I've done well.
So unfair!
Hiromi!
Hiromi...
About my work...
I think I'll take a vacation for a week or so.
Even as parents,
we can do little but watch her suffer.
So why don't we take Hiromi
out on a little journey?
I was once just like you are.
I used to forget many things.
Eventually, I even forgot
my body has a limited lifespan.
However, this one ball
is never like any other ball.
Therefore, you put your heart and soul
into each smash!
I only came to understanding those words with my heart
after I had to cut short my tennis career.
Because just like it did,
everything has its end.
Be it a life or a match,
it has its end.
Day by day, day by day, ball by ball,
steadily and invariably, that end draws closer.
Therefore, mindful that this moment will never come again,
you put your life into it, and hit this ball with all your might!
It was only later that I realized,
Oka, while you can move freely, while you can run freely,
keep playing without any second thoughts.
But... But!
I can no longer play any tennis.
I don't want to!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
This is Aikawa Maki.
Madame Butterfly, Todo and everyone
are worrying really bad.
After all, Hiromi won't even come to eat,
just staring at the sea instead.
If she cannot even take food,
it's over for her!
Really, what should we do about Hiromi?
Meanwhile, though,
Coach Katsura suddenly offers to take Hiromi
under his custody in the Temple.
Next episode: Into Sorrow