On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
I need this and this.
Also, that and that. And this!
Not happening.
No way I can take you along.
We won't be playing around there.
This training camp will decide if I can become the junior team member for the first time.
Oka, Ryuzaki, tomorrow you'll move to a joint camp
of four Southern Kanto prefectures.
In this camp, with Oka as irregular member,
17 boys and girls will take part, of which
only 10 would be appointed to the junior team.
Listen, however hard it gets,
you are to persist to those final 10.
I will persist.
Like I always did before.
By whatever means!
I was granted an irregular vacancy.
Coach solicited it for me, so I have to return the favor
by persisting into the final 10.
My, Goemon...
You can't! You cannot come along!
Episode 23
Hit it! This one ball
South Kanto Tennis Training Camp
Hey, Kihara, hurry up and come out.
Majestic!
To think Japan is still full of such beautiful sights.
And would you look at who just got off the bus.
As you'd expect of players representing prefectures,
members are outstanding.
We absolutely can't be beaten.
Hey, isn't that...
It's Lady Orchid!
Lady Orchid from Kaga!
What a majestic place this is!
How rude of this discourteous bus!
Todo!
Hey, Oka, a fine day to you.
Did you just arrive?
Yes, that's right.
That's a pretty big bag you have.
What is inside there?
Well, you know, chocolates and crackers, and biscuits, and caramels, and uh...
Pass it here.
I'll carry it for you.
Oh, no, I can do it...
No need to be shy, Oka.
I'm fine, really!
Oh, I'm sorry, Oka.
It's all my fault.
Are you all right?
It's good.
But I guess all my spare clothes are soaked.
Goemon! Just when did you sneak in here?
Oh, jeez. That's why it was so heavy,
you mindless creature...
You're such a sticky fellow.
Making me carry you all the way here!
Also, what do I do now?
All my spare clothes are soaked.
Better wear this, lest you catch a cold.
Now let's hurry to the guesthouse to dry off.
But...
Todo's coat is so warm.
I'm so sorry!
Thanks for your work.
Morning, Madame Butterfly.
What are you doing just standing here, Oka?
Uhh, well, nothing important...
I see. Well, let's go.
Okay!
As you'd expect of various schools' top-members.
The practice is in full swing,
without a word from Coach.
All right, that should be it.
Now then, the coat I borrowed from Todo...
Let's see.
Here, here.
Wonderful.
Wonderful. Not only I'm among all that
beautiful scenery, but Todo is also here with me!
It's nigh like a dream!
Line up!
How untimely!
Has everyone lined up?
Not yet!
I'm sorry, I bogged down!
How can you be late even on the first day?
Have you any idea how serious this camp is?
Yes, I'm sorry!
Okay, get in line.
Is that her, Munakata's famous Treasure Child?
Yes, Oka Hiromi.
Among this year's members,
she is the only first-year.
Yeah, each prefecture sent four players,
but Munakata insisted on an irregular fifth one.
I see. That's not good. Everyone else struggles
to narrow their list down to four.
Just because he's a Chief Coach here, doesn't mean
Munakata's students deserve an exception.
Everyone, listen up.
The 17 of you gathered here
are superb players of your respective prefectures.
However, you should already have a hunch,
this camp isn't merely intended to improve your skills.
Here, we will select 5 boys and girls, 10 members
in total, representing the Southern Kanto block.
Right, 5 girls.
Only 5 of us will prevail!
Madame Butterfly.
Lady Orchid of Kaga.
Izuka with her Tornado Serve.
Kawamura from Ohara.
All are excellent players,
selected from a wide assortment.
I am the only one here to have made it this far
on someone else's courtesy.
And now I'm expected to get into the final five!
But... But he won't be forever by my side...
Oka, from now on, you and me
bid defiance to the world.
If we are getting beaten here,
all of my designs, all of my dreams, will vanish!
Oka! Give this training camp
everything you've got!
Then, certainly...
You will certainly be walking firmly!
What is that!?
You should be used to this kind of strength tests!
They would be crucial
for stage two members, so brace up!
Tamiya of Nishiyama High, down at 43.
Sato, down at 47!
Kawamura, impressive spring.
She also has some decent spring to her.
What an incredible hips spring.
With that, she return can any shot, no matter how high!
Even at such speeds,
she is not losing her balance one bit!
That sense of balance
allows her to control any ball with ease!
For now, I am a first time member,
enlisted along with Madame Butterfly and Lady Orchid.
But a gap...
A clear gap lies between me and them!
At this rate, I'll never get chosen
as a stage two member!
I want to catch up with those two!
I want to catch up with them, come what may!
I won't lose...
I won't lose!
Madame Butterfly and Lady Orchid are serious too.
They're seriously thinking of me as an enemy.
Fine! I won't lose either!
Her reflexes could use some more polish.
Tripping over a pebble like that...
Fine!
Until now, Madame Butterfly, Lady Orchid and others were going easy on me, because I'm a year below.
But I won't have that privilege any longer!
Now that I have joined this camp, I can only fight Madame Butterfly and Lady Orchid fair and square!
Okay, it's just the strength tests for today.
You can rest your bodies now.
Fighting Madame Butterfly and Lady Orchid evenly...
How do I do it?
How can I put myself on even footing with them?
Those two. How can they remain so composed?
While I have not a single clue about what to do...
Those two are just playing their own tennis earnestly.
What do I do to catch up?
I'm susceptible, impatient, and while it remains so,
I will inevitably fall further behind.
I don't want it!
I have to do something!
Coach! Coach, I'm begging you!
Madame Butterfly has her own unique style of tennis.
Lady Orchid has her own style of tennis as well!
Please, teach me, what is my tennis style?!
I know I have no talent nor aptitude
neither am I a quick learner at that...
But I'll try my hardest to make up for that!
Therefore... Please teach me what my tennis is like!
I don't want to fall behind anyone!
You finally said it.
I've been waiting for a good year already
just to hear you say that yourself.
A whole year... Then you had this
planned for me from the beginning?
That's the point.
Oka, if I can't teach you your own tennis,
what do I even worth as a coach?
Coach...
In exchange, I want you to follow me.
Grit those teeth and even if you have to crawl,
you're following me unwaveringly. Deal?
Yes.
Okay, then look at that.
Don't you admire that sort of play
as a fellow player?
Powerful drive, sharp volleys, lightning-like net dash.
Hit power, worthy of a whip, and bird-like movements.
So? What do you think?
I admire it the most.
I think it's a wonderful play.
But Todo is a man. I don't think any girl
could pull off that style of play.
And what if you manage it?
Oka, your shoulders are still weak
and arms have a ways to go as well.
You use a light racket.
Go take the heaviest one
and meet me for a special practice later.
How much will I be able to teach you depends fully
on how much your body will be ready to endure.
Okay!
All right. Don't expect a special treatment as a woman.
Come! To the training!
Okay!
Munakata, what in the world
do you have on your mind?
It can't be...
Earlier, Coach said I would be able to adopt
Todo's play style of a male.
I wonder if it's true.
I'm sure it was just the spur of the moment.
But I'm fine with that too.
Especially with Coach
doing all that for me and with me.
He's doing it for me.
To teach me what my tennis is!
Okay, I'm not falling behind!
Oka! You're supposed to endure my coaching,
not to tire out from such a mild roadwork!
Right!
I see. So Munakata is taking it
with all due seriousness.
You decided to bring to life
the cherished dream of every women's' coach.
Right now, the world of girls' tennis
is rapidly shifting.
From the classical Beautiful Tennis
towards men's Power Tennis.
The two currently on the frontline are
Mrs. Bang and Madame Gold.
Both have left their marks in tennis history.
Their techniques and strength
are no inferior to those of men.
They play on a whole other scale,
by far transcending the girls' tennis.
Is that what his design for Oka Hiromi is?
However, in that training regimen,
even a trifling mistake may ruin the player.
Will you still go for it, Munakata?
Such a dreadful thing...
Keep going!
Put some strength into it!
100 and... 6.
100 and... 7.
Oka, you're good for today.
But you'll do this tomorrow and the next day as well!
Okay!
Oka, your hardships only start now.
But when you overcome those hardships,
your dreams will expand to infinity.
The time for you to daze the world will surely come.
Oka, what's the matter?
Well... I couldn't get myself to sleep...
Me neither.
Would you have a seat with me?
- Well, the thing is... I have to return your coat.
- No, no! It's fine.
Yeah, it can wait until later. Later.
I... like you.
I like your cheerfulness, honesty and that spirit
of yours that helps you fight off any hardship to come.
Please, don't lose.
And be sure you do your best
to be one of the five remaining members.
I'm glad I chose to play tennis one day.
Our tennis is to leap forth from the courts
of this training camp, to the courts of the world!
The courts of the world!
The days of difficulties are bound to continue.
But our tomorrow only lies
across those difficult days.
Oka, let's get there together!
Todo, I'll be sure to do my best!
All right!
To Be Continued
Hiromi won the practice match
for becoming a stage two member.
However, Coach Munakata says a victory is pointless
if she didn't score an ace for it.
He gives Hiromi a special training.
This evening... I'll be waiting for you by the lake.
T.T.
And then he orders her to redirect towards tennis
her soul flame, now burning for Todo.
Will she choose love or tennis?
Suddenly, tears precipitate from Hiromi's eyes.
Look forward to the next Aim for the Ace:
The Love Letter that Danced Around the Court
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo