On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
My, even the sun isn't up yet…
The first morning train uptown
should be coming soon.
See, there it is!
This means, by the time I finally make my way back
across this long bridge, the sun will already be out.
Today is my third day running like this.
It's hard get to get up early like this, but…
It's almost time
for the Kanto Junior Championship finals.
I can't be dragging my heels now.
There he is again today.
The sun is so bright
I can only see his yellow muffler but…
I wonder what kind of athlete he is.
Soccer? Baseball? Or maybe…
Oh well, anyways, I've got to do my best
so I don't lose out to Mr. Yellow Muffler.
Episode 20
Rally in the Morning Sun
As the date of the Kanto Junior Championship's
final match closes in, only a week away,
with both the boys and girls' teams in the finals,
Nishi High tennis club intense training
should now be in full swing.
Especially for the team that beat Ohara High's
Kawamura-Okazaki team in the semifinals,
Ryuzaki-Oka team.
It gets good here!
Having completely overcome
the common difficulties of forming a new pair,
they can now be seen on the courts daily, struggling towards victory under Coach Munakata's supervision.
It really feels like all's well in the world.
Right, Hiromi?
Guess it wasn't just a feeling.
She really is at ease.
Then me too.
Hiromi, it's practice time you gotta wake up.
Jeez, Hiromi.
Hey! Are you still asleep? Get up!
Okay!
Hey, Hiromi, it's practice time!
Practice, practice!
Let me just a little longer...
Even if you ask for longer…
Quiet you!
Oka!
What do you want?
Hurry up and come to the court!
Madame B. is already there.
Yes, I'll be right there.
In doubles, two partners can find their true strength
by both putting in equivalent power.
Don't rely on Madame B. forever.
Okay.
Equivalent power.
I understand, Coach.
Every win that Madame Butterfly and I
have conquered so far…
Every time, it was thanks to Madame Butterfly
covering two thirds of the court.
And so we aren't putting in equal power, are we?
If that's the case, secretly every morning…
I know they say a child who sleeps a lot will grow up
strong but you've been taking this to heart lately.
Did you say something?
No, no, not a thing.
Really?
Okay...
You sure are working hard.
Yes, doing my best!
How about you, Mr. Yellow Muffler?
Later then, Mr. Yellow Muffler.
Hiromi. I wonder who is that mysterious
Mr. Yellow Muffler?
Who do you refer to...
Either way, I know nothing!
He has nothing to do with me...
Let's get home.
I've gotta get to bed early.
You're going to bed early too?
It's perfect time.
Ciao!
Adieu!
That Mr. Yellow Muffler…
I know!
Tomorrow I'll try yelling "Good morning!"
to him as loud as I can!
Here he comes. All right!
Good morning!
Oh no. Maybe he didn't hear me.
All right, I'm feeling good this morning so…
I'll double my usual 100 practice swings to 200!
What?
Even someone considered prefecture's Number One
like Todo is out this early!
All right! I've got to do my best too!
Stupid stairs! I hate you!
Hey, Oka. Good morning.
Good morning to you too.
And... I'm sorry for interrupting your practice.
No, you seem to be doing early morning training too.
Uhh, no, what I'm doing
can hardly be called training, so…
Well then, could I ask you to join me, Oka?
Practicing here alone is by all means depressing.
Come on.
Here!
I get to practice with Todo…
It's true when they say the early bird gets the worm!
Go ahead!
Okay!
Got it!
This is wonderful!
I never thought tennis could be so wonderful!
With every hit of the ball my heart dances!
Each time the ball returns
my happiness builds a little more!
It's my second time
exchanging the ball hits with Todo.
Now I can perform them
so much more smoothly than last time.
I'm happy.
So happy!
Somehow, I've gotten to the point
where I can return balls from Todo.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I figured we'd done enough warming up
and it was time to start playing seriously.
We've just been warming up until now?
Then, all those balls up until now
weren't Todo's real balls?
Fine. If someone takes me lightly because I'm a girl,
even if it is Todo, I won't forgive them!
I'll show Todo that I can handle even his real ball!
Aim for the Ace!
You ready, Oka?
Here it comes.
Yes!
There!
Okay, Oka, here comes another one!
Yes! I'm ready!
What's wrong, Oka?
That serve just now wasn't unreturnable.
Give me one more!
Okay!
There!
This time! This time, I'll hit it!
Looks like you hit a home run.
Maybe it's impossible after all.
Maybe I can't return Todo's ball.
Hurry! First period's going to start!
I'm doing the best I can!
No! You have to try harder!
Okay! Don't get scared!
Here we go!
Good grief, it looks like we're totally late now.
I'll go on ahead!
Oh, Oka.
I'll be waiting on the court for you tomorrow too.
All right?
Yes…
It's weird… Why can't I just be happy about this?
Even though he told me so kindly
that he would wait for me there tomorrow.
Why?
What could the reason be?
Hey, Hiromi…
What's going on? You slept yesterday
you're deep in thought today.
I'm sleepy today as well.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Okay! That's all for today.
- Thank you!
Listen, Oka.
Doubles only find their true strength
by both putting in equivalent power.
Equivalent power…
Equivalent power!
I see… Equivalent power!
I understand now…
The reason I couldn't be happy about it
when Todo said he would wait for me earlier…
Is the incredible difference in our abilities.
Even though he generously practiced with me,
I was worried that Todo might have actually
been feeling a little bored because of my ineptitude.
If I could just return
that powerful serve of Todo's even once…
Then I could gladly do it every day!
On that sunset court together with Todo.
I lied after all.
About meeting Todo on the court today.
You want to do late night serve-receive drills?
I'm begging you.
Come with me.
Well, sure, if you want me to,
but why tonight all of a sudden?
Well that is, I'm practicing for another practice.
Practicing for another practice?
What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you see, it's…
I can't admit I'm practicing
for my sunset practice with Todo.
Please understand, Madame Aikawa.
Hey, Hiromi, wouldn't it be better
if you moved a little farther away?
This is fine!
Considering the speed of Todo's serve,
I should get as close as I can.
Okay, Maki, keep going!
All right!
That's right.
I've stopped doing early morning training
and switched over to late night training for now.
Night!
I can't believe those two!
Lately they take naps during every lunch break!
You're right!
This is the fifth day.
Todo has probably given up
and stopped going there by now.
But…
It can't be helped.
I'm… still not at the point
where I'm ready to be Todo's training partner.
It's Mr. Yellow Muffler again.
FIght
Fight?
I see. He must think I'm skipping practice.
Okay, let's try waking up early again!
So you've finally come, Oka.
Ozaki!
I never would have thought
you were Yellow Muffler.
Now get going to the court in the park.
How did you know about that?
I've been running across this bridge
every morning for a year now.
Nothing that happens in the morning escapes me.
Now, would you please go?
The poor fellow has been feeling dejected
for five days now.
It's tough being a friend.
Dejected…
Hey, you're here.
I've been waiting, Oka.
Oh, what's this?
He doesn't seem dejected in the least.
What a letdown.
Hey, Todo, I'm really bad at this,
but don't hold back on my account!
I know! That's exactly what I intend to do.
My, how frustrating.
All right!
There!
That's amazing, Oka!
Returning my serve like that.
You're almost like a boy!
I returned it!
I returned that one Todo's serve!
I'm happy whether he takes it easy or not!
Hiromi is so happy!
What do you think, Oka?
Doesn't it feel like when you hit the ball
you put a little bit of your heart into it?
A bit of my heart into the ball!
That's right!
So when your partner returns the ball,
don't you feel like they give back
a bit of their heart as well?
I do! I most certainly do!
You strike the ball.
The ball returns to you.
Thus, the two hearts communicate.
Am I wrong?
I strike the ball.
The ball returns.
And thus, our hearts communicate.
That's right! I think that's right!
That's right!
That's how it is!
So the more strength your opponent puts in the returned ball, the more you can feel their heart in it.
But right now,
Todo is holding back a little for my sake.
Oh, I want to hit it!
Someday, with Todo,
with both of us putting in equivalent power…
His true heart!
I want to hit Todo's true heart!
To Be Continued
At last, the time has come for the finals
of Kanto Women's Doubles tournament.
Hiromi's heart as she stands on the court
swirls with uncertainty and anticipation.
At the same time, an unexpected tragedy befalls the car bringing Madame Butterfly to the match.
But what sort of tragedy is it?
And will Hiromi and Madame B.
still be able to win the match?
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"Close Call! The Doubles Finals"
Look forward to it!
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo