Video by Pachinko      Subs by Perevodildo
Aim for the ace!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Amazing...
What a dashing game, dear viewers!
Another set point is being played already!
Ryuzaki is aiming to finish the match quickly!
She did it!
Ryuzaki wins the championship!
Ms. Ryuzaki, is there anyone,
you want to dedicate this victory to?
I dedicate it to Ms. Oka.
My present shape would have not been possible
without Oka's help.
If you say so...
In this tournament, of all the girls,
she was the most challenging opponent for me.
Episode 1
I'm even more convinced, I love you      !
Everyone has a dream.
As well as everyone experienced feeling lost.
You have to take a first step to the dream,
lest you start bogging down in everyday routine little by little.
When that happens,
one is bound to lose himself in that bog.
One needs some courage to do this,
yet he has to be not excessively reckless.
Then eventually if you are brave enough,
you will end up trying to become reckless anyhow.
- Easy to say, Chiba...
- You are no exception!
While your dream is still in sight, you put your every effort into it.
That's right, Todo.
At what time do you expect Oka to come here too?
At 2 she is free from her studies.
At 3 we have a training.
Let me introduce, Coach Katsura.
They are public relations executives from "Sanyu" inc.
They were the most persistent about being introduced to you,
Oka's full-time coach.
How may I be of service?
Well...
The goal of our visit is to inquiry Mr. Katsura's intentions
and if your answer is positive,
the rest of our executives will schedule
an additional visit to you.
Despite being eliminated in the second round
at the recent Japan Open,
your trainee impressed us greatly
with her significant abilities and prospect.
We are convinced that she fits our corporate image perfectly.
In addition to annual contract payment, our company will cover any expenses inflicted by attending the matches.
Do you mean Oka will have to transfer to pro league?
That's right.
Our company will provide an extensive backup.
Without a doubt,
Oka will make a first-class tournament pro.
Alright, Oka. You're free for today.
But we usually do a hundred more...
I said you're good to go.
Rest is part of the practice.
Thank you!
Let me say just one thing.
Quit acting like some pesky peddlers.
Player is not a merchandise!
Coach, who were the people filming us?
They observed our practice closely.
Don't mind them.
Just old acquaintances of mine.
Munakata Mansion
I am home.
Welcome back, Daigo.
Will you have dinner?
Yes, if it won't bother you. Thank you.
It was quite...
an eventful day, Munakata.
The time has come when we no longer mention you
on a daily basis.
Don't get me wrong,
but I'm happy with it.
That means Oka, Todo, and Madam B.
can now cope with your death in their everyday lives.
The sore spot you occupy in their hearts
shrinks and dims more and more.
Whether they like it or not,
those fellows will have to blaze their own way from now on.
And it appears they are finally starting to move forward.
Hiromi, are you sure? Won't you catch a cold?
Please prepare a hot bath for me, will you?
I'll do it, and still...
If I don't run every morning,
I feel bad for the rest of the day. Later!
Good morning...
Oka... Good morning.
Roadwork sure is hard under such heavy rain.
What's the matter with you?
Whatcha mean?
This!
Here.
You'll catch a cold!
You're soaking wet!
You gave me a shock.
It was the first time I saw you looking so lost...
Sorry, I was in the middle of training.
Had nothing else on my mind.
You should not apologize...
You are the most clear-headed person I know,
the most composed. And also kind!
You are equally bright, strong and good at tennis!
And also handso—
That's why... I was so shocked.
Thank you, Oka.
Now I'm even more convinced I love you.
Ryuzaki Mansion
Reika, isn't it time for you to come out?
Yes... I was just about to go.
Look here, please!
Here.
According to our news informants,
Japan's leading sports equipment manufacturer Sunstar,
as well as a certain foreign commodities and food producer
both announced offering you a sponsorship.
Ryuzaki Reika - Aspiring Amateur Tennis Player
Which one do you intend to sign a contract with?
Do you maybe have a concrete plan
for your transfer to a pro league?
If you become a pro, does that mean your official record-setting
amateur win streak will stop?
For the moment, I still have nothing concrete to say.
I have indeed been approached with contract talks,
but have not yet responded to neither of the sides.
I can judge matters concerning me turning a pro
only after having conferred them thoroughly with my father.
Can decide on your turning to pro
only after conferring with me, you say?
Thanks for exalting me, Reika.
But in reality you have had it decided since long ago.
Isn't that so?
My eyes do not deceive me, right?
Father, since you understand this yourself,
please rid me of further questions.
Todo is a whole other thing.
He submitted a withdrawal from the university tennis club.
I think he will also drop out of the third year of university.
What is the reason?
No clue. I was also notified just today
by a report from university.
Only the summer remembers the map,
yet it's about to hide behind that horizon.
Whilst my memories are frozen inside a glacier of rusty colors,
through which countless days and nights have passed.
Woman, why are you acting so morose?
You know I've already paid a fortune for you.
I spent last eight years in disgrace and moral decline.
That is more than enough for memories to fade
like an old photofilm tape.
I had but to tuck the fleeting love in the box and ribbon it.
Aikawa!
Maki!
I had to enclose it in the back of a drawer,
just like some trifling woman thing!
The Drama Club presents a play:
"One Step to Midnight"
Starring: Maki Aikawa
Gotcha!
It was so good, Maki!
I genuinely felt your character!
Maki, jokes aside!
That was an ingenious paraphrase!
I'm no good at playing tennis,
so I figured I'd be good at playing roles.
You're a future actress superstar!
Nothing like attending the "Park."
Mistaking reality for a dream come true
is a routine occasion there!
Knock-knock!
However, thy dreams are someplace far away.
Drink more and get drunk more
in the name of song, future and love!
So, what is it you want to tell me?
You called me out to have a talk with me, didn't you?
There's nothing I want to talk about.
I just felt like seeing you suddenly.
I see. Your face suggested
you may be up to something, though.
I guess your practices are as intense as ever?
Unabated!
You are well-nigh a pro now, aren't you?
Your tennis career!
Have you not thought about that?
It's just...
How can you not care about your own future?
I mean, becoming a pro is not such a big deal.
If you say so.
At least it is much more realistic
than me becoming an actress superstar.
Now, closing subject — tennis news.
Winner of the Japan Open Men's Championship, held this June,
Todo Takayuki announced his transition to the pro league.
Todo Takayuki - tennis player
His plan includes dropping out of university
and leaving Japan in order to fight in the global pro-circuit.
Now, the next section...
Ozaki is listening. Yes, it's me.
What a surprising call! Long time no see.
How have you been doing?
Good. What about you?
You have not been appearing a lot in "Park Hill" lately.
At this rate, I will have to retire from tennis.
No, it's both joke and true. Fifty-fifty.
You see, Medical Faculty exhausts me completely.
Yeah, I wish I could play tennis daylong again.
Well, this perplexes me just as well.
He stopped seeing anyone and wanted to be left alone.
I called his house several times, but to no avail.
I need to talk to him, by any means necessary.
He is embarking on some journey.
He will stay in Japan for something like two more weeks, I believe.
What's going on, Oka?
You make junior mistakes!
I'm sorry!
Oka.
Yes?
For the next two weeks
I won't be coming here.
Here is your practice menu for those two weeks.
Instead of hitting the ball,
focus on enhancing your physical strength.
Don't cut the corners because you're alone.
Excuse me...
In two weeks, you will have a physical fitness test. Until then.
Coach!
Excuse me, but did something unexpected happen, Coach?
Spare yourself effort and don't try to stop your Coach.
It's just a two weeks span.
Can you at least tell, where are you going?
I will return to the temple.
I have some errand there only I can do.
Thank you, Oka.
Now I'm even more convinced I love you.
Todo Takayuki is entering the pro league.
He drops out of university and leaves Japan.
Yes, this is Oka family.
Mom, has anyone called me?
Called you?
No, there was nothing of the kind.
Are you sure? Not in any other way?
Why are you asking?
Is someone supposed to call you?
No, nothing of the kind.
Well, okay, thank you.
Todo Takayuki
Isamu Ozaki
Takashi Chiba
For such an occasion,
I don't mind dialing.
It's Todo. For the moment, I am not home.
I'm sorry for having to call you out to this place.
I heard it from Ozaki.
You had more luck than anyone else reaching Todo
on the current matter. Please, share it, Chiba.
I have indeed reached him,
but he never spilled anything concrete to me.
He merely reassured me this is his personal matter.
Can you at least share his current whereabouts then?
I'm sure, as his friend, you are aware of it.
Yes, I am aware of it.
However, he has already started running.
"Whether I prevail or fail miserably, until I return to Japan again,
I don't want to see anyone." That's how he expressed it to me.
Why?
That is the product of thorough consideration
and his solid determination. That is how it appears to me.
After graduating from Nishi High,
we've lost Coach Munakata.
It appears, since then, everyone has been going their own way,
distancing from each other.
I see. Somehow it seemed to me
I'm the only one left behind on the court of Nishi High.
That's not true, Madame Butterfly!
I'm sure Hiromi feels being left behind as well.
Madame Butterfly...
There's no way the mere two weeks of whetting a rusty blade
would make any difference. Come!
I will show you everything I know, regardless!
I'm at your service!
In tennis, it's not the passed test that makes you a pro.
Anyone can go ahead and announce their transition to pro.
Send a notice to association — you're already a pro.
But to fight in the global circuit major matches,
you need to prove with your actions you're a real pro.
Todo, are you prepared to go to the extremes?
I don't understand.
The wall between you and the world of men's tennis is high.
Would you be able to get over it?
I don't understand!
And still...
I still want to prove you wrong!
Alright, Todo! In two weeks you will pass your pro test
and become a pro!
Yes!
I hear you have to conduct trainings by yourself lately.
Is it going fine?
Yes. I strive for the best no matter what.
Having that said,
it still feels a little off.
You can address me anytime.
I hope you don't mind practicing with me.
Is that so?
Thanks a lot!
Well then...
Excuse me...
Excuse me, maybe it's just a rumor,
but are you planning to become a pro as well?
Along with Todo?
Had that been so, you'd be the first one to know, Hiromi.
Attracted by Coach Munakata at the center,
we have all entered this tennis solar system.
Don't you think so?
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
I'm Aikawa Maki.
We're now on our way to the seaside training camp!
We're gonna make the most of
our 19th summer!
But for Hiromi this summer will be difficult.
Todo suddenly takes the undreamed path.
I feel sorry for Hiromi.
Actually, to do this, Todo even asked Coach Katsura for a special training.
But, Coach, why do you keep saying that Todo is not young enough now?
Coming soon: "My 19th summer."