On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Yahoo!
Yahoo, Hiromi! I finally made it here!
To cheer you on, I made it here!
Here, asparagus for you.
And some beef to top it off.
As well as tomato juice.
Now, Hiromi, build up some enduring stamina,
so you can fly confidently forth into the world!
Maki, I know you went to a lot of trouble to come
and support me but it's already over.
The hard training and practice matches -
everything ended on schedule yesterday.
My, so I am too late?
Did you do well, Hiromi?
They chose you as member?
I cannot have any idea about that.
They should be holding the selection meeting
to decide that right now.
A selection meeting?
Episode 26
Hiromi vs. Madame B!
The Final Showdown
Now, let's summarize everyone's views up to this point.
First, these five from the boys.
Todo Takayuki, Ozaki Yu,
Kimura Toshio,
Kato Shunzo,
Ishida Masayoshi.
They are the members advancing into stage two
we agreed upon, am I correct?
Let us then proceed
to a much more complicated part - girls:
Ryuzaki Reika, Midorikawa Ranko,
Kawamura Yumi, Izuka Keiko.
These four members didn't cause any dissent,
but we've yet to have a long debate about the final one.
I think we have already reached unanimity
on this one as well.
That's right!
We all agree that for now, no other player excels
as much as those four to become a selection member!
Isn't it just Munakata?
The only one to oppose all of us.
I'm not opposing anything,
just saying the last one should be Oka Hiromi.
But look at it yourself:
if we include Oka Hiromi, that would mean
disregarding lots of other players of the same level.
Correct. The omitted players
would certainly make a fuss.
That's why I insist on going with these four, instead of including someone unqualified just to fill the vacancy!
Munakata, what can you say to it?
It seems to be 3 against 1.
I am absolutely sure Oka should be on the list.
If Oka does not get included,
I will have to resign as an Association Coach.
Munakata, I can understand how you feel,
but there's nothing to justify for this...
No, due to the camp being a short term one,
the fameless Oka had no chance to show her abilities.
So if I fail to convince you to recognize her,
as Oka's coach,
I'd be guilty of making Oka
come all the way here in vain.
I will leave the rest to you.
Munakata!
Hey, wait, Munakata!
You're still as bullheaded
as back in the college days.
I think I understand how much effort
you're putting into this Oka.
I may even concede that we are the ones
still oblivious to Oka's true power.
Igarashi!
No, wait-wait-wait,
I'm just saying it's possible.
So how about this, Munakata?
I have a solution...
Why won't we give Oka one more chance
to show us her true power?
With a match. She'll have to play and win
one more match against a proper opponent.
In that case, we will, as well, unanimously accept Oka
as one of the members. How does that sound?
How about this, Chairman Ryuzaki?
A brilliant idea. I approve.
Kobayashi, Takatsuki, what do you say?
That sounds reasonable, I agree.
And you, Takatsuki?
Well, I guess it's fine.
However, if we go to such measures,
I want Ryuzaki Reika to be this "proper opponent."
That's ridiculous.
Ryuzaki's isn't just strongest in Kanto,
her power is truly of a national level.
So what's ridiculous about it?
If she's a player Munakata is willing to go this far for,
it seems perfectly reasonable.
Isn't that right, Munakata?
Very well. Let us settle it this way!
Hey, Munakata!
Munakata!
Win! There's nothing else you can do!
Hiromi!
Beat Madame B!
You have no other choice!
Whether the path we've walked together
ends here or keeps on going...
Everything will be decided in this match.
Well, I'll be going ahead, Reika.
Madame Butterfly!
Father told me about the reason for this.
But regardless of the reason...
I knew a day like this would come.
Let's do it. Don't hold back
and give me everything you have.
Jin...
It seems even the great Munakata Jin
is beset with misgiving this time.
It will certainly be fine. No matter how Oka performs,
she will make sure to live up to your expectations.
However unsettling...
Well, let's be on our way.
The match is about to begin now.
Keep being the most confident big bro
in the world for me, okay?
Now, get to the venue.
Let Oka handle the rest.
Best of three set match!
Ryuzaki Reika vs.
Oka Hiromi!
Service: Oka! Play!
The reason I became so obsessed with tennis...
As well as the reason I started playing tennis myself was because I had Madame Butterfly as my role model.
Everything that happened
was thanks to Madame Butterfly.
And now that very Madame Butterfly...
Not only that, you also said
I have to beat her by any means.
What an ironic twist of fate it is
to find myself in this kind of fight.
0-15!
You'd better understand, Oka.
I am an absolute queen who has not yet lost even once.
That's why, in this match,
though I feel sorry for you, I will definitely win!
I may not stand
a 1 in 10 000 chance of winning.
But more than for anyone else, for myself...
For everything I have, for my tennis, I want to win!
I want to defeat Madame Butterfly!!
15-All!
I'm amazed, Todo. They're both putting out
everything they have from the very beginning!
Yeah.
Game: Ryuzaki!
Oka: 0
Ryuzaki: 1
Oka: 1
Ryuzaki: 2
Ryuzaki's lead!
It's hot! I feel like my entire body is boiling!
First set finished!
Game count: 6-3, Ryuzaki!
The score says I'm winning with 6 to 3,
but you're the first ever to make me sweat this hard!
You're so strong! Like a stone wall.
A wide and heavy wall, Madame Butterfly, it's you!
Everyone is so tense,
not daring to spill a word, let alone applauding.
What a grim silence.
Everyone realizes it.
In this tiny training camp in the mountains,
the two shedding blood and struggling,
Oka and Madame Butterfly
are determining their fates.
Oka, can you hear the waterfall?
Yes.
You may be a very thick wall, Madame Butterfly.
But in this second set,
I will certainly break through that wall.
I can feel it.
It's your burning spirit.
However, in a true Ryuzaki Reika manner,
I will put out that spirit.
0-15!
Oka's lead!
Advantage: Oka!
Took it! I finally took the advantage
in the second set, as I promised!
Just one more point!
Just one more point and this set is mine! Okay!
Jin! Look there! Oka's right hand.
Oka...
It's bad! She has a cramp!
Second set finished!
Game count: 6-4, Oka!
Reika!
Finally, it's the final set.
Yes.
Let's do our best.
Game count: 2-1! Oka's lead!
Oka...
3-2! Oka's lead!
Game! 4-4!
Deuce! Deuce!
How peculiar.
I cannot feel the pain in my hand anymore.
At this point, it doesn't even matter if I win or lose.
For me... For me to just chase that ball...
To keep hitting that ball is enough!
Well done, Hiromi.
You managed to follow me this far.
All we can do now, until either you win or I win,
is to conclude the match fighting with all we've got.
Advantage: Ryuzaki!
Hiromi, you'll lose if you don't take this point!
Deuce!
Is this what Munakata wanted us to see?
The true Oka Hiromi?
That swing! That spring!
Those reflexes!
But more than anything, that fighting spirit
that keeps her going for 4 hours now!
We are awake now. No matter who wins this match, Oka Hiromi must remain on the best members list!
Munakata, it's enough. I've seen enough!
No need to do this any further.
Stop the match!
If we don't, it will ruin both of them!
Stop this?
Who can do it now?
Who do you think
has the right to interrupt such a match?
At such moment, when they both
put everything on the line in this match...
We may have been a reason they started
playing this match, but it's different now.
Right now, this match, as well as this entire court, belong to those two, burning their youths relentlessly.
We no longer have any authority over it.
Let those two handle it by themselves.
Advantage: Oka!
She finally did it!
Oka has Madame Butterfly cornered!
Game set! Set count: 2-1 for Oka Hiromi!
Hiromi.
Yes?
Today I lost for the first time.
But I'm proud of it. More than of all the wins
I've had to this day, I'm proud of this single loss.
Madame Butterfly...
Here... For my first victory at the nationals,
I was awarded this pendant.
I'd like you to have it.
Thank you.
Oka.
Yes?
For as long as you keep climbing on,
I will never quit tennis.
Me too.
As long as Todo keeps on climbing.
The burning love...
The burning tomorrow...
On the white tennis court.
The End
Ah, on the tennis court.
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Thank you for tuning in to this series with us!
We'll be waiting for you in Ace wo Nerae 2 🎾
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo