I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Nishi High 53rd graduation ceremony
Our dear graduates,
Since the day you all joined Nishi High,
three quick years have passed already.
But it pleases me to believe, the bright memories
of Nishi High will keep illuminating your hearts hereafter.
Even though in those three years
we also knew a bitter parting.
The loss of tennis club adviser, Coach Munakata,
is, of course, the one I'm talking about.
One has to face all kinds of separation
throughout the lifetime.
Still, a separation always marks a beginning
of a new journey as well.
You, my friends
about to fly out into a new world,
if you ever end up looking for something
that'd illuminate your lives,
from now on, don't forget
that you yourselves are the brightest stars.
Congratulations on graduation!
...month after month,
Through rote we gained our wisdom.
Unnoticed, years passed us by,
And now, though way too soon,
I open up the next of doors -
This morn we're parting ways.
Episode 10
Rivals
Ryuzaki
Yesterday, the board
issued a formal decree.
The Japanese Tennis Association
approved a coach license for Katsura Daigo.
You have been appointed Oka's exclusive coach.
You have my gratitude,
Chairman Ryuzaki.
Oka matriculates at university next month.
She can no longer be a junior.
From here on, we expect her
not just to represent Japan's women tennis,
but also to achieve
great heights in her personal career.
I believe, that was what
both you and Munakata aimed for all along.
Quite so.
It's settled.
All-Japan's Open schedule will soon be announced.
My daughter Reika, Midorikawa Ranko
and finally, Oka...
All-Japan's courts look forward to seeing
what future holds in store for those three.
Roger.
That was a fine tune.
Still, I thought it has a much less violent outro.
Congratulations on becoming
Association's licensed coach.
I'm sure Hiromi would be
the most delighted.
I hope so too.
That's the point.
Maki decided she is resolute
about celebrating our graduation with a lot of Chinese food.
I'll probably return a bit later than planned.
Mr. Katsura called?
Yes. Yes, understood.
What is it about that priest killjoy again?
Don't know yet.
He called me from Coach Munakata's house for something.
What should I try first?
So, what did that Buddhy buddy say?
He said I don't need to join
the university tennis club.
He arranged for me to join
the Park Hill Tennis Club.
Katsura has been appointed
my full-time coach from Association.
So he'll be coaching me in that club.
Splendid!
I know a thing about this club too!
It's Chairman Ryuzaki's exemplary club
with own history and traditions!
In addition, it's super-deluxe! They have cutting-edge training facilities and an indoors heated pool to top it off!
You know, they told me,
this June I'm playing in All-Japan's Open entries.
Naturally! It's a perfect chance to show off Hiromi's true abilities throughout the country!
"How well she fares!
Oka Hiromi embarks on a new journey!
A future of brilliance is waiting for her!"
Go, go, go forth...
Hiromi, what's up with you?
I don't know.
If you don't know,
where are those tears coming from?
What happened?
All-Japan's Open entries...
I want to withdraw.
I understand. Becoming an entry is a matter
of one's personal volition. I cannot have a word in it.
But as your full-time coach,
I would like to hear your motive for that.
I want just a little more time.
What do you want the time for?
I can't understand yet.
You can't understand, then?
Before, everything...
Everything went to my favor before.
I was even sure, just devoting myself to tennis...
Just devoting myself
with all my might would be enough!
That's how I thought it is. And that's what I intended to do.
Moreover, I still understand - it's the best course of action.
And now, chance and circumstances are better than ever.
As though all has aligned together!
But...
It has been three months
without Coach Munakata.
"I'm back on the track already,"
that's how I thought of it.
No, to be completely frank, I made my every effort
to make myself think it is so.
Yet I still can't help it.
It was almost imperceptible at first,
but as time went by, it swelled tremendously -
this impenetrable darkness
that pervades all the empty space in my chest!
It seems, I can't help it, whatever I do!
I'm sorry.
Can you see?
I can't help it!
From time to time, it makes me feel so hollow,
I can't bring myself to doing anything.
Even though I know -
I should be fighting an important match soon!
I'm sorry.
Enough.
The world does not revolve around All-Japan's Open.
But only if you keep on practicing.
Okay.
Can you believe it? Courts exceed 50 in number,
more than anyone in prefecture has!
Chairman Ryuzaki's father, I.e. Madame Butterfly's grandpa
founded it, they say.
It's a clubhouse
with own lineage and traditions.
And then, right on the spot,
they have a first-grade skyscraper hotel.
Within which, a combined sports center
and a heated pool are situated.
We're here.
On Hiromi's new home court.
I scrounged up this club's membership
for myself too.
Though in my case, rather than tennis,
I had the indoor pool in mind when joining big sports!
Where are you supposed to meet with Coach Katsura?
He told me to wait in the tearoom of clubhouse.
Right here?!
There he is...
Then, I'll see you... Until later!
Go change and wait at the 18th court.
I'll join you soon.
Okay.
Changing room is on the first underground floor.
All-Japan's Open
Come in.
We were waiting for you,
Coach Katsura.
Here, here, have a seat.
They inscribed my name already.
I allotted the 18th court
for personal use of you two.
Feel free to use it whenever you feel like it.
Chairman, chances are,
we are not making it in time.
Not making it in time?
Ryuzaki!
It's been a while, Oka.
Have you been doing well?
If, as you say, Oka decides to withdraw,
my daughter Reika won't be the only one discontented.
Miss Midorikawa formally applied for entries today.
Now then, number 18...
Over here, Oka.
Okay!
Todo! Ozaki!
Hello, Oka!
Hi, Oka! Take a look here.
Chiba here too!
Both Todo and Ozaki
have been club members before.
But on this occasion,
I, too, had to start doing tennis.
Oka, what do you say?
Doesn't it make you feel like the entire Nishi High tennis club moved here in full?
It really did!
Alright! Now that the roll call is finished,
why don't we play some mixed doubles?
Madame Butterfly-Ozaki pair vs.
Todo-Oka team. How about that?
This is truly just like the time
I was only starting to play tennis in Nishi High.
Standing on the same court as Madame Butterfly,
enjoying the play, alongside Todo and Ozaki.
Still...
Coach Munakata is nowhere to be seen!
A practice match with me?
Just some one-set match would do.
I'm fine with any place and time convenient for you.
How much I have recovered -
you want to know it, don't you?
Well, I, too, want to see how well
you can handle my bullet serve. Only one way to find out.
I'm sorry to turn you away, but alas,
I have my own, personal training schedule.
Moreover, if I have to receive your bullet serve,
I'd rather do it in an official match.
Gosh, you're as prudish as ever.
But so be it.
So what I've been told is true?
Apparently, the wounds are too deep
for her to overcome yet.
Days and months after the impact,
as, on the outside, she was starting to return
to an undisturbed everyday life,
on the inside, she was growing all the more aware
of how profound her wound really was.
There's no longer anything we... No, this wound
is so serious, not even she has any power to alleviate it.
So that's why she absents
from All-Japan's championship?
She would like a bit more time.
That's what she said.
It's a no way, Hiromi.
I can never turn a blind eye to that.
Aight! Last 5!
4 more!
Last 3!
You know, Oka,
you just hit 997 serves.
900, 90 and 7.
That itself is not a half-bad amount.
But after hitting that much,
why can't you hit those remaining 3?
The former you would have hit it as well.
Not just 3, but a whole 10 more.
No, you used to hit 100 more.
So is it this impenetrable darkness filling your chest
that won't let you hit last 3?
I can't understand it.
What a poor timing.
I'm sorry.
That talk we had the other day.
I changed my mind. I say OK.
Glad to hear. Thanks.
Can I put forward just one condition?
Go ahead, whatever you want.
Instead of one set match,
we'll play a three set match.
Also, just because it's a practice match, doesn't mean
one can throw it in midway, or give in to second thoughts.
Who do you imply by that?
Both you and me alike.
It's like heaven, like heaven!
Say, Hiromi, isn't it good to relax once in a while?
Life is not just about the practice.
Hey, hey, apropos, Hiromi.
When do we go fill ourselves up next time?
Not anytime soon, I reckon. After all, Hiromi would be up to her ears in special practice for All-Japan's Open.
Well, gonna go once you're a champion then.
I'll go have a swim.
Swim?
It won't do.
At times, I don't even feel myself
myself anymore.
Still, something like a big hole
keeps dilating in my chest.
In tennis too... Even while on the special practice,
my thoughts wander off to some unrelated place far away.
Keep yourself together, Hiromi.
At 5AM tomorrow,
come to the ninth court.
I have something to show you.
Oka, will you do me a favor
of being a judge for the match?
Rule is tie-break suspended,
three set match.
Okay!
Midorikawa! Service, play!
Look closely!
Bullet serve!
Oka, count!
15-0!
It ain't no practice match.
Those two are having the most earnest showdown!
It's not over yet!
15-All!
30-15.
Midorikawa spent many weeks hospitalized,
so her stamina is still lacking.
Too bad for you, but the true bullet serve
only works during the onset.
Yet I'm not going to hold my hand back.
I still have to show it -
my determination
to Hiromi!
Look out!
Midorikawa!
Are you alright?
Don't touch me.
A match is underway!
I don't need no one to lend me a hand.
From game's beginning, until conclusion,
a player is alone on the court!
Alone as on the Moon.
You just have to watch.
I will emerge victorious.
Oka, return to the referee seat!
Okay.
Anyone of us is suffering.
Anyone of us has one or two
of those pitch-black holes in our hearts.
You shouldn't think you're somehow special.
You see, to fight that black hole back,
or to run away from it, is one's personal choice.
Look at those two, only a year older than you.
Do you see them running away from it?
Do you see them giving way to the pain?
You are by far not the only one
afflicted by loss of Munakata.
Do you really believe the scar on Midorikawa's heart
have healed completely already?
Look!
Their power gap is apparent.
But in regard to the fighting spirit,
Midorikawa and Ryuzaki are on even grounds!
Even Ryuzaki throws all her power at Midorikawa
in response to her onslaught.
Don't you think it's an honor to be the only special guest
invited to such a magnificent match?
Shouldn't the fact you play tennis at the same age
as Midorikawa Ranko and Ryuzaki Reika
be enough to get you absolutely elated?
Return to light, Oka.
I'm not the only one waiting for you.
Game! Match won by Ryuzaki!
Coach Katsura,
well, I... Well...
with those two amazing people...
You think you can take them on?
Those two.
I can't know for sure yet.
But... But I want to win!
I will join the entries of All-Japan's Open!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   Johnny-englishsubs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I'm Aikawa Maki.
Hiromi and I have become young college student girls,
outblooming even flowers!
But with Hiromi, it's business as usual.
From sunrise to sunset,
she is busy with All-Japan's Open special practice.
Will she be alright?
But I guess it's nothing. Because she is so lucky
to have Katsura and Todo, I know she'll be fine.
But I won't let my guard down.
After all, Madame Butterfly leaves the practice court
covered in bruises!
Next time:
The Night Before the Showdown