I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Hiromi Oka, it's time.
Come to the court.
Okay.
You hear? It's raining, all day raining.
Here it's rainy New York!
It's raining here too.
All the remaining snow
nearly disappeared because of it.
For real?
Why would I lie...
Then it rains all around the globe today.
But that means,
I absolutely wanna report it to Coach Munakata!
What is it?
About how far I could advance!
Made it all the way to final round!
And opponent is the most prominent
next American tennis queen candidate, Belle Mackenzie!
You know what it means?
At 18, she is a world-ranker already!
I can't tell if it was by abilities or luck, but after getting this far, you'll make it to the very end, won't you?
When you put it like that,
you're making me uneasy too, you know.
Say, Maki, haven't you got sick recently?
Ah, sorry. Yeah, just a bit.
Think I might have a cold.
You did well up to this point.
Great job!
That's why he said he's looking forward to your return.
He knew Hiromi would bring home a medal!
Who?
Dummy, ain't that obvious?
Coach Munakata, who taught you everything!
For real?
And that's why you should keep going!
OK, OK! Got you covered!
Coach, this is my final match here.
I could only make it this far thanks to Coach
walking this way alongside me, in my thoughts.
And that's why, with all my heart,
I want to bring back a medal now.
After all, that will make Coach
commend me wholeheartedly for once!
You're not getting away this time, Coach.
Coach, this will be your penalty
for not coming to America!
Alright, I'm doing it!
Episode 5
The Diary Left Behind
The best of three set match.
Oka's service. Play.
Fault!
Ms. Magic Girl that comes from the Orient, then?
Isn't it a bit too soon for you
to stand on this court?
Madame Butterfly,
how did Belle perform in semifinals?
Physical force of a man,
won't ever let slide a light-headed serve.
If she doesn't secure the first serve,
this will turn into a messy match.
Calm down...
I have to calm down!
Calm down, Oka!
This kind of second serve will never do!
No good! Course is light-headed.
You'll be stopped in your tracks at once!
One more time!
Okay!
Toss with more precision!
Twist your hips more!
Be light in your balance!
You think it's always excusable
to use the second serve, don't you?
Hit your first serve with confidence,
like that of your second serve!
Hit your more powerful first serve
without hesitation!
Now, go on!
Okay...
Repeat it over and over
until you do it reflexively!
What is this serve?
Nonsense!
This is some nonsense!
I'm wide open!
How can this be?
Such power in that petite body?
15-0.
I see. Her getting in this final round
was by no means a fluke.
The expression of #1 Seed just changed.
Oka...
Thanks to your and Munakata's hard work,
the US #1 Seed is now compelled to fight you as equal.
While you are free to fight any way you want.
This legacy is what one man named Munakata Jin
has been honing until the very last flicker of his life,
and then left behind.
This feels so good!
My body moves like a perfect image!
I can't hit an ace.
She won't let me score at all!
But I cannot lose!
After all, I am the #1 Seed!
I got this!
She got this!
Game. 6 to 4. Set - Belle.
This may have turned the tide completely just now!
But it's still Oka who sets the pace of the match.
She will take the next set.
I think so too.
This feels great, Coach!
Coach, I can move
exactly the way you taught me!
She'll come home soon.
In the span of the next two days.
Then a big turmoil will follow,
for you will no longer be gone just for me.
After all, the person who is coming home
depends on you even more than I do.
Till later, Munakata.
From now on, it's my turn to become a Demon.
This is mine!
No good!
Hiromi!
Oka!
She stopped halfway, going for that ball...
Something was off just now.
In the last point, with Oka...
Oka must have injured her knee.
Bell, what's the matter? You're not your usual self.
But instead, you're terrified!
The fear wells up in me,
but I have to hold on!
I'm the one still holding the points' lead,
Belle Mackenzie!
Hiromi...
Game set.
Match won by Belle Mackenzie.
Warmest congratulations.
Thank you.
I hope we meet again, someday.
Not just someday.
We certainly will!
Hiromi Oka, please come to this year's Wimbledon
to be my opponent.
Okay!
Coach, I made it to the end.
New York adventure without Coach
is hereby concluded!
Now, I return to Japan!
Till next time, Angie.
I hope, I come to Japan soon too!
Please do.
Goodbye!
Hiromi.
Yes?
My dearest Hiromi...
Now it's winter outside.
But spring is always around the corner.
Only those, who endured it all the way through winter,
can enjoy the warmth of spring to follow - don't forget that.
Because I hold a firm belief -
you are the type of person to endure it to the end.
Deal? Whatever comes at you,
don't lose your spirits.
Okay, Coach Reynolds.
Did Papa just say
My dearest Hiromi?
That time, too...
In the pro tournament, I was vanquished
and swept out with a laughable score.
For the first time in my life,
I plunged so deep into desperation then.
My dearest and only daughter...
Papa also started this way
and so brought the tennis player in me back to life!
But now, he used this word
for the second time ever!
There must be something really grave
about to hit Hiromi!
Hiromi!
I wonder, where we are flying now.
But either way,
I can feel Japan getting closer.
In order to show it to Coach Munakata right away,
I put the medal in the pocket on me.
My handmade souvenir is also here with me
to present it at once.
Coach...
Though it's been just three weeks,
it felt like we haven't seen for a full year.
When you find out I was thinking about such things
during matches, you'll throw a fit. It's fine.
Because it's the truth!
I just wanted to see you.
Sleep well, Oka.
After this,
it would probably be a long time
before you can sleep as soundly.
Coach, your health...
Your health finally got better?
Yes, absolutely...
My condition is absolutely fantastic.
It really is?
I'm so glad!
Well... Here it is.
Your runner up medal, is it?
You did well.
'Twas a fine match.
Then, you've read the news...
No, I saw the match itself.
You mean, in America?
Didn't I tell you I'd come later?
A fine match, in all truthfulness.
Hiromi, here, here!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Oka.
Keep up the good work.
Sure! I mean... Okay!
Welcome back, Hiromi.
Welcome.
Even dad attends!
I'm really home!
My, Maki, did you happen to gain some
while we haven't seen?
Is that how you treat your lifelong friend?
I'm sure it's Hiromi who has been gorging
on America's mammoth steaks!
Think again!
I burned all of my cholesterol in matches!
By the way, what about Coach?
Coach Munakata.
My, my, you really expect that Coach to be yelling
something like "Yo, welcome back!" at such a place?
- But you know...
- Instead, hey, what about souvenirs?
I've been looking so forward to it!
This car! Hurry-scurry onboard,
Madame Souvenir!
Hey, Maki, you could use some more reserve,
even as a friend!
What are you talking about?
Who would ever want a reserved friend?
Everyone, I appreciate your cooperation
in such circumstances.
However, the real difficulties begin just now.
4-6, 7-5 and 5-7?
That gold medal was so close!
Hey, Maki, Coach has not been discharged yet?
Even a close checkup can't take that long!
About that...
They shouldn't have called it "close" then!
Actually, know what?
Goemon has become a Papa meanwhile!
Right, ma'am?
Yes, immediately after you left for America.
By the way, Hiromi, recently
we received a call from some Mr. Katsura.
He now lives at Mr. Munakata's house
and asked you to come.
Oh my, so Coach is no longer hospitalized!
He must have returned home then.
There was no need to deny it until now!
Mr. Chauffeur,
please get us to one more place.
'Kay.
You go ahead and return home.
I've got a lot of souvenirs and reports to present to Coach.
Hiromi!
Well... You know, Hiromi.
What is it, Maki?
The thing is,
I'll stay awake through this night.
So if you wanna call someone,
I'd listen to your stories gladly.
What are you talking about?
There'll be another day full of stories tomorrow!
Later!
Yeah...
Ms. Aikawa, you have our gratitude...
It's nothing.
Coach! Coach, I knew you'd be here!
I'm finally ba—
Welcome.
I'm sorry,
I mistook you for Coach just now.
So, is Coach here?
Come in.
But...
I have chills all over my body.
Oka, I can almost hear you wailing.
My dearest... My dearest Hiromi.
There is no longer a way for anybody
to protect her from this reality.
So...
I've got something to show you.
A diary? Instead, can't you tell me
where Coach Munakata is?
Read it.
From where I squeezed in the bookmark.
Coach Munakata's handwriting?
So it's Coach's diary...
"I took over the coaching
of Nishi High tennis club."
A player worth bringing up, to bet my everything on,
has finally appeared.
Oka Hiromi. Though still crude,
I think she has a strong natural predisposition.
He writes about me here!
At twice the usual... No, at God knows how many times
the usual speed, I will be bringing Oka up.
There's no other way around it.
But it's still to be seen
if she manages to keep up with such regimen.
Coach's diary... Why now?
"It seems, my time is running short eventually."
It seems, my time is eventually running short.
Sharp pain - I occasionally lose consciousness.
Three times already in this week alone.
For how much longer will I last?
December 15th.
A long-awaited letter from Daigo says,
in a matter of days, he'll come too.
I hope, I'll have enough time
to introduce him to Oka...
Coach!
Coach Munakata, where are you?
Oka came to see you!
Read further!
For you, it is a duty
to read this Munakata's diary in full!
Duty?
Exactly.
December 25th.
Daigo arrived,
accompanied by his usual 24oz.
I could finally introduce him to Oka.
Oka, when I first wrote him a letter about you
two years ago, his first conclusion was that you are a guy.
It was only later that his error surfaced
when he found out you're a woman.
But as of now, from your predispositions and habits
to your body rhythm -
he knows you like the back of his hand.
From 16 till 22, we fought others in a pair, or chased the same yellow ball, with net squeezed in between.
And as for the next 5 years,
we envisioned us spending them the exact same way.
First death, then hope...
I allude to you.
December 26th - hospitalized.
I was given 3 years at best,
yet I endured it all the way until today.
Had I just a month more,
your results from America would have come.
No, even two weeks is enough!
Just greeting you all
on your everyday training would be enough.
This way, I'd send you all off
without ever giving you any idea.
Because Oka, I know Katsura Daigo
will relieve me as your pillar of support afterwards.
Oka, I will be by your side
until the end of times.
Your play is my play!
Meeting you was the grandest blessing of my life.
January 15th.
Plane to US.
Oka, aim for the ace!
Blank page?
Nothing else is written...
What's next? Next? Next?!
Tell me, what about January 16th?
17th? 18th?
What about January 19th?
Please show me it!
There has to be a diary from January 15th on!
Mr. Katsura!
At 6:37 of January 15th,
the man who was a coach to you
and a bosom friend to me
stopped making new entries in his diary.
Coach...
No!!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I'm Aikawa Maki.
Hiromi is acting somehow weird.
She just lost someone so important to her.
Yet on the very next day
she fights hard on a training!
Is she really that insensitive?
Moreover, she invites me to have fun
in the amusement park!
And all of that just before the funerals...
Just what the heck is going on in her head?
Next time: Goodbye, Coach.