Video by Pachinko      Subs by Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Thank you, Oka.
I'm even more convinced now, I love you.
Episode 2
My 19th Summer
The sea, you say?
Sounds great...
But you know, I need to go to club every afternoon.
The "menu" has to be fulfilled.
What are you talking about? Coach Katsura returned to the temple.
And a practice for girl can be done on the seaside as well.
The drama club is coming too. We rented a house by the sea.
There will also be 8 guys and 3 girls.
House by the sea: 2 nights, 3 days
Don't you see we have a shortage without you?
You'll never get bored!
Everyone is excited over the top!
But I really can't afford to be away for three days.
I might get a call during that time.
Who are you getting a call from?
You just said, "I might get a call while I'm away."
Whom from?
Champion Takayuki becomes a pro
Don't play stupid now!
Did I really say that?
Not gonna tell?
I'm intrigued...
Come on, it can't be Coach Katsura.
Local train departs for Hashimoto at 14:54 from track 4
Todo...
What are you doing now?
Where are you now?
I saw it in TV news.
Your announcement of becoming a pro.
Your announcement of dropping out of university.
I tried so hard, but I couldn't reach you by phone...
They say Todo is now having the hardest times ever.
I can understand that. I tried calling you
because I don't think there's anything I can do for you now.
Since that morning...
we have not seen each other.
Ms. Oka Hiromi, right?
Sorry to bother you.
I am a "Sports Toto" reporter,
and I hope you won't mind a quick interview.
Mr. Todo is the subject.
You both graduated from Nishi High, right?
We are writing a short biography of Todo.
Collecting info from various sources.
Yeah, but when we approached him for an interview today,
he turned us down.
Approached him?
You mean you are aware of Todo's whereabouts?
We looked for him tenaciously and it bore a fruit.
Won't you please tell me where Todo is?
Sure! But take it easy,
we're the ones interviewing here!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Mr. Todo, in fact
moved to one of the Buddhist shrines of Kamakura.
Yes, the one he trusts the most.
Hiromi? Going somewhere?
Yes... I'm...
I'm going to Coach Katsura's shrine.
I suddenly needed his advice for my practices, therefore...
Will you go there this late?
Won't you even have dinner with us?
Yes...
Have you called him?
Sure you won't wake him up that late?
It's also raining now.
Maybe it'd be better if you visit him tomorrow?
Follow the racket with your eyes.
Control its movement tightly till the end.
Is it still too long?
It is!
If your reach is further,
you can handle the ball without leaving the baseline.
For a Japan Open Champion this should be a piece of cake!
"No matter how pleasant was the touch of silk satin dress
to the skin, I just could not stand still here and cope with it.
I was too much scared of that person!"
Great! Ms. Wei from Yamashita, keep it up!
And now a letter from Shimano,
Ms. Keiko, class A of year 2. Let's read.
"I hate this thing called love."
Interesting already!
"My sister is a traitor, and I am a fool!
I don't want to see my sister! I only want to die."
But...
Todo seems...
to have made up his mind
to leave for America in about two weeks.
In two weeks?
Right...
After that, he won't come back to Japan soon.
Many thanks!
There's nothing to fear, Hiromi.
What about the independent training?
Take courage!
What about the plan I drew for you?
Well... Actually...
Why did you come here? You should be at "Park Hill" now,
performing a weight training!
That's why I'm here! I can't take it anymore!
This lonesome practice drives me crazy, but here...
At Coach's place I can carry on training alone!
What...
I swear, I will keep myself occupied every day here!
Hello, Todo...
Oka... Hello.
Oka.
Yes?
I am constantly busy here.
I can't spare time to look after you.
If it's fine, you can stay in this temple.
Really?
I see you brought along two weeks' worth of clothes.
Yes...
You can stay in the room you lived in before.
Okay!
How most unexpected!
I had no idea you are that skilled on piano!
Parents made me take lessons
ever since I was in middle school.
The piano was first,
but then you switched to camera?
Well... yeah...
I could meet with Todo not long ago.
Naturally, I informed him about your request for a meeting.
He is OK with that, you can visit him anytime...
However, he now has his hands full
with pro-test preparations.
With Coach Katsura?
You know already?
Yes... Our mutual acquaintance told me where to find him.
Since you are going to see Todo...
Do you mind if Ozaki and I accompany you?
Naturally I don't.
But what for?
To avert any injustice.
Injustice? I'm going there merely to discuss Todo's announcement.
I just want to know his view of it, that's all.
Madame Butterfly,
the idea of becoming a pro is detestable to you.
That is not so.
No. You rejected every contract from major sponsors,
and refused to become a pro.
That is a matter of my personal judgment.
Answer me then, what do you want to hear?
How is this different for him? For his personal judgment?
You have some wrong ideas about me, Chiba.
You and Ozaki are not the only ones to call him a friend.
During our days at Nishi High,
we played countless matches in doubles.
What is it, Todo?
Out of breath with just 2000 swings?
This way you would never win a full set.
You need to apply more strength,
timings are also not even close to exact.
Power should have more sway over rocket
since you're already an Overripe!
Okay...
An Overripe?
He said Todo is an Overripe?
Todo who is still in his early twenties is an overripe already...
How is it possible?
That's nonsense!
Good morning.
Morning.
I see you're doing fine since then.
Yes.
I have lost count
how many times I called your phone.
TV and newspapers were so solemn about you turning a pro...
But in my memory the image is still vivid of you,
looking so hurt and broken that rainy day.
It was only later that I figured out you looked so lost then
because of all the worrying pondering about turning a pro.
That's why I was so terribly worried. I had no idea what to do.
I thought "I love Todo, and that's all that matters..."
Then someone told me you are here.
I still have no idea why, or what for,
but I came here because I didn't know any better.
I'll be fine no matter what, Todo.
There's just this inexplicable trembling in my chest.
You will be fine, right?
Thank you.
Well... Coach, I brought this along.
Please treat yourself.
Todo, you too.
Have some.
Thank you.
So... This is a "Sports Drink." With orange, pine, peach...
Oka!
Yes?
What about 1000 serves, 50 meters of shuttle run,
5 kilometers of roadwork?!
Finished already!
I got up early.
Then...
Go back to your room,
let your body rest.
Okay!
Sports drink, want some?
"Dear Maki,
I hope you enjoy your midsummer to the fullest.
This nineteenth summer of my life
will surely make a great memory!
Because so far this summer
has already became quite unforgettable.
Let us both take caution to not fall into unreserved drinking, eating and resting.
Well, one way or another, for me this 19th summer
is special for so much reasons.
In ten years or so I could tell you the whole story...
That's all for now.
Wholeheartedly yours, H.O."
The reason I sought to see you
and the reason I needed to have a word with you is...
Despite all the differences between us,
we spent precious high school years on the same court.
Please answer me sincerely, Todo...
Why would one not be content with a once climbed peak?
Why would he climb it again?
What do you mean
"be content with once climbed peak?"
Todo is still in a good shape
and cannot be seen as a "player without future."
Even knowing you'll get shattered to pieces,
even knowing that in the pro world
you don't have a single chance to shine,
you still advertently doom yourself to this.
What for?
- Madame Butterfly!
- Chiba...
Please give us an answer, Todo.
Please answer to me as to someone who climbed this peak along with you.
Coach Katsura, you do, of course,
understand it as well as I do.
Why, then, are you not making a single effort to stop Todo?
Why are you sending hopelessly Overripe Todo
into the pit of the pro world?
I did not force him.
Todo chose this path himself.
Madame Butterfly, I don't get it one bit!
Todo is just 21 years old!
Just like me, Todo started playing tennis
at the age of 8.
From the age of 8,
we were both spending our daylongs on the court.
Does it make the idea clearer?
In middle school you become a regular.
During the 6 years of high school
you're supposed to appear in players' top regularly.
Does it make the idea clearer?
Speed of reflexes, instantaneous power, whole body strength...
In boxing it's the retiring age,
and tennis is no less harsh a sport.
Come to your senses
and see that the world's top is occupied by 10-odd players!
While you may reach it by your mid-twenties at best.
The time when thirty-odd players
could make it there is long gone!
Nowadays they are taught
to give their all to tennis since infancy!
So that they reach their peak while still young,
and then leave it.
Well, but what if Todo could just...
Todo, you and I had a chance to become pros,
had we started to aspire for it as long ago as back in middle school,
when we were approaching our peak,
but not now, when we're past it.
Right now, our experience and techniques
wouldn't stand a single chance in the pro world!
You'll be ridiculed like a whipping boy!
Don't you still get it, Todo?
Why are you doing this regardless?
Why are you still trying to do the impossible?
For the same reason Coach Munakata then
began teaching tennis to the newbie Oka
and not the experienced me, which drove me mad.
I was just a year older!
But only recently I realized
I was already on my peak and had nowhere to rise...
I felt desolated...
Coach Munakata's demeanor was so dignified,
I used to loathe it back then.
Todo, I love tennis no less than you do.
Tennis is my whole life, but I don't dare to become a pro.
As an amateur, you can forever keep playing at your comfortable pace, without having to part with tennis. That's how I see it...
I am worried about you, with all my heart.
Like a true friend.
Thank you, Madame Butterfly. Thank you.
Everything you said was a gospel truth. Thank you.
I was full of determination to keep this to myself,
without ever telling anyone.
I should have told you earlier.
When Munakata Jin fell ill and retired from athletes,
he was 21.
Which is my current age as well.
Therefore,
had Mr. Munakata eluded his incurable disease,
would he have continued his career unabated?
What do you think?
That is what bugs me now.
I'm sure he'd unleash on the world,
get involved in everything within his reach.
But then death called him. He left us while still young,
that genius player of an unfortunate fate, Munakata Jin.
Since I inherited his teachings,
I had to follow that urge, whether I like it or not,
as the one fortunately wielding a healthy body.
Even though chances are,
I will never be able to reach his level.
At 21, he had to give up a player's life,
but I'll try to finish what this man couldn't.
Madame Butterfly said everything right.
I am indeed already past my peak.
Mr. Munakata started playing tennis when he entered high school.
But I do it since 8.
In terms of tennis, I might very well be an elder.
But... But that's what I believe in.
I believe in Mr. Munakata.
In what he saw with his own eyes!
I hold firmly to his way of life,
engraved on my heart.
If I have already reached my peak once,
I can certainly get there again!
To drop out of university...
To announce transition to pro...
I hesitated, I was restless.
But I ultimately chose to go forward.
Now or never!
Even now I still can and must achieve something!
For I don't want Munakata Jin to shrink
to just a fading reminiscence! Not this way...
The way he lived while was still alive...
I want to live this way too!
What happened, Oka?
I thought you were to stay for two weeks.
Excuse me. I'd better go home.
At such an important moment for him
I don't want to get in the way.
But... Todo will pass his pro-test brilliantly, right?
Well, who knows.
Whatever is ahead,
please don't give up.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
The day when Todo embarks on his long journey is here.
But we should not be sad about this.
We should keep our chins up!
Right, Hiromi?
Can you imagine, on the day of departure, Coach Katsura organizes
a training match with Madame Butterfly. What a heartless coach!
Hiromi, hang on!
You might run out of time to say goodbye to him!
Coming soon: "Never Say Goodbye."