Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Central Park, 6AM
I'm getting closer.
I can feel myself getting closer to Todo!
Episode 6
New York,
the city where Todo is
Who is it?
Are you Todo?
Are you Todo Takayuki?
Yes...
Greets! Sorry for the poor timing.
You can call me Sayama.
Mr. Sayama?
I'm a local sports articles curator.
Well, it'd be fair to call me a free rep-writer.
Don't be surprised.
Chiba told me a lot, this and that.
Chiba, then?
I was interviewing someone in this area,
so I decided to stop by for a moment.
Going elsewhere?
Yes, this apartment's lease is due today.
Switching for a better apartment?
No. It's just that I have to go to Boston tomorrow.
Boston?
Yes. For regional qualifiers.
The match for the right to enter the US pro-circuit?
Sorry about that.
It's nothing.
Good luck out there.
This one is attended by a lot of players,
so you should not expect an easy ride.
Your flight is at 3 PM tomorrow, right?
Yes.
But that's more than a day away!
You are not quartered now, are you?
Yeah...
Then come to my apartment!
I was renting it together with a companion
who dropped out recently, so there's a lot of free space now.
Mr. Sayama...
It may be a little noisy at times,
but I'd say it is mind-straightening.
Thank you so much.
I'd be glad to. However.
I'm told near the airport
one can find a cheap and decent motel, therefore...
I see. Well, I understand.
Then, if you get into trouble in this country, feel free to call.
Okay.
Don't let us down!
For the second time, I'm in New York!
When I was here for the first time nine months ago, Todo, Ozaki,
and of course, Madame Butterfly were here with me.
However, this time I am all alone here.
Just as lonely as Todo, whom I am visiting.
New York,
the city where Todo is...
Maki, this is the place!
I made it here safely!
Let's see... Room 501.
Here it is!
Maybe he is out for practice? Well, it's fine.
Sooner or later, he should come back here. I can wait until.
What are you doing over here?
Well...
Are you Japanese too?
Visiting the guy from room 501? Something like Todo?
Yes. Right! It's him!
Well, Mr. Todo moved out of the room
this morning with his belongings.
How can that...
He just packed and left without a word to landlord.
I didn't even have a chance to ask where to.
This is so wrong...
I warned him about my today's arrival in New York in the last letter.
I wonder if this letter ever reached him.
Because upon receiving such a letter,
Todo would certainly wait for me.
What should I do now?
Calm down...
Calm down and think the situation through, Hiromi.
First of all... I need to find a place to stay.
Right. Hotel. I need to find a hotel.
I need to find a hotel and have a meal.
But above all, to calm down.
And after that, make a call to Japan.
Right! To Chiba! Chiba will definitely
have some news about Todo. And will share it.
Alright, that's the way!
You'll make it, Hiromi!
It's no use... He would have never called for help.
That'd make everyone even more worried.
And that's why I can't call either.
What matters is that I'm in New York.
Which means Todo is somewhere within the vicinity.
First of all, find a hotel.
That's it! During my last visit, I was staying in a pretty hotel
with a tennis court near Central Park.
It's a great idea and a great place to go!
Excuse me, I don't have any reservation,
but can I have a room?
I'm sorry.
Our rooms are all reserved for today.
This one is full to the brim.
Well, can't be helped. Have to look for another hotel now.
But before that, gotta fill my stomach with something.
Can I have a cup of coffee and sandwich?
What am I seeing? Can it be Oka? Hiromi?
It's really you!
How on Earth did you end up in such a place?
Midorikawa...
Midorikawa Ranko!
Oh no! My coffee!
Come on...
It's okay, Miss.
I'll take care of it.
I'm sorry.
I am kind of completely lost now...
Thank you. I'll have a lemonade.
Come on, start eating.
Isn't it what you came here for?
- Cheer up.
- Yes...
I came here about a month ago
to use a special practice at the local tennis club.
My right is much better already.
Though not enough to hold the racket yet. I'm a southpaw now.
I am still planning a comeback.
It's unfair to give all the honors to you and Madame Butterfly.
I'm glad. Everyone was worried about you,
like "Where did Ms. Ranko go so suddenly and why?"
That's how it is. I'm so relieved.
For some reason, I feel so much better.
Well, let's listen to your bio now.
Will you tell me
how you ended up here all alone?
Your pitiful look suggested
no one in the world is more upset than you are.
Well, I came here to visit one person,
but it seems that he had already left...
Who is it?
Do I know him by any relation?
Yes. It's Todo, if you want to know...
So well... Support him.
I wanted to support him.
Todo is trying to become a pro here.
That's why I...
Why I...
It's getting cold already.
I believe, you are living in that hotel now?
No, I didn't manage to check-in.
Then, my apartment is open for you.
It's not far from here.
What are you up to, Oka? Apparently, I'm a little lost.
It feels like I'm at the very bottom.
At the moment, I'm about to leave New York,
the very city I was so eager to get into.
I intended to start my climb by winning in US Open preliminaries.
However, my plan crumbled when I suffered a devastating defeat.
This time, I'm going to Boston. The competition to be held there
does not hold a candle to the US Open.
Now I plan to start by taking part in tiny tournaments.
Forgive me, Oka.
I'm afraid your next letter won't reach me.
These are my own mistakes.
My own weaknesses.
But returning now is not an option.
During all this time,
the main beam supporting my heart was you.
Whenever I have a minute to spare,
all the thoughts in my head are about you.
At the moment, I'm so lost.
I want to see you.
You were the main support for my heart
When easier times come, I want to tell you something
But right now I can't do it
First I have to make a name for myself
Idiot. Pull yourself together, Todo!
To begin with, I'll contact the local Tennis Association.
Sorry for the trouble.
Hello?
I'd like to know about a Japanese player.
Yes... His name is Takayuki Todo.
Uh-huh. T, A, K, A, Y, U, K, I...
Their manager has already gone home,
so they can't say anything.
First thing in the morning,
I'll try to call them again.
Don't worry. There are not many
male Japanese pro players in the local pro-circuit.
It's only a matter of time for us to find him.
Want some coffee?
Yes.
Here you go.
Sorry for the trouble.
A shower will be excellent.
And while you're taking it,
I'll make a bed for you.
Okay.
You can find bath towels in the top drawer.
If you need a conditioner,
feel free to use mine!
Thank you, Midorikawa...
Have a good night.
Have a good night too.
Jin, we've not met in a while,
but your former students seem to have grown a lot.
Not to sound dismissive,
but I'm rather happy with that.
I see. So you did not see it dismissive, did you?
It's fine. There's always another way and a hand.
Dead end.
They don't know anything.
The Association does not store the addresses
of players outside of rankings.
In New York,
there are about a hundred of tennis clubs of all sizes.
But the ones fostering pros...
Let's say, maybe about twenty in total.
As long as he stays in New York,
he will certainly practice in one of them.
Provided he has not left already. If we track the clubs
he visited before, we can deduce his whereabouts.
We will rule out all of them one by one.
This will definitely bear fruit!
Right. Thank you so much...
Since yesterday you only say
"Yes" and "Thank you!"
Is that so?
It's fine.
I'm sorry...
Ah! And this one too.
Have no worries.
Although New York looks long, it is actually narrow.
Together we will get to the bottom of it.
Takayuki Todo...
Is he a Japanese?
Yeah.
We will surely find him.
Don't give up yet!
We only visited three places yet!
This club's team is formed already.
Klutz!
Wanna have lunch?
Yes.
What is Madame Butterfly up to?
Holding fast to her assets as usual?
Still without a boyfriend?
No. I'm not aware of anything of the kind.
What she lacks right now
is guts to make up her mind for something bold.
Tennis would become times easier for her then.
If not today, then tomorrow!
If not tomorrow, then the day after.
Don't lose patience, Hiromi!
I'm sorry, but I hope you don't mind
if we postpone our tennis club tour until tomorrow.
The truth is, this afternoon I have my own practice in the club.
Tomorrow I have a day off,
so we'll devote it to the search.
Okay.
Take this.
Spare key to the house.
Make yourself comfortable.
The fridge is at your disposal. Okay?
I'll be back by 5.
Okay.
See you!
I am troubling Midorikawa
at such an important moment for her.
I'm such a nuisance...
Tennis clubs... Tennis clubs.
It's here, here. Alright!
Sorry to interfere,
but are you by any chance Midorikawa?
It's you, after all.
Well, who'd ever think!
Isn't it incredible how you and Todo
are both in New York right now?
You mean you know Todo, and where he is?
This is strange. She should be at my place now.
I wonder if she went to sleep.
He said he'll depart at 3 PM.
There is still some time.
I'll go to the airport right away
and try to hold him back.
Hold on!
I am going with you.
I'm looking for a Japanese player. Named Takayuki Todo.
Yes. Takayuki Todo.
He must have come here from Japan about a month ago.
Does he have a reservation of the court at this club?
Boston, huh?
Yeah.
Obtaining a pro license is not a small deal.
LaGuardia Airport
Attention, please. All departing passengers bound for Seattle on United Airlines Flight 1,
please proceed to gate number seven.
Midorikawa!
And Mr. Sayama, but... But why?
It's been a long time, Todo.
It certainly did!
Midorikawa, it's such a surprise seeing you here!
You have also surprised us all recently, Todo-pro.
It's getting late, Oka.
Where on earth would you go out alone?
I think I should go look for her.
Sit back down, Todo,
or you will miss each other again.
That's right. Don't worry.
She has nowhere to return, but this place.
You should stay put!
No need to hurry for your tomorrow's flight to Boston now.
Yeah... And still...
I'm the one who should go out!
I will report to you by phone every hour!
If only I had stayed in my apartment
for just a day more...
On the other hand,
I made it all the way to the city where Todo is.
Although we didn't meet,
I did my best to make it happen.
I think I've done well. Up to this point.
You did a great job, Hiromi!
Well then,
Reckon it's high time I buy a ticket home.
Gotta apologize to Coach Katsura.
But firstly, to mom. I know.
I'll get her some souvenirs from Akihabara to distract her.
I'll also take time
to write a letter of gratitude to Midorikawa later.
I should get myself together.
I can only imagine
how fed up everyone is with my tantrums.
New York, I don't have any regrets!
Todo, have a dinner.
I made sandwiches.
Oka...
I think I still should go look for her.
Hit the brakes!
Stop, please! Stop!
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
I'm so happy for you, Hiromi,
you've met your adored Todo!
Also, now you are leaving for Boston together!
While Midorikawa makes her pro-debut,
isn't that fantastic?
Hiromi, you do your best too!
It's good that you're supporting Todo,
but you should also get back to Japan sooner!
Coach Katsura is waiting for you.
Alright, Hiromi?
Coming soon: "Advantage."