On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
I like you.
I like your cheerfulness, honesty and
the unyielding spirit that lets you fight the hardships.
And you. Oka, I like... you.
Episode 24
The Love Letter
that Danced Around the Court
Everyone, listen up for a moment.
Munakata, please proceed.
Listen. This morning, you are all to complete your basic and individual training programs.
After lunch, according to schedule,
we start playing practice matches.
Games are one-set matches,
quick play showdowns.
However, "practice matches" in name,
they are not intended to help you practice.
And of course, these matches
are not about winning or losing.
Instead, through analyzing them,
we'll determine round two members.
Be sure you play to the best of your abilities.
Okay!
Also, the matchups list
is posted on the billboard in the courtyard.
It's third day of the camp.
Finally, the 17 participants
start playing practice matches.
Now, let's see who I'm playing...
First Match: Nishi High's Oka Hiromi vs. Fuji Academy's Nakata Sachiko
The very first match?!
And the opponent is... Nakata. Nakata?
Nakata... I wonder what kind of person
this Nakata is...
Hey!
Todo!
What's wrong, Oka?
You look pretty tense today.
Umm, do you know anything
about Nakata of Fuji Academy?
I think she was the player who finished third
at the nationals last year.
Third... Third at the nationals?!
It's fine. You should now be of about the same level.
Besides...
Besides, I'll back you up.
Just kidding!
Umm, you're playing in the third match today, right?
I'll also come cheer for you.
Thanks. At this rate,
we should both win big today!
Now, we will begin the first match.
Nishi High's Oka Hiromi vs.
Fuji Academy's Nakata Sachiko.
One set match!
Fuji High Nakata's service! Play!
Net!
Calm down. Calm down.
She came third in the nationals?
She's a tough opponent.
But in the one set match a good beginning is crucial.
I absolutely have to take the initial one point!
0-15!
To screw up a ball that way...
I see. Nakata is getting tense as well.
All right, time to strike then!
You got it!
You're doing good, Oka! Keep it up!
0-30!
Oh gosh, Todo.
You don't have to shout it.
But I'm still happy!
Just thinking that Todo is watching me!
0-40!
Could this actually be love...
Is that what they call love?
Game! 1-0. Nishi High Oka's lead!
In one set match,
6 games like this mean victory.
I can do this! If this keeps up, I can do it.
And now for a court change.
Oka's growth is astonishing,
taking the first game off the nationals' number 3.
Could you ever see it being so one sided?
And also...
She is sparkling now.
I'm envious, Oka. This must be love.
You're in love, aren't you?
Now it's my turn to serve.
This game will be mine too!
15-0!
Just one more game to win!
I won! I have already won this match!
He really is watching me!
Todo is watching over me all this time!
Oka.
Yes?
Just one more game.
Go wrap this up, okay?
Sure!
Coach says, "Go wrap this up."
I know all that already.
I must be doing so well,
he has nothing better to say.
Number 3 at the nationals?
It had me scared at first, but now I'm over it.
What's wrong, Nakata?
Oka's vanquishing you so far!
I'm sorry. When she tricked me with that smash
in the first game, it messed up my pace completely!
Silly! She is an overblown newbie,
only accepted to the camp on someone's whim!
Get it together!
Yes. Either way, only one game is left.
Win or lose, I'll throw in everything I've got!
Service: Oka! Play!
Oh no!
0-15!
No good!
It'll be fine. I still have a huge lead.
One point is nothing.
That's it! Good job, Nakata!
Attack, attack, attack more!
Game!
No good! If she takes one game more,
she'll catch up, making it a deuce!
I can't lose it!
I cannot lose this another game!
Is that all?
She had me worried.
Her defense is still full of gaps!
All right! I'll take this game and make it a deuce!
Then turn the tables!
Safe! 15-0!
Ack! You're lucky, aren't you?!
That was close...
Out! 30-0!
40-0!
Match Point for Oka!
Nice, I did it!
I'm finally on the next match point!
Okay...
It's mine!
Game set! Game count: 6:4 for Nishi High's Oka!
Oka, this is unforgivable!
Coach!
I won! I really did it!
What do you think you did?
I refuse to acknowledge this match as won by you.
Come to the backyard court in ten minutes.
Special training!
Special training?
Was she crying just now?
Yeah.
So cruel! What was that for?
I was trying my best, but he says I didn't win?
I'm not going anywhere!
Who'd ever return to court after that?
Hey, what's the matter?
Did something happen?
No, not a thing.
Right, Goemon?
Okay, that's good to hear. Later!
By the way, take a better look
at that paper airplane later.
Airplane?
This evening... I'll be waiting for you by the lake.
T.T
This evening...
I'll be waiting for you by the lake.
T.T
That's right, I almost forgot!
Todo's match is about to start soon!
I have to go cheer for him!
Okay! I'll talk to Coach
and have him put off the training!
Of course, after all that nonsense he said,
this should be something granted!
I'll be unyielding about this!
Umm, Coach!
You're late, Oka!
That was miserable!
What are you doing? Get up at once!
I'm going!
Coach, please tell me!
Why didn't you recognize me as today's match winner?
Because you aren't the winner! Had this been an official
three set match, you'd be guaranteed to lose!
No way!
If you don't get it, I'll tell you.
Remember once more everything that happened
after you had a lead of 5 to 2.
Everything after I had a lead of 5 to 2...
That's right. From when Nakata was cornered
and tried to turn things around...
To when Nakata's repeated mistakes
brought the match to an end.
During that period,
I have not seen a single one!
You never pursued Nakata further into the corner,
or scored an ace even once!
How can I recognize that?
He's right... I was merely trying my best
to keep up with the ball.
The match outcome
was already predefined by then.
But instead of ending it with an ace yourself,
you just waited for opponent to self-destruct!
How can one ever say you won that match, Oka?!
What I'm trying to engender in you...
In other words, the essence of tennis
I am insistently trying to teach to you
consists in only aiming for the ace at all times!
That's the tennis you should play!
Everything Coach said is right!
Something was wrong with me back then!
I forgot about returning the ball, dilly-dallying instead,
getting bogged down in the opponent's pace.
What was wrong with me?
That's right, Oka.
You weren't your usual self today.
Therefore I have to return you
to your usual self now.
My usual self?
Exactly, the usual you.
The ball-chasing and constantly looking to score an ace
while playing to her limits, usual Oka Hiromi.
And to do that, I have to remove from the court
anything other than tennis, that makes your heart burn.
Even if it's something like love.
Love?
Now, take your racket
and get in position, Oka!
It's way too early for you to bring love onto the court!
Too soon. I cannot allow it!
Coach...
What... What are you saying to me?
Don't you mean...
The letter!
The letter from Todo!
Leave it, Oka!
You must let it go!
The letter!
Oka! Leave it! Oka!!
Oka, pick up your racket.
I want you to give your soul,
now burning with love, to me.
What I'm putting my life on the line for...
I want you to give your soul to tennis.
Oka.
Coach, please give me an intense training!
All right!
Do you truly understand it now, Oka?
Your feelings for Todo...
Will you let tennis to take them over, Oka?
I'm really happy, Oka. Nothing could make me happier.
I won't hold back any longer.
All the passion I've accumulated for tennis. No...
Every last ounce of this man's, of Munakata Jin's life,
every last drop of my blood...
Oka, I'll gladly shed it all to fuel your tennis!
Is that you, Oka?
Coach Munakata?
Todo, Oka isn't coming.
Just this one time,
I will have to curtail
this thing you two call love.
Todo, please understand.
Coach Munakata.
I understand. It's fine,
as long as Oka does not stop playing tennis.
Todo.
It's fine. As long as Oka
remains on the court, I can wait for her.
No matter for how long.
I'm sure, Oka would also tolerate that,
as long as I keep playing tennis. I'm sure.
At the end of the day,
I couldn't betray you, Coach.
No, rather, my tennis.
Now, I chose this path,
so I have to do my best.
This evening... I'll be waiting for you by the lake.
T.T.
That first little love
I have ever known...
It's all good. Until the day I can put these feelings
to use, I'll hold tight onto them in my heart!
That's good enough for me!
To Be Continued
Against the backdrop of a beautiful Mt. Fuji,
the joint training camp begins to heat up.
Today's first practice match
is Ryuzaki Reika vs. Midorikawa Ranko.
The second match is Oka Hiromi vs.
Kimura Toshio of the boys team.
Of all these members, who will be selected
to proceed into the second stage of the camp?
On the next episode of Aim for the Ace:
Don't Lose to Men's Tennis!
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo