I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Game! First set won by Midorikawa.
Game count: 6-2.
I'll defeat her, Jin.
Just like I already did in the first set.
At the moment, my bullet serve
is completely invincible to Oka Hiromi.
I have scored 16 consecutive service-aces.
Hiromi is still too inexperienced
to undermine my serve even once.
Watch as I earn this victory, Jin.
My bullet serve has been revived!
This heavy 180 gram ball...
I was hitting and hitting it day after day.
While sending the ball, I thought of Jin,
I heard Jin's voice!
No offense, Jin,
but my true target is not Hiromi.
It's Madame Butterfly, waiting for me
in the round two - Ryuzaki Reika.
Look, Hiromi prostrates under my serve again!
I'm sorry, Jin. Because you raised her yourself,
I know Hiromi will probably catch up with me soon.
But before that, I'm gonna have to get
just one step ahead of her.
Game: Midorikawa.
Game!
Next is Midorikawa's service-game again.
If Oka doesn't return a single one, the match is over.
If Oka doesn't break through the bullet serve now,
it would be a complete defeat.
Not decided yet.
Nothing is decided yet.
Even the very last ball
can turn the tide of match.
Oka is the kind of player
to hold such potential.
That was exactly
why Munakata noticed her and brought her up.
To the very last game...
To the very last ball...
Munakata believed in it,
we believe in it.
And because Oka herself believes so too,
it all began and came to this point.
Therefore, even if she should lose this match,
if Oka never finds a way,
she will still make sure to show everyone here,
what she's worth.
Even if for a moment,
she will show us her brilliance.
That's what I believe in.
Episode 13
I'm Sure... He's Watching.
A little more...
I need just a little more!
Eventually, I'm starting to read the course.
I'm also getting used to the speed.
What lacks is timing.
I just need to adjust to her timing!
30-0.
Out!
40-0.
Match point: Midorikawa.
How unfortunate!
Just as she finally managed to receive it!
So close...
You really deserved to score it, Hiromi.
Still... Still, Hiromi, at least with this one shot,
give her a hard time!
After all, it's match-point already.
You're this one point away from losing!
Really, why does nothing in life
ever goes the smooth way?
Chiba, I want you to archive this game for me
in its fullest.
No matter if she wins or loses,
for Oka, there will never be a second match
like this one she is playing today.
My bad.
I got a bit disheartened. Sorry.
That's right. If I don't capture it,
then who else will?
Oka's today...
As well as the rest of Oka's days...
One more ball.
Just one more ball, Jin.
Look at me!
Coach, I will send this final ball back! Certainly!
Jin!
I just need to hit one last ball!
Midorikawa...
Midorikawa!
Player Midorikawa
is unable to continue the game.
Consequently, this match's winner becomes Oka!
Whatever you make of it,
a victory is a victory.
Next is battle with Ryuzaki.
Well, about Midorikawa...
You think she'll be alright?
It appears her special training with a heavy 180 gram ball
has taken a heavy toll on Ranko's right wrist.
You shouldn't be worried.
Nothing of that is your fault.
Forget it! Instead, focus more
on your upcoming battle with Ryuzaki.
What if... What if she never manages
to recover from that condition?
What do I do? After all, Midorikawa
is experiencing the same thing as me.
Just as she finally escaped that dark tunnel...
Just as she returned to the light...
I beg your pardon.
Come inside,
I've been waiting.
If you excuse me.
Before your tomorrow's battle with Ryuzaki,
she wanted to meet you, by all means.
I've heard many talks
about how much you're worried for me.
Well... How could I not be?
After what happened to your right...
But I'm sure, soon,
it would be able to wield a racket again.
It certainly would! Wouldn't it?
The diagnosis was pretty clear.
No longer an option.
My right hand
is now completely useless for tennis.
Can't be helped. I'm reaping the consequence
of my own rash decision.
At least I know I did my utmost
to defeat you and Madame Butterfly.
I regret nothing.
Coach...
Coach Munakata...
Please save her...
You have to save Midorikawa!
It's all alright, no worries.
Have no worries just like I do!
There, see? There, there!
I still have my whole left hand on me!
It's a matter of time.
Though it can probably take a while, but I made a decision:
reborn as a southpaw, I'll give it a fresh start.
That's why, whatever is to come,
remember - I haven't given up on my tennis yet!
No way I ever give up on it.
Therefore... Therefore, just like me... No,
just like all of us, with exception to Jin,
you still have a plenty of time ahead of you!
Do your best at tomorrow's match.
On my behalf too, okay?
Hiromi, I would gladly face you
with all you've got!
I hope it won't start pouring
in the middle of a match.
Yes.
Did you have a good sleep?
I think you were still playing piano
very late into the night.
I'm sorry.
Father, I must have disturbed your sleep.
No, quite conversely.
Rather, listening to your piano
works like a sedative for me.
Inadvertently, it became a splendid lullaby for me.
Playing the piano
allows me to process many thoughts
in the meantime.
Like those of tennis
I've been playing since I was six and to this day.
Of countless matches,
numerous awards.
Time after time, without any bitter afterthoughts,
I burst into flames on the court until I burn my life out.
My opponents change,
time and place differ as well.
What remains the same is myself!
It's a fight of Ryuzaki Reika against herself.
I have always been coming here
with this conviction in mind and heart.
Yet this time it's different.
Today's match is different.
This time, I need to live up to the expectations
of many people.
The expectations of Midorikawa Ranko,
of Coach Munakata...
Finally, to Hiromi's expectations.
Up to this point, I have always felt
like there's no one else but me on the court.
For the first time, it's different.
Reika, you should think of this as a usual match,
the same as all the previous ones.
No, it's different.
I will have to disobey this one, father.
This makes me happy.
At last, I don't feel left out
completely alone on the court.
This is something I never experienced before.
To think that on the court, where only victory or defeat ever had any significance, I would feel a human warmth!
Reika...
That is why Hiromi is so amazing.
Unlike me, she has probably been experiencing that
ever since when she tried tennis for the first time.
Even though I managed it so naturally,
Munakata Jin preferred Oka Hiromi over me,
and I've finally come to understand the reason!
Reika, you...
It has been haunting me for those three years -
"Munakata Jin -
why did he prefer Hiromi over me?"
Father, I will hardly ever
say this for the second time.
So please hear me out just once.
Munakata Jin, save for my father,
has become the first ever person that I...
The first person in my whole life,
whom I held in the highest regard.
Reika!
Do your best.
Naturally, father.
I'm going there to reap my victory!
Fault!
Munakata...
The one you chose
and bet your everything on, Oka,
on this big stage of All-Japan's Open
is having a face-off with Ryuzaki Reika.
In one of your letters of praise,
you put it this way for me:
"Oka will conquer the world.
Ryuzaki Reika is but one big concrete wall
that Oka will have to break through on her way."
That said, the reality seems to be a bit different.
It's not just about Ryuzaki.
Midorikawa Ranko, too, grew frantic
about not letting your selectee Oka break through.
They are trying their utmost to pose for Oka
much thicker, much higher walls than usual.
That minuscule sapling you planted in Oka,
now grows not just in Oka.
In Ryuzaki and Midorikawa too,
it starts to take root.
No, I would go as far as saying, it has probably already sprouted in the rest of our bunch as well.
Munakata,
you've bet your everything on tennis alone,
throwing it all in.
And now, that perilous wager of yours
is finally starting to pay off soundly!
They are still hobbling in zigzags,
but move steadily towards their limitless potential!
Deuce!
We can but to watch them silently, Munakata.
Both Oka and Ryuzaki are using up
all the power in their possession.
Particularly Oka - by whichever course the ball comes,
she is trying to catch up with it.
In whichever position it reaches her,
just like you taught her to, she is trying to nail an ace.
Moreover, I'm convinced her body
remembered to do that reflexively.
You did a splendid job, Munakata.
While Oka keeps on playing matches like that,
while she puts herself out
for superb opponents like that,
Oka's potential is infinite.
She may have lost yesterday and today,
but she has all it takes to become the ultimate winner!
Munakata, it was you who chose her,
you who raised her all the way up to this point.
It starts to dribble...
Coach...
Coach Munakata...
Hiromi!
It was winter when Coach left us.
An excruciating spring followed.
And now, on this rainy court,
I'm hitting the ball again!
Completely focused, with all my might,
in this one moment of my 18-year-old life,
mindful that each one of those is not like any other,
I'm hitting a ball after a ball!
Harsh, yet kind... All the words I ever heard from you
were full of that kind of duality.
Day after day, you kept on looking at
me with those benevolent eyes.
And time after time,
this look was never like any other.
The warmth of someone very dear I've lost
is still here with me,
and with one after another ball
I'm hitting wholeheartedly,
this fire inside me is burning brighter
with ever-growing confidence.
Coach, can you hear it?
The upsetting things, the delighting things -
when I put everything in and hit the ball wholeheartedly,
"PON!" - it makes such an uplifting sound!
Game! Game count: 5-4.
Oka leads.
In the second set,
Oka may break into the lead!
She just needs to take one more game
to bring the set count to tie with 1-1!
I wish this match would last forever,
with neither of the sides losing or winning.
In this particular match, there has to be a winner,
and an only one at that.
But in the long run, it's nothing but one point
in the initial game of a lifelong match.
In two years, three years,
maybe even ten years,
the fire of their incredible rivalry, that has just started,
will still burn in a long match with everything on the line!
Ryuzaki, Oka, both players.
Please come over for a quick word.
We would have probably tolerated the rain,
but now a strong wind also picked up.
What do you say if we suspend this match
and finish it tomorrow from where we left off?
I wish to continue it now.
Ms. Oka, what about you?
I'm unanimous with Ms. Ryuzaki.
Hiromi...
Yes?
This match, I feel that he is watching it.
Certainly, from somewhere...
Yes.
He must be!
Then, let's do it, shall we?
Yes!
Because it was so unbearable,
I used to cry by the window
But now, next spring is on my doorstep
Oka, hit!
On the bare branches,
Suddenly, I notice fresh verdure
Still so weak, struggling through the wind
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
He gets to see what was going on all this time?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
I'll stay forever by your side.
So I made a promise
to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Keep looking after me
From your far away
Oka, meeting you
was the grandest blessing of my life.
AIm for the Ace! 2    End
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
We spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Thanks for tunin' in
See you in Final Stage, space cowboy
Original English script/Encoding   Johnny-englishsubs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo