On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
190!
191!
192!
193!
194!
195!
196!
197!
198!
199!
200!
This is hard... Too hard!
But... But I have to do it!
Even at the cost of everything else,
to withstand this training!
As a player who bids defiance to the world!
The world! The world!
Episode 25
Don't Lose to Men's Tennis!
- Fight!
What do you mean, Munakata?
Kimura is a man, you know!
I understand that.
That's precisely why I'm asking for this favor.
But...
Now, now, Kobayashi.
No need to get so bent out of shape.
How can I...
Munakata recognizes Kimura Toshio's ability this way,
that's why he is asking for this kind of favor.
Isn't that right, Munakata?
Naturally, I don't hold delusions
about Oka beating Kimura.
Hey. Morning, Oka.
Good morning.
This morning, Mt. Fuji is totally enchanting.
Yes, totally.
Listen to me for a minute, while you eat.
Today's practice pairs have been decided, as follows:
First match: Ryuzaki Reika vs. Midorikawa Ranko.
Madame Butterfly and Kaga's Lady Orchid?
Both are genius players.
Gotta be spectacular!
It's like a sequel to their prefecturals game.
At last, the time has come to settle it, Midorikawa.
I have been waiting for this moment,
Madame Butterfly.
Those two are so amazingly calm about this.
I wonder, when will I be able
to spout lines like that too?
Be quiet, the announcement is not yet over.
The second match: Kimura Toshio vs. Oka Hiromi.
Excuse me, but isn't Kimura Toshio a boy?
That's right. The four of you, do your best
and show us some good matches.
That is all.
Coach!
- Oka is playing against Kimura?
- What's going on here?
Hey, Kimura, say something!
It's what the coach decided.
We can do naught.
Nice to meet you, Oka.
Make it count, okay?
Sure!
Glad to meet you.
Coach!
What is it?
Please, tell me! Why did you arrange it for me
to play against Kimura, a man?
Are you revolted against playing with a man?
I didn't say I'm revolted! It's just...
It's just... what?
It's just that boys don't usually play with girls.
That's what everyone is saying.
Don't be spoiled!
I'm not spoiled!
It's just that difference in strength is too great!
Strength? No matter who your opponent is,
such a thing should never concern you.
But...
The only thing that matters
is what kind of match you show us.
What kind of match?
Ryuzaki and Midorikawa's match
is certain to teach you something important.
Madame Butterfly's and Lady Orchid's match
should teach me something?
One set match!
Ryuzaki vs. Midorikawa!
Before we begin, I should let you know,
with both participants' outstanding abilities in mind,
we will hold this match with a tie-break condition.
Tie-break! A 9-point system,
where the first to score 5 points, wins.
It means whoever is better with the high ball.
A harsh system!
Midorikawa's service! Play!
Their match will teach me something important.
That's what Coach said.
Whatever it would be,
I gotta make sure to not let it out of sight!
The prefecturals match
that I lost out of clumsiness...
To redeem for that ridiculous match,
Madame Butterfly, I'll make this a pivotal showdown!
Now, come at me
from wherever you want, Midorikawa.
I'll let everyone see, that prefecturals turnaround
wasn't a fluke even in the slightest!
I dare you to try and receive this serve of mine!
Of course, Madame Butterfly.
No less than that!
If you plan to beat me with tricks like this,
you're dead wrong!
Oh no!
0-15!
I'm put to shame
by seeing girls exhibit a match like this.
Absolutely true.
We'll be out of business at this rate.
40-All!
40-30!
Deuce!
Haughty girl! How dare you return my serve
in that easygoing manner!?
All right, not this time!
Fault!
Oh no!
Fault! Double fault!
Midorikawa's double fault?
I can't believe it!
Do you understand the reason?
It lies in Ranko relying too much on her own power.
Certainly, Ranko's serve
has a power like that of a man.
And yet...
Something even stronger than that
is the way Ryuzaki receives it.
Her forehand drive is flawless,
so she sends Ranko's serve right back to her feet.
As a result, Ranko is forced
to use a half volley whether she wants or not.
However deadly serve she has,
when facing a worthy receiver, there's little she can do.
Return the ball
steadily to opponent's feet?
That's right.
Against an opponent who relies on power,
you need a superior technique and a sharp discernment.
Without those, power will push you back.
I see...
Just one more point!
Just one more point.
Attack from wherever you want!
Impressive.
True Power Tennis of Lady Orchid.
I'll stop you!
I've won! This is the victory of Power Tennis!
Game! Ryuzaki's victory!
I see. You're allowed to hit
with any part of the racket. That means...
Your Power Tennis is incredible, Midorikawa.
Had I had that strength, I'd be unstoppable.
I was relying too much on my power.
I merely got lucky this time.
Let's both keep doing our best.
This must be that "Something"
Coach Munakata told me about.
To just play my own tennis with might and main.
Just like those two,
I should also show a great match.
Even if the opponent is man,
I should just fight with might and main!
The second match:
Kimura Toshio vs. Oka Hiromi!
Don't underestimate the opponent, even if it's a girl.
She won the Kanto tournament after all.
And besides, her Coach is none other than Munakata.
Coach.
Coach, please say something!
Oka, hurry up and get on the court.
Okay!
Coach, why did you refuse to say anything?
Oka, this match should become a discovery for you.
Moreover, you can only make this discovery by yourself.
One set match! Service: Oka!
Play!
All right, I just have to fight this
with might and main!
0-15!
He's as good as you'd expect a man to be.
There's no delay between one move and the next.
She's nothing special.
Still just a girl after all.
It's like he's not taking me seriously!
But I won't lose!
Game: Kimura!
Bring it on!
I'll be sure to receive this one!
15-0!
Astonishing serve!
I've never seen a serve like this yet!
It's heavy!
Is every man's serve so heavy?
Kimura's serve is the same as Midorikawa's serve!
I see. I should also return it to opponent's feet.
If I do that, the ball's force will be halved.
Okay! I'll do it!
Did it!
Missed! I'm nowhere near as good at it
as Madame Butterfly!
Game: Kimura!
Okay, the rest of you head back inside.
We don't want you to catch a chill.
Now that it also rains,
what are you hoping to achieve?
How can you ever understand?
How can any man ever understand?
As a man, born to be taller than women,
stronger in hands and faster in legs,
how can you ever understand?!
How can any of you ever understand how painful is the training required to make up for that handicap?
How can you understand!
Like when I had to let go
of the only support for my heart - Todo's love...
How can you ever understand these feelings!
All I have left now is Tennis!
So I cannot lose!
He's scared!
Kimura, what's wrong with you?
Opponent is a girl!
Hey, look at what happened to Kimura's face.
Unlike before he's gotten totally serious.
Understandable, isn't it, Ozaki?
Given how splendidly Oka is doing.
Her strokes only get stronger over time.
If this goes on,
she'll play on even footing with men.
She achieved this by just redirecting her passion.
How terrifying.
Somehow, in that special training,
Coach Munakata
made her use all those resources for herself,
for Oka Hiromi.
It is clear to me already,
if anyone is going to stand in my way from now on,
Oka Hiromi, only you can be that person.
It's tough!
How strong a man's ball really is?
I have to train my shoulders more!
While legs, arms and hips
are in need for a lot, lot more training!
That's right, you start to understand, Oka.
Every woman has to face worries and weaknesses,
intrinsic to her.
As well as to suffer to overcome them
in the women's way.
However, I will have to ask you
to go even further than that:
To eradicate completely your weaknesses,
intrinsic to women.
A new tennis is being born that transcends girls tennis.
That would be our own tennis, Oka!
Game set... 6-1 for Kimura.
Oka, don't think of this as a loss.
Cause I certainly don't think I've won.
Were you a man,
I'd be no doubt vanquished.
In the course of our match, eventually,
I lost sight of the fact you're a girl.
That was the only way to reach out for victory.
"How things would have gone, were you a man" -
the very thought gives me shivers.
I lost, Coach.
I'm sorry I couldn't live up to your expectations.
Oka, the tennis we're aiming for
is Power Tennis. Strength-based tennis.
However, there would always be someone
physically stronger.
I wanted to see how you would perform against
a male player hopelessly outmatching you in power.
But in the end, I lost.
No, you did well.
You may have lost, but you showed the potential
to eventually be able to win.
Besides, power is not just the raw strength.
I saw it myself. During that fight, your determination became a huge power, giving chills to Kimura.
Coach...
Just a little more to go.
Keep up the hard work, Oka.
Okay!
To Be Continued
The second stage members selection meeting begins.
Those who remain on the members list will be able to fly forth into the world.
However, Hiromi's name was not on the members list.
Therefore, Hiromi was given just one single chance.
She would have to win a match against Madame Butterfly.
Hiromi and Madame B's
incredibly fierce showdown begins!
On the next episode of Aim for the Ace:
Hiromi vs. Madame B! The Final Showdown
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Encoding   Moozzi2
TLC/QC   Perevodildo