I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Midorikawa?
I don't remember telling anyone.
You don't need to. My dad is a chairman.
Player's reports to Association are no mystery to me.
All by yourself, you're taking on the Australian circuit.
It's so much like you.
For how many days will you be away?
Two months.
That long?
All the way until All-Japan's Open in June.
This blank period of recovering
has taken a heavy toll.
I felt it during the match with you.
Therefore, even if it's a bit of a shock therapy,
I believe, it will make the best special practice for me.
I guess...
Maybe I should go too.
A joint trip?
Our next meeting
will only take place on All-Japan's Open.
Take care, will you.
You as well, Madame Butterfly.
Thank you.
Really, I'm glad you came here.
All things considered, I owe it to you
that I keep on fighting to this day.
Just be reasonable, okay?
After all, I know what a hell-bent you can be.
Much more so than me.
You can only imagine your life through tennis, making it your Sisyphean labor to retain the top spot by all means.
Madame Butterfly,
Your unfathomable solitude
must go far beyond my boldest fancies.
Episode 11
The Night Before the Showdown
68...
69...
70...
71...
72...
73...
I heard, last afternoon,
Midorikawa departed from Narita airport.
Central University Main Campus
But what a daredevil she really is.
Challenging Australian circuit must be a big deal.
Midorikawa sure is amazing.
All by herself...
Hiromi, you shouldn't be so impressed
with her ventures.
You'll soon become an entry
for the magnificent All-Japan's Open yourself!
However you look at it,
you two are rivals!
See? Thanks to you,
I have been remonstrated already!
Well, guess I'll have to swallow it.
Very early in the morning - roadwork,
afternoon in the tennis club - special training.
Your youth sure is an austere one.
I wouldn't really say so.
No way! You say something like that
without batting an eyelid!
Matriculation pushed you a great deal
towards adulthood!
Maki, if you're not having it, I will .
Hold it a bit there! You're a college student girl,
outblooming even flowers!
You can't have udon
followed by curry rice for tiffin!
My stomach is particularly unquenchable these days.
I feel like I can gobble a horse!
Jeez. Instead of pheromones,
you ooze hunger.
You haven't changed a bit
since Nishi High after all!
Is this seat free?
Yes, yes! It's free!
Please go ahead!
Much obliged.
No, it's no problem at all!
Hiromi! Wait for me, Hiromi!
No way! I can't miss my bus ride!
But what about our plans?
We settled on the afternoon movie!
I'll have to pass on the romance.
Gotta practice.
Zarn, why would you promise to come then?
Hiromi, this fellow just asked me out!
Date! Date!
I'll tell you the details later!
You have my word! Later!
At least Maki is having a full-blooded youth.
Switch your mindset to intelligent play.
Okay.
By altering back with forth, left with right, slow with quick
and high with low, make her lose composure.
Whatever you do,
aim to disrupt Oka's pace.
On top of that, use a dynamic Power Tennis.
With your perseverance, power and endurance,
play as though you want to knock Oka down.
Understood. No holding back.
I'll give her a run for her money.
Hey! There they are!
Mr. Katsura, we're from Toto Sports.
Can we have your brief comment
on All-Japan's Open?
This won't take long.
All right.
You'll have to excuse me and go ahead.
Okay.
Fight!
Like that, like that!
So? Does it bode well for Oka?
Just take a look yourself.
Yes, looks good.
Her movements are charged with speed now.
No, not this way.
The side worth witnessing here is Todo's one.
Todo's?
Can't even tell which one
is undergoing a special training.
Seeing Todo break a sweat during the practice
is extraordinary.
Besides, that earnest approach
isn't customary for him.
He rarely, if ever, puts on that attitude,
playing against me.
In breach of male solidarity!
Quit saying nonsense!
Still, that's so Oka-ish. After such a long blank period,
she regains her knack before you can say Jack Robinson.
I wonder if that's what they call a natural genius.
Oka.
Let's take a little break.
Okay.
Oka!
Chiba, Ozaki!
You both are doing great.
Here, Todo. For you too.
Thank you.
I got the whole thing on video.
If you want, I can lend it for a detailed home study.
I'd be much obliged.
What's more to it,
you seem to be on your peak.
Not really. After all, I haven't nailed a single ace
against Todo yet.
I'm sorry! That sounded awfully arrogant... I just...
Well... I didn't mean to say
you're butterfingers! It's just...
What was it you meant to say then, Oka?
Well...
Relax, relax! If you don't fight till your last breath,
it ain't no special training at all!
That's right.
Everything is the way Ozaki puts it, Oka.
With your mind clean of thoughts, just come at me
with all you've got. That's the part and parcel.
I too, will, put my every effort into receiving it,
as long as I still have any power left.
Thank you for all your trouble.
Just be careful not to smack Todo's self-confidence
too hard into the ground.
Right, Ozaki?
Quite so!
Under a tough appearance,
this fella hides a naive and sensitive nature.
Keep your fantasies to yourself!
If you're thirsty, I have more, Oka!
You have a spare supply of anything!
Just wondering -
why won't you ever offer supplements to me?
You're gonna have to earn your treat yourself!
Go!
Court #10
(Special indoors court)
Go!
Fast!
Stop!
Go!
What's the matter, Oka?
Pull yourself together!
You should, by now,
be following his ball with ease!
Roger!
Oka!
Don't get distracted, Todo!
That's the point,
I told him so too.
"Are you kidding me?
That's the most natural way of things!" - like that.
"But I see nothing rude here.
I'm only supposed to pony up in the beginning."
So on the second date - coffee shop, cinema, restaurant -
we split the bill everywhere!
Can you believe that?
On a date, the boy provides everything.
That's how it works!
Hiromi? You listening? Hiromi!
Lisennin...
"Before I could notice,
two weeks have passed already since my arrival.
Even to this day, the competence
of Australian athletes never ceases to amaze me.
Still, to begin rotating in the local circuit,
I keep kicking throughout the country, four days a week.
"I'm on a winning streak,
no one is match for me" -
not something I would claim yet,
but I manage it somehow in half the cases.
Feels quaint to say so myself, but I feel that my bullet serve
is getting more and more honed with each one.
I can't wait to play with you and Oka again.
I miss the thrill of fighting with all my might.
Consider that my cherished wish.
PS: for the moment, considering how you tend to get
more than anyone intense and unsparing to self,
while practicing all the harder without a word of complaint,
your body is my prime source of anxiety.
Take care, see you later.
— Passing through Sydney, Ranko."
Yes, looking good, Oka!
Keep that spirit up!
You're trying pretty hard, aren't you?
You enjoy playing tennis?
Yes!
Will you follow my lead then?
Yes! Wherever you want me to.
Alright.
Come!
Okay.
Coach...
Oka...
Coach! Coach Munakata...
Alright!
Another day of earnest hard work for me!
We should stay fresh, Goemon!
Spoiled child.
Today, Oka seems to be in much greater shape.
This way she may actually score today.
Almost!
So close!
Out, huh?
Alright! The timing was not half-bad right now.
Do it once again!
Okay!
Ready!
Shower Room
She weightened her racket!
Also, all those bruises on her body...
Just what kind of training
is Madame Butterfly having?
You look pretty committed to the practice.
Yes, I try my best to keep up with it.
We're just a month away from All-Japan's.
Midorikawa is also
pushing herself to the limit in Australia.
What's the matter?
No, nothing...
These bruises are my tribute to you
and to Midorikawa, going through such trying times.
Ryuzaki
Only having done everything that can be done,
I come out to the court.
Regardless of winning or losing,
you should never fall into self-indulgence.
My biggest fear
is becoming spoiled enough for self-indulgence.
I'm waiting until you put your everything into one ball
and hit it towards my side of the court.
My everything?
Yes. Everything you have.
Coach!
Coach Katsura!
What's the matter, Oka?
You aren't heading home yet?
Coach, I need your help!
Please teach me to receive that serve of yours!
That serve no one but Coach Munakata could receive.
I want to receive it by any means!
By what means, exactly?
By any means!
That's not an answer.
You refuse? I don't deserve it?
I never said anything of the kind.
Are you ready, Oka?
Yes!
Grip tightly and engage your whole body!
Okay!
I can curb it!
I want to receive it!
To harness it!
Oka, glue your hand to the racket!
Muster your whole body and your soul reserves,
then use them to hit it back!
Right, put in everything I have...
Do everything that can be done!
For Madame Butterfly,
for Midorikawa,
and for every opponent
that I'm bound to face on this court!
And finally...
Finally...
Finally, over anything else,
I do it for Coach Munakata!
Todo?
Oka?
Good morning there.
I see. So you picked this course as well, Oka?
I myself only switched to this course
three days ago.
I'm thinking of extending it a bit.
So that's how you'd end up here?
Oka, watch out for that shoelace.
Uhm, Todo?
What it is?
For the moment,
I can only truly live for tennis.
I can't properly recall the moment it started,
but as for now, I devote myself to tennis entirely.
I have probably caused a caboodle of nuisance
to people around me, like a spoiled child.
I think I was insufferable, even.
But somehow, I'm sure,
I have turned to better now.
I just want you to know - I'm truly and forever indebted
for having you watch over me all this time.
For a long time, should a chance present itself, I wanted
to express my heartfelt gratitude.
Thank you ever so much.
Oka,
I really...
I come to realizing it more with each time -
I love you!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   Johnny-englishsubs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
Aikawa Maki here.
Our Hiromi must be
one particularly unfortunate fellow!
Her All-Japan's Open opponent for first round
is none other than Midorikawa!
She wasted no time in Australian wilderness.
Instead, her special training was
utilizing a ball three times heavier than usual!
What will you do, Hiromi?
Our Kaga's Lady Orchid seems full of confidence.
Now, Hiromi, you can take on
the bullet serve, can't you?
Next time:
Bullet Serve: Revival!