On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Coach!
Oka, how many days did you slack off?
How many days of training missed?
Four days!
All right, start making up for it from tomorrow on.
Okay!
Hello? Yes, that's me.
I understand. Good night.
Oka Hiromi decided to defy me.
The Fearsome Spin Drive!
Episode 11
Hey, keep pulling!
I'm winding it!
Okay!
It's all crooked!
I can play! I can play tennis again from today on!
Hiromi!
Maki!
Hi-ro-mi!
It all turned up just like I said.
There's no way that you can quit tennis!
Now, welcome back!
Back to your court of so many memories!
Don't do that, Maki,
if you pull so hard, it hurts!
Yes, yes. First thing,
just sit down and set your mind on the work.
Slow it down a bit, Maki.
And everyone… Everyone… Everyone is…
My, what a surprise. The rumor of you
turning in a resignation letter was a hoax?
Well... I'm terribly sorry,
I took four days off unnecessarily.
Let's work together from now on.
My! What is wrong with her?
Hiromi, don't mind the others, all right?
Hey! What are you grouping up there for?
Quit dawdling and line up!
Okay!
Now, Hiromi, it's time to assemble!
The prefecture final round is only three days from now.
Our opponent is highly skilled and reputable
Nansei High School, got it?
- Yes!
Nansei High?
That's the way. If we're laid back,
there is a chance Nishi High loses.
Everyone, especially those five in the varsity,
in these next three days you practice
as if it were a real match.
All right, start!
Okay!
All right, I have to try hard for my first comeback!
Captain!
Excuse me, can you be my stroke practice partner?
Sure, but only after I finish with Madame Butterfly.
I'm sorry, I wasn't being considerate.
I shouldn't have done that,
I got myself further into trouble.
I'm s-sorry, Madame Butterfly.
Wait, Ryuzaki!
Hey, Captain!
Yes?
Change with Oka.
It's starting again.
Coach's obsession.
That's right, every time that girl appears.
It annoys me!
Captain, I want you to swap.
Okay, I understand.
Oka, it will be your turn now.
Get on the court.
What's wrong?
Come here!
Okay.
If you excuse me.
Go ahead.
She's looking at me with her sharp eyes, but... But,
compared to the pain of four days without tennis,
I will fain endure this kind of pain!
You came back after all, Oka.
So, are you happy, Todo?
Don't be silly! What are you saying?
But the girl who loves tennis
has returned to the court.
Oka, this is just the beginning.
Tennis is something that brings on the real hardship
only when you start to love it.
Oka's service is first. Begin!
Okay!
She hit a spinning one!
What's wrong?
Has she torn a hole in the new racket already?
I'm sorry. Can you serve again?
With pleasure.
A spin ball is no excuse!
I was able to receive those before!
What's wrong with me?
It's as if my senses have gone all wrong.
I'm surprised, Madame Butterfly is serious.
That's her special spin drive.
There is no way
that Oka in her current state returns that.
Here it comes, are you ready?
Yes!
All right, that's enough, stop there.
Oka, you have to withstand this pain.
If you are willing to return to the court,
this kind of pain will only continue.
Hiromi!
You're bleeding!
Leave her!
Those are not even scratches.
And what were those serves?
It's like you're still retired!
Listen Oka, after tennis practice is done,
you must stay behind and practice your serve.
From today on for three days,
serve 1 000 balls before you go home.
A thousand...
Until the net or something else breaks,
keep on hitting!
Got it?
Excuse me, Coach!
Which kind of serve should I hit?
Your own serve that fits you the best.
You'll show me results in the coming tournament.
But...
That's cruel.
I don't know what to do by myself.
Without a good serve, I should hit a 1 000…
Hit a 1 000 serves!
Darn it! Like I would cry.
A journey begins with a single step.
1 000 balls or 10 000 balls, I'll do it!
Why, you!
Tomorrow is the final tournament.
Todo!
So, how was it?
You hit some nine-hundred balls?
Not yet, I still have 300 left.
300, huh? Just a bit more effort!
Even with a bit more effort, it's the same.
No matter what I do,
I can't find that one ball I'm satisfied with.
I must be so terribly full of weak points.
What are you talking about?
The more weak points you have,
the more room there is for growth.
Those who are perfect have no room to improve.
Having weak points means you are clearly capable
of finding the new techniques.
Am I wrong?
Capable of finding new techniques? Me?
Yeah, so don't worry.
At this rate, even if you go against Nansei High's
Hyuga, you'll have nothing to fear.
My opponent? Hyuga?
What? Wait, Coach didn't tell you anything?
Yes, not at all.
I see. I may have screwed his design.
Has the formation already been decided?
Yes, just today.
What kind of person is Hyuga?
Well, she's Nansei High's captain.
Captain?
Her spin drives are top notch,
but if it's you, you will be fine.
Do your best!
Top notch spin drives?
I would lose. That's right.
That's why Coach didn't tell me anything.
He gave up on me!
No! I don't want to lose!
Aim for the Ace!
Oh, the prefecture's women's final event.
Emerging victorious every year,
our Tennis Kingdom of Nishi High
makes me feel proud when this time comes.
Yo, Chiba kid!
You must be pleased to be here to check things out.
Yes, when it comes to tournaments,
I unsheathe my finest writing.
Also, Nishi High's 900th article,
has to be flawless.
Now, move aside,
I have to interview the female players.
Prefectural Womens Tournament
Hey, I'll wait for you in the stands!
Okay!
Prefectural Womens Tournament
Madame Butterfly, how are you?
Just one line about the upcoming match, please.
I'll fight as I normally would.
Entrance
Captain Hoshino, what do you make of finals?
I'm planning to win so we can join
the inter-high competition.
Wakatsuki and Miyako?
Win for sure!
No doubt about it.
As expected of the Nishi High tennis players.
Oh, that's right, there's one more.
Hey, Oka! Oka!
Yes?
Please, tell us how a rookie first-year
feels about this competition.
What's wrong?
Coach thinks I don't stand a chance,
but I don't want to lose!
I'm sorry!
"I don't want to lose" and "I'm sorry"?
Well, she has the spirit!
I started to like tennis. And because I like it,
I cannot lose my first individual match!
Game set. Set count: 2-0
for Nishi High's Ryuzaki.
Here are the two players for the next match.
Nishi High's Oka Hiromi versus
Nansei High, Hyuga Aya.
She must be the one
with the special spin drive, Hyuga.
Oka! Why do you shillyshally here?
Get to the court!
Just as I thought,
Coach won't tell me anything.
He must be thinking that I'm going to lose.
Oka!
Let me tell you one thing.
Opponent's techniques are several time better.
But you still must prevail!
Let me see the results of your training.
That's absurd!
Nishi High's Oka! Oka!
Yes!
Please hurry to the court.
Okay!
Hiromi, do your best!
Oka, who chose tennis over me,
will see it for herself.
She will learn that one cannot
just love tennis and call it a day.
You're quite serious, Madame Butterfly.
Is that girl bothering you?
No, not at all.
Really?
Because she does bother me.
Coach Munakata treasures her after all.
Everyone… Everyone is looking at me!
Best of three set match.
Nishi High Oka's service!
Asking me to win against all odds is absurd. And still...
I had to return, because tennis is too unforgettable,
so I cannot lose either!
All right, whether it's a spin or a drive,
or whatever, bring it on!
It was the truth! An amazing spin!
Crap! It's inbound!
0-15.
Oh no, I kept thinking about how to return
the spin ball, but I never considered my next move.
I see. I should have a plan of what happens
after I receive the ball.
I won't fall for that again!
All right! Now it's my turn!
15-All!
She did it! Hiromi scored an ace!
Oh, this is already a good match!
Yeah, that's right!
That girl plays pretty well!
Yeah.
I did it, I broke her spin ball!
At this rate, there's nothing to fear,
all I need to do is run when I expect a spin ball!
If I run, that ball won't work.
She's laughing!
I see. She must be trying to hide her dilemma.
All right, I'll attack her now!
Attack! Attack!
Deuce!
Just one more point and I'll win this first set!
Game count: 7-5. First set for Oka.
She did it! Hiromi won the first set!
Good job, Oka!
That's right! At this rate,
you'll win the second set too!
I understand now.
So the rumor that Oka Hiromi is a princess was true.
Hey, Chiba, slow down...
No worries,
this won't be in the article.
For the moment,
I just wanna know if I can join your club.
Oka Hiromi Fan Club, that is.
Coach, I won the first set!
I broke the spin drive technique!
Don't talk smart yet.
The first set ended mere seconds ago.
Oka, the real battle only begins here.
Start of the second set.
Service: Nansei High's Hyuga!
Hurry up and go.
You'll get a penalty.
I understand. I'll win the next set too.
What was that, you awful coach…
If I continue like the first set, I won't lose.
Looks like it's over.
From this set on, it will be mine.
She's laughing again,
even though I won the first set!
A spin serve?
Darn it! My legs, my legs are already worn out!
Your legs are already exhausted from the first set.
30-0!
Oh no, this set is with a hitch!
Oka used all of her stamina in the span of one set.
Even if you take one set,
you need two sets to win.
This is the true danger of the spin ball.
She definitely played right into the opponent's plan!
Game count: 6-1 for Nansei High's Hyuga.
Hiromi...
Please understand, Oka.
You cannot just love it.
Wait a moment.
Is it so painful to watch, you're going back early?
Think whatever you like.
You're trying to act nice.
But it's not the case.
Who do you think Oka Hiromi has?
Listen, she has Munakata Jin behind her.
Coach, I can't go on.
My body won't move anymore!
So, you understand the terror of the spin ball now?
Yes, but I want to win!
I don't want to lose to it, Coach!
I'll teach you the method on how to win.
In order to win against the spin ball,
you have to use legs and be persistent.
You probably got this yourself by now.
Yes. But, those legs are already…
Not yet! Those legs of yours can still move!
Listen, you did 1 000 serves
for three days in a row, right?
Yes.
What did you do when it was time for the last one?
It was tough, but I hit it.
After all, I already made 999 shots by then.
Stand up then!
Stand up and keep running!
Right now, you've made 999 shots.
Just one more and it will be 1 000.
If it's you, you can do it!
Coach.
999!
That's it, Hiromi! That's it!
The 999th shot!
Where is this girl finding that stamina?
Just one more point.
One more point and I'll win!
Here it comes!
Ah, my eyes…
I can't see!
Hiromi doesn't want to lose!
Oka!
Hiromi!
Game set!
Set count, 2-1. Nishi High's Oka!
You won! You won, Hiromi!
To Be Continued
Hiromi's achievements become the school's top article.
While Hiromi is overjoyed with her win,
Madame's attitude toward her is about to become cold.
And finally, the individual competition,
Madame is to fight for her title of Queen,
she can't afford to lose.
While the fiery Lady Orchid showing tenacity as well.
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"Showdown! Butterfly vs. Orchid"
Staring at Madame and Lady Orchid makes Hiromi's mind sway violently.
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo