I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Alright, Oka!
That's enough for today!
Okay!
All-Japan Open's matchups are announced.
The opponent you are to face
in the initial round is Midorikawa Ranko.
Moreover, whoever wins
your clash with Midorikawa,
Midorikawa Ranko
Oka Hiromi
Ryuzaki Reika
is to bump immediately into the third seed,
Ryuzaki, in round two.
This draw is carved in stone now.
Originating from chaos,
those matchups turned out quite ironic.
True struggle only begins now.
Though there was no avoiding
facing them sooner or later anyhow.
Episode 12
Bullet Serve: Revival!
Midorikawa!
Just when did you return?
Last night. I thought to give you a call,
but figured it was too late already.
Let's continue inside.
I was just about to have a tea.
It's fine here.
I only stopped by for a moment,
to give you this little thing.
Souvenir for you!
What?
Meet the ball I was using during practices in Australia.
If you don't mind,
it would be nice to show this ball to Hiromi too.
There's no fun in her bumping into me
unaware of my new tricks.
Okay, I got you.
Now then, see you in round two.
I'll be looking forward to it. Truly.
We only have three days left.
Catching a cold in such a rain
would be a very stupid move now.
You're exempted from practice today.
Return home and make sure to rest well.
Okay.
Oh, before I forgot.
Ryuzaki suggested you could use this.
That is the ball Midorikawa used for trainings
during her trip to Australia.
Try to take it with hand, Oka.
Okay.
Is this...
It weighs six ounces. A special purpose ball,
thrice as heavy as your usual ball.
Ranko's bullet serve is even more formidable now,
having used this ball for practice.
If she managed to grow accustomed to hitting this ball,
her serve has received a truly horrifying power-up.
'Tis me - Ranko.
Jin...
No hard feelings, but I'm going to defeat Oka.
I'm confident I will.
And then, after that, Madame Butterfly.
That said, an intention is still just an intention.
I explored a new place by myself,
did what I have never done, then returned.
Thank you, Jin.
Tennis can be a truly wonderful thing.
Hiromi, I hope you're in high spirits,
because I brought along some shortcakes!
You don't like it?
It's from Roland in front of station you know!
No, it's delicious.
You don't say!
Why won't you show some more relish then?
Relish-relish!
Maybe it's the start of rainy season already?
If it goes on pouring like that,
you imagine they'll postpone the tournament?
I should go there after all. If I hit it
against the wall in the park, I can practice by myself.
You should stop after all!
Haven't you had plenty of practice up to this point?
Even this brute Coach Katsura
ordered you to get well-rested today!
I may have had enough,
yet some did twice...
They did three or even four times
more than what I did.
Moreover... Moreover, there might as well be someone
who did even more than that!
Say, Midorikawa.
As well as Madame Butterfly.
Hiromi!
Are you alright, Hiromi?
What happened?
Intact. It's nothing.
Are you sure?
More importantly - isn't she astonishing?
Having practiced with a ball like that.
Absolutely fantastic.
What a fantastic person Midorikawa is!
Maki, hold it for me!
It's one of those nights, Munakata,
when I can drink sake happily.
What am I so happy about?
Well, why shouldn't I be happy?
Let me think.
Well, for instance, about those matchups.
The very first match is Oka vs. Midorikawa,
then the last man standing fights Ryuzaki.
Those matchups cut straight to the chase,
just like you used to.
No use denying - it must have been you
who arranged the whole thing from your next life!
I knew it the moment
those matchups were posted.
After all, I'd do the same myself.
I guess, we still have you.
That Munakata Jin guy,
still looking closely after each one of us.
It's no good,
I may have overdrunk a bit.
January 15th
Departure for US
Oka, aim for the ace!!
Colosseum "Shonan"
All-Japan's Open Tennis Tournament
Thanks.
Jin, light more sparklers!
More fireworks!
It was the last one, Ranko.
No, I want more!
Then, tomorrow, I'll buy a whole lot more.
No-no-no!
Now or never!
Jin, how lovely!
Right? Lovely, isn't it?
Yeah, charming...
It must have been you who summoned them here!
All of them, for me!
Ranko, I'm not some kind of magician.
Jin can do something like that.
Jin can do anything!
Did you have a good sleep?
I remember distinctly
one dream that I saw at dawn.
I've been seeing this dream for some time now.
What kind of dream?
It's a secret.
Coach!
You've finally been discharged from hospital?
When you're having such an important match,
I can't afford getting hospitalized!
Meeting you
was the grandest blessing of my life.
This train...
Where is it heading to?
Know knows...
But... But we'll be together on it, right?
Together with Coach, always...
Naturally.
You aren't going somewhere else now, are you?
Just where do you imagine I can go now?
Perfect! That's perfect!
Maki, you heard it?
Distinctly.
I think Coach gave you an irrevocable promise.
He won't ever again go somewhere else!
Perfect! Just perfect!
Oka, let's go. It's time!
Okay!
All-Japan's Open Tennis Tournament
The best of three set match.
Midorikawa vs. Oka.
Midorikawa's service. Play!
15-0.
30-0.
I'm confident I'll win, Jin. Certainly.
A thousand daily.
This red ball, even though it weighs 180 gram,
I kept hitting it.
All alone, in Australian wilderness.
When no one was there,
"Keep it up. Keep it all up!" -
I could hear you cheering for me, Jin.
Except for your voice,
there was nothing else in that wasteland.
I will defeat Oka Hiromi.
I will defeat Madame Butterfly.
And thus,
my own, brand new tennis will be born
from the ruins.
I want people to say,
"That's what you'd expect from Munakata Jin's sister!"
And I will make them say so, Jin!
40-0.
Just as expected. Australia gave her a first-class power-up
for her bullet serve.
How does it look on Oka's side?
In order.
It feels like she's just getting started.
She has a leeway.
That said, she is actually starting to sweat.
But it's hot today after all.
Game!
Game count: 1-0, Midorikawa.
A love-game...
Oka never managed to return that serve even once.
Court change.
Astonishing.
I'm actually stupefied.
Wish I could ever hit a serve like that too.
Coach,
Accept my thanks.
Had Coach not been there
to teach me all those things about tennis,
playing on this court today,
against an amazing player such as Midorikawa...
I wouldn't have ever experienced all of this!
For the moment, though still shivering a bit,
I flare up with every ball!
15-0.
All right...
15-All.
Whatever I do,
I can't enforce my own service game over her.
But even if Midorikawa aces every single ball
in her own service-game,
I will still be able
to make it to a tie-break somehow.
If I manage that, sooner or later, who knows,
maybe I'll find a way to undermine the bullet serve.
And even if I never find a way,
I would at least be contented with losing in a close match!
30-15.
The men's first round that only starts tomorrow
is completely overshadowed already
by this women's match alone.
Yes! 40-15!
Game: Oka.
Game count: 1-All.
Dad, mom... Well, if you want some, here.
They exchange hits pretty evenly.
No, rather, if we talk speed, Oka has the upper hand.
Therefore, the only obstacle
is Midorikawa's serve.
For Oka, in order to win this match,
it is imperative
to eventually find a way
to undermine that knockout serve.
My wrist warmed up properly.
I'm ready to receive in whatever direction you hit it!
15-0.
Midorikawa is amazing! If you include previous games,
it's her fifth consecutive service-ace!
While Oka couldn't handle a single receive yet.
This is the first time I see a girl
wielding such a mighty serve.
Bullet serve of Kaga's Lady Orchid.
Haven't you heard?
She was renowned since her days as a junior.
Why do I have a feeling
it's due to my stepping-in timings being a bit tardy?
One...
Two...
Three!
No use... Whatever I do,
I can't undermine that serve.
It's turning ugly.
Oka dropped a game of her own serving.
Nailed it again!
Midorikawa just scored her 16th service ace in a row!
Dead end!
I can't win it. This one match...
If you excuse me...
Well...
Hiromi's gonna lose?
Gonna lose?
I'm sorry.
I thought there might be something I could do.
Well, the opponent is Midorikawa,
so whoever wins is still a part of our family anyhow.
But I'm sitting right next to Hiromi's parents,
whom I brought along.
Who is she, Jin?
Hey, tell me, who is she?
Who is this Oka Hiromi girl?
Jin, what is this girl to you?!
Just as I thought you're finally back to the tennis world, day in and day out, it's just Oka, Oka, nothing but Oka!
Like she is some sweetheart of yours!
Maybe she is my sweetheart.
How do you know?
Having one always on your mind,
wanting them to tell you everything about themselves...
Accepting in entirety
both everything good and bad about them...
Being forgiving. But above all, making every effort
to share the same path that lies ahead of them -
if that translates to holding her as my sweetheart,
then it's quite possible.
Come over, Ranko.
The nightscape is beautiful.
I refuse...
I refuse.
I refuse! Refuse!
Is she really that important to you?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
Madame Butterfly is still watching.
And perhaps, Jin does too.
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
We spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   Johnny-englishsubs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
Aikawa Maki here.
It's here at last!
The grand showdown with Madame Butterfly.
But I'm happy with any outcome.
After all, with all the different things that happened since,
we have Hiromi standing on the court once again!
That's enough to dispel all my worries!
Behind her back, Hiromi has Todo and friends,
and Coach Katsura,
as well as Coach Munakata,
always by her side!
Next time: I'm Sure... He's Watching.