I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Munakata Family Hereditary Tomb
Dear Munakata Jin.
Dear Jin Munakata,
I wonder how many more I will bring here.
I never pasted a stamp,
nor put one into the post box.
Yet I kept writing and hoarding
my letters to you this way.
I have been yearning for you
ever since I was a child.
And so, whenever I wander through my many memories,
you end up appearing before me, in one form or another.
When I entered middle school,
I was disquieted by being much taller than everyone,
so much, I barely ever showed outside.
You were the person who coerced me to show up
on the tennis court for the first time.
Since then, I was obsessed with this - writing love letters
one after another, without ever handing them to anyone.
After all, you were also the one
who brought me two raison d'être in one go -
tennis
and my first love.
By that time, I have only been told
you are a son of dad's ancient friend.
And then I learned the truth
as soon as I entered high school.
Though we had different mothers,
you turned out to be my blood-related brother!
However, my feelings were already
past the point of no return.
Hey, Jin, did you ever tumble to my feelings?
Cos I truly... Truly...
Loved you.
Read them all, my love letters.
Now I can finally confer them to you.
As for now, Dear Munakata Jin,
I can no longer receive a ball from you,
therefore...
My tennis is no more as well.
Episode 7
Into Sorrow
Sunrise is magnificent here.
I wonder if she managed to get some sleep.
No, she stayed up all night long.
Without ever touching the futon, she sat by the window,
looking at the sea, though she couldn't see any.
"What are you looking at?"
When I asked her so,
what do you think was this child's answer?
"The sound of the surf. Time after time,
it's always different.
It never produces the same sound twice.
Something that passed
can never return again."
I was completely at a loss
as for what I should tell her.
As parents, we can do naught
but wait and look.
After all, it's the first time for her.
However, what we're seeing is perhaps a beginning
of Hiromi's existence as an independent individual.
Don't worry. It's for the times like that,
that we brought Hiromi up this way.
She won't cave in. Not Hiromi.
- Fight.
- Fight!
What's the matter? You alright?
Yes.
It hurts!
You alright?
It hurts so much you can't get up?
Let me see.
Why, you didn't even break or twist anything!
Please put me down!
I'm alright, Coach! Coach...
Coach, I'm alright!
Good. Be careful next time.
Okay.
So, shall we carry on?
Yes!
- Fight!
Coach, this morning I called the hotel
where Hiromi is staying.
Then her mother picked up.
Hiromi barely touches the food,
doing nothing but staring at the sea.
What an idiot Hiromi really is!
If she doesn't eat,
it's all over for her, Coach!
Really, she's an idiot!
She gives me nothing but worries!
After this, I'm going after Hiromi too.
Coach, I beseech you.
- Give me some strength...
- Aikawa?
This racket... Who left it here?
This?
It was Midorikawa.
By discarding tennis,
you can't drive away the sorrow!
But as long as you keep playing tennis,
as long as you keep hitting that yellow ball, Coach lives on!
Both in our hearts
and in our tennis alike!
Discarding tennis like that
means discarding Coach as well!
You have to overcome it. Hiromi too, and Midorikawa too.
As well as the rest of us!
Only by overcoming this grief,
you can then rise back to your feet!
It looked as though Madame Butterfly
is talking to herself back then.
And I think she is right.
Isn't she, Hiromi?
Hiromi, are you listening?
I want to die.
I would rather die!
Hiromi?
Hiromi!
I would rather die, Coach!
Hiromi! Hiromi...
Coach! Coach!
Coach!!
- Idiot, idiot, idiot!
- I would rather die!
Hiromi...
Thank you for answering my call.
My name is Daigo Katsura.
It's nothing, we are grateful to you likewise
for coming all the way here to help our dear daughter.
If you excuse me,
I'll get straight to the point.
Would you entrust young lady
into my custody in the temple for some time?
Buddhist temple?
What do you hope to achieve?
I hope to relieve the young lady.
I'm sorry for detouring into my own story...
When Munakata Jin
received a first blow from his disease,
we were in the middle of a practice match
for that year's All-Japan Championship.
This is mine!
Like hell!
The exact diagnosis was not yet apparent.
So we only let the barebones
of "seizures of unknown origin" to leak out.
But his actual diagnosis was
marrow leukemia.
He had a lethal disease
with no chance for remission.
When he first learned about it after the hospitalization,
with an eerie glow in his eyes, he told me this:
Daigo, I got three more years to live.
I was utterly shocked.
When such fate hit my one and only best friend,
obvious emotions like grief or bitterness
were just the tip of the iceberg for me.
He'll die in three years.
Somehow, it felt like a death sentence in just three days
would have been more bearable.
But now, for the next three years,
he'll be constantly hearing the breath of death.
Second after second, day after day...
Just a thought of Munakata's next three years
was agonizing to my very existence.
I began drinking heavily,
cursing myself for leading a carefree life.
World lost its color completely.
I learned the hard way that anyone is powerless
when facing a fate of death like that of Munakata.
I wandered.
Aimlessly.
Until one day, with nothing left to lose,
the flow brought me to Eihei Temple.
It was as though my soul is screaming.
And aside from that,
I had no other way forward.
That was exactly my season of wailing.
Till then, I didn't have a slightest idea
what this life is actually all about.
But with this experience,
the understanding shook me to the bone.
In that wailing I found
a piece of mind and the pith of life!
The young lady's bereavement
is just entering her wailing season now.
By trying to run away from sorrow and anguish,
she dooms herself to spending this way the rest of her life.
If she doesn't confront this wailing head-on right away,
she'll never be able to move on to a new life!
It must really be so. Running away is as good
as losing yourself. I don't want such to happen to Hiromi.
While this man Katsura Daigo
may actually be the straw for Hiromi to clutch at.
I understand.
We trust you to take care of her.
How come I suddenly have to go to the temple?
You need this to break free from the anguish.
Mr. Katsura has been the most earnest
about relieving your soul...
He will never become what Coach was to me!
Hiromi...
I only have one Coach - Coach Munakata!
Hiromi? Your friends are here to pick you up.
Hiromi...
Won't you come out
to meet Maki, Ryuzaki and Todo?
Hiromi...
You came through all the trouble
of coming to pick her up...
You don't have to apologize.
Really, if only there was anything I could do.
Uhm, Mrs. Oka...
Do you mind if I have
a little talk with Ms. Oka?
Oka, Todo here.
If you don't feel like it,
you don't have to answer.
But please let me tell you just a few words.
Both me and Ozaki, as well as Chiba
have always been looking closely after you.
That is why, whatever calamity you're going through,
whatever anguish, everyone else is going through it as well.
One way or another, today we're leaving at that.
But please don't forget -
everyone is waiting for you.
Trying to figure if there's anything else we can do for you,
everyone is waiting.
Well, so long.
Did Hiromi answer anything?
No.
She has been like this all along
since we're back from the sea.
Anyhow, I'll come again tomorrow.
If not tomorrow, then the day after.
Hiromi!
Hiromi...
I'll come to the temple.
I can go wherever,
won't change a thing.
Thank you again for waiting.
Hiromi's belongings.
Give my warmest gratitude to Katsura.
Okay.
Hiromi?
Ma'am, we're off.
I want you two to escort Hiromi to this temple.
Bring Oka?
Her parents are at risk of caving in to the pressure.
If Oka bristles against coming here,
what do you sanction us to do?
If need be, bring her by the scruff.
Let's go.
This way, Hiromi.
I take her in my custody now.
The rest of you go home.
Okay.
Hiromi!
Hiromi...
Stop this at once!
What's gotten into you?
Out of the way!
Hiromi can die!
Her body is tempered by training!
It can withstand much more than this!
Out of the way!
Ryuzaki, Aikawa,
we decided to entrust her to Katsura.
Cold...
Alright, bit by bit,
you're regaining your humanity.
Now...
Get up.
It's not time to sleep.
Yes.
Oka.
I believe, nothing is unbearable in this life.
Not even things like sorrow or anguish.
Let's eat.
Why won't you start dinner?
And you?
I don't want to eat.
Then neither do I.
Mulish and dogged. Also selfish.
She inherited your every downside, Munakata!
It's here.
I wonder where can she be now.
Maki, I'd prefer to return
without meeting Hiromi.
Just knowing where she is would be enough.
Besides, such was Mr. Katsura's request.
Give me a moment then!
Right now, she is Zen meditating in that building.
You sure you want to come home
after just that?
Yes. We have already entrusted
Hiromi to Mr. Katsura.
Hiromi, don't give up, okay?
I'll come visit you again.
Can I ask just one thing?
Just what am I supposed to do now?
It doesn't seem like I can die.
But at the same time,
I can't go on living like this either.
Did you come here
hoping to find an answer to that?
I didn't think of that.
Five years ago, while Jin was still alive, I first experienced the sorrow of parting. The anguish, the heartbreak.
From 16 till 22, we fought in a pair, or chased the same yellow ball, with net squeezed somewhere in between.
And envisioned us spending the next 5 years
the exact same way.
First death, then hope.
I'm talking about you, Oka!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
Aikawa Maki here.
It seems Mr. Katsura
decided it's for the next step.
He wants Hiromi to inherit Coach Munakata's racket.
He's very insistent about her taking it!
But can't you see?
Hiromi is still nowhere near sorting her feelings out!
It's too brutal, Mr. Katsura!
She is not yet ready to accept it!
In the meantime,
Midorikawa gets into a terrible accident!
Next episode: Munakata Jin's Racket