I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
A journey?
After this,
I'm hitting the road
to see Jin's favourite Sea of Japan.
I see.
I am now free.
Once I finally let go of racket,
I found freedom in these hands!
This leaves me with plenty of time
I can spend thinking of Jin.
I see.
See you.
Midorikawa!
Don't quit playing.
I wish to see you one day
hitting that cannon serve again.
You sure is one of the kind.
But unlike you,
I cannot live off tennis only.
Sorry. Jin bequeathed his sardonic tone to me.
Jin, the way you saw it, the way you felt it,
I want to feel it too!
That sea is among the few things
that grant me momentarily tranquility.
The lives of people from bygone ages
are sealed in it.
At a moment's notice,
it can drag you all the way to the seabed.
Jin...
Episode 8
Munakata Jin's Racket
Munakata Jin
Munakata!
Marrow leukemia.
At such a late development stage, it's but a miracle
he was able to lead a physically active life up until now.
Three more years.
Even the cutting-edge medical advancements
cannot grant him more than that.
It pains me to inform you.
University Hospital
Patient: Munakata Jin
Shit!
I'm becoming a coach.
I can no longer be playing myself
with this good-for-nothing body.
Instead, I'll seek a player
worth putting my everything into.
Somewhere...
Somewhere, there has to be one!
Daigo, when the time comes, can I expect you
to take over that player from where I leave off?
Only by years of tempering,
you can bring up a good player.
Two or three years is nowhere near enough.
That's why I ask you to lend me some of your time.
When the time comes for me
to bid farewell to this earth,
I'd prefer to fuse into a guiding light,
than to get lost in the darkness of times.
Munakata!
It's time to pass it over to Oka.
I ask you to lend me some strength, Munakata!
Oka.
Take this.
Munakata Jin
Coach?
Coach Munakata's racket!
You will turn up on the court once again,
holding this racket, Oka.
It's so cruel!
Don't you have a heart!?
I'm still trying to figure what to do next!
Death is not an option for me,
yet I can't go on living like this as well!
And then...
Then you tell me to pick up the racket again?!
Moreover, you want me
to rob Coach Munakata off his racket?!
It was my 14th spring.
I just enrolled in Nishi High.
That was when I saw a butterfly
fluttering about in the sakura petals.
Gorgeous, elegant, and beautiful.
That was Madame Butterfly.
I even joined the tennis club
just to play tennis alongside her every day.
No, to just stand on the same court
would have been enough!
So that... That was my initial motive
for joining the tennis club.
But then, Coach Munakata's path crossed mine.
I was selected against all odds,
so Coach had to be especially demanding.
I considered quitting tennis countless times!
But on each such occasion,
the look in Coach Munakata's eyes was telling me:
"Oka, keep following me.
Trust me to show you the way to brilliance!"
That's how... That's how I managed
to keep going with tennis for so long.
It was through tennis
that I got to know so many great people!
Madame Butterfly, Midorikawa,
Todo, Ozaki and Chiba.
I met everyone
thanks to Coach Munakata introducing me!
The only way I could make it this far
is thanks to Coach!
But Coach is no more!
So my tennis is no more as well!
You are waiting for me
to yell, "Stop, don't do it."
However, deciding whether to die or to live
is a matter of one's personal volition.
Ain't no one is in position
to meddle with this decision.
Oka, it's training time,
let's go running.
Eyes open, Oka!
You were brought up by Munakata himself!
There's no way you give up so soon!
Coach Munakata is no more.
Please refrain from mentioning Coach.
It's the sea, Jin!
Nishi Medical University Hospital
Operation underway
How did it go?
You informed Midorikawa's parents?
Yes, I contacted the place
they're visiting next.
But even if they burn the rubber,
they'll only return by tomorrow morning.
I see.
Hiromi?
Hiromi? Hiromi!
Midorikawa's...
How is Midorikawa's condition?
Have you even seen yourself!?
What in the world has happened? How did it come to this?
Don't wibble-wobble!
You look too macabre to shake me off!
You ain't no the usual Hiromi!
You're so weird!
So macabre! Macabre...
Oka...
Operation underway
Here, Hiromi.
Thanks.
Hiromi!
For all's sake, what the hell happened to Oka?
She looks so emaciated and worn out.
Just what is Katsura trying to do to Oka?
Ozaki, we entrusted Oka wholly to Katsura's custody.
We can no longer have a say in her recovery process.
Still...
What else... What else you think is there
we can do for her now?
Todo...
Operation underway
Finished!
Hiromi.
We made every effort.
Yet we barely managed to put her leg back together
and the head hit the asphalt pretty hard.
Tonight will be a crucial point.
At any rate, we're rushing her
to intensive care unit for now.
Hurry.
- Be careful!
- I'll get the elevator.
Midorikawa!
Stay strong!
Hiromi?
No way! This can't be!
You cannot die!
Never!
Racket...
What was it?
What was it?!
Racket...
My racket...
Let's return, Oka.
We overstayed our welcome here.
Be not intimidated, Oka.
You cannot alter the life's ways, neither the death's ones.
When facing a fate of death,
anyone is powerless.
Much like one is powerless to attach any significance to the trifling process of hitting the tennis ball.
Yet this very trifling tennis may too reciprocate by
somehow doing you a service when survival is questioned.
My...
racket...
What kind of service?
Probably, insignificant as well.
In the great variety of major indicators
that can tell you for certain you're still alive,
it'll serve you no more
but one miniscule oblique cue.
But to one, even this minuscule oblique cue
can be a motive driving his hand forward.
This is Todo.
Good morning.
She stabilized. The worst is already over.
Her attending physician said so.
I see. Thank you.
Just a minute please.
One more thing...
Well... I guess there's nothing I can do on my side?
What do you mean?
Oka... To help Oka,
if there's anything I can do...
...not. Not a thing.
My bad. If you excuse me.
However, to dispel your worries,
you're free to come see her, whenever.
Just keep in mind that you will thus trade anxiety
for an unmitigated torment.
Stop running away, Oka!
It may be tormenting.
It may be heartbreaking.
But you shouldn't be running away!
Confront it head on, as someone
who Munakata would choose against all odds!
Five years ago, the same way you do now, I was myself
succumbing to unbearable pressure of Munakata's death.
Shit!
That was the first time
I got to see Munakata in that light.
Even for a tough nut like Munakata,
death turned out to be too irresistible and immense a force.
Remember, Oka.
For you will only hear it once.
The comprehension of Munakata's death
sent me straight to hell.
I agonized, I lurked in the shadows,
for the last 5 years.
Yet my season of wailing lasts to this day.
No, I don't believe it will ever expire.
And so, even now, the deep cut that Munakata's death
left in my chest still pains me,
as the blood of remorse keeps flowing.
Look! Even now, like many years ago,
I can't help bursting into tears, thinking of Munakata.
Oka, don't try to forget it!
Keep it as a proof.
Keep it constantly within sight
as a reminder that you cannot revert Munakata's death!
Then move on!
Get up and start walking.
As long as you are supplied with more courage,
more chest-sundering sorrow than anyone else,
you must yourself choose living this way!
Hit it, Oka. Direct all your thoughts
towards this yellow ball, then smash it!
Hit it.
Smash it hard, Oka!
I'm going in, Coach.
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
A message from Aikawa Maki!
Thank God,
Hiromi regained her tennis again, at last!
But who'd guess,
Katsura went all-in on her at once!
It's a super-hard trial!
While her body is still not quite in shape.
He's making me so extra worried with that!
Hold on, Hiromi!
Especially after Katsura puts up
a knowingly lost practice match for you.
He wants you to play a boy from Nishi High!
Next time: Battle-Scarred Court