I throw open the door to my heart
Kokoro no tobira wo omoikkiri akete starting
Because we're starting
Have been hobbling in zigzags
Ziguzagu shinagara dakedo aruki hajimetai
But it's about time
I start walking steadily!
You discover yourself anew,
Seishun wa itsumo jibun wo mitsukeru shizun
Youth is always an eventful season!
Aim for the Ace!
You know what to do - don't stop, young heart!
Dakara don't stop, young heart
But your answer
Aa kotae wa
Your answer
Has passed me by
sugi yuku
Passed me by
Wind is carrying it away!
kaze no naka
It's my endless dreaming
Still fresh in my memory
Oboetate no
It's like stepping on a marsh
Suteppu mitai ni nando mo tashikamenagara
countless times to find a solid path
It's my endless dreaming
So I keep on walking
Aruite yuku
Towards the blessed season
Watashitachi no kisetsu
Of me and you
Jin...
Nishi Medical University Hospital
Jin!
Munakata is asleep on drugs now.
It's all right, the sharp pain
seems to have been soothed already.
My, isn't it Ranko! What a long time it's been.
No less than 5 years.
Mr. Katsura?
The one who paired up with Jin in the middle school?
That Mr. Katsura Daigo?
I couldn't recognize you at all.
With that head...
Yeah...
For various reasons, I entered monkhood.
Why?
Like I said, various reasons...
It's nothing, compared to what Munakata
endured in those 5 years.
After all, in this 5 years span, even while facing
the despair of death, he never took a single step back.
He made it all the way to this point.
To this point, he never gave up.
Goodbye, Munakata.
Wait.
Please wait.
Won't you stay by Jin's side until the end?
You are, in fact, Jin's one and only best friend.
Stay by his side, I'm begging you.
Wherever I go, the pain of parting with Munakata
remains unabated.
Those 5 years I spent in ascetic practices,
seeking for strength to endure this pain.
Ranko, in my and Munakata's mind, our parting
already happened long ago.
What a stupid joke it must be!
Hospitalized? No way!
Coach...
How could he get hospitalized,
if he was so full of energy just yesterday!
Hiromi, where are you going?
Hospital! To the hospital!
Flowers... Right, I must buy some flowers before going!
Episode 2
Oka, aim for the ace!
Hiromi, here, here!
Hurry up, Maki!
Wasn't it you who asked me to wait?
What am I doing!
I forgot to buy flowers.
You owe me a treat for this.
I covered Hiromi's part too.
Mom, what is wrong?
Why are you crying?
Hey, mom, I have a favor,
please don't cry like that.
I'm sorry, Jin. I'm sorry.
What are you doing here?
What became of training schedule?
At 10 you're supposed to be on the court
to have a 3-set match with Madame B!
Who was it that promised me to win at least once
before leaving for America?
Dry your tears,
Oka!
Tears have no meaning! Begone!
Begone from my sight!
Coach! Coach on the hospital bed... This is the first time
I'm seeing something so unimaginable...
I'm sorry.
I mean... Coach hospitalized, what a nonsense!
Midorikawa, sorry to bother.
Here, flowers.
Maki, let's return.
And... If you excuse me.
Jin, I'll call her back.
Forget it.
Forgot something, Oka?
Well... Can you tell me your prognosis?
Nothing to worry.
Diagnosis is a trifling overwork.
Is that true?
Truest ever. In preparation for the trip to America,
they imposed a hospitalization upon me as a precaution.
I'll be discharged in a week.
Really?
Have I ever lied to you before?
No.
Come in.
If you excuse us.
- Excuse us.
Oy, what's this all about?
Are you trying to sabotage everyone's practice
when we're so close to going to US?
Oka!
Yes?
Go ahead and return to the court.
Start warming up!
Okay!
Oka sure wasn't the only one caught off-guard
with Coach's hospitalization.
Glad it turned out well, nothing serious.
I hope so. Because actually,
I tried to meet the doctor attending to him.
And then what happened is, upon conducting
a thorough examination, he just got fixated on that.
What are you trying to say?
I don't know.
I don't understand this case at all!
Then, Jin, I'll come again
first thing tomorrow morning.
Don't forget, the call. Can you do it for me?
I got you.
I'm sorry, but tonight Jin
wants you to come by any means.
Yes, all alone.
Come in!
Get closer, I got something for your ears only.
My diagnosis is marrow leukemia.
It began five years ago,
with no hope for remission.
At that time, I was only given 3 years to live.
This body managed to hold on for 5 years instead.
But it's finally caving in.
If it somehow manages to withstand it once more,
I may be able to go to America with you.
All the way until now, by clinging one by one
to every hope like that, I kept buying some more time.
But frankly speaking, it's clear to me -
the time has come. You understand?
Coach...
Don't spill a word about it to anyone.
Not just as a fellow player,
but also as her man, take care of her.
Perhaps, the person bound to become the closest to her
from now on, Todo,
is none other than you.
Coach, Oka is your...
I don't think this 27 years long life of mine
is in any way inferior to that of 80 years.
Just three years...
Does he really have to pass away already?
Just some 3 years after he appeared in our lives!
Us - we can probably handle it.
Me, Ozaki and Madame Butterfly -
we were all introduced to tennis long before meeting you.
But... But what will become of her, Coach?
She discovered tennis through you.
Learned to trust through you.
And perhaps, even love was revealed to her this way...
What would become of Oka if she's left alone?
It's ruthless, Coach!
Ruthless...
Katsura Daigo, perhaps,
this is the final letter I will ever write you.
The final favor I will ask from you.
My mother was a weak woman.
When she found out her beloved man
was making love to other woman,
she stepped aside voluntarily,
in favor of that woman.
However, mother never managed
to overcome the grief of that parting.
She cried. She cried. She kept crying because she forgot
any other way to pass time than crying.
And this way, eventually,
mom left me alone in this world.
That's the kind of woman she was.
Kind, affectionate...
But thus also weak.
Daigo, parting is a ruthless affair.
Because the kinder one's heart is,
the more kindness she needs.
As well as affection, the more affectionate she is.
But that also means she is more frail.
That is why, Daigo, when the bitter parting arrives,
I trust you to look after Oka.
After all, Oka has, among her amazing qualities,
this faculty for being boundlessly affectionate and kind.
Just like my mom did.
Ryuzaki
My friends, thank you all for coming here.
In preparation to your departure that is just a week away,
there is something I deem necessary for all of you to know.
To be precise, it is a story about our great predecessors,
so strong for their time, it's hard to believe even now.
In May 1916, on his first tour to US,
Kumagai Kazuya trounced Pan-American #1 Johnson.
He then achieved an impressive 5th place
in Pan-American rankings.
Then, in June 1920,
with Chieftain, at that time nicknamed The Tennis Giant,
Shimizu Zenzo put up an unexpectedly close match.
Then finally, what sparked a commotion over Japan
in the world, was the emergence of Sato Jiro.
Year is 1932. In Wimbledon,
he trounced last year's champion American Wadd,
advancing to the semi-finals.
Next year as well,
he defeated Britain's number 1 Perry,
giving rise to a world sensation.
From his 3rd position in rankings,
he gleamed at the world with magnificence.
Japan at that time
was spurred by achievements of those men.
One after another,
new tennis talents began emerging.
The tendency persisted up to this day.
Presently, there is no doubt that Japan's position
in the world's top-class echelon is unwavering.
However, the Japanese tennis world
had to face 3 major tragedies following that success.
The first tragedy being Sato Jiro's suicide
by throwing himself overboard in Straits of Malacca.
The reason remains a mystery to this day.
Despite his incredible genius,
he remained a sensitive fellow,
so it's said that the burden turned out too heavy
when the entire country put its expectations on him.
Then comes the second tragedy.
World War 2.
A young promising players is consequently a good soldier.
We suffered many devastating blows because of that.
What about the third tragedy?
Well, this one took place 5 years ago.
It's a relatively recent one.
Everyone present should either be acquainted
or even related with the victim.
After all, this tragedy affected our main young hope
of post-war days, 2 promising players.
Munakata Jin and Katsura Daigo
were struck by it.
Munakata and Katsura Daigo were both big game players,
so similar that there was no way to determine the best one.
Both played on par with westerners,
aspiring for the power tennis.
And both put it strikingly into practice.
Japanese tennis has once again appointed those two
as the golden pair in the vanguard.
Then unleashed them on the world.
It was this very moment,
when the incident struck.
The two were practicing like devils
for that year's All-Japan championship.
In high school and college,
they attended the same tennis club.
Those two were always together.
Each one knew the other's strengths and weaknesses.
On top of that, they trained each other,
growing only stronger.
They could play in full auto mode,
making perfect rivals while being best friends.
This one's mine!
Like hell!
Munakata!
Struck by sudden spasms and fever of unidentified origin,
Munakata was hospitalized.
Later that same day,
he announced his retirement.
Moreover, just a day after, Katsura Daigo also abruptly
cut ties and disappeared, remaining missing even now.
It was safe to assume he had retired as well.
Spasms and fever of unidentified origin...
What do you mean by that?
Literally that - the cause was never identified.
But...
Retirement notice
was the manifestation of Munakata's iron will.
We could do naught but submit to his will
that we held in high regards.
By collapsing on the court like that again,
he would have tarnished the pride of a player,
which he'd never forgive himself for.
But why did Mr. Katsura too...
The retirement of best friend
was perhaps too much a shock.
After all, we can but to speculate about it.
However, whatever tragedies may come at us,
they won't ever make us give up tennis!
And so, even Munakata
soon rose again as a famous coach!
This way contributing to nurturing
the young new talents!
We cannot live in captivity
of those 10 or 20 last years!
Because we already had a long history
before those events!
And in the course of that history,
we were, decisively, not the underdogs!
Therefore, colleagues,
go to the US with your head held high!
As proud descendants of the strong!
Just one week left.
Why then, Coach, they won't discharge you
from the hospital even now?
Nishi Medical University Hospital
Closed until tomorrow
Do you need something?
A visit...
That won't be possible.
Visits time is until 7.
But... There's...
Not possible.
At night, it may be a nuisance for other patients.
It opens at 7:30 in the morning.
Come back tomorrow, please.
I need to see you now...
What's the matter, Oka?
You lied! You said they'll discharge you in one week.
This one week has passed long ago!
So that's the case, Oka?
I guess I lied to you for the first time, didn't I?
That was mean of me.
Can you forgive me for that, Oka?
Can you forgive me?
You erred...
Demon Coach erred for the first time!
I see. Is this the first time
you see me making an error?
Yes, the very first time!
Then, I'll confess one more mistake while we're at it.
Actually, we won't be able to go to America together.
Detailed checkup will take just a bit more time.
How much?
Perhaps, I will depart 4 or 5 days later than you.
Once it's over, I will follow you immediately.
I forgive you.
Because you confessed it yourself, I trust you.
I trust you, Coach!
More than anything else...
Or anyone else, I trust you, Coach!
I'll be waiting!
I'll be waiting, Coach!
- Nail clippers.
- OK!
- Cards.
- Prepared.
- Books to read before going to sleep.
- Checked.
Isn't this a bit of an overkill?
It takes too much space!
- High socks, 1 pair.
- Next!
Oolong tea bags.
Did I really memo'd that?
- Long coat.
- Getting it now.
Yacht parka.
Gotta look for it!
Slim - 1 pair, corduroy - 2 pairs
black and white - 1 pair of each.
Not even started yet!
What now? You expect to be in time
for tomorrow's departure that way?
Isn't that why I called you for help?
You're always like that!
What a nice weather it is!
The sea is sparkling!
Jin, you shouldn't do that!
Wandering around while you're a patient.
What are you yourself doing here?
Already done preparing for tomorrow?
Well, I postponed it.
I have to tend to you until you're better.
Don't be selfish!
You're letting down many people.
I cannot go.
I'm not leaving without Jin.
You can't leave, can you, Jin?
Therefore I'm staying as well.
Hey, Jin, can I already
start calling you brother in public?
Though I understand you'll hardly ever forgive my dad
for betraying your mother.
Even if we had different mothers,
you're the only person I can call a sister.
Like this, Jin?
Here they are.
Yes, come in!
Coach, here. It's from all of us.
Thank you.
Coach, we'll go there one step ahead of you.
But we still expect you
to join us as soon as you can.
And you as well, Midorikawa.
OK!
The main objective of this tour
is to introduce you to the power tennis of the world.
Regardless of victory,
try to scout strong points of many opponents.
And of course, pay attention
to your own weak points.
Okay!
Alright, then go!
Ranko, the blinds...
Got it.
Stay strong, Hiromi.
Sure, mom.
Alright! Then, in lieu of Hiromi,
I'll be visiting Coach every day!
Count on you, Maki.
Have no worries!
Well, either way, I think, in the course of next week,
I'll set out to follow you too.
Just don't forget your camera.
You bet!
We're off.
We're off!
Don't forget the souvenirs!
I won't!
January 15
Going to US
Should be onboard the plane by now.
Ranko...
Yes?
Could you change the water in the vase?
All right.
Jin!
Brother...
Oka, aim for the ace!
Oka...
Oka? What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
He was 27 years old...
He was only 27 years old!
Saka no tochuu de hitori furi muku
While climbing up the hill, one turns around and looks
Even though there was not a soul in sight
Dare mo inai no ni
Hidamari no naka nayami mo shirazu
In the sunny spot, blissfully oblivious of worries
So we spent days when you were still alive
Ikiteita ano hi
Hey, why is it only when one loses something,
Nee hito wa itsumo nani ka nakushita toki ni
Ari no mama no jibun ni kidzuku no
He gets to perceive what was actually going on?
Hey, I wonder if you can hear me
even while you're not here anymore?
Nee ima wa inai anata kikoeru kashira
So I made a promise to carry on living my own way,
therefore you must also, even if for an eternity,
Watashi rashiku ikite yuku to yakusoku suru kara anata wa itsumade mo
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Tooku kara
From your far away
Miteite ne
Keep looking after me
Original English script/Encoding   JohnnyEnglish-subs
TLC/QC   Perevodildo
I'm Aikawa Maki.
They went to New York for overseas tour!
Clueless Hiromi is greeted by a completely new coach!
And a worldwide famous coach at that.
But Hiromi still believes
Coach Munakata is joining them any day.
Poor Hiromi...
Coach, why did you have to pass away?
Hiromi is still waiting for you!
Next episode:
Overseas tour without Coach