Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
7 to 5, 2 to 6, 0 to 6. 2 sets to 1.
Match won by Sekiguchi!
You can still participate in the second round.
In 6 days you will be admitted to a repechage match.
Episode 5
There's no turning back now
Father...
You are afraid not a single worthy fight will take place?
Makes sense.
After a wrist injury, Midorikawa left for an unknown location.
Oka was destroyed in the first round by an outsider.
The sacred rivalry between you two seems to be fading.
However, Hiromi still has the repechage match.
If you say so...
She will definitely surmount it once again.
Hiromi always does.
Hiromi, a phone call for you! It's Maki!
Hello, hello, Hiromi?
Hey, hey, you're free the night after tomorrow?
Let's go out together.
Watch the fireworks?
Right! There will be a plaza on the third pier.
It's certain to have a splendid view!
The real summer is already over.
Let's bring it to a conclusion with a lively party. Party!
We need to cheer you up,
cooping up in a room is no good for it!
I'll think about it.
What's the matter with you!?
Hey Oka! What's with that attitude of yours?
To the baseline at once!
You are on a court.
What else are you thinking about?
Those who don't want to work should go the hell home!
Todo, I knew it all along.
Todo, you've lost your match.
Standing all alone on a rainy court,
shedding big bitter tears.
You're far away...
Where are you now, Todo?
I can't do a single thing for you now.
It's so frustrating.
If only I could see your smile in front of me again,
hear your voice again...
My soul would be by such a great extent relieved.
Presently, I lose track easily
of wherever I'm going and whatever I'm doing.
Today, Coach Katsura scolded me especially hard.
He sent me home. But where is the place I can call home?
I don't have a place such as home.
I want to see you... I want to see you.
I want to see you!
While exhorting me with every his word,
Todo was shipwrecked himself.
While I'm still so useless to him.
Japanese Tourist Agency
Tours in the USA
Todo, I want to...
Sorry!
Did you wait?
You bet, I was here for like 15 minutes!
Let's quickly get some cotton candy!
So, feeling better now?
More or less.
Something just went wrong in that last match, right?
Make sure to definitely win in the repechage match, Hiromi!
Hiromi, is your cotton candy unflavored?
Maki...
I think...
I made up my mind, Maki.
What was it? I didn't hear a thing!
I made up...
My mind! I'm going to America!
Hiromi...
I'm going to New York.
I'm going to see Todo!
So that's what you have decided...
Sorry.
Didn't see that coming.
You are such a fool.
Sorry...
I can't stand you, Hiromi.
What? Refusing the repechage match?
Yes. Please suspend my practices for some time as well.
Why?
Oka, I understand your humiliation
after losing in the first round.
But do you hope to wash the shame away this way?
Wash away your bond with Ochou?
I don't want to. But nothing else is helping.
I can't concentrate at all!
No matter how hard I try to...
What is the reason? The reason!?
Answer me then. Which thing do you consider
the most precious in your life?
Answer me, Oka!
It's tennis. Ever since I was 16,
I decided to make it the meaning of my life.
Not when I was 11 nor 18.
However, the time came now
for me to be completely confused.
In such moments,
do you wonder what Munakata would have said?
Luckily for you I'm not Munakata!
For that very reason,
I won't waste my time on someone who is not devoted!
You need a passport now, right?
Going to America is not such a big deal today.
Well, gotta pick a plane first.
International Travel Agency
If they offer you different cost options,
just pick the cheapest one safely.
After all, it's the money issue
that is most worrisome for me.
ATM
Cash withdrawal
Payment details of the ¥61,000 bill
Even though it's minimal fare,
will it be enough for 3 nights?
Maki...
We always help each other when in trouble, right?
That's the kind of occasion
I worked part-time for.
But you'll be broke then...
Stop saying such nonsense!
You really need to get there, don't you? To New York?
But...
Oh, well! I'll have to go with you then!
Is that what you want?
Don't hesitate!
Maki, thank you.
Really, thank you so much.
Sure you are steady in your feet?
You will have to face serious matters soon! Cheer up!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
By the way, Ms. Ryuzaki called you by phone.
Madame Butterfly?
Sorry for calling you out at such an hour.
No... Nevermind.
Can you tell me a thing about Oka?
I know nothing at all!
Not a single thing, I swear!
Ms. Aikawa, please bear in mind
I've been constantly looking at Oka ever since Nishi High.
Both like her mentor and like her rival.
But most of all - like a friend.
Right...
I've heard it from my father.
Oka relinquished her right for a repechage.
How come Oka gave up on that match?
Please, Ms. Aikawa. What made her step back?
Be so kind to let me know it too.
I know... nothing.
So it's about Todo after all?
Don't you mean...
Hiromi...
Now is the time of paramount importance.
Both for you and Todo.
Hiromi, this is the thing I dreaded the most.
As a player, I wanted you to avoid this path more than anything.
The path you started treading on!
Hiromi...
Hiromi!
Madame Butterfly!
That's a rare sight.
Going for a recreation?
At this time, it's common to see you on a special court of Park Hill.
Turns out you're a human as well?
No, I'm just meeting someone. Oka that is.
That is Oka?
Say, would you mind if I come along?
Be my guest.
Such matters are not to be discussed by phone. Excuse me.
No...
I've heard it from Ms. Aikawa. Everything.
Hey, one coffee. "America."
Your flight departures at 6 PM tomorrow?
Yes.
You relinquished the repechage match. Gave up a chance.
After making it this far, you should not just turn away.
It's no use...
Hiromi, I beg you!
You can't do that!
It's just no use for me.
Hey, are you alright? Feeling dizzy?
I'm fine. Excuse me...
Be careful next time.
Oka...
Does Coach Katsura know?
About your New York trip and everything.
No. I have not told him anything.
Well, I wonder if learning the truth
will make him rather sad or happy.
It's probably better if you make him know yourself.
For everyone of us, treasuring just a single person
would never do good.
Okay...
I'm a little jealous...
If I were you, I'd be relentlessly tentative,
changing my mind back and forth.
I will always be happy to see you back.
On the court.
I'm sorry, Hiromi.
I didn't say a word to Madame Butterfly.
Forget it.
Well then, if your tomorrow's plane is at 6 PM,
should I come to see you off around 3?
No need. I want to go on my own.
Tomorrow, I think I'd better go there alone.
You think so, huh?
Not a big deal, huh.
New York, here I come!
Promise me then
to come back with a shining smile.
Sure!
When your family noticed, what did you say?
You certainly didn't tell the whole truth, did you?
My parents would have gotten ireful,
demanding to follow me along.
You can say you went on a trip with me,
to the Kamikochi Park.
I already said it would be Karuizawa. Play along.
Hiromi, can I come in?
Mom...
Here, this is a clarificant.
A treatment for distention.
Don't drink raw water, okay?
When moving to a new place,
you need to get used to the water.
Okay.
Don't sleep exposed to a draught.
And get along with Maki, will you?
Yes.
Mom!
Well, I...
Thank you for the medicine.
Well then...
Oka! Get in. I'll give you a ride.
Chiba...
Come on.
I'll get you to the airport.
But... Excuse me...
Hiromi, have you already left?
I guess you are already gone after all...
Oh, my!
Maki!
Mother... Aryagh!
I mean... It's you, mother!
Aren't you in Karuizawa with Hiromi?
Well, I'll leave you here.
Thank you.
I have always been eager to behold you play.
And I truly hope to behold it afterwards too.
See you.
Yes, flight 118.
A dream... This is all like a one big dream I'm having.
I may have let down some people,
but this is just a dream, isn't it?
I want to see you...
Todo, I so much want to see you before I wake up!
Flight to New York, departing at 18:00,
is now ready to accept its passengers.
The seventh gate is waiting for you.
I'm listening.
I'm sorry.
What for?
I just...
Where are you?
Forgive me, Coach Katsura...
Tell me where you are now! Oka!
I'm sorry, Coach...
Where are you!?
At Narita Airport.
I'm sorry.
Do you have enough cash?
Do you have enough cash
to settle in New York without having to sleep on the streets?
Yes!
If so, make the best of this trip.
YOU BIG DUMMY!!
New York you say?
So that's how it is...
Her sudden departure looked strange all along.
I'm sorry, Father, Mother, I betrayed your trust.
Oka is... No, your daughter is
not a simple-minded lady at all.
And Todo as well
is not a simple-minded young man at all.
There's no turning back now.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
Hiromi has finally arrived in New York.
But apparently, Todo left his apartment.
Hiromi is so unlucky...
However, a lucky encounter follows.
She suddenly runs into Midorikawa Ranko.
Now everything is fine, Hiromi!
You're with Midorikawa now,
so you two will definitely find Todo!
Coming soon:
"New York, the city where Todo is."