Video by Pachinko      Subs by Perevodildo
Aim for the ace!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Coach.
Your participation in Tokyo Cup in two weeks is confirmed.
Just what you need to get in shape for the autumn season.
We only have two weeks
so get used to the intense schedule starting tomorrow.
Was everything alright in the temple?
Which means Todo too...
I dismissed him from the temple so he could prepare.
He will enter America's circuit at 3000th position.
Todo's departure date has finally been fixed...
Well, it's the day after tomorrow.
So I thought we could arrange
some modest kind of seeing-off party.
Yes. Oka told me she approves it.
Right. Yes. Right. Got it.
Indeed, Todo chose an outstanding path.
Becoming a pro means suffering
huge travel, living, and entry fee expenses.
One finds a reliable sponsor first
to cover most of those expenses for him.
However, all the major sponsors were rejected by him.
As a winner of Japan's Open,
with a recommendation from our Tennis Association,
he could get into many American tournaments
without having to qualify.
But he never asked for a recommendation.
He is trying to start his journey from a true Zero.
Why do you think he does that, Reika?
Like a lunatic monk,
he pushes himself to the limit.
Why in the world is he so obsessed
with alienating his country?
Perhaps, somebody convinced him once
to follow his own way with a wholehearted dedication.
What? Who?
Episode 3
Oka! Hiromi!
Ms. Ryuzaki!
This way.
Okay.
We need to get to the top floor.
Summer is almost over.
Yes...
I wonder if Todo will be home by winter.
Our obnoxious friend is leaving Japan all alone.
It's not like going abroad is something special these days.
But for now we better get used
to no longer seeing each other daily.
Therefore, tonight, we send Todo off appropriately.
Quietly and collectedly.
So to make sure you fare well, I want to say:
neither the one sent off, nor those who send him off will have any regrets.
That's why we met here tonight.
Todo, to whatever is ahead,
we raise this 63rd vintage Château Burgundy.
Cheers!
Thank you...
Be in touch at least once a week.
Come on, Ozaki.
Todo is not some child.
Whether the times are easy,
whether they are rough,
either way,
anyone you see here -
make sure to stay in touch with any of us here.
Not because we fear you will feel lonely,
but because we will be uneasy.
As long as you don't give us any response,
we will be uneasy.
I heard you, Ozaki.
In conclusion, while you will be there,
you shouldn't be trying to impersonate Mr. Munakata.
You are you only. And not Munakata Jin.
You have always been Todo Takayuki. Let it remain that way.
Whichever the place and time.
Mr. Munakata has died.
He did not die.
He died!
He didn't die!
Fool.
Good luck, in absence of a better word.
No one managed to dissuade you after all.
Take care.
Thank you, Madame Butterfly.
Hey, Oka.
You have not been very voluble tonight.
Don't you and Todo have a lot to say to each other?
No. Actually... Actually, I don't have anything...
You do, you do, you do. You surely do. Now, Todo. She's listening.
Oka...
Todo remains loyal to the righteous cause.
He carries on doing what he has made his mind to.
And since Todo chose this
I will think of it as a righteous cause as well.
Don't give up, please.
Now, let's get a bit more boozed, Todo.
You applied for the coming Autumn Tokyo Cup,
didn't you, Oka?
Yes. I did.
I participate in entries too.
Let's do our best together.
Yes.
Cheers!
Crap! I forgot to ask the plane departure time tomorrow!
Hey Todo, sure you don't feel like calling your beloved one?
Tonight is your last chance to see each other.
I don't have any "beloved ones."
At 21 it's essential to have one or two.
Todo's love belongs to tennis.
Such is Munakata Jin ghost's precept.
You can't be sure.
Good God, you really need to mature, man!
You say that because you have like 5 to 6 ex-lovers yourself?
Ten of them!
Is something wrong with my looks?
I don't have a single one.
What's the matter, Todo?
Well then.
Shall we be on our ways.
See you, Todo. Make sure your luggage is packed and ready
when I pick you up tomorrow.
Sure.
See ya!
I wanted to talk to Oka just a little bit more.
He will, surely!
Todo will surely find a way to let me know.
It's too late.
She is sleeping already.
Hello? Hello!
Hello, is that you, Todo?
Please tell me this one more little thing.
What time does you plane take off tomorrow?
Just once more, even for a moment, I want to see you.
I don't want to be seen a capricious child.
I don't want to see myself a capricious child.
Oka Hiromi. 19 years old.
Falling in love is nothing extraordinary. And being thrilled about meeting someone is nothing extraordinary! Still...
Still, I'm not sure if it's love that is driving me now.
Everyone says the person I love is making a mistake.
That he should not try to climb further. That he should not be naive.
I myself have stopped halfway in every of my undertakings.
There is probably not a single thing I can do
to help Todo right now.
Besides...
I would probably lack courage for it...
Those are the flowers
I gave to Todo yesterday!
Dear Oka,
at 20:15 I am departing from Narita
Flight 522
T.T
To Oka:
at 20:15 I depart from Narita. Flight 522.
I'm ready!
Alright!
Sorry. We made you wait.
No, it's you who should excuse me.
It's been some time since I last fought an actual match.
Oka! You will play a 3-set match with Ryuzaki!
This training game will show you what to hone next!
So unexpectedly. Do I have enough time?
Get to the baseline!
To get there by 20:15,
I have to leave the court no later than at 5!
No slacking off!
Okay!
Hiromi, I'll keep my game plain, but rough!
Okay! I'm ready when you are!
And then practice?
Somehow Hiromi has less and less free time.
You think so?
When does your practice end?
Let me think... At 5 PM.
Then, let's go see a movie after that!
I'll meet you by the "Club."
Actually...
What now?
You can't again?
I am enlisted for the Autumn Tokyo Cup...
Coach Katsura's appointment?
Strategy meeting?
You could say that.
Figures. He always makes you go full steam ahead.
How can he not, since you're nothing like a usual player of my sort?
Of course! Hiromi is fine with it!
What's the matter?
Nevermind.
I'm sorry I couldn't go to the sea.
Did something happen there?
No, there was nothing.
Maki, cheer up!
I'm carving out a time to hang out with you soon. A whole day!
But today, sorry. I can't come along.
I should have carried on playing tennis too.
Game for Ryuzaki! Game count: 6-1!
Set count: 1-0!
Hiromi.
Yes?
When you rush in to the ball,
you make half a step less than usual.
You keep missing my forehands
even though I'm still out of shape.
I'm sorry!
It's not really about going pro or not.
As well as it's not really about standing on top of the world.
But when my friend puts on full power with no second thoughts,
it is a mighty incentive for me to start something great myself.
These days, there are no other guys that daring,
not even myself.
Among common folk, devoting oneself to something wholly
is seen as an outre way to embarrassment.
The best those people can do is to flock around one
who is considered favorite.
Such rabble lives just to yell "Loser!" to one another
and fress on every entr'acte,
with little repentance afterwards.
Please focus on the road.
Had I not known a man named Munakata Jin,
I'd never get here.
Out! The second set score is 5-1!
Ryuzaki lead!
This is bad! If I go on giving away every game with an out,
I'll lose the match!
However, I could leave this court once the match is over!
The flight is at 20:15.
If I go now, I can still get there on time!
I may at least be able to see Todo in the lounge!
Oka! Quit dilly-dallying!
It's your service!
That's why I must do my best either way.
The opponent is Madame Butterfly.
I cannot afford to lose intentionally!
Need your help. This is heavy.
Gotcha!
Leaving for New York with flight 522?
Yes.
Your luggage, please.
OK! There's still plenty of time until the boarding.
Let's drink and talk it away.
Yes.
Game!
Game count: 7-5!
Set count: 2-0! Winner - Ryuzaki!
Thank you so much!
More than to win, I was happy to see Hiromi fight
just as vigorously in the second half after such a long time.
You started the second set losing 5 to 1.
But pulled it to 7-5 eventually. Not bad.
Yes.
Alright, enough for today!
Dismissed, everyone.
If you excuse me!
Will I make it in time?
Will I not?
Goddammit!
Flight 522 to New York passengers
may now begin their boarding.
Madame, at what time do you have the flight?
20:15!
That's a bummer...
Going to your boyfriend?
I mean, seeing him off?
Yes...
What a spicy story! You fell in love with a foreigner,
but now he has to leave. My, how spicy it is...
Having to follow a foreigner sure is an ordeal!
My bad.
Don't worry, I'll get you there in time!
Passengers of the plane 522 to New York,
leaving at 20:15, are requested to proceed to the board.
The 63rd gate is ready to accept you.
Hey, Todo. About time you start going.
Just a bit more...
There's still some coffee left.
Hey, Todo!
What's with that sudden dither?
No, it's nothing...
Todo!
Wait, Chiba.
I have been playing
a practice match with Madame Butterfly!
6-1 and 7-5 - I lost both sets.
But this time I almost felt like I'm winning!
Just one step... No.
I was just half a step away!
I'm sure you can do it.
You can certainly make this one or even two steps more.
Goodbye...
Never say goodbye.
Okay.
Take care.
You too, Todo.
Todo, I love you too.
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into one tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
I'm Aikawa Maki.
Todo has left for New York
and Hiromi feels very lonely.
Fight, alright? Fight!
The Tokyo Cup match is coming at us imminently.
Though Todo is away, he'll surely do his best.
Still, when the game day comes,
Hiromi is still acting weird.
What's the matter, Hiromi?
Has something happened to Todo?
Coming soon: "I want to see you, Todo..."