Encoding - Pachinko    Translation - Perevodildo
Aim for the ace
!
OVA-2 (1989-1990)
—
Final Stage
Under the skies that are still unknown to me
I know, you're doing just the same -
Dreaming
Just a small glow
From those great days
Is what dragging you along
Giving you faith and some comfort
Under the sun that scorches badly
I only want to see your guise
But instead...
I only watch
With tears on my face
As you slowly disappear in this noon haze
We're alone
Walking this world on our own
Looking for each other since long ago
In the end, in the end,
After the day we finally meet
We won't ever have to say "Goodbye"
Do you believe such a thing can actually be realized?
This is what Munakata had in mind.
Sure enough, theoretically
nothing should get in the way.
Until now, Oka have lived and trained for this only.
I can't stress this enough.
Still...
We've been through a lot,
but Oka always remained loyal to this path.
Therefore, more than ever,
the time is ripe for her to master this technique.
We've already entered the point of no return.
Daigo...
The Queen's Cup '90 is to become our first and foremost,
tangible, full-scale challenge to the world,
posed by Oka, by myself, and, of course...
By Munakata.
Episode 9
Queen's Cup '90
Begins!
Are you going to the tonight's party, Reika?
Yes.
An unusual player should also arrive from abroad.
Their participation is sure to surprise you.
Unusual player?
Three days before the deadline, the "last minute application"
came from a player whom I couldn't help but to recommend.
What happened to it next?
Perhaps, we'll meet her on the venue.
Looking forward to seeing her if so.
Do you want me to entreat for the answer?
One should not peep inside a present before it is handed!
A present?
For me?
Queen's Cup '90 Championship Opening Ceremony
Allow me to introduce to you...
Soviet player Sinyachova!
As well as Chanseska from Hungary!
West German player, Henkel.
Thank you all for coming.
The mass media of all kinds are welcome too.
From now on, the Queen's Cup '90
opening party is considered open.
Hiromi, are you feeling steady today?
Yes. I'm all excited.
But this is the first time I'm attending such a party.
Everything is the spirit of luxury!
Hiromi, look there for a moment.
The one we saw in the video, Jean Ryder.
She is also the spirit of sombre today.
Sombre?
It's her personal trademark -
to always dress in black.
She swore to wear no clothes of other colours
until she becomes the Wimbledon champion.
Wimbledon...
Like a sign of her solid determination
to achieve her dream and never lose grasp on it.
And finally, the Spaniard Marchesa Broir.
The suits surrounding her
is her coaching staff.
Each one of them has a contract
with her parents, being paid $100 000 per year.
Only the top-notch coaches here.
Probably...
she is the only person in the world
to carry this variety of personal coaches back and forth.
Ladies and gentleman!
Let's begin the party!
Queen's Cup Opening Party Venue
The highlight of the evening!
Queen's Cup '90 matchups!
Let me present you with the
matching schedule for the first Queen's Cup stage!
Hiromi, come along.
Entry on the verge. Last minute application
is so much like Midorikawa. You're here after all!
Very well.
Means I did it in time.
Midorikawa, please.
Thanks. Hiromi, how are you?
Doing fine now?
Yes.
But what a surprise it is!
I'd never imagine seeing you in this tournament too!
Prize money can do wonders.
This is an lucrative tournament. Couldn't help.
So, are you a pro now?
Yeah, once and for all. Got a pro tournament license.
An American one.
And you, Madame Butterfly?
Finally giving up noble pupa tennis to become a pro-imago?
Perhaps... Have been thinking of buying myself
a new Mercedes for a long time now.
You haven't changed a bit!
Laughing it off like the good old days.
Don't be so strained, relax!
Do your best, okay?
I will. But there's still a long way to go.
I was brought here rather by inertia, drawn by you.
What are you talking about?
As long as it is upsets him,
I am never... quitting tennis.
What is it you're talking about?
Greetings, dear Todo.
The Queen's Cup '90
first round matchups have finally been announced.
Turns out, mine's the third match
of the very first day.
Morita Kyoko will be my first opponent.
It appears that Morita
is very different from myself.
Middle-aged veteran pro
with 5 years of experience.
She used to be an exchange student in Australia
and became a pro during that time.
Remember, Oka. The difference between you and Morita
will become apparent in the upcoming match.
But don't think that it is in your abilities.
This match's outcome will be decided
by your concentration and determination only.
By how well can you concentrate on your play.
Self-confidence will also be a factor.
All of it will manifest in points ratio.
Okay.
The opponent is a pro. For the sake of your future,
you should also become a keen pro,
devote your whole body to the court.
Okay!
Right, that's good!
Father.
Father!
Ah, Reika!
What is it so absorbing you saw there?
No, nothing.
It's a lie!
I also saw the 18th court residents.
Oka's shape seems greater than ever.
During this whole morning...
During the morning they only took three short breaks.
Those two were endlessly practicing
groundstrokes all that time.
Nothing else?
It seems Oka and Daigo
are taking some completely new step forward together.
What kind of?
The Queen's Cup '90 is bound to determine
whether she's ripe for the next stage or not.
What do you think those two are trying to pull off?
Reika, just like you always did before,
you must now stick to your own path.
I'm sorry, father.
Something that made me lose sight of it
has gotten into me.
The present me has forgot momentarily
everything my father taught me ever since I was so little.
If Hiromi suddenly grows up in front of me,
I must also grow and catch up with her.
To climb the highest peak,
I have to fly higher than the peak itself.
Reika.
Reika!
But can I fly now?
You can do better than this!
Step more!
You cannot afford any doubts now!
Okay!
Midorikawa's match is the first one of the first day of the first round. Her opponent is an American player Smith.
Madame Butterfly, Ryder, and Broir
will play with the first round' winners.
Because of the seeding,
they won't enter the contest until round two.
That is why, Todo,
me and Midorikawa
have to get through the first round by all means,
in order to cross rackets
with Madame Butterfly and other promising players.
For us to be reunited again,
I must defeat Morita whatever the cost.
What I know for sure is
this time repechage match is not an option for me.
First round, first match. Midorikawa Ranko against Irene Smith.
The match is starting any minute.
30-0.
This is it!
The revived southpaw cannon serve!
40-0.
What a stunning game!
This is a truly impressive comeback by Midorikawa!
She overcome her right hand crisis,
that almost made Midorikawa retire on the health basis,
by turning into a southpaw,
and making a brilliant comeback to the court!
In continuation to the first set,
she holds a significant lead in the second!
Yes, Ozaki listening.
Why, it's you!
Yeah, I'm watching.
Midorikawa is playing her first match now.
What a pity...
Why can't they rebroadcast it to Los Angeles as well?
Todo? That fellow is practicing at the club.
Haven't returned yet.
Oka's match is the third one today.
By the time it's over, it'll be way past midnight on your side.
Doesn't matter. Whatever the outcome is, let us know at any time.
Todo is all out of patience.
Sure, sure, sure.
Midorikawa just served such an ace!
She is amazing, what a miraculous revival!
Flawless...
Match point already!
Alright, this is the first round secured.
Now just to get ahead of her, then the victory is mine!
Ryuzaki Reika, Oka Hiromi...
Our rivalry has always been
the greatest honor for me.
I even returned to this court
just to taste it once again.
Game over.
Match won by Midorikawa.
The audience is not allowed beyond this point.
Authorized support.
The second match is just
on the "play ball" stage now, you know.
Want something of it?
Melon pie, fried chestnuts,
ice, supermarket spicy chicken.
All of Hiromi's favourite snacks!
Thanks.
I'll use it later.
Later?
When I win.
OK!
You are... Oka, right?
I'm Morita.
Nice to meet you today and stuff.
Right. I'm Oka. Nice to meet you.
You know I've been in Australia all this time, right?
I'm not familiar with Japan's amateurs. Barely know a few.
This time I was so busy settling things with sponsors,
I couldn't attend the party.
So I'm seeing your face for the first time.
You are using a fairly heavy racket here.
How cheeky.
Don't let yourself be provoked, Hiromi.
This person is one of the few Japanese pros in rankings.
And that's how she achieves it:
In spite of mediocre abilities, she is the type of pro
winning rather with mouth than skill.
What did you say!?
If you want to threaten me - come out on the court
and show how well you handle the ball, will ya?
Get lost. And don't you dare to trick my buddies
with your pathetic performances. Now.
Hamburger. May I have one?
Please, please!
Thanks.
Hiromi, do your best, okay?
Sure!
Then, I'll be watching you from the stands.
Midorikawa!
Thanks a lot!
Finally, the long-awaited third match
of the first round begins!
In this match we're giving it a try to see
if our practices promoted you to a new stage.
But have I mastered it enough
to bet an actual game on it?
You will do it.
We will!
But...
You can do it.
You're the only one who can!
The first round was great.
Congratulations on your triumph.
Thank you.
They are just about to begin now.
Oka serves.
Is she winning?
Tell me.
Nothing yet. Instead, hurry to bed.
Don't you have an important match tomorrow yourself?
But...
Let me clarify, are you defying the advice
of your free yet competent manager?
I heard ya.
Oka, I have faith in you.
In your victory.
No... In you doing your best
and showing everyone a wonderful match.
Out! 0-40!
As expected, she knows some techniques.
Yet she's still but an amateur.
One shot, one shot,
she is obsessed with hitting only one type of ball.
This one's mine!
Out!
Game won by Morita.
Zounds!
What an unfortunate miss!
Fault! It's a double fault!
Oka suffers a service-game,
reaching the break already!
In the course of the match, Oka remains under constant pressure,
while Morita's score lead keeps growing.
One can say, Morita indulges herself to savoring the victory,
as Oka's power is being masterfully dodged by her all along.
From the moment my match has begun,
he was staying there silently, not even approaching the stands.
Coach... What's that supposed to mean?
What are you trying to say by suddenly turning your back on me?
It's no good!
Even though during our practices
it took effect sometimes,
when you do so in a real match,
I may not be able to handle it!
I know it for sure...
I'm definitely gonna miss the timing a little
and will then have to wait for another shot chance.
In the end, I will lose this match!
Do it, Oka!
I can't!
Try it!
Got it!
Hiromi!
15-0.
By yourself, Oka.
You can only do it this way!
Wait though...
At this rate, losing is a matter of time.
That's it, Oka!
I'm not letting you through!
Got it!
15-all!
What was that shot now?
Hiromi!
Oka switched to offense
as though she is a whole other person now!
Hey? What happened there, Ozaki? Hey!
Incredible. I have never seen Oka
playing such an incredible kind of tennis.
Now that is is indeed a one-side match!
No telling which one is a real pro now.
Hiromi is clearly putting her back in it now.
It's like when she returns the ball,
it becomes invisible to opponent, making them stagger.
Hiromi and Coach Katsura have really taken this huge,
completely new step this time.
This time they did it!
This is just unbelievable!
6-3, 6-0. Set count: two against one.
Match won by Oka!
There is one song I cannot ever forget
Still, there's a face I'm willing to forget
With her feelings mixed up,
Alice got completely lost
The midst of summer
Brought her into tricky love maze
I want you to hug tightly
And never let go of me,
One scared and timid tiny girl
I quite remember our very first kiss
And the beginning of all of this
While birds were singing for us...
I'll take a car and take a lonely trip
I know it'll bring me
To the seashore
Where only the the sun,
Dazzlingly bright,
Could witness my long-awaited happiness
Aikawa Maki here.
Queen's Cup '90 is on!
It's growing hotter by day here!
But unbelievable things happen at the same time.
Like the Midorikawa's struggle for example.
Although her opponent is some 14-years-old pro!
Midorikawa, despite all the reasoning,
uses her right hand again!
Keep fighting, Midorikawa!
After that round, you'll face Madame Butterfly!
Next time:
"Challenger Ranko!"