On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
and my pain
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Aim for the Ace!
Coach Munakata, please head
to the Principal's office right away.
I'm sorry for calling you out
of practice, Munakata.
Actually, for the ceremony party,
that is to be held tonight,
Mr. Ryuzaki has just come here
to deliver an unbelievable present.
A present?
Ryuzaki, does that mean it's been set in motion?
That's right, Munakata. Just now,
while leaving the Japan Tennis Association meeting,
I thought of making you happy and flew straight here.
The Japan Tennis Association
has accepted your proposal with full support.
Mr. Ryuzaki...
Thank you very much, for everything.
That's unnecessary, Munakata.
As the Association Chairman, I only did what's right.
If it's for Munakata Jin, an outstanding coach,
the Association fain did me this favor.
In the future, the attention will be on you
and the player that you've selected.
Best of luck to you both!
As long as she sticks with it,
I will put in all my effort!
Tonight's winning party will be an event
like we've never seen before.
I love, love, love Todo!!!
Episode 13
I wonder what we will do.
What do you mean?
Tonight we're having a party
at Madame Butterfly's residence.
For such a day, we should just wear a little make-up
and wait as the party slowly begins.
I think that's the only correct course!
But to practice instead
until the party almost starts is nonsense!
There's no choice,
the Kanto Tournament is coming up.
Pausing the practice
means falling behind the other schools.
That's right.
Oh goodness, it seems her drive
has made her too serious.
What's wrong, Otowa?
I'm fine. My arm just tingled a little.
My right… My right hand is…
Otowa!
Kyoko! Kyoko!
- What's with Otowa Kyoko?
- Are you okay?
Captain! What are you doing here?
Call an ambulance!
Okay!
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Ryuzaki
Congratulations
Nishi High Tennis Club
Hiromi, these cherries are pretty good, want one?
What's wrong?
Otowa… I wonder if she's okay.
That said, Coach who went with her
to the hospital, is late.
Otowa…
Otowa!
Doctor, how is Otowa?
There is no hope for her right hand.
The tendons in her forearm are severely injured.
If she goes on playing tennis for 2-3 more months,
her hand will barely be movable.
But up until yesterday, Otowa was…
No, she must have been hiding it from everyone.
She knew of this diagnosis for a long time it seems.
Everyone, thank you for your patience.
It seems that Coach Munakata has just arrived
and we would like to begin.
Hey, Japan's number one Demon Coach!
A suit looks good on you!
Hey Hiromi, the Coach in his suit and tie
looks pretty stylish!
I'm smitten!
Geez, that's so like Maki.
Maki, look! It's Madame Butterfly!
She looks wonderful.
It's just like a wedding dress.
So true.
Hey, look, look!
Look at the men's teams stunned faces!
Even Todo!
I should have worn a proper evening dress too.
Did you say something, Hiromi?
Nothing!
Everyone, please be silent.
I would like to invite the man
who provided the venue for the party,
Japan Tennis Association Chairman Ryuzaki,
to hand out the winner cups now.
Men's group team division.
Ozaki Isamu, Todo Takayuki,
Ota Yasuho, Oga Seichi.
Representing the team, Captain Ozaki Isamu.
Okay!
Congratulations.
Thank you!
Next, Men's single division, Todo Takayuki!
Todo, you're wonderful!
Next, the women's division.
Women's group team division, Hoshino Miho,
Ryuzaki Reika,
Wakatsuki Aoi and Miya Mariko,
Oka Hiromi.
The women's representative - Hoshino!
Now, let's congratulate Nishi High's new star,
Oka, by lifting her up!
Heave-ho!
Congratulations!
Do your best!
Okay!
Lift up! Lift up! Lift up! Lift up!
That's surprising. I didn't know Oka
was so popular with the male students.
Yeah, me neither.
Hiromi, are you okay?
Lift up!
Let me continue then…
The women's representative, Hoshino Miho.
Okay!
Otowa, I heard the news from the doctor.
Why did you hide it until now?
Not only you, Coach.
My friends as well.
Not even my parents knew.
Because if I didn't hide it,
I couldn't keep playing the tennis I love!
"Until my arm can't move anymore,
I'll keep playing the tennis I love!"
That's what I've lived for!
tIon
ResIgna
Curse you, Coach, at least…
at least until my arm gave out,
I wanted to be a varsity player.
I really envy Oka.
Women's single division, Ryuzaki Reika!
Congratulations!
Otowa!
How is your injury?
Want to know?
It's just a sprain!
Just one week and it should be fine.
Anyway, both of you get back inside.
The party hasn't ended yet.
Okay.
Otowa, thank goodness it was just a sprain.
Well, you know, seeing as even an ambulance came for you, I was really worried!
Take care!
Otowa!
Going home?
Yes.
You curse me and can't endure staying here.
Those feelings are understandable.
But Otowa, please stay
for just a little while longer.
There's something that I'd like you to see.
What? The lights are out?
Oka Hiromi…
Ryuzaki Reika…
Todo, Ozaki, as well.
Would these four people,
please step up to the front?
I would like to make
an important announcement.
Important announcement?
Aim for the Ace!
Those who I have just called,
please hurry up to the front.
Well then Ryuzaki,
I'll leave the rest to you.
Thank you.
Most likely, the four people called up here
don't know what's going on.
What I'll be announcing now
is the prospects of Japanese Tennis Association.
To be frank, Japan's tennis level is unfortunately
not currently up to the international standards.
And so,
the Japanese Tennis Association has decided to select
strongest students from high schools in each region
to start nourishing their physical and mental strength
in high school already.
Allowing them to reach international standards
in the near future.
Therefore, according to that plan,
along with Midorikawa Ranko from Kaga High,
those young people will comprise
our prefecture's selection of 5 players.
Me… as the representative for the prefecture!
Hiromi, that's great!
That's great, isn't it?
Congratulations, Hiromi!
But, Maki, I…
Congratulations Oka!
Well then everyone, shall we lift her up again?
No!
How cruel!
Holding me up to make me watch this…
You've gone too far, Coach!
I… I…
Wish that I never played tennis in the first place.
Ah, everyone. Coach Munakata
will be the one supervising those players.
Coach, please say a few words.
Listen up, everyone.
No, those of you who love tennis, please listen.
I won't ask any of you
why did you ever decide to play tennis.
In other words, I don't intend to ask
what you think of tennis.
However, if you think you know what tennis is about,
why are you crying?
More precisely, why regret having spent
your whole youth playing?
Didn't you yourself make this choice,
however fleeting it was,
of dedicating your whole precious youth
to playing tennis?
But if there are those of you
who compare yourselves to others remorsefully,
I don't think you ever
really burned with passion!
It isn't too late to start.
For your own sake,
burn with passion.
Coach is somehow pretty different today.
Burn with passion, for your own sake.
Do you understand, Ozaki?
Yes, I think I get it.
They're words especially for us.
Bravo, Coach Munakata!
Bravo! Bravo!
Take your courage and for yourself,
keep your passion alight.
You fool! It's not a dream, not a dream!
Chairman Ryuzaki clearly stated that:
"The Japanese Tennis Association selected students
from high schools of each region,
making them, in the near future,
capable to meet international standards."
The international stage!
Hey, Hiromi, it's the international stage!
Huh, aren't you happy?
But you see, for the international stage,
100 players would gather from across the country,
but only a few will get a chance!
So what? If it's Oka Hiromi,
no one will be in a slightest doubt!
You dummy, let's be serious!
Whatever, I'm free to dream anything I like.
A lousy player like me, together with
Madame Butterfly, Kaga High's Lady Orchid,
and even Todo and Ozaki in selection, to top it off.
I've got to do my best or I'll be laughed at.
Coach said it, too! Burn with passion!
Yeah! That's right.
Well then, sorry to keep you up so late.
No, not at all. Take care.
All right, Munakata, this is my way.
Thanks.
I knew it. Oka had something that I didn't have -
unwavering spirit for fight and fierce tenacity.
And so, no matter what anyone says,
she always persisted playing her own tennis.
Compared to that,
my tennis has always been intended to please others.
When my right arm started giving out,
"She is a top class player,"
that's what people said and it kept me going on.
And now, soon, this arm
will cease moving altogether.
But with the little time that remains, until that day,
I want to play tennis for myself!
I want it!
Re
Resignation
ResIgnatIon
Resigna
tion
I'll return it. Is that okay with you, Otowa?
Yes.
Otowa, go and make some friends.
Friends that you can share happiness,
and who you can entrust your dreams to.
If you do that the springtime of your youth
will double, no, it'll be everlasting.
Whether you can move your arm or not
won't matter. Got it?
Everlasting youth…
Friends that you can entrust your dreams to.
That you can entrust your dreams to.
You're still going after me, aren't you, Hiromi?
I'll consider anyone who pursues me an enemy.
You understand that don't you, Hiromi?
Madame Butterfly is fired up.
All right!
Maki, let's go!
Oh, all right!
Here I come!
Okay!
She's planning to compete with Madame Butterfly!
Really, just because she was selected at the meet,
she thinks she's all that!
My, a player like her is only capable of making a mess!
Tennis Association is yet to realize!
Everyone, listen up!
The pairs for the Kanto Doubles Tournament
have been decided.
Captain Hoshino!
Okay!
Your partner is Miya.
Ryuzaki.
Yes.
I'll have you pair up with Oka.
That's all. Starting tomorrow,
we'll be practicing doubles. Prepare yourselves.
Coach!
What is it?
I refuse.
I can't play doubles in an unbalanced pair.
That's not a valid reason!
That's too much!
Yeah really! I feel sorry for Madame Butterfly.
If you have a poor partner in doubles,
you'll never be able to win!
If it leads to Madame Butterfly losing,
I wonder who'll be responsible.
I'd hate to see her make a fool
out of Madame Butterfly!
Hey Maki, should we have a race?
Let's go!
Unfair! Wait!
Sorry! Ah! I feel bad I made such a mess!
Are you not hurt?
Todo!
Oka, I'm sure a lot must be happening
to you off the court.
But you should still follow
Coach and trust him.
Okay!
This is the third time that Todo
has brought me home.
Every time I'm in a dilemma,
he appears with kindness
"I'm sure a lot must be happening to you
off the court."
When I heard that, I genuinely almost cried,
but I did my best to endure.
That's because if I'm always a crybaby,
Todo will dislike me.
Oh? This isn't my pencil.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
That's the right number, though.
I see, when we crashed,
I must have mixed up mine with Todo's.
So that means
that Todo now has my pencil as well!
Listen, never lose trust in Coach!
Okay!
To Be Continued
She can't get along with Madame Butterfly.
The doubles aren't going well together.
Worrying so much, Hiromi's play worsens.
Fiercely refusing Hiromi,
Madame Butterfly quits practicing.
But Coach Munakata's training continues.
Now, stand Hiromi! Bear this training!
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"Fired up! Special Training with a Chill in the Air"
In the chilled air, Hiromi's soul trembles.
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo