On the court, everyone
Aim for the Ace!
is alone, all alone.
My love
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
and my pain
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
Based on the Original Work by Sumika Yamamoto
Serialized in
Weekly Margaret
nobody understands them.
The shining wind blows.
The sun beats down.
With rose petals on my lips
I leap forth.
Just like the white ball.
Serve! Smash! Volley!
Do your best!
Director
Osamu Dezaki
Ace! Ace! Ace!
Director
Osamu Dezaki
Aim for the Ace!
The Demon Coach Strikes!
Episode 5
Even though it's another beautiful day,
I still feel blue.
But…
This time it's completely my fault.
I can't run away from that.
I can't say it,
that I lost the racket she gave me.
How could I ever tell her?
Hiromi, are you still worried about it?
There's no escaping the truth.
But…
No buts!
A sincere apology soothes anyone.
Right, Hiromi?
Excuse me, Ms. Ryuzaki.
Well, about the racket you gave me…
Well, I've lost it.
It's entirely my fault, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's all right.
You don't have to worry so much about it. I gave it to you, it's yours, so it's all right.
But, well…
It's all right. Forget about it already.
Okay.
If you excuse me.
Oka, what do you think you're doing?
That's right, how arrogant of you.
Don't you know how important a racket is
to a tennis player?
Especially since the racket in question
was a gift from Madame Butterfly.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Well, that's…
Was that the best apology you could make?
Now, go apologize one more time!
Oka, it's all right.
Madame Butterfly, but…
Just forget about the racket.
And you too!
Otowa Kyoko
Madame Butterfly…
She might have just given up on me.
I so much dread it...
Excuse me, please take this towel.
Thank you.
Madame Butterfly,
she doesn't care about me anymore.
Since I lost the racket,
there's no reason for her to care about me anymore.
Thank you very much!
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Might just fall asleep right here.
Hiromi, you must be tired too.
Oka!
You're not free yet.
Practice returning the ball to me.
Yes!
Again?
I want him to leave me alone
on such a terrible day.
Fast!
Don't wobble while running!
Yes!
Don't hit to sides!
Too slow! Run faster!
Run! Run!
If he keeps being that tough on Hiromi every day,
she'll die.
Even if she tries hard to stay on varsity,
it won't work out for her.
Sure, all she gets is a tough time.
That's right. Continue
to suffer like that.
What are you doing?
The reason you fall
is because your form is bad. Get up!
Y-Yes.
Hiromi!
Aikawa!
Don't even try to do anything for her.
It's okay, Maki. I'm all right.
I can get up.
Right, that's it for today.
Before you go home,
work on your backhand 100 times.
Understood?
Yes!
Well, everybody, about time for us to retire too.
After practicing for such a long time,
she doesn't seem to have understood a thing.
Madame Butterfly…
All right!
82! 83!
84! 85!
86! 87!
88! 89!
90! 91! 92!
93! 94! 95! 96!
97! 98!
99!
100!
I'm exhausted.
Don't come near me.
Don't touch me!
Coach is actually awful.
But I don't mind since he makes it easier for us.
It will be the same today:
"Oka, come, hit."
No wonder for her dedicated tutor.
It's like she is some "Model Player,"
deserving a special treatment.
What can you know!
They're just so nasty, not a hint of reserve!
Are you all right?
Well, my movements seem fine
in the rest of the body, see? It moves fine.
Easy, easy, just be careful.
Maki, don't hold me! Don't hold!
My racket!
Sure, sure.
Here you go.
Look, Hiromi! Practice is about to begin.
Oka, come!
Yes!
Demon, devil, monster—
Maki!
Oka, the practice will get harder from today on.
Be prepared for it.
Get closer to net!
Okay!
Your grip is weak!
It's not a heavy punch!
Try to make the hits snappy!
Look at that pose,
she's just faffing about as always.
Naturally. She can't play as proper
varsity member anyway.
What are you doing?
Oh no!
This too!
Why, why is he only so heartless to me?
He can make me practice as much as he wants.
But it's not going to work out.
Following the balls is already too much for me!
Coach is paying too much attention to Oka.
That's right, he doesn't care about us.
She's his favorite.
She definitely is.
Maybe I was wrong that her suffering
would serve her right.
The coach is way too over the top about her.
Hey, Kyoko. You think she's getting any better
by doing that?
Doubt it.
She is!
Madame Butterfly!
Can't you see that yourself?
Oka is already showing signs of a aptitude.
Her aptitude!
Aim for the Ace!
Oka, your grip is getting weak.
Concentrate!
Okay!
That's incredible,
she can actually follow the ball now.
That's what you can expect
of the girl Mr. Munakata chose.
So, Todo, let's go home.
Fine, go home.
Hiromi! Finally finished?
Here's a towel.
Hiromi, are you all right?
Hey, hang in there.
Come on!
You must be hungry.
Why don't we go eat noodles with tempura?
What's that "V" sign for?
Oh! You want two bowls of noodles?
I guess I didn't have to worry about you so much.
Welcome!
So crowded!
Look, I found a table!
Hey, this table has room, right?
Oh, Oka, you surprised me.
What do you mean?
You're the last person I'd expect to see in a restaurant like this.
I come in here whenever I eat noodles. We came here together the other day.
I thought you would go
to a special restaurant of some kind.
After all you're treated so specially.
What do you mean by that?
H-Hiromi!
Am I treated that special?
Cut it out, Hiromi.
Maki, you keep quiet!
Now look, I—
Hey! Why don't you two come here and join me?
Todo.
You can sit here.
When you're hungry,
your temper wears thin.
Now, come take a seat.
Welcome. Can I take your order?
After practice, don't you get hungry?
Now, what are you going to have?
I'm going to have tempura soba.
Me too. We'll have two each—
She meant to say two orders of the tempura soba
for the two of us, if you could.
Sure! Two orders of the tempura soba, kitchen!
Whenever I think about getting a hard time tomorrow
from the demon coach, I feel so down.
But Hiromi, you are lucky in a way.
Because of that,
Coach is in a way always with you.
Madame Butterfly also cares about you.
And apparently Todo does a great deal as well.
I see.
Seriously!
I can tell if I see such a thing.
Those people might be seeing your potential.
Otherwise it doesn't make sense.
It's unlikely.
Captain! Is Hoshino here?
Yes!
Ozaki, what is it?
Coach Munakata has a message.
He said everyone should train on their own today.
Coach had some urgent matters, so he didn't come.
Okay, I understand. Thanks.
Everybody, did you hear that?
Manage personal practice by yourself today!
Practice on our own?
It's not like we are not used to it,
unlike a certain one.
I wonder how will Oka handle this.
I guess we're just too weak to practice with her.
This thick wall doesn't miss balls,
nor does it get tired.
In a way, just like Coach.
Serves her right! If there's no coach,
nobody cares about someone like you.
Doing your best?
Todo!
You're not done yet?
Don't be too hard on yourself.
You're doing well
with that personal everyday practice.
Todo, have you been checking on me?
Of course. I watch your training every single day.
But, the more I train,
all I get is more bruises.
Not at all!
That is not so. You show aptitude already.
You certainly are, little by little, developing.
It's not possible.
Why? Don't you believe it?
Yes, I don't feel like it is so.
It's all right. You'll get it soon.
Madame Butterfly!
I'm sorry I asked you to come here.
What's going on?
Is it urgent?
Yes, I have something to talk about.
So, how do you think,
why I wasn't chosen for varsity?
I don't know, I'm not the coach after all.
That's why I asked the coach as well.
Then he told me that I imitate
Madame Butterfly's tennis.
That was the reason why I wasn't selected.
That's what Coach said to me.
Is that so?
What's wrong with imitating the way you play?
It appears, your tennis is a beacon to everyone else.
I'm not an exception.
So what's wrong with that?
As I said, only Coach knows that.
But, if it's wrong to imitate you,
then looking up to you in general is wrong as well!
Is that all you wanted to talk about?
Yeah.
Then you have to excuse me.
Wait!
This is nothing but an excuse!
An excuse to pull off a backstage deal
of making Oka Hiromi a varsity player.
Can't you tell it yourself?
It's so obvious.
Coach pays attention to her only.
My! That's actually Oka Hiromi.
Right there!
My! She's with Todo!
Look.
It got stuck in your hair.
Dear me.
What kind of girl is that Hiromi?
She's attracting not only the coach but also Todo.
Don't you agree?
Otowa, what kind of person are you?
Well, Oka, we'll have to part here.
Yes, goodbye.
Oka!
Don't you dare give up on tennis.
No matter what happens,
don't ever give up.
Tennis is becoming of you.
You got it?
Yes!
Hiromi, you're truly energetic today!
We have the semifinals tomorrow.
Is that all?
But something brand new
peeps through that color of your face.
Shut up! You trying to be nosy?
Not at all.
I see, I can't tell since I went home early yesterday.
Did something happen then?
Oka!
He finally came!
Yes!
Come out to the court!
Ryuzaki. Play against Oka.
Okay.
Oka, make sure you're ready for the semifinals.
Yes!
Madame Butterfly, if you please.
It comes!
Isn't that enough?
Thank you very much.
Wow! Madame Butterfly
didn't show any mercy.
That was extreme!
What just happened?
I got so worked up playing against that girl.
Don't give up on playing tennis, all right?
No matter what happens.
You got it?
We have semifinals tomorrow.
I'll do it.
I'll try!
I'll try to do my best!
To Be Continued
Eastern
District
Tournament
Semi-finals
Finally, the semifinals are here.
Tournament
Semi-finals
Hiromi's heart is beating so hard.
Kita High already won the first set, 6-2.
Relax Oka, relax!
Munakata's telling off pierced Hiromi's heart.
Next time on Aim for the Ace!
"Ah! The Day of the Semi-Finals"
Hiromi's play will reveal itself.
On the tennis court at sunset
I saw a pathetic broken tennis racket.
On the tennis court, late at night
I saw a girl who was always crying.
Her initials, written in tears, were H.H.H.O.
The burning love
and the burning tomorrow…
On the white tennis court.
Ah, on the tennis court.
Original English script   ILA-BlueFixer
Checking/Editing/Typesetting/Encoding   Acebuster
TLC/QC   Perevodildo