Am I the only one who thinks
that my cat is the cutest of all?
Translation        Perevodildo
No one really knyouws what a cat’s thinking, right?
Editing                               Collectr
A question mark again, drifting with the wind today
(Hey!)
Quality check                            Marty Mcflies
(LonelyChaser Fansubs)
A carefree, happy-go-lucky kind of lifestyle
When things go wrong,
I dance it off and lead the beat
(C'mon!)
Meow-meow, somehow it works out
Meow-meow, the Michael dance!
Meow!
Meow-meow, somehow it works out
Meow-meow, the Michael dance!
Meow!
Meow-meow-meow-meow-meow
Ah, meow-nyan goes meow! (Hey!)
All right, let's get started!
Listen up! No way we're losing to some cats!
Now then...
The Animal Baseball League's opening game—
the Dogs vs. the Cats—is finally here!
The Dogs' first batter
has entered the batter's box!
Play ball!
Okay, bring it on!
On the mound is Michael,
the Cats' ace pitcher.
The battery is carefully exchanging signs.
They can't seem to decide!
Michael takes a big windup!
He throws!
What?!
Not so fast!
The ball is rolling through the outfield!
Whoa! The Cats' centerfielders
are playing around with the ball!
Come on, stop playing around!
Throw to second base!
All right! Second base, here I come!
No, you don't!
Why are you taking a break, second baseman?!
All right, go for home!
Okay, I got this!
Safe!
Safe at home! One player scores!
The Dogs' score
in the first inning is 18 runs!
Darn it! We can make up 18 runs in no time!
Michael!
All right, leave it up to Michael
to hit a home run for us.
Bring it on!
Now then, Michael is the first batter for the Cats.
Pitcher takes a big windup!
He throws!
That's it! It gets past the shortstop!
Okay, do it.
Yes, sir.
Out!
It seems that cats aren't meant to play baseball, after all.
Episode 1
Michael Appears
As it happens...
this here is Nekomaneki City.
And at a certain apartment complex...
Oh? There's a cat on the railing.
Huh? Wait...
Did it fall?!
Whose cat are you?!
You should go home at once!
Walking on that is dangerous!
Don't just relax and sit there!
Come on, come down here, please.
I beg you to get down, please!
We're on the eighth floor!
What if you fall?
No, don't run on that!
And don't scratch your head on that!
Come on, here! Come here.
Yes, that's right, come here.
It's only a sparrow!
Don't you think about jumping!
What, are you saying cats aren't dumb enough
to fall when catching a sparrow?!
You know I'm worried to death, though!
To hell with you!
Done here.
H-Huh?
What's wrong, Sensei?
N-No, it's nothing.
S-Say...
Huh?
Even a cat would die
if it fell from the seventh floor, right?
W-Well, cat or no cat, no one
would be able to take such a fall lightly.
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
Anyway, Sensei, the deadline is almost here.
Please hurry up with the manuscript.
Oh! What a cute cat!
Don't look at it.
We've never seen that cat before.
You too.
I wonder if it'd fancy some fish.
Forget it. It must be a stray cat.
Once you feed it,
it becomes attached to you.
It's best to ignore it.
Just don't give it any mind.
Don't make eye contact.
What's going on, Sensei?!
You haven't finished your work yet!
C-Cat...
And what are you doing here?!
Don't just enter other's apartments!
Goddammit...
Where did that cat come from?
What a complete lack of discipline!
Get out, you!
Stupid cat!
Geez... I can't even drink my coffee in peace.
You jerk! Now you're dead!
Stop, you!
Don't you ever come here again!
If you only just landed now,
you must've taken your time falling.
Nice catch!
For real!
Dear! What are you doing here?
I was on the verge of committing the crime of cat-killing.
Huh?
No, I just saw this guy,
and it made me curious.
My, it's a cute cat!
Hey, where do you think this cat lives?
I haven't seen him before.
Hey, why don't we keep it?
Keep it?
He's pretty cute for a stray cat.
There, little one...
And that's how Kobayashi-san, the manga artist, ended up adopting this cat.
And they named him... Michael!
Now for the next news item.
Yesterday, the mayor of Nekomaneki
called a press conference.
Please stop!
What, you want to see more of what happened to Michael? Very well.
Then, let's hear from our broadcasting van
at the Kobayashi's place.
Ah, Inuyama-san, the outside reporter,
can you hear me?
Michael?
Michael!
Oh? Why are you hiding there?
Didn't we just build
a shiny new house for you?
Come on out, Michael.
Look, Michael. Food!
Go ahead, don't hold back and eat up.
Yes, go ahead!
Why are you taking it there to eat?
Here, your coffee.
Thanks.
Ah, I'm starting to hate Michael.
I mean, it's been a week already!
Isn't it about time for him
to get used to his owners?
Cats, unlike dogs,
are always going their own way.
But...
Stop sneaking around the house already!
Is sadness second nature to stray cats?
Stray cats?
That's what causes him to sneak around.
Well, he'll get used to us eventually.
There's no need to rush him.
Will he really?
Oh? Michael!
You've finally gotten used to me?
Dear! Come quickly!
What is it? I'm busy right now.
Look at what's Michael doing!
Finally!
Oh, Michael, you sweetheart.
I'm so glad!
I'm sorry!
It wasn't on purpose! Forgive me!
What the hell are you doing?!
Michael opened up to us!
I'm sorry! Please come out!
Michael?
Michael, please, come out!
Yes, we won't do anything to you!
We're on your side now, see?
Ah! You finally understand, Michael?
Okay, okay, good boy.
Go ahead, Michael. Come here.
You idiot!
Things were just starting to look up!
I guess cats can't get used
to humans, after all.
No, it's not Michael's fault.
Ours, then?
That's right. That's because we don't know a thing about cats.
I see.
I'll study Michael more.
If I do that, I'm sure we'll become friends.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Wh-What the hell is this?! It's awful!
Oh my God, it was actually cat juice!
What? You've learned a lot about Michael?
That's right, dear.
And that stuff is hilarious!
Sensei! The deadline is upon us!
Try to think more about your job
than your cat! Your job!
You write what happens next yourself.
What...
Here's something nice. Look closely.
Go, Michael. Walk.
Yes, go.
Here's the thing.
Hey, did you see it?
When you say "ps-ps-ps" to a cat,
it always turns to look at you!
So funny!
Madam! Now's not the time
to amuse yourself with silly stuff!
The deadline's just around the corner!
This is amazing.
There's more. Check this out!
Oh! What's that?
Isn't it amazing? Cats always smell
your finger when you stick it out to them.
Do you have more?
I do!
Sensei, please be reasonable! The deadline!
Look, when I let him smell the toothpaste...
He runs away!
Conversely, if I flap
the kitty teaser like this...
He immediately comes to play!
You got anything more?! More!
Conversely, if I let him smell a citrus...
He runs away.
However, if he hears
the canned cat food being opened...
He'll come bounding over happily.
Conversely, if he smells the mint from the pipe...
See? He's running away!
So, isn't it amusing?
I guess.
Did I overdo it?
All right, there's your manuscript.
Thanks a lot!
You shouldn't be taking it that seriously.
But...
There are times when we don't really understand each other, even as humans.
And when the other party is a cat,
you can’t expect to reach
an understanding that quickly.
But we already went ahead
and decided to keep one at home.
As time passes, he'll get used to us.
Could it be that simple?
Boss, it's an item, lost by the victim.
Wh-What's this?
Ah! Michael, your tail!
We can't see, Michael.
We can't see because of your tail!
Your tail!
Tail! Tail!
Tail, Michael!
No! Don't shake it, move it away!
Oh, please...
Keep your tail to yourself!
It's a tip-off. Go to Ginza!
Okay!
Hey, not again!
Geez...
Get off the TV!
It's warm on the TV,
so it became Michael's favorite place.
Now we can finally watch TV in peace.
I have a few questions.
Have you seen this ma—
Hm? What?
Huh?
Hey!
Just go away already!
I guess cats are difficult to keep, after all.
Unlike dogs, they always have a mind of their own.
He can't even do any tricks.
We have to give him time
and hope he gets used to us?
That's about right.
Th-The cat danced!
D-Dear!
Looks like we can become friends
with Michael, after all.
Yeah. Seems so.