The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let other see your tears
The enemy is diving on us!
Episode 3
Battle of Midway (Part 2)
Damn it! Kaga was hit!
Soryu had the same fate!
Emergency takeoff!
Out of the 4 Japanese carriers,
3 burst into flames in a blink of an eye.
The only operational carrier left was Hiryu.
Thus, the Battle of Midway
had become a milestone of the Pacific War.
As it is pointed out
as a stark example
of how erroneous decisions and miscalculations
may turn a certain victory into a disaster.
If during the time of decision making,
a commander opts to bury his head in the sand,
nothing but defeat can come out of it.
Yet, the captain of the remaining carrier, Hiryu, was taking a stand.
Curse it!
If only we had 5 minutes more!
No, not 5 minutes. Our only chance for victory,
that I told you about, slipped away 2 hours ago.
Instead, we've been idling for 2 hours straight!
Now it's our turn!
Meanwhile, on Akagi, the flagship.
Admiral, I understand your disarray,
but please transfer your flag and take our lead.
So far, our losses number 3 carriers.
We still have one carrier, 2 battleships, 2 heavy cruisers,
and 12 destroyers - a sizable force to be reckoned with!
Let's retaliate with the whole fleet!
I leave her to you.
Trust us to take care of Akagi.
Our hopes are with the fleet!
This is Hiryu's light signal.
"Hiryu. Alive and well."
They are urging us to attack.
An order to attack was issued to Hiryu.
As per the patrol aircraft's report,
one enemy carrier is stationed 144 km to the east.
Its only escort being vessels and destroyers,
our side has a clear advantage.
As of now, I proposed
a full-scale offensive to the admiral.
Therefore, the raid's goal is...
To send this carrier to the seabed!
Alright... An eye for an eye -
make it a reality.
Yes!
Commander, the attackers of Akagi are in my way.
Good. Keep following them,
take care to be stealthy!
So, being their cursed shadow?
There it is!
It's the carrier! Charge!
Alright, let's do it!
Okay!
Screw you...
However, that American carrier
was not alone in the area.
On the bridge of aircraft carrier Enterprise...
Dispatch the patrol aircraft!
Roger!
The report from Yorktown arrived.
Fires put away.
In working order.
Yorktown
Yorktown is operating normally, it seems.
Yet, I saw a huge cloud
of black smoke rising from it when we left.
It's been hit 3 times.
It's likely out of action.
The issue is, it was not the only enemy carrier.
There are 3 of them.
Exactly.
According to the captured pilots,
Yorktown, Enterprise, and Hornet carriers
are supposed to link up.
Info extorted under torture
is unreliable.
Still, it is backed up
with the subsequent patrol reports.
No room for doubt here.
The enemy is split into two with the two carrier task force much further from the single carrier's.
I see, so there are 3 enemy carriers in the area...
Yorktown
Enterprise          Hornet
Tallying with different reports,
Japan has undeniable firepower.
Our forces should be on par.
Quite frankly, we may even have the upper hand.
Makes you wonder how they pulled off
that sneak attack before.
Our big asset is the ability
to read Japan's radio traffic.
We spotted a golden chance and seized it.
And yet, after getting this far,
we're letting the last Japanese carrier go.
As long as this ship is still out there, the same fate
that befell them today might be ours tomorrow.
I propose a withdrawal.
The enemy losses are 3 aircraft carriers, ours - one.
This is a huge success as it is.
You see an opening - you hit.
For this gamble, only Enterprise will engage.
I will terminate them myself.
How about Hornet?
We'll keep Hornet in the reserve.
In the event of a Japanese attack coming our way,
we'd sacrifice Enterprise,
as a price for Hornet's escape.
Lets man up and finish this.
Not a fight.
A duel.
It's a duel!
A carrier versus carrier duel.
Out of the 3 enemy aircraft carriers,
one was crippled by Kobayashi's Squadron.
We'll take out at least one more,
even if we sink with it!
Left with only one carrier,
our fleet will destroy the enemy at night!
The first attack wing is ready to take off.
Commander.
Your plane only has a half tank
worth of gasoline.
Feel free to use my plane, please!
What happened?
A trifle. Shots scraped my wing away a little.
Well, I guess this works, too.
This way, I can carry more shells.
Commander!
You'll only need one.
A torpedo in the middle.
Roger.
Alright, that's our clients! Let's go!
Starboard! Barrage fire!
Barrage fire! Start shooting!
Get ready!
Keep shooting! Barrage fire!
More torpedo bombers incoming!
Damn thing...
Squadron commander...
Commander! Commander!
No use lamenting.
Evaluate the damage.
Roger!
Allow me to report.
Where's the commander?
How about the damage?
Another carrier, supposedly, Enterprise
was hit with two torpedoes.
One of which...
...Launched by the commander?
Which means, only Hornet remains.
Captain, about 16 km behind Enterprise,
two more enemy carriers were following.
What?
What? Does it mean the enemy
has two reserve carriers?
Yes. It is hard confirmed by all the survivors, too.
No two ways about it.
How odd...
The enemy had 4 of them in the area?
The Japanese had already crippled Yorktown before.
Why targeting her
with a following torpedo attack?
I'd venture they mistook her for Enterprise.
For us?
I had a chance to inquire about
Japan's naval engineering.
While having formidable offensive capabilities,
their setback is defense.
They put out
even small fires painstakingly.
Therefore, it must have never even dawned upon them
that Yorktown may be salvaged in under 2 hours.
Alright, now it's our turn to take a move.
As it turns out, the enemy
had 4 carriers in the area all along.
Moreover, they have been deployed
over a fairly vast area.
This renders the night attack
a highly perilous venture.
For a 3rd wave of attack.
Requesting permission from the high command.
But the sun is almost set.
We need a 3rd wave of attack!
Chief, your meal.
Chief.
Delicious.
Delicious. Really delicious.
I never had any idea a rice cake can be that delicious.
And the troopers?
They had their meal,
and are now waiting for an order to sortie.
Alright.
Enemy planes! Incoming swoop!
Full to the starboard!
Full to the port!
We're under attack!
Hiryu is invulnerable!
Still, Akagi, Kaga, and Soryu
were once invulnerable, too...
Idiots! Hiryu is never going down!
Hiryu has the Emperor's blessing!
By then,
7:25 in the afternoon,
engulfed in flames for 9 hours straight,
but still clinging to life, carrier Soryu
had also eventually went down
with a big bang.
Around the same time as Soryu,
Kaga had also set out on a 5400 m journey to the seabed.
Finally, Hiryu's final hour was also drawing near.
As long as we have this ship,
we can return to Japan to fight another day!
Hiryu is invulnerable! It's invulnerable!
Most invulnerable!
Soryu, Hiryu - as the captain of both those ships,
I will assume the ultimate responsibility for the loss of them
through sharing their fate.
The rest of you shall evacuate
to wage our future battles.
I bid farewell to my homeland.
Banzai!
Banzai! Banzai!
Banzai...
Fine. I won't try to convince you
to leave with us, if such is your wish.
The rest is up to you.
Captain! I beg you to reconsider this!
Well then, shall we admire the moon one last time?
Captain!
Please, leave us a memento.
On standby during the whole battle,
positioned 926 km behind the 1st Mobile Fleet
is the main body of Midway invasion fleet.
With it, on-board his flagship Yamato,
the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet,
responsible for all the fleet operations.
Upon hearing the news
of Hiryu being considered unrecoverable,
he had called off the operation altogether.
Issue the order for scuttling Akagi.
Thus, Akagi, once a symbol
of the Japanese naval victories,
had been scuttled by a friendly torpedo attack.
Battle of Midway.
Losses on the Japanese side:
Enterprise
Hornet
Hiryu scuttled                                       Yorktown
Soryu
Kaga              Hiryu
Akagi
Soryu sunk
Akagi scuttled
Kaga sunk
4 aircraft carriers, one heavy cruiser,
322 carrier-based aircraft.
Personnel - 3500 men.
American side casualties:
one aircraft carrier, one destroyer,
150 aircraft total.
Personnel: 307 men.
From this day on,
the offensive initiative over the Pacific Ocean
changed hands from Japanese to American.
Time is 5 a.m.
It was finally time for destroyer Kazagumo
to bid her final farewell to Hiryu.
We're linking up with the main forces!
Hiryu is still not sunk!
The enemy is coming.
Shouldn't we see to it?
To respect Hiryu captain's wish!
The fighting was over. The Japanese fleet retreated,
while leaving behind a trail of flotsam.
However, even amidst that,
Hiryu's tenacity kept shining.
A commanding officer,
who never lost sight of his mission and objectives
and stayed invariably master of himself
through lows
inspired his subordinates
to act fearlessly and unleash their full potential.
Because it's a quality
universally commended
both among winners and losers,
both among the enemy and the friend.
The Japanese infantry,
under the cover of a naval battle,
during sunrise in Yamagata,
landed on the Malay Peninsula.
The charge towards the article of English Pride,
the impregnable fortress of Singapore, started.
The tank corps and bicycle battalions
began to advance, one fierce battle
after another.
Next week's Decision:
Episode 4:
The Malayan campaign Blitzkrieg
The onset of the Malayan campaign Blitzkrieg.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2