Special Drama Episode 1
Everyday Life of Fantasian
Encoding: R-Raws
Script:
Yasunori Ide
(Dessan Doll)
Translation, TS:
Perevodildo
Digital Work:
Koji Tanaka
(Dome)
Editing:
Paul Geromini
Cast:
Madoka
Mariko Kouda
Hekiru Shiina
Pastel
Quality check:
MartyMcflies, imatu
Production:
Dome Co., Ltd.
So yeah, that’s basically what happened.
I see...
Really, so that baby with the bib
wasn’t your secret child, Pastel?
What a relief.
Of course not, Madoka!
I’m still in middle school, come on.
Sorry, sorry.
It’s just, when that kid said
“mama,” I totally thought...
Yeah, if you think about it, there’s no way.
I mean, you don’t even have a boyfriend.
Well… yeah.
Shimmering stardust pavement
I’ve already decided on it, though.
On what?
My future baby’s name.
It's gotta be a good name, doesn't it?
A blue wave leading me to you
Y-Yeah... Wow, you’ve actually
thought that far ahead, Madoka?
Yeah, I don’t want to panic when the time comes.
Everlasting twinkling distance
But first, you need to find a wonderful guy.
Huh?
Moonlight and sea breeze brush against my hair
Same goes for both of us, right?
Come now, Fantasian, teach me the ways of love
Well, I should get going.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
SHUT
Huh?
What’s that?
Hey, before I spread my wings, receive this legend from me
A crustacean... of some sort?
Looks like some rare species of crab.
Did Pastel forget this?
Oh no, I left it on purpose!
Go on, pick it up and take a look.
Hmm… I’ve never seen anything like this before.
I wonder what it tastes like…
Geez, Madoka...
Even if it was a misunderstanding, you definitely
didn't have to spread those rumors around school
that I had a child during my time on Venus…
Yeah… it's Pastel's fault for forgetting them here. I'm not doing anything wrong!
A wandering labyrinth of fantasy
POP
No! It's all your fault. Now then,
enjoy this little taste of a Venusian threat!
Even hesitation turns into courage
Even hesitation
Ah! I even feel kinda rude doing this.
A dreaming...
Here goes…
Oh...
She ate it!
PASTEL'S FIST
My god, was that good!
This is amazing! What is this?!
What is this?! It’s so good!
No way…
What is Madoka, really...