Special Drama Episode 2
Everyday Life of Fantasian
Episode 365
Encoding: R-Raws
Script:
Yasunori Ide
(Dessan Doll)
Translation, TS:
Perevodildo
Digital Work:
Koji Tanaka
(Dome)
Editing:
Paul Geromini
Cast:
Madoka
Mariko Kouda
Hekiru Shiina
Pastel
Quality check:
MartyMcflies, imatu
Production:
Dome Co., Ltd.
Ugh... it’s hot... so hot!
Why is it like this every single day?
This heat just keeps coming
whether we want it or not...
Yeah, that's true...
But complaining about the heat
won’t change anything.
I mean, yeah, but that’s kind of killing the mood.
Isn’t there some way to cool down? Like something
that sends chills all the way down your spine.
Huh? Even if you say that...
Like when you eat one of Madoka’s cookies,
something that intense.
Ah... Madoka! I-I was joking!
A joke! Come on, laugh! Okay?
N-No, that’s not a “haha, funny” face at all!
Sorry!
I’m sorry, Madoka! It was my fault!
Welcome!
Here. The usual, right?
Here you go.
M-Madoka, what are you trying to do here?
Huh?
I-I mean, w-why are
you putting the coffee there...
What’s wrong, Pastel...?
Don’t scream like that,
you’re bothering the other customers.
I’m going home...
See you...
DAN
DANGLE
Gee, so clamorous.
Sorry for the disturbance.
What on Earth is Madoka, really?