WinBee
TwinBee
GwinBee
WinBee
TwinBee
GwinBee
Madoka
TwinBee
Episode 0
WinBee's 1/8 Panic
TwinBee
This city, glittering with memories, casts a blue shadow
A déjà vu just like in my dream is revived at that moment
Soaring high towards the future, my heart pushes forward
Who will illuminate the darkness? Tell me
Close your eyes now
and a wonderful journey to a distant, foreign land begins
Open the door to your heart
and we'll carry on to the endless, eternal city of Soltias
Carry on!
The Miss Donburi Contest
finally starts tomorrow, Pastel.
But I don't think I can win!
I should probably just withdraw.
How can you say that, Pastel?! Are you going to
let all that effort you’ve poured into this go to waste?
Can't you hear the passionate cries
of encouragement coming from your fans?
L-Light...?
Since when do you talk like that?!
Anyway, Pastel, there's something
I want you to test for me.
My newest creation!
I just baked my first batch.
If you like it, I might add it to the menu.
They look delicious! I'll try one.
Not so fast!
TwinBee, how many
calories does this cookie have?
Give me just a sec...
Um, it should bee 20 calories!
Okay. Then you can eat half of it, Pastel.
Huh? I can't even enjoy one measly cookie?!
They look so good though...
Well then, I'll give half to WinBee.
Good idea!
Here.
How is it, Pastel?
It's really good!
It’s like... eating tokoroten in Santa Monica.
Weirdly unique, you know?
Well, I'll be...
Ma-Madoka...?
W-We'll be leaving now, okay?
And we're off! We'll do our running
and crawling training all the way to the lab!
Huh? Again?
No complaining! Let's go!
Hey, why're you so
impatient to get there, anyway?
Gulp!
Huh? When did everybody leave? How rude.
Hey, Madoka, do you know where
that potion I made earlier ran off to?
No, I don't!
I bet it's some kind of
weird creation again anyway!
You sure are a harsh granddaughter.
All right! It's perfect!
What a genius of a scientist I am!
Hey, ZakoBee, how're
the repairs going over there?
It'll still take a while.
Are you dumb?! What are you even doing down there?
It must be ready by tomorrow's contest!
Yeah, I get it.
Sheesh...
One of these days, I'm replacing them.
Still, she completely fell for my trick.
Girls are just like that, after all.
AUDITION FORM
PASTEL
And on top of that,
I get TwinBee as a bonus prize!
AUDITION FORM
PASTEL
KYAAA
That's most unusual.
How did this happen?
Look how tiny they've gotten!
Wait a minute... W-We're screwed!
In this condition, there's no way
she'll be able to be in the contest!
Light! Instead of worrying about the contest,
can't you worry about me for once?!
That's right! You're so insensitive!
Sorry, sorry.
Yes? Hello?
Ah, Light? It's me.
Oh, Madoka?
Is something the matter?
S-Say, isn't something strange happening?
Strange how?
Well, maybe...
like a severe change in someone's body?
Doctor! Hurry up and
change us back to normal already!
Right, sorry about all this. I can easily
change you back with this magnifying ray gun.
Never mind the explanations,
just hurry up and do it!
B-Be patient, dear.
This gun runs on bell-power.
Oh, sorry, but could you get me a bell?
Geez, you're hopeless.
What? Something the matter?
Doc! The clouds!
The clouds?
What is it about the clouds, Light?
The clouds are gone!
Now, that's not good... Huh?
There's not a single cloud within a 60 km radius...
No, wait! That's where the clouds are gathering.
What was that?
It looked like an old castle to me,
but what's a thing like that doing up there?
Spirit Castle.
It might be the Legendary Spirit Castle.
Spirit Castle?!
What's that? Is it like an air-island?
The truth is that our Donburi Archipelago
used to have one more island in it.
Though it was last seen 800 years ago.
And on that island lived a queen
who governed the entire archipelago.
But that queen couldn't be satisfied until she
was prettier than and high above everyone else.
She ended up building her own castle
that floated in the sky.
But why is she
hoarding all of our clouds now?
Well, even I don't know the answer to that.
Regardless, unless we get some bells,
we can't change Pastel back!
And if we can't change her back,
then that also means she can't be in the contest!
Thanks for the timely explanation!
You're welcome!
Let's go, Pastel! I swear I'll get you
back to normal in no time!
Brother...
Okay, TwinBee Team!
Hurry to the Spirit Castle!
Yes, sir!
We have no more than three hours
until the contest starts.
Then we'll have to get it done before that.
Look at you talking beeg as usual!
What did you...
Stop! Now's not the time for bickering.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that the Spirit Castle?
If we continue on this course, we'll get intercepted by an anti-aircraft beam like Fork Eye.
Well, even so, we don't exactly have
a better strategy for sneaking inside.
Huh? Can't you think of anything?
Fine. I'll leave it to you.
There's the beam!
I said the beam is trying to shoot us down now!
Yeah, figures!
They dodged it?! Their agility is far
greater than that of the previous invaders.
What are they?
Why are they closing in on us?!
Don't fuss. I shall ask them for you.
What the...?
They suddenly stopped shooting.
It's huge!
All right...
Let's try goin' in through there!
Alert! Energy surge detected ahead!
What's the beeg idea?!
You're not fighting fair!
Who are you? Why are you trying
to invade Queen Juliana's castle?
We could ask the same of you!
Why are you hogging all the bell clouds to yourself?
Oh, dear. You want some of our bell clouds?
But they are very important to the queen!
You shall be punished!
Light? Light!
Why aren't you flying up to fight back?
Oh, yeah!
Don't mind if I do!
There you go!
Oh my...
We did it!
Easy-peasy!
That girl still hasn't shown up?
I certainly hope I didn't forget anything.
No wait! Stop! Let me explain myself!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What's that?
I don't really know what it is,
but it sure is pretty!
Ah! Look at that! So many bells!
Yay! Bells! We got the bells!
Aye!
TwinBee, how much time do we have left?
Forty more minutes.
Then I guess we'd better leave.
Even if we still have no idea what's going on here.
Good idea.
Ah, wait for me.
Ah! Bells! The bells!
Hey! What's the big idea, scaring us like that?!
GwinBee!
D-Damn, now you're getting it!
Hold up! Why did you kick me out?
Explain yourself!
If you wanna know that badly, I'll show you!
Off you go!
POP
We did it!
How many times do I have to tell you
not to use me as a projectile?!
Guess we might as well go this way...
The other route is blocked off anyway.
Ah, come to think of it, we left GwinBee beehind.
GwinBee, where are you now?
We're back at the glowing room...
I see. Well, catch up with us soon, okay?
You'd better beelieve it.
Ow!
What's with this grandma's corpse?!
Is this the queen we've been running around here for?
Hey, Light! Look at that!
Whoa! She's hot!
And who might you children be?
What happened to my soldiers?
Soldiers? You mean that
balloon guy and that lightning guy?
Do you mean to say
you defeated Raijin and Fujin?
I see. Well, it seems you’ve bought me
some time to prepare for my resurrection.
Oh, come on... I don't really get
what you're talking about.
I am Queen Juliana.
My beauty is eternal.
However, the power of bell clouds
is required to maintain my beauty.
To that end, I awaken once
every 400 years to summon the clouds
and use up all of that bell power
to preserve my beauty.
But for me, it's a major problem!
Put the clouds back the way they were!
Why should I? Tell me, Bean Girl.
B-Bean Girl?
Don't you have any sympathy?!
Oh, don't you worry about her!
Just ignore this little inconv—
Ow-ow-ow!
I've finished replenishing my beauty.
It's best that you leave this island at once
since I'm going back to sleep now.
Finished replenishing it? So then...
Fear not. The bell clouds shall return to the skies of Donburi in good time.
Phew! That's a relief.
So I guess I'll be able to change back eventually.
Light, what time is it now?
Huh?! It's this late already?
Miss Donburi is gonna start any minute!
What? Oh, no!
Miss Donburi?
Whoa! What's happening?!
Miss Donburi—that is me!
I shall not tolerate that anyone else in the
world be declared more beautiful than I!
WAAAH
Go forth! To the Miss Donburi Contest venue!
That dirty hag... I'll get ya
for treating us like that! Let's go!
Damn right!
Whew... those are tough!
Okay, next!
W-What the...?!
Ugh! So arrogant!
How many times do I have to smash you?!
Ah, here it comes.
Ah, another one!
And you. And you. And you!
This is never-ending.
Fine, then it's carpet bombing time!
Light! Make it stop!
Huh?! What?! I can't hear you!
What's going on?!
Where the hell is Mint when we need him?!
Mint! Where are you?!
Mint! Mint! Everyone's calling on you.
We'd better bee going!
Oh, what'll I do with you?
Darn it, I don't have
time to waste fighting these!
I've gotta get Pastel in that contest!
Light... Thanks.
But you don't have to do it anymore.
It's not like I absolutely
have to be in the contest anyway.
You idiot! Don't just give up so easily!
Your dream of becoming
Miss Donburi isn't yours alone!
Sometimes, even Light says nice things, after all.
Light?
Sorry for the wait!
Huh? Where were you all this time?
Inside the Spirit Castle!
If you were inside the castle,
you should've at least sabotaged it, you idiot!
Sorry...
Your Highness, the enemy has multiplied.
What bothersome pests.
Give them a taste of our
Crazy Night attack at full power.
Yes, Your Highness!
Sheesh, to think you were chilling
in the castle while we were fighting! Huh?
What's that?
Mint refused to leave
without it, so I had to take it...
But it certainly is pretty.
Oh, no! They're preparing
for another beam attack!
What the...?
It's not another beam attack?
What? What's going on?
Oh, no, my queen!
The generator is going wild!
Ah! The main coil is gone!
What?!
The energy leak cannot be stopped.
W-What?!
So many, so shiny!
I won't let you decide who Miss Donburi is,
while I, the prettiest woman to ever live, am absent!
All right! We did it!
Now we've got more than enough bells!
Pastel! Pastel, can you hear me?
Yes, I can, Madoka.
The contest has already started!
Huh?! What should we do, Light?
Did you get the bells?
Yes!
Then hurry! Grandpa will
bring the magnifying gun with him!
Hurry!
Light!
Okay! Step on it, TwinBee!
Okay, okay, thank you, thank you.
That was Kumiko with a lovely ponytail.
And now, let us continue
with entry number 15, Pastel!
Pastel? Huh? Pastel? Pastel!
Oh, no, Pastel! She didn't make it in time!
This is all your fault, you know!
Since the participant seems to be absent,
a disqualification is...
Not so fast!
Entry number 15, Pastel!
Where are you, Madoka-chan? Hurry up and change me back!
She's late! Too late!
Master, they've just appeared!
What? Both she and TwinBee? All right...
TwinBee! Over here!
Throw us the bells, quick!
Aye-aye! Get some!
Now, how do I aim this thing?
Wow! I can see her perfectly!
Grandpa! Just do it already!
No! No! Seriously, stop it!
10 points, 9 points,
9 points, 9 points, and 10 points!
Entry number 13 has
received a sudden surge of points!
I suspected something like this might happen,
so I placed another grabber!
What a genius of a scientist I am!
So cruel! No!
Geez, Grandpa, can't you aim better?!
Let me help.
Try aiming a little more to the right.
Ah! You idiot!
No! Please!
Oh! This time, it's number 14, Kumiko!
10 points, 9 points,
10 points, 10 points, 9 points!
Master.
Never mind me. I never expected it
to work out anyway. That's the kind of role I play.
We didn't even have any budget to speak of this time.
The sky is beautiful in itself, they say.
Mesmerizing...
Now I can never get married!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Oh, no! If I get magnified too,
the same thing will happen to me!
Madoka! It's your fault I missed!
Just sit there and don't interfere!
No! Stop it! Don't shoot me!
No!
No looking!
10 points, 10 points, 10 points, 10 points, 10 points!
An absolute perfect score!
The winner of this year's Miss Donburi Contest
is entry number 15, Pastel! Congratulations!
Yippee!
All right! Now that motorcycle is mine!
Light, what's that about a motorcycle?
Yeah, well, you see, if you're chosen as Miss Donburi,
you get a Yamasaki Gaia 400 as a bonus prize!
And since you can't ride motorcycles,
you'll let me have it, right?
I see... So that's what this all was about?
So I was right... your excitement about
this contest was suspicious, after all...
Ah? P-Pastel? I'm sure
we can work this out with words.
Here you go! Put something on.
We don't want you catching a cold, do we? Right?
Let's see how much you enjoy being big!
No! Stop! Ouch...
Give that to me!
No! W-Wait... Whoa!
Damn it, he's too nimble.
Let's crank this thing up!
How dare you do that to my bike, Pastel?!
Fire!
Oh?
M-Miss... Donburi...
Th-That's the main coil of the generator...
Yes, here you go.
He's saying that you can have
this diadem because you're so pretty.
You're such a nice boy, Mint.
When you grow up,
the ladies will all bee crazy about you.
Starring: TwinBee—Mayumi Tanaka.
Pastel! Did everyone enjoy it?
Hekiru Shiina.
WinBee—Kumiko Nishihara.
Mint and GwinBee—Miki Ito.
Dr. Cinnamon—Kazumi Tanaka.
Madoka—Mariko Kouda.
I hate it when you whine
Dr. Mardock—Jouji Yanami.
I like you when you're having fun outside
Dr. Warumon—Yukimasa Kishino.
You act tough in this city to the rhythm of rap
You're such a monkey for it, pathetic
ZakoBee and others—Yuusuke Numata.
Oh, yes, Queen Juliana—Youko Kawanami.
Rappy rapper party
Shakin' shakin' party
Whoosh-whoosh! Fujin—Hirohiko Kakegawa.
I gotta work hard!
Zap! Raijin—Atsushi Kisaichi.
Rappy rapper party
There's another party tomorrow afternoon
The announcer robot
was Takahiro Yoshimizu.
I better start writing my schedule down
Naoko—Yuko Sumitomo.
Rappy rapper party
When I get home tonight, my body
Kumiko—Mariko Onodera.
I gotta polish my body until it shines
Light—Kappei Yamaguchi!
That should be all!
Yes!
Rappy rapper party
Shakin' shakin' party
Tarastattatarattaratta
I hate it when you whine
I like you when you're having fun outside
You act tough in this city to the rhythm of rap
You're such a monkey for it, pathetic
Rappy rapper party
Shakin' shakin' party
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Rappy rapper party
Shakin' shakin' party
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Encoding
Translation check / Typesetting
Original translation
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Random Masters
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
And the password is?
Bee!