Special Drama Episode 3
Everyday Life of Fantasian
Final Episode
Encoding: R-Raws
Script:
Yasunori Ide
(Dessan Doll)
Translation, TS:
Perevodildo
Digital Work:
Koji Tanaka
(Dome)
Editing:
Paul Geromini
Cast:
Madoka
Mariko Kouda
Hekiru Shiina
Pastel
Quality check:
MartyMcflies, imatu
Production:
Dome Co., Ltd.
Yeah, yeah, exactly!
Oh right, Pastel! Remember how you
were acting kinda funny the other day?
Hm?
Like climbing onto the train luggage rack
or curling up on Light’s lap.
Also when you ate Ms. Apple's lunch and got totally
obsessed with the rhythmic gymnastics ribbon.
So you mean when I switched bodies with that cat?
But honestly, I kind of liked that.
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, you know... when you ate
all my cookies like they were delicious.
Eh?!
EH?!
You didn’t even use your hands,
you just went at them nonstop!
D-Did I, really?
Come on, don’t play dumb, Pastel.
It's you I'm talking about!
R-Right...
Yeah, but that wasn’t me!
That was the cat!
My, how you ate them... so moving!
She’s seriously got the wrong idea… this is bad…
is this turning into something worse?
Here!
Cookies!
Whoa! You scared me!
Wow, yelling like that...
are you that happy?
Go on, Pastel, don’t hold back!
Dig in!
Help! WinBee! Mint! Light!
W-What a way to go...