TwinBee Paradise Special
Tulip Beach Stories
Take that!
Okay!
Here we go!
I got it!
Aw, thanks for wasting my brilliant play!
Oh, geez. I'm sorry, 'kay?
Mint, GwinBee, won't you play beach volleyball with us?
Huh? What?
He says don't trample all over that area
because it's the planned site for the palace.
Ah, I see. Sorry.
Mint, can I see it when it's finished?
Ah, I can't take this anymore! I'm so bored!
Watching after kids bores me to death!
If I’d known it would turn out like this, I’d have
been better off having a beer at the beachside café.
How about it? Won't you have one with me, Cinnamon?
Oh? Guess I've got no choice.
Hey, GwinBee! If anyone asks,
we went to that bar over there!
I gotcha!
Man, it's hot...
Master, one curry and one ramen, please!
Oh, ZakoBee! The two orders of corn are done,
so carry them out to the customers for me.
Gotcha!
Excuse me, can we have
some beer and boiled peas?
Coming up!
Hey, there was a big sale at that store yesterday! I hear they're going out of business.
Welcome! Welcome!
Oh, you're a cutie.
What are you selling?
Welcome.
I'm selling Madoka’s Special Cookies.
Then I'll take a bag.
Here you go!
Thanks for your purchase.
I'll try one right away.
Hey, I hear there's a cookie stand around here that's to die for!
To die for?
It sounds like it's totally life-changing!
Wanna go with me and try it out?
Yeah, let's go.
Ah! Wait for me!
Huh? Ms. Apple?
Oh? It's you, White!
You came to the beach too?
Light and the others are over there.
Huh? Really? Well then, bye.
Wait, don’t go, White.
Your timing is perfect. I'm sorry,
but could you rub sun oil into my back?
O-Okay...
This Rainbow Color brand is really good!
There's not much left, so use all of it, okay?
Oh, geez! Why can't you ever
think of anyone other than yourself?
Couldn't you get me a drink too?
Why should I care? Get one yourself.
Geez, you're killing me!
Huh?
By the way, where are the doctors?
Oh, the doctors said
they would bee at the beach café.
Don’t tell me they’re
drinking this early in the day...
Oh man, that was great!
Hey, we'd like another beer!
Bring more beer!
Right-o. Let's explore the grandeur
of nature and the mysteries of life.
Whoa! I found plenty of mysteries already!
So you’re here too?
Hey, Headband.
I challenge you to a game of beach volleyball.
Come on. Get out in the sun!
Uh, sorry, but I'm really busy now.
If you absolutely have to,
you can play with the TwinBees.
Will you do it, TwinBees?
I don't mind at all!
Me too!
All right, I'm definitely going to drag
you out onto the court. Let's go, sis!
Yeah!
What’s this?
Are you going to do it in your Black TwinBees?
Yes, of course.
It's a no-brainer! No way we can compete
with you unless we're on the same scale.
Anything's fine with us!
Let's get started already!
Ready when you are!
Now then, guess I'll put on
some sun oil and get a great tan!
Ta-dah! Meet my imported
premium-quality suntan oil, Venus!
Ever since I saw an ad for it
in last month’s issue of Heart Teen,
I just couldn’t hold back
the part of me that craves beauty.
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
FOR HER,
WHO WANTS TO BE THE PRETTIEST GIRL
THIS SUMMER
So despite my abject financial situation,
I've dipped deep into my secret stash
to finally get this luxury oil—Venus!
If I rub this on my flawless skin, I can become
the Summer Princess of this Tulip Beach!
Or maybe my perfect tan will win me a pageant,
or I'll become a sexy little mermaid?
"MISS DONBURI ISLAND" CONTEST
Are you stupid?
And... got it!
Put plenty on, okay?
My oil!
Thanks for your purchase.
Please form a line.
Don't worry, there's plenty to go around!
There, there, don't be such a wimp.
If you're really a man,
then you must have more guts than that.
If I miss and strike the bone, don't blame me!
D-Doctor Peach, did you see my bottle
of expensive sun oil fly anywhere around here?
Oil?
Water...
Water!
Ah! That!
What the hell is this?
Bring another one!
Hey, part-timer Warumon!
Hurry up and give us another beer!
Bastards! How much more of this crap do you think
I’m gonna take just because you’re customers?!
Oh dear... What's wrong?
Did we make you mad?
Hey, is the manager here? Manager!
I think your new kitchen hand here
has an attitude problem!
PATIENCE
What?! I dare you to say that again!
Oil... My oil...
Oh?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Bee!
Huh? I mean, it's flattering, of course...
Bee! I didn't get a chance to use even a drop
of this oil I just bought! My imported premium sun oil!
Rainbow Color sun oil? Imported?
Rainbow Color? Lemme see that.
Rainbow Color?
Ah! This isn't my sun oil!
Huh? But then, where is mine?
That's right! It might've gotten swapped
with Ms. Apple’s oil!
Not all hope is lost!
Teacher! Ms. Apple!
White, could you check if that oil is mine?
Um...
Venus?
Huh?
Oh, she's right! This isn't my oil.
Huh? Pastel?
Pastel!
You still wanna continue?
Whaddaya sayin'?
Everything before this was practice!
TWINBEE, WINBEE, SEEDS, SALUTE,
TwinBee, WinBee, Seeds, Salute.
Woo-hoo! The great outdoors is something else!
LIGHT,
Light, Madoka, Dr. Peach, Dr. Cinnamon,
Dr. Mardock, Dr. Warumon, Ms. Apple, White…
LIGHT,
MADOKA, DR. PEACH,
DR. CINNAMON, DR. MARDOCK, DR. WARUMON,
MS. APPLE, WHITE,
YOU IDIOTS!
you idiots!
Awesome! This taste is unparalleled.
LIGHT, MADOKA, DR. PEACH, DR. CINNAMON, DR. MARDOCK, DR. WARUMON, MS. APPLE, WHITE, YOU IDIOTS!
Seeds, let's try the Z-Attack next.
Yeah!
LIGHT, MADOKA, DR. PEACH, DR. CINNAMON, DR. MARDOCK, DR. WARUMON, MS. APPLE, WHITE, YOU IDIOTS!
Mint, how much bigger
are you gonna bee building it?
LIGHT, MADOKA, DR. PEACH, DR. CINNAMON, DR. MARDOCK, DR. WARUMON, MS. APPLE, WHITE, YOU IDIOTS!
The password is Bee!
It won't start if you just wait
What I want to do is...
No matter what comes my way, I won't give up!
The password is Bee!
Don't cry about yesterday anymore
Be brave and Bee!
You can make a miracle happen
The blue sky is yours!
Encoding
Translation / ts
Editing
R-Raws
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini, imatu,
MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)