Worker-066.
How's it look?
Have they been wiped out?
Worker-066!
What's the status on squad 14275?
I don't know.
They should've been
back 20 hours ago.
You're to return to Town.
Worker-066!
Do you read me, Red?!
Just a little longer...
I want to wait a little longer...
How does it look, Cricket?
No good, there's no sign of them. Looks like they've all been wiped out.
What do we do, Red? No matter how much we search, if we don't get any respon—
What is it?
Did you get one?!
Just one man.
Can you make out his ID number?
TFA-404953. Class C.
It's Grey!
Town
I'm sorry!
You dumbass!
Saying you're sorry don't cut it
when you bump into a Trooper!
We put our lives on the line!
We're better'n you People!
PEC 300th Battalion, Squad 16422.
Squad Commander: TNO-112004-C, Hawk.
TNC-095042-F, Nova.
TNR-813155-D, Sky.
TPB-009717-D, Leo.
TPA-268379-E, Tures.
TNN-436747-D, Tim.
Squad 16422 verified.
Request for replacement personnel granted.
TFA-404953-C, Grey: confirmed.
Over. Squad 16422, general orders: combat in Area 807, commencing twelve hours from present.
These orders will be
rescinded after 720 hours,
or upon complete destruction
of the squad. Over.
Any questions?
Grey? You mean 'the' Grey?
Grey Death, huh?
He jumped from F to C
in only thirteen operations.
Nine out of those thirteen, his squad was totally wiped. Except for him, Grey.
Make that ten.
Grey just returned from
his 14th operation.
He was the only survivor
this time, too?
I requested two replacements.
Granted he's the Class C
Grey Death and all...
We can't spare even a single man.
And you will find that this one can
do the work of five class E troopers.
So, Komon Rope...
Where do we find this Mr. Death?
At the Factory, probably.
Where you headed this time, Grey?
Area 807.
Western USA, huh?
How about you, Red?
Africa, S44.
By the way, how many more credits
do you need to reach Class B?
680.
That means you made
290 on this last one?
I don't want to die, that's all.
If you want to survive,
you kill all your enemies.
You're the one who
taught me that, Red.
Did I really?
Anyway, once you make Class B,
why not become an Inspector like me?
It takes longer to make Class A this way,
but you don't have to worry about dying.
All you do is drop off Troopers in a demilitarized zone and then wait for them to come back.
An Inspector, huh?
Hey!
Bring it back in one
piece this time, Grey.
It's a pain in the ass
to rebuild her just for you!
Take it up with the enemy troops.
See you around, Red.
Think about what I said, Grey!
She's dead.
Area
One, two, three, four, five, six...
17 self-propelled guns,
1 light tank, and 3 fuel trucks.
So 21 units?
If we wipe 'em out,
we'd all go up a rank for sure!
And who's gonna do that?
Who else? Us!
Only, it might be a better idea to stay alive.
I'd hate to get aced as soon as I joined you.
Oh, but who says that we're going to die?
Their tank could never catch your jeep.
Grey, draw them in to within 1200 meters,
then I'll be able to destroy them. No maybes.
Their self-propelled artillery can't pierce this
tank's armor unless it gets up to 800 meters.
And who's going to drive
the jeep as a decoy?
It's your jeep, isn't it?
It's my life, too.
How'd you get the name, "Death"?
You're just chickenshit.
Who's to say we can't use
your bike as the decoy?
Hawk! The enemy's
sent up a Bee!
Battle stations, people!
Must be nice to have
those mini-trackers!
Sky! Grey! Come at 'em from
both sides to break them up!
Break right, Grey! I'll go left!
Where are you going, Grey?
Are you deserting?!
Damn it! You bastard!
Once I'm done with these guys...
...your ass is mine!
Left, Tim! Rotate left!
Gotcha! Howdya like that?!
Sky's down!
There's no end to these bastards! Hawk,
if they get any closer, we're in serious trouble!
What am I supposed to do about it?!
They're faster than we are!
Hawk! One of them
got behind us!
Nice save!
Get off your asses
and give me some cover!
Grey!
We took out 12 men on those
4 self-propelled guns,
so that works out to 2.4 men each.
That's 60 credits.
Add in the 0.7 men I have
left over from my last Fight...
That comes to 90 credits! 90!
I'm not too far from
moving up a class myself.
At this rate, I'll bounce to Class A
in a hop, skip and a jump!
I know what you mean!
Once I'm a Citizen, I'm really gonna live it up!
Otherwise, what's the point
of risking our lives out here?
You're amazing...
You took out 5 SPGs and 15 men!
That's 450 credits!
Is that flashy helmet of yours
a keepsake from somebody?
So?
Tim! Sky's not even cold yet,
and you're after Grey already?
When you die, that's goodbye.
And my life still goes on. Right, Grey?
Their Bee is still functional.
You're counting your chickens
a little early, don't you think?
Let me ask you something, Grey.
Why'd you disobey my order?
I ignore a stupid order when I hear one.
It helps me stay alive.
Really? So you only obey it
when you like it?
Hawk's our commander!
Even so, we're both Class C.
Which means I don't have to jump when you bark.
Does that answer
your question, Hawk?
Pretty much.
Glad to hear it.
Bad news.
Bee!
They're here!
Grey! Head out in your jeep!
We'll cover you!
Okay.
Bingo! With those fuel trucks
out of the picture, it'll all be over!
Tures! Hang on, Tures!
What about Hawk and Tim?
It was a direct hit.
What about the enemy?
Their command vehicle
and two SPGs got away.
Tures, Please! Say something!
Please! Tures!
Nova. Stand aside.
Grey?
She doesn't need
to suffer any more.
They don't pay us for suffering.
She was still alive!
What're you doing?!
Corpses don't need guns.
Take it.
Can you walk, Leo?
Yeah, I'll manage.
Okay, let's move out.
Wait a minute!
We can't just leave her lying here!
I'm not in a rush to turn into a corpse
myself while burying another one.
Nova, Grey's right.
There's still enemy lurking about.
We gotta hurry and leave.
Death...
Grey, now I understand how you managed
to make Class C after just 13 operations.
You ignored your commander's
orders and betrayed your own people.
You waited it out in safety just
to waltz in and rack up the credits!
You're really nothing
more than a coward!
Drop it, Nova!
We're still alive because of Grey.
You know I'm right.
Don't take it personally, Grey.
Nova's just worked up because
Tures died the way she did.
That's okay, Leo.
Nova's right.
I'm a coward.
Is your eye bothering you?
I'll be okay. We have to soldier on for 210 more hours until our combat orders are lifted.
How far is it to
the rendezvous point?
About 1000 klicks from here. How will we advance 100 klicks a day without vehicles?
That, and the enemy's still got
three operational vehicles left.
We'll capture them.
How? We don't even
know where they are!
Wait, do you plan
to use their Bee...
Yep. We're gonna use this
to ask 'em out on a date.
How about the ruins of
the old town up ahead, Grey?
Sounds good.
What's wrong, Leo?
Can you make it?
It's okay. I'm fine.
You're bleeding again.
You can rest and
sit things through.
No, they have three tanks.
You two will definitely need a hand with it.
I suppose. One's yours, then.
Sure.
Are you really okay?
Don't worry about me, Nova.
I won't die that easily.
Look, that is our missing bee!
How'd it wind up here?
Somebody's up there!
Hey! Over here!
There you go!
Not so fast!
Leo?
Leo!
Grey, are you hit?
Yeah, I got winged.
I'm sorry, this was all my fault.
It's Leo you should be thanking.
I'd like to bury him,
but there's probably not much left to bury.
Scavengers.
You mean the Resistance?
That underground organization?
Yeah.
Most of 'em are
Troopers who deserted.
Are they going to attack?
No, they don't get any supplies, so they're
more interested in salvaging the battlefield.
Still, better not to point
our guns at them.
Get in and start the engine!
Okay!
Interval
Respite
TFA-404953-C: Grey.
Battle results: 14 vehicles destroyed.
21 troopers killed.
Credits: 630.
Plus 50 Fight Money credits.
Advancement to Class B approved.
TNC-095042-F: Nova.
Battle results: 6 troopers.
Credits: 180.
Plus 50 Fight Money credits.
Advancement to Class E approved.
Something's fishy with those totals.
Yeah.
Hold it! The numbers don't add up!
What part of it do
you find unsatisfactory?
I took out nine
Troopers, not six!
And I killed 45 of them, not 21!
Ah, so you're
counting with "dolls".
Dolls? They were using androids?
Correct. Or are you implying that the attack sensors in your clothing are malfunctioning?
If that's true,
that was one well-equipped squad.
What town were they from?
Town 15.
Why do you want to know?
No reason.
Good day, Grey, Nova.
Hey, Sure.
Congratulations on your advancement.
Here is your class B card.
And here is your class E card.
Thanks.
Grey, did you come to a decision
about inspectorship?
You may apply right
now if you wish.
I'm sorry, I need a bit more
time to think about it.
Very well. I will be waiting.
Please enjoy your respite.
Thanks, Sure.
I really don't like that Sure.
For a doll, it's got a real attitude problem.
And you! Showing courtesy to a machine like her! You look stupid!
What, are you jealous?
Get real! Why would I
be jealous of a stupid doll?
So tell me... Why don't you
want to become an Inspector?
You could reach Class A in five
years without having to fight!
You could qualify for Citizenship
without having to risk your life!
Five years is a long time.
Anyway, it really stinks
about all those dolls, huh?
Town 15...
Three missions ago,
we were fighting a Town
that didn't even have any tanks...
Oh? Some Towns are poor, I guess.
Really? That's what I don't get.
Every Town has a Little Mama
that runs it, right?
So how can there be so much disparity? Factory production capacity shouldn't be much different.
I wouldn't know.
Come on, let's forget
about the fighting, okay?
We're at my place, remember?
What are you staring at, anyway?
Out past River Seven.
River Seven?
Oh, the slums, you mean?
My apartment's over there.
What? Why?!
With all the credits you make,
why do you live in
a place like that?
There's a lifestyle that goes
with being a Trooper.
How can you bear
to surround yourself
with all those apathetic, timid,
and gloomy People, who only earn
a few nickels a day, eat and sleep?
D-Did Troopers do it?
What if they did, Grey?
Would you make them pay?
We, the Troopers, get paid handsomely
because we have the drive to be Citizens,
unlike all those People
without a goal in life.
We're given these brief respites to heal our wounds
and work up the energy to go back into battle again.
That's what credits are for!
Come on, Grey.
Go take a shower, okay?
I'm sick of it!
I'm sick of living in fear
every day of my life!
our own Troopers,
and of working all day
for a couple of nickels.
What brought that on?
If you become a Citizen,
you're guaranteed food and a place to live.
You don't have fear
enemy attacks, either.
It's not easy to become a Citizen...
When you're a Trooper,
you get 50 credits per mission!
Plus 30 for each enemy you ice!
You start out at Class F and go up
a class each time you make 1000 credits.
If you make 5000 credits and advance to Class A,
you can earn the right for Citizenship!
Lips!
Forget about it, Lips.
That's only if you survive.
They say only 0.3% live long enough
to make it to Class A.
It's still better than this!
Better that than rotting here.
Hey, Grey, do you want something to eat? I made breakfast.
Nova, have you ever seen one?
Seen what?
Somebody who's become a Citizen.
No. I don't even know where the City is.
Still, I'll get there one day.
This is goodbye, Grey.
Hurry it up, Lips!
We don't have much time!
This is Red, my CO.
He's the commander of Squad-09283.
He's Class C!
Well then. Goodbye, Grey.
Grey here.
Grey! We just got word!
It looks like Red got taken out!
Huh? What?!
What are you going to do, Grey?
Even if you go to the Center, Little Mama won't talk to you if it's not mission-related.
You can't even go see Komon Rope,
for that matter.
Yeah. Judging by that last communication, Mama hasn't even sent out a rescue team.
Grey? You wouldn't...!
Escape
It's gone.
Let's go!
There it is.
A Bird?! Don't tell me you're
going to steal this, Grey!
I'm just gonna borrow it for
a bit to go look for Red.
But these Birds are under
Little Mama's control!
It's a breach of regulations!
Now's your time to backpedal.
Hey, wait! I can't let a wounded
man go off alone, can I?
I'll go find us some bikes.
If you have the time,
pop the lock on the Bird.
"If I have the time?"
Ugh! What is this attitude?
Air Bikes! What a break!
"Pop the lock," he says,
but that's easier said than done.
Isn't it the whole point of the lock—
that it's hard to pop?
This is hopeless.
I wonder what's taking Grey so long?
State your business here.
That airhead!
Nova! Take the Bird out!
Take it out?
But the lock's still...
Forget the lock!
Rip out of it!
Then don't blame me
for what happens to it!
Nova, open your rear!
I'm coming in hard!
Kinky!
Oh boy... I'm gonna need more
than nine lives if l hang around you.
We're not out of the woods yet.
It's Town Defenses!
What are we going to do?
If they catch us fighting Town Defenses...
It's too late to turn back now.
How about this?
Whew! This baby has a beam cannon!
Our town had weapons like that?!
Seems so.
We're looking at more than
a Class demotion for this...
They'll revoke our registration!
We'll be People again.
Can't be helped.
It's no big deal for you! You can just re-enlist and rack up the credits again in no time!
But I'm not Death, you know?!
I owe Red one.
Up until he made Inspector,
I was always in his squad.
He saved my life more
times than I can count.
He taught me everything I know,
from how to shoot to how to survive.
He tried to make up
for failing to save Lips...
Nova!
I just did a little digging
back at the Center.
I was too curious
about that helmet of yours.
The records said that Lips died
while she was under Red's command.
You're not mad,
are you, Grey?
Now entering Area S-44.
What's going on?
Isn't this zone demilitarized?!
How should I know?!
Damn! Time for a crash landing!
Resistance
Underground Organizations
Hey, what're we gonna do?
About what?
You didn't give this
much thought, did you?
We're a good 10,000 klicks
away from Town 303!
Even if Red is there and we do rescue him,
how are we supposed to get back?
Beats me.
Honestly!
And another thing!
You're not done yet?
No! If that really was the Resistance that attacked us, where'd they get a beam cannon?
Beats me.
If they stole it from some Town,
then it's even stranger.
Because we only ever get old tanks
with barely any autopilot, or shabby armored cars.
And what's with the Bird
and these Airbikes?
They may be prototypes,
but they're combat capable.
There! It's Red's worker!
What a mess.
It's been stripped of every
usable piece of hardware.
It probably was Resistance, all right.
It's like a pack of hyenas hit it.
What's a hyena?
My grandpa told me
about them when I was a kid.
They're animals that lived when the oceans were still blue and dozens of times larger than they are now.
He said that when they were done
with their prey, only bones were left.
Back when the oceans were blue?
It's kind of creepy, you know—
to imagine the ocean blue.
Grey?
Cricket!
I hear Grey finally made Class B!
Is he going Inspector?
I suggested it, but you never know.
Well, killing is Death's
stock in trade, after all.
What is it? Bosch?
No, not him. It's...
The enemy?
This is a demilitarized zone!
It's the Resistance! They've got a tank!
Are they going to attack?
Look! They've got a beam cannon!
What? Impossible!
Here it comes!
Let's go.
Nova, try to trace Red's card.
Okay.
3500 to the North-Northwest...
What the?
I'm picking up some kind of weird building!
A torii? That's a shrine!
Shrine?
A religious building.
Some religion over in Asia, I think.
Something strange is going on.
There it is!
What the heck are those
huge Dolls down there?
I don't know what's going on,
but this fight's got nothing to do with us.
Could you help me up?
My legs are messed up.
I don't think so.
I thought you were on our side.
We're not with those monsters, either.
Are you with the Resistance?
Damn, they got through.
Tell us what's going on around here!
You really don't know?
Where are you from?
Town 303.
303? Oh, you're from
out in the sticks, huh?
Out in the sticks?
So, what's a couple of Troopers
from Town 303 doing here?
We're looking for a man
you people took prisoner.
An old mustached guy.
His name's Red.
Red? Oh, right... He said he was
an Inspector from Town 303.
So he's here?!
Red cleared out with our Guji
just before the attack.
Guji?
Our leaders.
They ought to be at Nagoshi by now.
"Nagoshi" is Resistance HQ.
This group is called "Shidara".
Damn, they hit us hard...
Looks like they wiped us out.
I'm Lee.
Grey.
Nova.
Grey?!
You're Town 303's Grey Death?!
I guess.
Wow, you're famous.
What were those big dolls?
Garbs. They're an anti-Resistance
unit out of Town 50.
A Town has equipment like that?
Most double-digit Towns have 'em.
Mei! Fan!
Is that you, Lee?
Am I glad to see you two!
We were on our way to the hangar.
I'm glad you made it, Lee.
Yeah. I helped Death
and it saved my hide.
In bed at night when it's cold
Even the underground levels are trashed.
Incredible base for the Resistance.
I sleeping, yearning for your love
This used to be a Town.
Its Little Mama went on the blink,
and most of the People died.
When their Worker didn't show up,
some of their Troopers hiked back.
I remember all the things I believed in,
And they found Town 424 dead.
They then rebuilt the Town,
led by Shidara, a Class-B Trooper.
So that's where the
group got its name?
When I'm alone
That's right. Shidara became
one of our leaders—the Guji.
Towns are so fragile...
When there's even a little glitch in the Mama,
all the computers in the town go.
That day when we were apart
We're heading to Nagoshi.
Want to tag along?
You're tracking down Red, right?
Thanks.
Ah... It became a dreamy murmur
So many times I'm wishing
What's this?
Looks like it made it through in one piece.
This is our Ohm prototype.
To be reborn
Ohm?
Are you guys driving these?
Yeah. It should work fine
once its battery's charged.
And to meet you again someday, without you
Mei, could you take a look
at the other one?
Okay.
I'll go grab the batteries
out of the damaged ones back there.
Don't overdo it, Fan.
Sure.
I keep leaning again and again
Why was Red taken?
Red went with the Guji voluntarily.
Searching for a familiar voice
Oh, right.
Eat up. I have enough for everybody.
It's a long way to Nagoshi.
I'll take you through time
I'll come for you
Search your shadow
Here, let me help.
Thanks.
So, is Mei your boyfriend?
Unreachable, you're far away
Yeah.
He's a real sweetheart.
I'm carrying his baby.
Really?
Lonely, you're probably crying somewhere
We're going to get married soon.
That's why we're fighting.
For our ideals.
Your ideals?
Right.
So tell me,
are you and Grey a couple too?
So many times, I'm wishing
No way! He's a total jerk.
Many loves...
I'm surprised they've
held together so long...
Is it much farther?
No, it ought to be near here.
Near here?
Yeah. Shidara's waiting
for us at Nagoshi.
Something's wrong. I'm not
picking up Red's tracer signal.
Red's a member of
the Resistance now.
He doesn't need his card anymore.
That's a damn big unit.
Are they with you?
No, they're not Resistance.
What's that?
Nagoshi!
That's Nagoshi!
A flying base?
Damn it! Just as we found it,
it's under attack!
Don't worry.
A unit like that can't even faze Nagoshi.
Just watch.
A Krag Shot.
Someday, Nagoshi's going to wipe out
the Big Mama for all the Towns.
No more Citizens, no more Troopers,
and no more People.
Yeah, our ideal world. Come on!
Hey!
Over here!
There's a special substance
implanted in our arms.
They can pick it up on their sensors.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Down here!
What the hell is going on?!
Ruins
A Doll...
They're coming back!
You shouldn't shoot at those Brians.
If they find out there are survivors,
they'll just send out more Big Dolls.
Who's there?!
A Halfling?
What Resistance group are you with?
Who are you?
Robert J. Dimitri. I'm on my own.
Not a Trooper,
not Resistance.
What's that tune?
A song from my childhood.
Are those "Brians" the same
things we saw earlier?
They're anti-personnel
Big Dolls from Town 18.
Those first dolls you saw
were Chambers, anti-tank units.
That squad they wiped
was from Town 508.
This building won't
last much longer.
There's a tank in the basement.
Can you take me there?
I also have food and water
that I don't really need.
You can have those too.
This is it?
I mean, that tank
had definitely been around.
I've been using it for
about ten years now.
Sorry but could you hook me up?
You use it as your legs?
The shape I'm in,
I can't even make it to the bathroom.
How long were you stuck up there?
About 4000 hours, I suppose.
I got caught up in a crossfire
between two Towns.
You didn't eat or drink?
One of these tanks can last me
a couple of years without any food.
I just need enough
to keep my head going.
Okay, old man, you're hooked up.
Could you put me on
that platform there?
You're real hard to please,
you know that?
That's what I don't like
about you Halflings. Here you go.
I'm not the first
Halfling you've met?
There's Komon Rope,
in charge of Town 303's...
Hey! Come to think of it,
you look a lot like him!
The Brians are back!
No, those aren't Brians.
Okay, get us out of here!
Leave it to me!
Just don't drop my head, okay?
I know, I know!
What're those?
Ohms?
No those aren't Ohms.
They're some of Nagoshi's Kubandas.
Kubandas?
And those?
Gasps, out of Town 7.
Single-digit Towns...
They're out to obliterate Nagoshi.
Nagoshi's gotten too big
as a Resistance group, that's why.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it? The City's Big Mama
thinks the Resistance is necessary.
Big Mama in the City?
Here they come!
Damn, those things are fast!
You got one!
You've got to be kidding!
That's a computer-controlled Total Doll.
Those damn single-digit Towns...
It's a machine!
Look for a pattern!
Once you see the pattern,
you've won!
I don't see any pattern, dammit!
Now!
What was your name?
Grey.
Grey?
Grey Death from Town 303?
That explains everything...
Sounds like you know a lot.
Well, I've lived for
500 years, after all.
Look, about what you said earlier...
Oh? What do you mean?
About Big Mama in the City.
Oh, now I remember.
Big Mama's the master computer
that controls the world.
Master computer?
In other words, each Town's Little Mama
is one of Big Mama's children. You get it now?
You mean Big Mama arranges
all the fighting out in the Areas?
That's right.
And the arms gap?
That too.
That's what you get
for living for 500 years.
I was born when the world
was still overflowing with humanity.
The ocean was blue, with fish in it.
Fish?
Yes, fish. Toy was created
around that time, too.
Toy?
Toy was originally an incredibly advanced computer
that was built for human entertainment.
It came with many games,
and it would play them with you.
Toy evolved in the blink of an eye.
And as it developed into
a self-aware supercomputer,
countless wars were being fought that paralyzed human society.
Eventually, only the computer
and a chosen few survived.
It realized that what little plant life remained won't last another century.
Who are those "chosen few"?
Citizens.
By the time the human population
began to grow again,
Toy, which had already grown to enormous size and stood at the top of all computers,
came to dominate and control humans.
Eventually, we came
to call it Big Mama.
Where will you go from here, Robert?
I don't know. I don't really
have any plans. West, I suppose.
What's to the West?
Everywhere's the same.
Nagoshi's heading west.
We've been tracking it for a long time.
You've been tracking Nagoshi?
You know more,
don't you, old man?
Lips...
Old man, tell me one more thing. What do
the Citizens do in the City? Protect Big Mama?
Go and find that out for yourself.
If you need it, then...
I think you need it too.
S-So, you've guessed?
You knew that each Komon Rope,
every Town's director is a copy of me?
Grey Death... You may actually
be able to destroy Big Mama.
What have you done?
Grey... Look, I...
Grey! They're here!
Nova!
Grey!
Red
After me!
Listen, Grey, when you're running,
keep your center of gravity lower!
Are you scared, Grey?
Even so, you've got to keep fighting.
They day you stop fighting
is the day you die!
You understand me, Grey?
That's the way, Grey!
When killing enemies, show no mercy!
Be a cold, precise machine!
I'm going to make you
into the ultimate
fighting machine!
Finally awake, Grey?
How do you feel?
R-Red!
Grey.
Real fancy outfits they got here.
I guess.
Wh-What the hell is this?
We gave you a Halfling operation.
Halfling? You're telling me
that I'm a half-machine now?
You would've died if we hadn't.
You're now armed
with Nagoshi's latest technology.
Nagoshi?
Right. You're inside Nagoshi,
the Resistance's stronghold.
Nagoshi's now heading for the City.
My friends, the day Nagoshi
will destroy the master computer draws near!
The day when we shall realize
our ideal society is nearly upon us!
For that, we shall exact merciless revenge
on those who revere and worship the City,
its Citizens, and its master computer!
Lala! Lala! Lala!
We fight for our ideals!
For our ideals!
The woman on the stage is Lala,
the goddess of Nagoshi.
She ordered that you be saved
and given our latest technology.
The merciful goddess who spares her enemies
just to keep them as pets, huh?
I said the same thing
when I was brought here.
Which way should I go?
Keep going this way.
We're heading due west.
West, west, west... Are you sure
we'll find Grey if we keep heading west?
Probably, possibly, perhaps, maybe,
Quizás, Quizás, Quizás. Whoops!
Hey! Nova! Stop joking around!
You never give me a straight answer!
If you keep pulling my leg like that,
I'm gonna ditch you!
And anyway, you're heavy!
All right, I'll stop. I apologize, see?
Like this. I mean it!
I'm exhausted,
and my feet are killing me.
You have to trust me.
Nagoshi is heading west.
Be honest, was it really
Nagoshi that took Grey?
It was them. Only the Resistance's
Guji use those Garudas.
Still, given his condition,
I wonder if Grey made it...
Don't be stupid!
He has to be alive!
Grey's... He's Death!
I know he's alive!
Have you been with
Grey all this time?
Well, that's certainly strange.
Why did you give up on your Trooper career?
Because I wanted to!
So Grey's more important to you
than becoming a Citizen?
What the hell?!
Let me tell you something,
just in case.
If you keep heading west,
you'll see a mountain.
On the far side of it,
you'll find the City.
The City?
That's right.
And just past the City is Big Mama.
Big Mama?
Robert, how do you know all this?
I didn't spend all these
years doing nothing!
What a find!
I wonder if it's operational.
I think we'll be able to fix it.
Nagoshi
Lady Lala, this is Grey.
Grey, show your respects!
There's no need.
You are a magnificent warrior,
just as Red said.
It's an honor to be immediately granted
an arms conversion by the Lady Lala.
This is Shidara, the head Guji.
Shidara?!
Do you know him, Grey?
Why did you save me?
Something tells me it wasn't out of pity.
It was your rage.
My rage?
Yes. The rage that
boils within your heart.
Rage at having to become
a Trooper to earn Citizenship.
Rage at having to kill others
who also dream of becoming Citizens.
And rage at the City
where the Citizens live.
That is how you survived all
those battles and come this far.
What about it?
I'd like to use the strength
of your rage to aid us.
If we destroy the City,
this world will change.
What do you say, Grey?
Will you fight at our side?
With your abilities,
you'll soon be a Guji, too.
One of your missiles
destroyed a prototype Ohm.
When it went up,
Lee and two of his friends died.
Lee? Oh, I remember now. It's unfortunate,
but our sensors can't discern individuals.
There was no guarantee that the two
other people near the Ohm weren't enemies.
You fired, even though you knew Lee
and his friends were down there?!
Grey!
Are those...
what you call your ideals?!
Is that it?!
Stop it, Grey!
Kubandas!
Are they returning to base?
Judging from the fuel gauge,
Nagoshi ought to be pretty close. Here goes!
You are cleared to land at C-Road.
Opening hangar D-77.
That's Nagoshi?
It's humongous!
No matter what you do,
it won't work, Red.
I'll never go along with what Lala, you,
or anybody else says. Give it up.
We can't give up that easily.
You're a masterpiece
created by Nagoshi's science.
You're also the ultimate soldier that I trained.
Don't betray our hopes in you.
What's there to betray any longer?
Intruders in C-Road!
Security team B and C,
assemble in C-Road immediately!
I repeat, security team B and C...
Nagoshi's full of
nothing but Halflings.
That means Grey's
probably been...
What do you mean?
What about Grey?
There!
Why? Why is Nagoshi
so important to you?
This is the ideal.
The ideal for the chosen few...
That's no different from City, Red!
Y-You're wrong!
It's no different, Red.
Looks like Grey's been captured.
Huh? I knew it! Can't we do something?
If we don't hurry, he'll...
Don't be in such a rush.
Grey!
I don't want to fight you, Red.
Just turn around and walk away.
I can't do that, Grey.
I had a feeling
you'd say that, Red.
We've got a situation
at the prisoner restraint area!
Security teams A, D, and E,
go to the prisoner restraint area!
I wonder if Grey's all right?
Worried about him, huh?
Let's see now...
Nova, could you lift me up there?
What're you going to do?
I'm going to destroy
Nagoshi's central computer.
Listen, take care of Grey.
You can't leave Death after
what you've been through!
Well, Robert J. Dimitri, it looks like your
500-year-long age is coming to an end.
So this is the place?
Grey!
Nova!
Grey! Thank goodness
you're all right.
What did they do to you?
Emergency in main
computer power section!
Controls unresponsive,
all systems failing!
All personnel, evacuate at once!
It's Robert. Robert's doing this!
The old man?!
Hurry, Lady Lala!
Grey...
Planning to be
the sole survivor, huh?
Run, Lady Lala!
A Doll!
Grey! Can you hear me, Grey!
Robert!
Well, I'll be!
Sounds like you're okay!
Old man! Robert!
Where are you?!
Listen, Grey.
It's about Nagoshi.
Nagoshi's always been
the City's guardian!
What're you talking
about, Robert?
You heard me! Forget about me!
Just head for the City, Grey!
Robert! Old man! Old man!
Toy, my son...
I'm sorry I won't
live to see you die.
I don't mind dying,
now that we're together again!
We're not going to die!
How? How could Nagoshi
be destroyed by so few?
I won't let it end like this!
A Garuda!
Is Lala piloting it?
Is she trying to
escape to the City?
Nagoshi!
It's that mountain!
Robert told me about it.
We're finally here!
The City is a stone's throw away!
The City
Why is the City like this?!
Where are all the Citizens?!
Robert said that this
was the City, right?
That's what he said!
And that Big Mama was here?
Yeah, that's what Robert said!
Where have all the humans gone?
Is this really the City?
Looks that way.
What do you mean,
it looks that way?!
There probably never was
a City or any Citizens.
Doll S100: Lala.
Mama...
Nagoshi has been destroyed.
You are no longer necessary.
Will now cease transmission.
Wait, Mama...!
What is it?
That's as far as you go, Grey.
Red! You're alive?!
Red!
Red! There's no reason
for us to fight!
The City and Nagoshi were a lie!
Snap out of it!
He's pinned down!
I've got to do something...
No! Get away from me!
Shit! I've come
too far to die now!
This is what Hawk, Lee, Lips,
and the others died for!
Grey!
Grey...
Red! Is there really not even a
piece of real you left in there?!
Red!
It's that tower?
That's Big Mama, isn't it?
Yes, Just like Robert said.
Grey, your arm...
Yeah. I guess I'm human again.
So we didn't find
anything here...
Sure we did.
At least one thing.
Something I have to protect.
O-Oh geez...
And for you, I'll definitely...
trash that thing!
I'll never get lost
in the city's
digital world
The sun shines
with a switch
and never sets
Chasing nothing but the future, Science
I forgot how to laugh!
Love is Heart, teach me that love
is the courage to fight, Humanism, Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, people are children of stars
Justice on earth, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, no one is alone
It's the dream I believe in, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, I want to protect
your passion, Humanism Mr. Grey
You can read many human hearts
like a book, Digital Target
In this feigned scenario,
there's nothing that I want
Memory hidden in a scar on my bare skin
Flutters in the wind and sweat
Love is Heart, teach me that love
is the courage to fight, Humanism, Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, people are children of stars
Justice on earth, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, no one is alone
It's the dream I believe in, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, I want to protect
your passion, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, teach me that love
is the courage to fight, Humanism, Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, people are children of stars
Justice on earth, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, no one is alone
It's the dream I believe in, Humanism Mr. Grey
Love is Heart, I want to protect
your passion, Humanism Mr. Grey
Encoding
Original translation
Translation check & typesetting
Quality check
[Blasphemboys]
WOWmd
ILA through APC through Gutterspeak
Perevodildo
TougeWolf
'2025
Ten hours later,
Big Mama ceased all operations...