Following on from "Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind,"
"Arion,"
and "Castle in the Sky"...
Tokuma's latest sci-fi anime!
An invulnerable warrior, nicknamed "Death."
His name is Grey.
It's 2588 AD.
An enormous computer
developed its own consciousness.
The final battle for the survival
of humanity has begun.
Gray's anger goes into overdrive.
Love, obsession, and unfettered rage
turned him into a God of Death.
A new type of endless battle action.
Grey: Digital Target.
Grey commands this world and the afterlife
Love and rage turned him into a God of Death.
Tagami Yoshihisa.
We'd like to ask you about Grey.
What was the incentive,
the starting point for Grey?
Let's see...
I wanted to draw science fiction.
Well, so it goes.
That's how I felt.
But I also didn't want it to be a plain
sci-fi that was all the rage at the time.
What I mean is...
With mechas coming out
and snapping to a giant battle scene.
So I wanted to draw
something different for a change.
Something no one else
would have the folly to draw.
So one day I sat myself down
and started drawing it.
So, let me sum it up, then...
Sure.
You just had the urge to draw science fiction
and Grey was born from that wish.
I see.
And about his name—Grey—
is there any meaning to it?
Not particularly, you know.
Just a normal name, yes?
It just... How to put it?
I think it sort of fitted my vision of him.
So, in other words, he's an "SF hero"
before anything else, right?
That's right. I just felt that since he's the protagonist, I might as well make his name the title.
That was my logic behind it.
There are various mechas
appearing in your work.
A lot of them sound like their names were inspired by Buddhism, such as Kubanda and Ohm.
You must've consulted
a lot of historical records for it?
I wouldn't say so.
Then you just did it by feel?
Kinda.
Not sure how I did it,
I think I just liked how it sounds.
The sound of it?
Yes. I did it by feel.
Not because I'm a devout believer
or something like that.
Not a believer. So you just thought to yourself
"Kubanda, Ohm, yeah I like how it rings"?
- Yeah, sounds about right.
- So that was your process?
Story.
The year is 2588 AD.
Humanity is ruled
by the central government—"Big Mama."
People were divided into six classes,
from Class A to Class F.
Only the privileged elites of Class A,
the Citizens, are guaranteed their right to live.
Most of the population is made up
of the lowest classes, "the People."
To advance to Citizens,
people have to become warriors called Troupers,
and fight for their survival
in an endless war against other towns.
However, of the lowest, class F, Troupers,
only 0.3% live long enough to advance to Class A.
In that age, an immortal warrior appears,
feared by his enemies and his allies alike.
His name is "Grey the Death."
Encoded by WOWmd
Translated by Perevodildo