The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let other see your tears
Ever since the surprise attack on Pearl Harbor,
the Combined Fleet under Isoroku Yamamoto
has seen consecutive victories in all its operations
on Solomon Islands and the Indian Ocean.
Since April 1942,
the Combined Fleet Command,
actively backed by Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto,
planned the Midway invasion operation.
The Naval General Staff had been pressured to approve it.
Midway invasion operation
was aimed at capturing Midway to use it as an air base,
at the same time,
curtailing American naval operations in the area.
Moreover, the underlying plan was to decoy
the main American fleet and crush it in an open battle.
Episode 2
Battle of Midway (Part 1)
However, the Naval General Staff understated
the strategic unimportance of Midway Island.
The Combined Fleet Command were in heated confrontation with them,
until the Commander-in-Chief...
If this operation is not approved,
I resign as Commander-in-Chief.
Just as before the surprise attack at Pearl Harbor,
In one jostle, Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto
was able to push the initiative through.
He believed
that the homeland's protection,
came with the need to seal the fate
of the American fleet on the Pacific.
That day, the Japanese Navy
was celebrating the 37th Navy Day.
Year is 1942. May 27th.
Led by Vice Admiral Chuichi Nagumo,
Akagi, Kaga, Hiryu, Soryu - four aircraft carriers,
comprising the core of the first Mobile Fleet
under the veil of morning mist,
had set sail from the Island of Hashira in Hiroshima Bay.
Commanding the main forces from his new flagship Yamato,
Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto
would follow them two days later, on the 29th,
departing for a voyage of 480km.
The Invasion of Midway took place
concurrently to the Aleutian Islands.
Which was then the biggest operation
in the history of Japanese Navy.
The total force is 350 ships,
1000 aircraft, personnel - around 100,000.
The combined fleet is dispatched in full.
Banzai!
Our heroes!
The Japanese fleet is invincible!
Radios have been playing
army marches since morning!
Everyone's rooting for us!
Must be so, indeed!
It seems, our victory is predestined!
Fighter Corps Respite Tent
Say, war correspondent, wanna see Midway personally
from aboard my Zero?
But I know Zero only has one seat!
Never mind it.
We can seat you behind me, on a pillow.
Should I really do that?
Naturally! It's faster than a Grumman
and has a 20mm cannon.
You'll get to see an encore of Pearl Harbor.
I can't wait for the enemy's carrier to show up!
No, no, they can stay put,
we'll Pearl Harbor them again!
Hey, you alright?
Just a small fever.
Must be a cold.
Make sure you don't get pneumonia.
If a senior gets confined to sick bay,
the lower ranks may also call in sick.
This mist is ideal for clouding enemy's eyes.
Think they'll come out?
Not until we make them to.
This time, the enemy is careful.
Even though Yamato and the main forces
are well behind, we proceed. This is unnerving...
If the foe attacks,
we're a sitting duck.
Battleships are a drag
more than anything.
Our pilots are battle-hardened veterans
of Pearl Harbor. We can achieve another surprise attack.
Meanwhile, on the flagship Yamato.
Admiral, we have analyzed the enemy's communications.
Our findings indicate, the enemy's fleet
is likely to have left Pearl Harbor.
Akagi must have caught it too.
And yet, wouldn't it be safer
to inform them personally?
Remember, by doing so,
we reveal Akagi's position to everyone.
However, at the same time on Akagi...
Due to fog, the searchlights are useless,
we have no way of reporting back.
Let's use the radio.
We can't. It'd give away our location
to the enemy.
Still, as we launch a surprise attack on Midway,
they'll notify their fleet anyway.
And yet, information on the foe's
position is crucial.
For the moment, there are no signs
of them being dispatched.
If anchored at Pearl Harbor,
they wouldn't make it in time to thwart us.
The probability of an enemy aircraft carrier
operating near us is negligible.
Operational plan involves
that we report on a low frequency wave.
The signal sent from Akagi
has not been caught by the American Pacific Fleet.
However, the general outline of the Midway Operation
has already been known by the American side.
Successful intelligence and code-breaking efforts
made that possible.
Any new information
on the enemy's task force?
Their whereabouts are still unknown.
On carrier to carrier battle,
the advantage of dealing the blow first is decisive.
We will keep patrolling the north-northwest area.
Right under their nose,
we'll strike them from the northeast,
As a courtesy for Pearl Harbor.
American task force hinged up on three carriers -
Enterprise, Hornet, and Yorktown.
That formation was comparable in size
to the task force deployed by Japan.
The Japanese and American task forces
were separated only by a measly distance of 240km.
As both were plotting an ambush,
the opposing forces were in a deadlock.
The operation was hanging by a thin thread,
separating the victor from the loser by minute proceedings.
The Midway landing party came under attack.
So much for a surprise attack.
The enemy maybe intercepted their communications.
Hey, you should be resting!
I'm restless anyway, too excited.
I may as well see our boys off.
Wing commander, don't exert yourself!
Say, is the patrol plane out?
No, it'll take off with 1st wave squadron.
All-at-once strategy?
Business as usual.
What if the patrol aircraft spots an enemy fleet
as the strike on Midway is underway?
Let them, the 2nd wave
is armed with torpedoes and all set.
1st wave wing takeoff!
Show 'em hell! That's it!
What's with the patrol aircraft?
Is it in order?
It's running 30 minutes late already.
Hey-hey, why are they still fiddling with it?
What could be the matter?
Show up, Grumman.
Assume attacking formation!
Enemy plane on starboard! 166 degrees!
It is close enough in distance to tell - it's the enemy.
No, it's a flying boat.
Prepare for anti-aircraft combat!
Personnel in position!
Cowards, hiding behind the clouds!
The Japanese Mobile Fleet could not have anticipated
the sudden deployment of American Aircraft Carriers.
And yet, there they were drawing near,
Steadily.
Enemy task force spotted. Four aircraft carriers,
several battleships, distance 280km, course - 150 degrees.
No response from the patrol aircraft yet?
Yes. We've not heard from them as of yet.
Shit...
Hey, call the headquarters on Akagi,
a 2nd wave wing is needed.
The radio station is busted.
Cretin! Fix it, then. It's your job!
Roger!
This is nasty...
Ouch! Hot!
Can't be helped.
Ask another plane to do it.
Roger!
We've received a signal
from the 1st wave wing.
"1st wave of attack ended, returning home.
2nd wave is required."
The enemy's combined air power numbers 400 planes.
Their pilots are also superior.
The moment we can emerge victorious is...
When their attack on Midway stops
as the planes retreat to the carrier...
Precisely.
The enemy is about 380km away from Midway.
According to the Intel received at 6:40,
The foe is advancing towards the attack wing,
at the speed of 25 knots.
If we were to sortie now,
our planes would only have to travel 270km,
Arriving at the enemy location
during the refueling.
Thus, seizing a golden chance for offensive.
This would be especially efficient
if we get the planes stationed on Midway to also attack.
To game successfully,
timing is the key, before we overwhelm them!
A Surprise attack.
Our golden chance!
Give it all you've got, Admiral.
Meanwhile, on the Japanese side, no sighting
of the American carrier had been recorded as of yet.
Any news from the patrol plane?
Negative.
The area is swarming with enemy flying boats.
Theoretically,
the enemy is using 1/3 of his planes for scouting.
Even so, they are too numerous.
Even if their fleet
had a hunch of what's going on,
They would only be
freshly off from Pearl Harbor.
Do we launch the 2nd wave?
Prepare the 2nd wave of attack on Midway!
Roger!
Replace the torpedo mounting with ground bombs!
Get the emergency conversion going!
Faster!
Enemy approaching!
Four aircraft!
Six more enemy bombers this way!
Eat this!
Take off, faster!
Enemy patrol aircraft.
We've been discovered.
Tone's vehicle 4 reports: locating 10 "enemy-like" ships,
about 10 degrees away from Midway.
What do they mean by "enemy-like”?
A carrier?
A carrier!
Bridge to Tone,
reckon the enemy fleet composition.
Tone's vehicle 4 reports: enemy forces are 5 cruisers,
and 5 destroyers. The carrier is seemingly not present.
The enemy is accompanied
by a "carrier-like" vessel in the rear.
They're here?
It only states "carrier-like."
We need hard confirm.
With "-like" upon "-like."
Nothing is certain.
A request from Hiryu's second squadron commander:
It is crucial that the attack wings
take off at once.
Admiral.
The 1st wave vehicles are on their way back.
Dispatching the attack wings
without any fighter coverage is risky.
Look!
Then, fighters, bombers, torpedo bombers
will deal a decisive blow as one.
As soon as the 1st wave lands,
the entire fleet heads north-east.
We'll rearm for the all-in attack
and crush the enemy.
Prepare for anti-ship warfare!
Arm all the planes with torpedoes!
The Hell?!
Gotta switch them again!
Hurry up!
Commence the emergency conversion!
On the carrier Hiryu...
Transmission from Akagi. Once the 1st wave lands,
commence the emergency conversion and head north-east.
What?
As soon as Tone's patrol aircraft was spotted,
the enemy dispatched their attack wings...
Which means, two hours later, around 10:20
we will come under attack!
They think we can afford
to wait for the 1st wave?!
We have no time to mount torpedoes!
They must take off
with whatever setup they have!
Anything's fine against their carrier! Fools!
The reckoning of Hiryu's captain
hit the nail's head.
The formation of American bombers that took off
from Enterprise, alongside its task force escort
was already on the way.
They seized their golden chance.
The 1st wave vehicles finally landed
while the 2nd wave was just merely preparing to take off...
Admiral! Kaga is attacked!
Emergency takeoff!
Every battle-ready vehicle takes off immediately!
Swoop!
Watch out!
Damn it, just five more minutes...
If only the enemy was five minutes late,
we'd be in a lot better place!
Wrong, it's not five minutes,
but two hours.
We missed our last big shot two hours ago.
Alright, I'll strike back!
In just five minutes,
the Battle for Midway turned into a debacle.
However, some say,
this outcome with such time window was obvious
The ability to think several moves ahead and
apply aptly calculations after decision taking
is what sets apart a victor from a loser.
Those indulging on wishful thinking,
losing sight of their objectives at a given time,
are liable to experience disaster.
The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
Akagi, Kaga, Soryu -
in an instant, three carriers
were lost in the battle of Midway
The only carrier still afloat being Hiryu.
Faced with American advantage of three carriers to one,
Hiryu commits to a suicidal raid.
In a three-on-one battle,
next week comes the tragic fate
of the aircraft carrier Hiryu.
With the decision of her captain,
the Battle for Midway meets its end.
Animentary: Decision
Episode 3
Battle of Midway (Part 2)
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation by
Quality Checking by
Supplementary materials by
Video by
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2