The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
On December 8th, 1941,
the IJN initiated the war on the Pacific
by launching a surprise attack on the American pacific fleet,
stationed in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii.
Meanwhile, commanded by
Lieutenant-General Yamashita, the Japanese Army
was poised to seize
the crucial British redoubt of far east - Singapore.
To that effect, they landed
on the northern coast of Malay Peninsula.
They were given the strategic goal
of traversing the Malay Peninsula and capturing the great British fortress of Singapore in just under 90 days.
For that, blitzkrieg tactics had been adopted.
Later on, in February 1st, 1942,
the Japanese troops were already on the doorstep
of Singapore, in the coastal town of Johor Bahru.
Ships of capital interest for the British Far Eastern Fleet -
Prince of Wales and Repulse, had also been sunk.
The Japanese had become the undisputed masters
of the skies and seas.
Singapore being completely shut down,
its capitulation was believed to be but a matter of time.
Repulse
Kuantan
Prince of Wales
Johor Bahru
Bukit Timah Heights
Singapore
Episode 5
The Fall of Singapore
However, upon immediate danger
Singapore was exposed to,
The British Far Eastern commander,
Lieutenant-General Percival said:
"It if of utmost importance for a commander
to keep the lid on premature Intel.
As by not doing so, the risk is undermining
the morale of the troops."
But I'm convinced that moping around
is way more detrimental to my men's motivation.
Our army is tasked with holding Singapore
to the last man, for three months at least.
Why, then, not redeploy
the forces on Malay Peninsula to Singapore Island,
so as to mount an organized defense?
No! On it, there are not nearly enough barracks
to host everybody.
Lieutenant-General Percival flatly dismissed
all the suggestions of the 8th Australian
Division Commander with a single word.
For the Malay Peninsula it is over.
But the struggle for Singapore is still afoot!
Presently, our British army
is all but trapped in this Fortress of Singapore.
Our common duty is to hold out
in this fortress until reinforcements arrive.
However, the commander of the British Far Eastern Army
never precisely specified
how the defense of Singapore had to be carried out.
Neither the citizens nor the soldiers
felt much change in their everyday lives.
Meanwhile, it became quiet in Johor province,
across the strait separating it from Singapore.
The Japanese army seemingly
stopped carrying out any operations at all.
But during that tranquil period, the Japanese army earnestly put the finishing touches to their attack on Singapore.
But still, the whole process
was facing difficulties.
The 55 days of continuous blitzkrieg
thoroughly drained the Japanese army
since their landing on the Malay Peninsula.
Moreover, their ammunition needs were only 1/3 fulfilled.
Finally, with the acute shortage of landing craft,
even the Strait of Johor, of only 1km in width
could not be rowed across
by the troops of 5th and 18th regiments
in less than 7 to 10 hours in total,
despite their best effort.
On Singapore Island,
The enemy troops estimation is 70,000.
Having quite possibly, over 500 artillery pieces.
Even a single day allows the enemy to consolidate defenses, lowering the odds for our success.
In regard to our situation,
I believe we should go for the shock effect,
so as to minimize the casualties on our side during landing.
No, after getting this far,
just crossing the strait brazenly would do.
As soon as we control the fresh water source from Bukit Timah Heights, they will surrender
and if they refuse,
a deluge of artillery fire will make them.
Any landing operation is likely
to cost us 1/5 of our own forces anyway.
Northeastern coast is the fortified area,
landing there will be deadly.
Yet, with all our forces
converging in this very part,
the sub-objective
of securing Bukit Timah Heights is at reach.
Yes, I also don't think we have any other options.
The enemy also knows it is a one-way trip
for the landing party,
so they'll launch all their forces at stopping it.
All the way from the north of Malay Peninsula - Singora,
Pattani, and Kota Bharu, we made it here to Johor Bahru
before their most pessimistic previsions.
And yet, the enemy still had time
to thoroughly prepare a counter move.
It is now more than ever capital
to gather and face them all.
Once the attack is on,
none can afford to lose focus, even for a short moment.
The Commander-in-Chief of the British Far East
still advocated defending Singapore Island
with all available resources for 3 more months at least.
If we hold out for 3 more months,
we'll buy enough time for aid to arrive.
If we manage to stalemate the Japanese,
it will be possible to counterattack.
Certainly. But that would require us
to remember one thing -
No stirring up the soldiers
or the common citizens if possible.
Are we supposed to simply bear with it?
It indeed seems impossible
to dodge the battle.
Our strategy should be defense in depth.
So a coastline protection strategy?
Most naturally.
Finally, some spark of combativeness
from you, Commander.
First, we foil the enemy's attempts at landing,
then we hit them back across the strait right away.
No, we only ensure that the island itself is defended.
The Japanese will do their utmost
to capture this point.
Sir, this is a heavily fortified area.
The Japanese would surely enough know that much.
It'd drive them
to more vulnerable spots!
The northwestern bank is a dense mangrove jungle,
isn't that so, governor-general?
Indeed, it's a marshland,
most unwelcoming to man.
Advancing in wetlands is extremely taxing.
So even the Japanese would know better
than just doing this.
Commander, do you really think so?
The Japanese army had been straightforward
on its way here.
attacking the forts is their most obvious choice!
Then, we'd better start
fortifying each and every position.
There's no way we turn every golf course
into a machine gun post.
Without the city planning board's permission,
erecting buildings is ruled out.
But sir, aren't we under wartime regime?
We don't want the population upset,
the laborers are giving us enough problems as it is.
There was no labor shortage of any sort.
However, the wages had to be raised.
The salaries far exceeded
the range that the British Army Department had settled on.
The colonial administration's finances were strained.
Does that, then, mean we will sit on our hands,
being sitting ducks for the Japanese?
The commander of the Far Eastern British Army
ordered the defenders of Singapore to be as frugal as possible
so as to have enough artillery shells
for a 3 month siege.
As a result, the British anti-aircraft batteries were only firing
a token amount of rounds, with little to no effect.
Not just that, Tengah, Sembawang, and Kallang -
the only three airfields the British had
were thoroughly ravaged by the Japanese bombers.
Brand new Hurricane fighters, a recent arrival
from the British mainland never managed to get airborne.
They were blown apart
right where they stood, in cold blood.
What? Drop the shell saving policy?
No way. Intense bombardment
would win us nothing but more of civilian unrest.
The Japanese were in working order
to commence the attack on Singapore.
Lieutenant-General Yamashita set up his headquarters
at the Johor Bahru Royal Palace,
in the immediate vicinity of the Strait of Johor.
He was hoping for the upcoming
landing at Singapore to be a success.
The 5th Division landed successfully.
The 18th Division landed successfully.
Good.
The Bukit Timah Heights were an essential stepping stone
in the capture of Singapore.
This key location was where the British troops
showed determined resistance for the first time.
For the Japanese as well,
the Bukit Timah Heights were the place
where their advance,
unstoppable up until now, was finally halted.
On the night of February 9th,
the Planning Staff visited the headquarters
of the 18th Division Command.
The overall theater commander had expressed the necessity
of occupying the Bukit Timah Heights by February 11th.
As for the enemy's capitulation,
the military headquarters are offering negotiation.
Oh? They want it in just 2 days?
Yes.
But here, we're running short of bullets.
And of shells as well.
I know the task appears taxing.
However, the theater commander hopes
to thus prevent the enemy from catching breath -
by seizing the Bukit Timah Heights.
If need be, even without bullets, with bayonet charge.
Having discussed it with the 18th division,
the Planning Staff
headed immediately to see the 5th division commander.
Sir, the 18th Division Commander already pledged
to attack the Bukit Timah Heights.
Well, there's nothing 18th division can do that we can't.
On February 11th, the leaflets calling for surrender
were dropped on the British positions.
However, the response from the British side never came.
The Bukit Timah Heights were not yet ready to capitulate.
We'll defend them. That is our only call here.
Sir, it was reported that the
Imperial Guards Division launched an attack
from the eastern side of the Bukit Timah Heights.
They started?
Alright.
On February 12th, at last, the Bukit Timah Heights
were occupied by Japanese troops,
Making the fall of Singapore a mere matter of time.
The British command came to grips
with the inevitable invasion of the city.
To keep their facilities and equipment in Singapore
from falling into the Japanese hands, the high command
ordered the destruction of anything deemed of potential use.
I think this was their last stand.
On the morning of the 15th, the Chief of Staff
reported the situation to Lieutenant-General Yamashita.
Our side only has an average
of 100 shells remaining per machine gun.
Exhaustion is also taking a toll on soldiers.
how about we suspend the attack for a moment?
The resupply of rations is also required.
Well-rested, an army is better coordinated.
It may be taxing for us. But do you think the enemy
is having it any easier? It's just as grueling for them.
Only attack. An attack here and now is the way to victory!
However, the battle dragged on.
And it only became even more grueling
with a fierce British counter-attack.
Is it something important?
Ah... No...
How'd it go?
But if nothing is done
, our side's death toll will skyrocket.
We need to hurry and think of countermeasures.
What? They did it?
At last, the Japanese army had received
the British response, conceding to the capitulation offer.
Lieutenant-General Yamashita decided to negotiate
with the British in the automobile factory building,
near the infamous Bukit Timah Heights.
The British army commander presented
various conditions for their surrender.
However, Lieutenant-General Yamashita
kept insisting on unconditional surrender until the very end.
Do you surrender or not?
We need "Yes" or "No"!
Answer just that.
We've no time to waste.
Yes.
Singapore has fallen.
By that time, the Japanese troops were running so low
on shells, they had no more than 3 per machine gun.
What it means to be a commander?
It means always being in full control of the battle,
it means putting yourself on the forefront,
setting the bar for your subordinates' actions,
and ultimately, be there personally,
spearheading your men towards victory.
A commander, unable to abandon
paperwork for war,
leaving subordinates only the dirty bulk of the work -
is meaningless during wartime.
What the struggle for Singapore taught us is,
of both opposing commanders who conducted it -
the Japanese and the British one -
they were, as it turns out,
the embodiment of those two extremes.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
In the wake of the Malay Peninsula invasion,
the Japanese army commenced Hong Kong's.
Desperately, the British tried their best to hold on
to their fortifications on Gin Drinkers Line.
Until the very end, they were hoping
for reinforcements, which never materialized.
The Japanese army kept harassing them,
wave after wave.
The next decision: how should a commander
conduct himself on the battlefield?
Episode 6
The Fall of Hong Kong
We present to you:
The Fall of Hong Kong.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2