The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
December 2, 1941, Sanya Harbor, Hainan Island.
With the heavy cruiser Chokai as its flagship,
a considerable escort fleet quietly rallied.
Led by Lieutenant General Tomoyuki Yamashita,
the 25th army prepared to embark.
Carrying them was the mobile transport fleet,
composed of a dozen ships, including Ryujo Maru.
Excuse me.
Sir, we just received
an emergency telegram addressed for you
from the Commander-in-Chief
of the Southern Expeditionary Army.
I will read. Sender:
Southern Expeditionary Army Commander-in-Chief.
Recipient: 25th Army Commander.
"The sun rises in Yamagata."
"The sun rises at Yamagata."
So then, the war starts on December 8th.
On December 8th, war was declared
and the Japanese Navy
had dealt a surprise blow to the American fleet,
stationed at Pearl Harbor, Hawaii.
Meanwhile, the infantry
would also be dispatched on the mission
of roaming the Malay Peninsula to take the
Pride of the British Empire, the great fortress of Singapore.
Episode 4:
Blitzkrieg on Malay Peninsula
Confronting two major powers at once:
America and Britain, Japan had planned
to engage the Pacific war with a decisive move,
bound to enter the annals of history.
In accordance with the Southern strategy,
the units 5 and 18 formed a special corps, the 25th army.
It was put under the command of lieutenant general Yamashita, honorably cited on the battlefield.
The capture of Singapore would become a major operation,
of immeasurable importance for the Japanese Army.
Singapore, also known as “Gibraltar of the East"
is in fact a big impregnable fortress.
A siege from the sea was deemed
too costly on our forces and therefore prejudicial.
Instead, we will approach Singapore from inland,
where it's more lightly defended.
In order to deceive the enemy, we will pretend to head
for Thailand, only to go off course abruptly.
We'll disembark at 3 points simultaneously - Singora, Pattani, and Kota Bharu, advancing in two groups.
However, this strategy has
3 issues that might complicate matters.
Firstly, our planned route has
over 250 bridges towards our destination.
If the enemy sabotage them,
our advance will be hampered.
Secondly, the enemy's troops amount to about 80,000.
In comparison, our forces
come to no more than 20,000.
Finally, the third problem is that it has to be captured
by March 10th, the Army Memorial Day.
Through conventional warfare, we won't capture it,
even after half a year! We must sweep it!
As soon as we land, we overrun them,
without half-measure.
The forward units
have to cut through the enemy's lines!
Don't even look back! Just let the vanilla units
deal with the bulk of the enemy!
Charge. Charge!
Aim for Singapore straight on
in a lightning-fast charge!
On the morning of December 3rd,
the fleet escorting the 25th Army
departed for the northern coast
of the Malay Peninsula.
On December 7th, the fleet went past the southern tip
of French Indochina, and instead of turning north,
it went off course,
towards the northern cost of Malay Peninsula -
Singora, Pattani, and Kota Bharu
being the 3 starting points of a scattered assault.
Singapore is considered to be the gateway to the Indian Ocean.
A cornerstone to anyone
aiming to be the master of the Strait of Malacca.
Capturing it was the key to the success of the entire Southern Operation. Moreover, it was a critical priority.
Prepare to disembark!
December 8th. Led personally by commander Yamashita,
the special 25th front line unit landed in Singora.
Hold it!
Commander, you can jump now!
Don't let commander down! Hurry!
The Japanese army thus succeeded
to land unopposed in Singora,
and headed straight for Singapore.
The blitzkrieg through Malay Peninsula had begun.
Meanwhile, the landing party in Kota Bharu
met a fierce resistance from British defenders on the beach.
Nevertheless, this formation also managed to honor the "Charge" order
and broke through the enemy by dint of melee attack.
Moreover, on December 10th,
the Japanese naval bombers' attack
British East Indies Fleet sunk off the coast of Malaya
sunk two major ships of the British East Indies Fleet:
Prince of Wales and Repulse.
The efficiency of the lightning-fast torpedo
With aerial and naval supremacy over their targets,
Proved the Japanese planes' flawlessness!
the high command
was now even more in favor of securing Malaya.
On December 11th, three days after
the Japanese landing on the Malay Peninsula,
the 8th Australian Division Commander
visited the global commander
of Britain's East Indies forces, Lieutenant General Percival.
Sir, I beg your pardon, but the actual war began.
Wars are not won through formalities.
Our forces are obviously too scattered.
If we don't consolidate the front line immediately,
we'll be at great risk!
Division Commander, with respect, aren't you
fretting about the Japanese army more than necessary?
But sir, the jewels of Singapore's defense,
the flagships of the East Indies Fleet,
Prince of Wales and Repulse were sunk!
It's true that the Japanese army has airplanes,
whereas we don't. Same goes for tanks.
But Division Commander, the Malay Peninsula
can only be crossed from north-to-south via two narrow roads.
Moreover, many fortifications are in place
along the border, starting with the Jitra Line.
It will take the Japanese army at least six months
to reach Johor Bahru.
By then, Singapore would teem
with reinforcements from Britain.
Such a degree of concern is unwarranted.
Don't you think so, Division Commander?
Oh no, I'm still worried, sir.
The Japanese are as determined as wolves!
As wolves, you say?
However, the Jitra Line is also a robust position.
I expect them to hold off the enemy for 3 months at least.
However, this very day, the tank Corps of the 5th Division
of the Japanese Army stormed into the Jitra Line.
The British Far East Commander had erred in his reckoning.
In contrast to the Japanese Commander, this Commander
was more preoccupied
with paperwork than the actual conflict.
The enemy's here!
The Japanese army advanced at a tremendous pace.
Sagging under the charge,
the British troops couldn't counterattack.
Thus, the element relied upon by the commander of Britain's East Indies,
the border encompassing Jitra Line,
was completely cut through under a day.
First, tanks rushed in. The trucks were falling into step behind.
To finish, the Mobile Infantry,
"Silver Ring", followed on bicycles.
This tactic was carried on
even after Jitra line's dismantlement.
25th Army was thrusting its way
through the Malay Peninsula.
On December 28th already, the 5th Division's charge
staved the British defenders in of Kampar as well,
only grinding to a halt at the Sungai river.
They had to, as the bridge over it
was detonated by retreating British troops.
They boldly foisted this on us.
Let's sit this out and wait for the engineering battalion.
Got it!
On the night of January 4th, the Independent Engineering Regiment had arrived to rebuild the blown bridge.
The Independent Engineering Regiment arrived on the spot.
Please accept our apology for the delay.
Good to know. Feel free
to enjoy relief at our camp tonight.
No. We appreciate your hospitality,
but our Blitzkrieg cannot suffer any delay.
We've no time to sleep.
Please let us start the reconstruction work at once.
I see. Permission granted.
Roger!
Through conventional warfare, we won't capture it
even after half a year! Speed is the key.
As soon as we land, we overrun them,
without half-measure.
The forward units
have to cut through the enemy's lines!
By dint of hard, strenuous labor, under just 2 days,
the construction battalion had completed their job.
Thank you!
Yeah! Good job!
Keep it up!
This enemy stronghold, a sentry to Slim River,
is 350km from the capital,
it is the most impregnable position in Malay Peninsula.
The success or failure of the entire blitzkrieg
campaign hinges solely on our ability to capture it.
It we take our time with it,
the perspective of capturing Singapore is jeopardized.
Tomorrow, the 7th, our regiment will commence the attack.
The planned time is at dawn.
Tank corps, I would ask you to spearhead the attack
through brute force. That's all.
Commanding officer, sir. I believe, there is a way
for us to level the enemy stronghold easily.
Would you mind hearing me out?
I don't think a night's wait would make our tanks helpful.
But an assault tonight would unhorse the enemy.
I believe, however, that for a global attack,
our infantry on legs would need to wait for dawn.
What? Are you implying a night attack with tanks?
Yes. From my analysis of the enemy state,
a night attack appears to be the best course of action.
Also, at night a tank
would completely conceal it to the most watchful surveillance.
Besides, such tactic is completely unheard of.
For these reasons,
we get an excellent opportunity to catch the enemy by surprise.
I see.
All right. Let's give it a shot.
Succeed or die trying.
Late in January 6th, after the sunset,
a dedicated force of 15 tanks
and 100 personnel in leg infantry and engineering battalions
drove straight into the British encampment.
All right. Those fires in the woods
must be where the enemy camp is.
Full alert!
Gun position at one o'clock.
Lock those woods down at once!
Fire!
Over there are the enemy's big guns.
Close the distance!
All right! Rush straight into the enemy camp!
Close combat mode!
Already weary from retreating, the British would also
regret not taking the situation seriously enough.
The rift between them and the Japanese,
who succeeded in executing the Blitzkrieg
was made explicitly clear
on the battlefields over the last few days.
A report had arrived.
Sir, Kuala Lumpur finally surrendered on January 11th.
I see. So we're currently going a week ahead of schedule.
After our tanks overran their positions on the Slim River,
the enemy morale was at its historical low.
However, it's not yet time
to let our guard down. Continue the Blitz!
Yessir!
Now then, would it be the 5th Division
to cross the finish line first, or the Imperial Guard division?
I look forward finding it out.
The Javanese army advances,
the British army retreats.
The fighting in Malaya had become more or less one-sided.
However, the commander-in-chief of the British forces...
Sir, the Japanese army
is approaching Singapore at an alarming rate.
The wartime regime has to be instated ASAP.
Excuse me, division leader,
but my opinion on this differs from yours.
But sir... Look at it yourself, sir:
Even Kuala Lumpur had surrendered on the 11th!
You shouldn't give way to panic, Division Commander.
It is of the utmost importance for an officer
have his troops and himself stay calm.
Then, why not gather the available Malayan ground troops in Singapore to drive the Japanese out decisively?
No.
The islands of Singapore don't have
nearly enough barracks to accommodate our entire army.
That's the last you will hear from me.
I will make a last ditch effort
of halting the Japanese advance at Johor Bahru.
The Japanese army was on a winning spree
and marched straight to Singapore, practically unopposed.
And just as the Commander-in-Chief anticipated it,
the competition for crossing the finish line first had started.
Sir, it is reported that the Imperial Guard Division
is one step ahead of us on the way to Skudai.
What? Our 5th division
must be the first to arrive!
Yes. However, the Imperial Guard division
will only overtake us by a small margin.
Yeah, like hell we let them do that!
Sir!
Come on, off we go!
Roger!
These 5th Division guys are in for a surprise!
Yeah, they stand no chance
of crossing the finish line first.
Which unit do you guys belong to?
Sir, Imperial Guard Division.
Forward reconnaissance unit.
Oh, that's interesting.
Our 5th Division had passed through here a long time ago.
I am the 21st Brigade Commander of 5th Division.
Good job anyway.
Eh, so we're too late, after all?
The heroic defense of the Singapore's lifeline, Johor Bahru
by the 8th Australian Division also proved vain,
and the city soon fell.
What exactly is this thing they call war?
And then, what are its goals?
Finally, when to take a decisive action?
A commander, able to fully grasp this basic principle,
or a commander, entirely ignorant of it -
is the most precise indicator
telling a winner from a loser,
as we have witnessed just now
from the outcome of this campaign.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
The Japanese land forces' Blitzkrieg through Malaya is over.
The new battle for Singapore now begins.
Notwithstanding their seclusion,
the British had decided to hold onto
their Fortress of Singapore until the bitter end.
Their opponents - the Japanese were forced
into a bloody and brutal battle.
Like the Southern Cross star,
attack and defense intersect, in a gamble for one side's survival.
Please take part in the next decision:
The Fall of Singapore.
Episode 5
The Fall of Singapore
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Project manager / Editor
Translator
Quality Checker
Supplementary materials by
Encoder
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2