Rolling Ryota
Okizari Fansubs presents
Otaki Appears
Storyboard
Direction
Hyoga Shinichi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Yo, Ryota-san, don't be so cold!
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Honmachiw
Third Street
wwHonmachi
Protagonist Takao Ryota AKA
Rolling Ryota
Told you already, no dice.
Oh, come on, take us for a ride, will ya?
Megumi
You've got nothing better to do.
Yukari
We're your only passengers anyway.
Perfect timing, wouldn't you say?
This month, I've been flooded with complaints.
If I don't drive properly, I'm screwed.
Don't say boring stuff like that.
Just floor it for once! Let's go wild!
Everything's been pissing me off lately.
Please, take us somewhere quiet.
You could use a little fun yourself,
don't you think?
Hey, Ryota-san.
Well, maybe that's not such a bad idea.
FORBIDDEN
A passenger?
Otaki
Yo, long time no see, Takao.
Otaki! Otaki, that you?!
Hey, please, Ryota-san.
The ladies are asking you nicely, you know.
Yeah! Karuizawa sounds perfect.
It's settled. Let's hit a motel in Karuizawa!
You little brats!
High schoolers puffing cigarettes,
talking about motels.
Don't you have a shred of decency left?!
Hey, drop the act, grandpa.
Yukari, you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Wh-What the hell's your problem, bastard?!
Shut it!
Hey, Otaki!
Jeez. I wonder what happened.
When did girls start talking like that?
Everywhere I go, it's the same:
sloppy, careless, vulgar women!
Greasy hair, black teeth,
and nose hair flying!
Dumb as bricks,
spitting like some unknown weapon!
The only thing they know how to move
is their hips in bed!
Ah, this kind of women...
gets this!
Thinking trash like you might become mothers one day... It's terrifying! Take that!
This country's going to hell!
Hey! Stop it, Otaki!
This medicine is bitter.
With girls like that, you gotta teach them
with your fists! That's the only way they learn!
I said stop it, damn it!
Get the fuck out!
Jeez, Takao...
You're even wasting time
on girls like that now?
You're too lenient!
Women are all like that. Treat them too nice,
and they'll climb all over you.
Watch yourself.
Don't go drawing the short straw.
Yoshimoto, summer's almost here.
Time to get out and feel free again!
This year, I swear I'll score on the beach.
Yoshimoto                      Tajima
Yeah, right. Good luck with that.
Man, you're no fun.
Oh?
Hey, look.
Huh?
Isn't that Yukari and Megumi over there?
What happened to you two?
Poor things, you look
like you've been through hell.
How about I take you to a hotel
and make you feel better, huh?
Seriously, girls fighting in public
is just pathetic. Cut it out!
Shut it! It was a guy who did this!
A guy?!
Y-Yeah!
And if you two take care of him,
I'll let you take me out!
M-Megumi!
It's fine. We'll just use them
and ditch them after, simple as that.
But...
Where is he?!
Where's that pathetic guy hiding?!
We... will... tear him apart!
What?! Otaki-san's in town?!
Yeah. He was just on my bus earlier.
Ryota's sworn younger brother
Ohno Takashi
E-Earlier... and where'd he go after that?!
He was gonna grab a drink with me,
but when he saw a group of delinquent girls
near Third Street, he hopped off.
Third Street?!
That's right around the corner!
Takashi's girlfriend
Yuki
Why are you freaking out, Taka-chan?
Who is this Otaki guy anyway?
Listen carefully, Yuki!
When Otaki-san shows up,
don't you dare cross your legs or act loose!
Watch your mouth too!
That guy'll smack any girl who acts sloppy
or talks back, no hesitation!
So act like a proper lady, got it?!
What?! Why the hell should I change for him?!
If he tries to hit me,
you'd better protect me, Taka!
M-Me?!
Of course! You're my boyfriend, aren't you?
I-I'm saying this for your own good, you know!
So will you protect me or not?!
He was always rough with women,
but today, he was out of his mind.
Maybe he just woke up
on the wrong side of the bed.
Anyway, once he sets his eyes
on a girl he doesn't like,
he won't calm down
until he's hit her a few times.
If he's glaring at you,
expect at least three punches.
Ow! That's him! That's the guy!
No mistake?
Yeah.
Hey, you better let me have my turn after.
A deal's a deal.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Now get going!
All right!
Hey, you! Hold it!
Wait, you prick!
Hey, it's you two!
What the hell are you doing?!
That's him! That's the guy!
Hurry up and take him down!
You spoiled women!
Don't talk like that in front of Otaki-san!
Act more ladylike, damn it!
OUCH
Man, women these days are hopeless!
Indeed.
Oh, Otaki-san, when did you get here?
H-How did it come to this?
Why do I have to leave?!
I told you, that guy's not normal!
It's dangerous!
You sure are stubborn, Yuki-chan.
Huh, Takao's here too?
Look who I ran into by chance.
Takashi, you doing well?
B-Been a while, sir.
Glad to see you're still
in one piece, Otaki-san.
And who's this girl?
Look at that skirt. I can practically see her panties.
Wh-What's your problem?!
It's none of your business, you moron!
What?
P-Please, Otaki-san, go easy on her!
She's my girlfriend! I'm begging you!
Your girlfriend?
Then it's your job to make sure she's raised right!
N-No way! We can't let you lay a finger on Yuki-chan!
That's right. Even you, Otaki-san,
can't get away with that!
Yuki-chan's one of the few girls
we can actually talk to like normal people!
We won't stand by
while someone hurts her!
That's right!
When summer comes, Yuki-chan doesn't mind wearing light clothes around us, you know!
She'll cross her legs just right
so we get a peek.
Sometimes she doesn't wear a bra,
so you can see her nipples!
On sleepless nights,
she's been a real lifesaver!
You might not get it, Otaki-san,
but to us, she's special.
We won't let anyone hurt her!
Otaki, what the hell's gotten into you?
You used to be the kind of guy who could see
the good in women before the bad.
Shut up!
Listen, you punks...
If you keep putting women on a pedestal,
you'll end up crying later.
You've got to drill it into them that a woman's supposed to obey a man from the get-go.
Spoil them, and they'll just walk all over you!
You guys don't understand a damn thing!
Hey!
Otaki's wife, Mizue
Why the hell are you skipping
your work at the factory, honey?
M-Mizue... How'd you find me?!
If there's anywhere you'd be struttin' around
acting big, it'd be this town.
O-Otaki! You're married?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Forgive me, dear!
I skipped work today! I won't do it again!
Listen up!
I told the foreman you'd take the night shift,
so you'll work straight through. No sleep, got it?
Y-Yes, ma'am!
I'll work! I swear, honey!
Uh, sorry for the scene, everyone.
Now move it!
Honey, I get it.
Please don't be angry no more...
Mom, are we going home?
Yeah.
Rolling Ryota
When Sube Changes into a Swimsuit
Storyboard
Direction
Noboru Natsuoka
Koji Sagawa
Damn, it's hot as hell today.
If we go walking outside,
we'd melt right into the asphalt.
Man, I could go for a trip to the beach.
The beach, huh? Maybe we could invite
Tajima-san or Yoshimoto-san.
No way! You kidding, Megumi?
I'd rather stand under the blazing sun
than go with those two.
Yeah, guess so.
You know what they're always after anyway.
Let's do it!
I wonder if Ryota-san could take us instead.
That guy won't lift a finger
unless he's in the mood.
Wait, that's it!
We just gotta get him in the mood, Yukari!
Come on, you...
Whisper, whisper, whisper...
Get it?
You want to do that?
It's embarrassing!
Just trust me, okay?
NEXT DAY
He's here! You ready?
Yeah!
One, two...
three!
Ryota-san!
Take us to the beach!
He didn't even stop the bus.
I'm shocked.
More than shocked, I'm pissed!
Seriously, Megumi, you swore it'd work!
Now we just look like idiots!
I'm sorry, all right.
Let's just go change already.
So soft.
Wh-What do you think you're doing?!
Yarita
You've got a pretty solid ass there.
How about the other one?
Pet.
Y-You pervert!
Boobies secured!
No!
Don't get mad just 'cause
some guy touched your butt
when you're out here
half-naked on the street.
No!
C-Cut it out, you creep!
I'll show you what
a real man tastes like.
FORBIDDEN
Sneak out...
M-Megumi!
Your turn now.
FORBIDDEN
No!
H-How big is it?!
It hurts! You're gonna break me!
Let's take it slow back at my place,
real slow and sticky.
Gotcha! Caught me a couple of pretty ones!
No, stop!
Let go!
Hey, Yoshimoto, how about we hit the beach tomorrow?
The beach?
Yep, the beach!
Under the blazing sun,
hot girls in bikinis splashing in the waves,
and when night falls, sex on the sand
till you forget the sting of your sunburn!
That beach.
Man, I'll never get how you can talk about
that stuff at full volume
walking down the street.
Come on, man, who cares.
Let's just go!
My horoscope says tomorrow's
my lucky day for picking up girls!
To my place!
Isn't that Yarita?
Oh, Yoshimoto and Tajima?
D-Did he just say "Yarita"?
W-Wait, you mean it could be that Yarita?
Yarita the Jackhammer?
If he keeps at it,
he's totally gonna break us in two!
No wonder, his thing
was the size of a damn horse.
Hey, where'd you find those girls?
Snatched them from a pool somewhere?
Nice haul. Gonna have
yourself some fun, huh?
Hold up, that's Yukari and Megumi!
Please, help me!
If he does it, he'll tear me apart!
If you save us, we'll go out with you!
R-Really?!
Help me carry them,
and I'll let you have a turn too.
You traitors!
How could you side with that bastard?!
Didn't we promise to go out with you?!
Let me go, damn it!
Your idea of going out is probably
having some tea together, at best.
We know how you girls twist words.
Right, better take what's right in front of us
than dream about a possible screw.
No!
Save us from these perverts, somebody!
No...
She's so lively!
Ah, that feel, that smell... been a while.
Nemuro                  Kariya
Ugh... Digging holes in the summer heat
ain't easy, Nemuro.
What are you talking about?
It's your fault we got booted
from the pachinko parlor!
If you hadn't punched the manager,
I'd be chillin' under the A/C, smokin' right now!
Oh! If it isn't Kariya and Nemuro.
Still full of energy in this damn heat, huh?
Yarita?
Huh?
Tajima and Yoshimoto too!
Still full of energy in this damn heat, huh?
Yarita invited us out, can you believe it?
Wanna come too?
Better to sweat it out
inside a woman than out here.
Besides, these exhibitionists were strutting around the street in swimsuits,
so the more guys the merrier!
Let's go, boys!
Hell yeah, let's go!
Megumi, this is all your fault!
If you hadn't suggested we wear swimsuits,
none of this would've happened!
Like I knew it would make
all the other guys around here that riled up!
We're done for!
Five of them already.
I've never had more than
three at once before!
Yarita's the real problem here!
They say if he hammers you,
you won't walk right for a month!
What? A whole month?!
That'll ruin my summer!
We've gotta find a chance to run for it, fast.
Pass 'em, pass 'em, let's take turns!
Pass, pass, yeah, that's it!
Huh?
Weird. Where'd they go?
Guess they got pissed
and went to the pool or something.
Ikeuchi Clinic
Boss!
Hey, Takashi, you seen
Yukari and Megumi around?
Yeah, saw them near
the cleaning firm on Second Street.
Really, there?
Wait, Boss!
I wasn't done talking.
Hey, the girls are getting away!
How the hell did you idiots screw that up?!
Th-They kicked us in the balls!
Dumbasses! You let a couple of girls
get the drop on you!
Later!
Don't let them get away!
Like those snails
could ever catch up with us!
Not even the cops could catch us!
They're coming after us like maniacs!
H-How the hell can they run that fast?!
Don't waste your breath. At this rate...
...w-we'll definitely...
get caught!
Oh, found you two at last!
That hurt!
Wh-What the hell? Why'd you appear like that all of a sudden?
N-Never mind that!
Those guys were about to assault us!
Whoa!
Ah, R-Ryota-san!
So you idiots finally snapped from the heat
and decided to turn to sex crime, huh?
N-No way!
You got it all wrong!
We were just helping out, that's all...
Hey, did you catch them or not?
Ah, Ryota!
F-Fuck, he appeared at the worst possible time.
Yarita, you!
After all the warnings I gave you
back in the day, you haven't learned
and still treat women like toys?!
N-No, I'd never call them toys or anything...
If any one of you here is even thinking
of laying a hand on these girls,
then you'd better disappear before I count to three.
Do that, and I'll pretend I didn't see a thing.
One!
D-Don't expect a thank you.
If you hadn't ignored us in broad daylight,
this never would've happened!
Oh, right, I've got something for you girls.
This one's for Megumi,
And this one's for Yukari.
What's this?
Swimsuits. Women's stuff sure doesn't come cheap.
B-But why?
See, I just don't like the ones
you're wearing now.
Come on, hop in.
We're going to the beach!
The beach?
If we floor it now,
we'll make it to the sea before nightfall.
Tomorrow morning we'll hit the water
in those suits and swim our hearts out.
Yeah!
Nothing beats going to the beach
in summer, huh, Takashi?
Yeah, but... is this really okay?
You practically hijacked the bus.
No one's gonna miss one bus.
That's right!
Takashi, don't sweat the small stuff.
This bus is all ours, a private trip!
Takashi, why didn't you
bring Yuki-chan along?
Even I get tired of going out
with the same girl all the time.
I'm telling Yuki-chan on you!
Come on, Boss, just this once...
Nope, no way.
You kids should stick
to fooling around with each other.
That's right. We adults will have our own fun.
Isn't that right, Ryota-san?
Yeah, the sweet, fiery fun
only adults know. Right, Ryota-san?
FORBIDDEN
Ah, Ryota-san, you really are the best!
You're wonderful, Ryota-san!
FORBIDDEN
Hey, tonight, let's play harem
with Ryota-san and Yukari!
Harem. Harem...
Sounds perfect!
Let's start the prelude
right now, Ryota-san!
H-Hey, what about me?!
Kids should go poop
and hit the sack, right, Yukari?
That's right, bedtime for kids.
A-Aw, come on! I'm not a kid!
Fine then, if that's how it is,
I'll go flirt with some cute young thing myself!
R-Ryota-san, please pull over for a sec!
Hey, miss!
Wanna come to the beach with us?
Hey, come on!
Let's go, let's go!
No way! I'm too embarrassed!
Simply adorable!
No, really, I'm embarrassed!
Come on, get on the bus
made just for cute girls like you, okay?
I'm embarrassed, but...
kinda happy!
B-Boss!
Oh, how cute, he's blushing!
That's the spirit! Takashi, you and your girl shouldn't be shy. Go for it!
Here we go...
Help!
Tch. What a damn nuisance this bus is.
Let's blow right past it.
Why's a bus even driving on a road like this?
You're in the way, turtle-bus!
Heh-heh. Turtle-bus, huh?
Oh! They could've just passed quietly, but no.
Guess we'll have to show them
who the real turtle is.
Go all out!
Floor it!
All right, we can gun it full throttle now!
Think Masato can keep up?
Not bad, Masato!
Idiot! Behind you!
No way, seriously?!
How the hell's he hitting that speed
on a mountain road?!
Morons! Step on it!
Pedal to the floor!
We don't wanna end up tumbling
into the valley, so we're ahead! Like that!
Hell yeah!
I can feel it! Ecstasy!
I'm feeling ecstatic too!
Help!
Polish your driving, rookie!
Wh-What a maniac.
Hey, what the hell are you doing,
pulling up over there?
Ah, Kawai-san!
Hey, Takashi!
The boss gets all the fun! Geez...
Let's have some fun ourselves!
Let's take a boat out as well!
N-Nah, sorry, boats make me seasick.
Oh, poor thing. Then I'll comfort you
and help you get over it. Come on!
You've gotta be kidding me.
I always draw the short straw!
Oh, Takashi-san, you're so innocent!
What do you think
you're doing over there?!
Are you the one who was
rolling in that bus?
And what if I am?
Well, these guys here said your bus
nearly ran them off the road,
so I figured I'd stop by and have a word.
Oh, come on, Takashi-san!
Oh my, are those your friends?
Why the scary face?
Hey, don't be mean to Takashi-san!
Back off, ugly pig!
Raising your hand against a woman
who's not even involved? You're pathetic, man!
What was that?
Kawai-san!
You think you're tough, huh?
Y-You bastard!
T-Takashi-san...
You swine!
S-So cool! He's fighting for me.
Takashi-san, here,
help me up now, my knight!
Oh, you're such a tease!
Let go, idiot!
Don't be shy!
Stop following me!
Way to go, Takashi!
Look at him go!
What a wild scene, huh!
Boss! Help me!
Yukari and Megumi sure
are taking their time.
Maybe we went a little too far last night?
FORBIDDEN
Huh? Takashi's gone too.
Oh right, guess he was up all night too.
B-Boss! Help!
Oh?
Wait! My knight!
SOFT HALL
Oh no!
Those two never quit.
Hang in there, Takashi!
Hey! Hurry up!
BEACH HUT
Seriously, did you buy these
from an adult shop?!
You can't swim in things like this!
Rolling Ryota
Clash
Storyboard
Direction
Kanazawa Katsumasa
Yoshimoto Cycle
So? Look at this, Tajima!
I've got a new car!
A-A new car? Yoshimoto,
since when could you afford that?
Unlike you, I don't blow
my cash on good food.
I've been saving up bit by bit.
Thinking back to that summer
when I was eighteen...
I bought a used Cedric for 150,000 yen,
challenged Ryota with it,
and drowned it in the Arakawa River.
The long days when I had to make do
with the shop's pickup truck
and bum rides in your filthy cars...
All those ups and downs, while still spending too much on women... It was all for today's sake.
Yeah, that's nice, but all in all,
this baby must've cost around four mil.
So how much was the down payment?
A mil. The rest's on a thirty-six–month plan.
A-A mil?!
D-Didn't know you'd saved up that much.
Man, that's crazy.
But the monthly payments
must still be pretty steep, no?
Tajima, a real man's gotta take on some debt if he wants to grow big.
He's not acting like his usual self.
All right, first ride!
I swore I'd only let my girl ride shotgun,
but since you've always had my back,
I'll make an exception this once.
Make sure I'm not the only person you let ride here, all right?
All right, here we go!
Today marks my new beginning.
Go!
Damn, this feels incredible!
Y-Yoshimoto...
That's wrong, idiot, wrong, wrong!
Y-Yoshimoto, hang in there! You okay?
No! I said stop!
Why not, Yuki?
Just seeing your hips move like that,
I can't hold back anymore.
Geez, you're impossible...
in the middle of the day, even.
All right, just a quickie, okay?
All right, let's make it count!
Oh geez, Takashi, you're so bad.
All right, here I come, Yuki!
Ohno Auto Shop
Yes, Taka-chan! Taka-chan, right there!
Yuki!
Taka-chan!
Do it inside...
H-Here it comes!
Ah, Taka-chan, I'm coming!
T-Taka-chan!
Y-Yuki...
Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
He trashed Yoshimoto's brand-new four–million–yen car,
and then he took Takashi's Yuki-chan?
Just please find him, fast!
I can't forgive that driver, no way in hell.
Shut up.
I'm not doing this for your sake!
Yuki-chan not wearing any panties
is my only motivation.
Boss!
Yuki...
What's gonna happen to Yuki, boss?!
Quit your whining!
Looks like the bastards want
a head-on showdown.
KAMIKAZE
Wait up!
You guys okay?!
B-Barely...
Akada Shigeki
Oh! Akada Shigeki?
Akada? Then the one driving
must be Aoyagi Gunji, right?
Yeah, that bastard Aoyagi's
the one who wrecked my car!
Yuki-chan!
Ryota!
Thanks for the beating last time.
I came to return the favor today!
Yuki!
This time, thanks to a hostage,
I won't lose to you.
So think twice before you make a move!
One wrong move and this girl will meet her fate.
I can throw her off anytime! See?!
No, stop! Please!
What the hell are you doing
at a time like this?!
Seriously?! Peeping is all you care about?
Oh, gimme a break!
I shouldn't have told you
she's going commando, dammit!
Now, how should I have fun
with this chick first?
T-Taka-chan...
Akada! Lay one filthy finger
on Yuki and I'll kill you!
Takashi! This is what you get
for hanging around Ryota all the time.
If you've gotta blame someone, blame him!
No!
No...
Yuki...
This girl's got a pretty nice rack, huh?
Guess I'll strip her panties off next.
S-Stop!
Violating a girl like this out here...
Now that's a thrill.
N-No!
Oh?
Hey, wait, what the hell.
She's not even wearing panties!
What a slut, this one.
Maybe I'll drag her through the shopping district like this,
lift her skirt, and let everyone have a look! Whaddya say, huh?!
Come on, give us your ass!
Now, let them see it all first!
No! S-Stop!
Come on, up we go now...
There!
There, like that!
Taka-chan!
FORBIDDEN
There, there, there!
S-Stop...
Please stop!
All right! If you don't want to watch me
shoving my manhood into this girl,
Takashi, hit Ryota!
Hit the driver, Ryota!
Go on!
Do it, or I'll ravish her right now!
Takashi, do what he says!
B-But how could I?
Hitting my own boss...
Come on, what are you waiting for?!
Hurry up or I'll do it!
Why are you hesitating?
Takashi, if I see him screw Yuki-chan,
I'll burn that sight into my brain
and jerk off to it later!
Boss...
Damn it!
Yes!
Good, Takashi!
Now keep hitting him. Don't stop!
I-I'm sorry!
Just keep punching!
This is too damn good!
How's it feel, Ryota,
getting beaten down like that?
Keep going! Beat him to death!
Aoyagi Gunji,
who had surprisingly
little screen time
Aoyagi Gunji,
who had surprisingly
little screen time
Shit, he's having the time of his life up there.
You bastard, cut it out already!
Huh?
Don't "Huh?" me!
You bastard!
Even though he urged Takashi himself...
You don't wanna cross that man.
I don't know...
Whoa! The wheel...
Hey, can you really keep up, Yoshimoto?
You bet!
That son of a bitch totaled
my brand-new four–million–yen car!
If it weren't for Yuki-chan,
we could've rammed right into them!
See? 'Cause of you, they can't
make a move, only tail us helplessly!
Huh?
What the hell's this?
What the hell are you doing,
you bitch?!
Yuki-chan!
What's going on?
You broad!
I don't care if you die now!
Take this!
Bitch!
Move!
Fuck you!
You whore!
Cut it out, Akada!
Takashi! Catch her!
All right!
Tch! Unbelievable!
Damn it, I lost the hostage.
Aoyagi, isn't it about time
to give them a head-on showdown?
Tch. You're having all the fun yourself.
You could at least get a license, dammit!
Shit! He rammed us?
You're gonna pay for this, you bastards!
We're gonna dump you into the sea
together with your truck!
Shit! Aoyagi, swing us around.
Hit them head-on!
No can do! We got rear-ended earlier,
so the brakes got soft from the shock!
What?!
Oh, don't make me laugh!
They're trying to run!
You think you can outrun me?!
Hey, Akada, at this rate,
we'll fly straight into the ocean!
Even Ryota won't be able
to stop in time at this speed!
If we're going down,
we're taking them with us!
Go!
R-Ryota-san! Stop! Stop!
W-We're not gonna make it!
Relax, I've got this.
H-Hey, we're going down!
Wh-What the fuck just happened?!
We're sinking, Akada!
All right, let's get Yuki-chan to a hospital!
Yeah!
You okay, Yuki-chan?
Yeah...
Bastard hurt you so bad... You, a girl!
Me, I only lost a lousy
four–million–yen car...
R-Ryota-san, stop, stop!
We've gotta catch those bastards
and make them pay for my new car: four mil!
Treating Yuki-chan's wounds comes first!
No way! You're letting them escape!
Someone trusted me with their life
I'll give them mine
In the rear view, the city shines
With the eyes of starving beasts
Ambitious guys, they don't care for your opinion
That's how I roll, roll, roll, roll, Rolling Ryota
Translation &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
MartyMcflies
anonymous