Okizari Fansubs presents
Rolling Ryota
Someone trusted me with their life
I'll give them mine
In the rear view, the city shines
With the eyes of starving beasts
Ambitious guy, they don't care for your opinion
That's how I roll, roll, roll, roll, Rolling Ryota
If I leave regrets behind and wipe my tears
The woman I loved clings to me
Whether I live for love or die for justice,
I decide myself
Here I go, proud hands on the wheel
That's how I roll, roll, roll, roll, Rolling Ryota
Blown by the wind, deep in my heart
There's a song for the boys
The dawn over Mizutoge burns
Right here inside my chest
Fifty thousand horsepower, a man's pride
That's how I roll, roll, roll, roll, Rolling Ryota
Hurry up!
You gotta hang in there!
No! Help me!
Hey, don't drive like a madman!
I don't want to die!
God! Buddha! Or even the Devil!
Why didn't I get off earlier?!
Hang in there! You can do it!
It's starting! The baby's coming!
Protagonist Takao Ryota, AKA
Rolling Ryota
Just leave it to me!
I'll take you straight to the hospital!
Uh... Everyone on board, we'll hit a rough patch up ahead, so hang on to your seats, please.
Gramps and grannies with dentures,
hold your mouths shut.
Here I go! Make way for Lord Rolling Ryota!
Out of the way!
Please! Hurry it up! It's coming!
I-I'm gonna pee my pants!
I'm the Hero!!
Stop
Tch. Why stop now of all times?
When someone's in trouble, you help.
That's what you do.
Who did that?
Upsy-daisy...
It's that old hag?
Old women these days
are more spoiled than kids.
Please, hurry!
Hey, get off quickly, will you?
Next time I'm taking away the priority seats.
Takeoff!
H-Help me!
Learn to understand other people's pain,
from your own experience.
Here we go!
Faster, please!
Hey! There were tons of people
waiting at that stop.
Was it okay to blow right past it?
This is an express to the hospital!
Darling, our bus...
What was that?
S-Stop the bus! I want to get off here!
We're taking off.
What?
We're flying!
A cliff?!
Did it! Three hours, one minute,
thirty-two seconds. A new record!
Hey, Mama-to-be! We've arrived.
He was trying to kill us!
A penny a day.
Did a good deed today too.
Y-You idiot!
Takao-kun, you've done it again!
Bus Depot Manager
You're the biggest threat to public safety
this town has ever seen!
Driving a bus like a madman, not stopping
at bus stops... What do you think you're doing?!
Complaints are flooding in!
What are we gonna do?!
If you cause trouble again, you'll be...
Yes, yes, I understand!
I'll be careful. Thank you.
Horse Racing News
And one more thing: no checking racing tips in the driver's seat. Got it?!
Tch. I already have to refrain
from betting at my workplace,
and now I can't even make predictions? Fuck me...
MANAGER
Well, your job's on the line too.
DELIVERY ROOM
Thank God. Thank God!
You did really well.
It's also thanks to that bus driver.
SNACK LEVY
My shoulders are killing me today.
Ryota's sworn younger brother
................Ohno Takashi
You pissed off the manager again, didn't you?
Ryota's girlfriend
.............Mika
If you keep acting like a total moron,
you'll get fired, Ryo-chan.
Can't be helped.
All the bikers around the country
are scared stiff. Rolling Ryota...
He's settling down as a bus driver?
No way he'd be able to stand it.
Takashi, you've had enough for tonight.
What, already? It's still early.
Come on, Ryo-chan.
Don't ask. Just go home.
I see. If that's the case, I'll make myself scarce.
Mika, how much is it?
On me tonight. Ryo-chan's treat.
No way! That'd be rude to my boss!
Oh, don't be shy.
In exchange, make sure my car
gets fixed up real good.
Oh, so that's what you meant?
Sure, sure. Consider it done.
SNACK LEVY
Ryo-chan, I love you.
All right, attaway.
Ah! Spare me! Spare me!
His voice
Sounds dry now
When it came to loving
He got lazy
There are seasons
But he can't see them
Poison runs
Through his heart
My job
Is to do justice
To sing songs
In the far corners of the Earth
I'll stay free
Until I die
In this corner of the Earth
I'll sing my songs
Sunday shift, pathetic...
Tch. I'm out of luck.
All right!
Izumi Dental Clinic
No wins at pachinko,
no girls to hang out with.
Panthers' members
.............Toshi and Kawada
What rotten luck, just as we finally have
a Sunday all to ourselves.
Wh-Why's there a bus here?!
This narrow backstreet's
no place for a bus!
Whoa! Watch out!
Damn you, bussing motherfucker!
Take this!
Did it!
Did you dimwits throw that stone?
Whoa there! For a bus driver, you're pretty flashy.
I asked if you threw it or not!
Are you picking a fight with us members
of the Panthers biker gang?
T-Toshi!
Y-You prick!
Instead of hanging around
like you've got nothing better to do,
think of the folks stuck working the Sunday shift.
Who the hell was that?
I get it now.
Panthers' Leader
Henmi
That's got to be Rolling Ryota.
Rolling Ryota?
There's not another bus driver
in the world as reckless as him.
Who is that guy?
Well, he's from another era,
so of course you wouldn't know him.
Maybe we don't know him,
but if this keeps up...
I get wanting revenge...
but forget the wolf bite and move on.
Still...
You guys are good-hearted
members of the Panthers.
Better to avoid dangerous people like that.
Fuck!
I don't like this.
Even Henmi-san's changed.
Back in the day, if the Panthers got hit,
we wouldn't just be quiet.
Yeah, right.
We'd pick up our wooden swords
and raid the fuckers.
If the leader's like that,
the Panthers won't last long.
Truly.
But is Ryota really that dangerous?
Who knows? You can never tell from just one hit.
What are you saying?
You were sprawled out back then.
You idiot.
You were twitching too, weren't you?
Still, he one-punch KO'd us both.
That's a hard fact, bro.
What's wrong, Toshi?
Hey, hey...
Come on, hang out with us, Ryo-chan!
Ah... Hold up... Hey! I said no!
Working on a Sunday isn't like you, Ryo-chan.
A girl who admires Ryota
Umeko...................
Hey, keep me company tonight.
I said no, and that means no!
If I hang out with the likes of you,
I'll end up losing something important!
Huh? Isn't that Umeko, who you always fancied?
And that guy with her...
Ryo-chan, I feel so good.
You're reaching my deepest part!
Later, Umeko!
If I feel like it, I'll dump you!
Ryo-chan!
D-Damn it!
To think "Ryo-chan" was him, of all guys!
Huh? What are you on about?
That Umeko always used to say,
"Ryo-chan's an idol.
He's too good for someone like me."
So I just assumed...
Assumed what?
I thought it was Sugi Ryotaro!
Sugi Ryo?!
What are you thinking? Surely,
she wouldn't fall in love with someone that old!
But Umeko bought tickets
to Sugi Ryo's concert just the other day!
Maybe her mom asked her to?
Hey, Kawada! Tell me!
I don't know anything about that!
Was Umeko actually in love with that guy?
Damn! I was secretly practicing every night for her sake.
Kawada, that Ryota guy...
I guess the bus depot is
the best place to face him.
T-Toshi, what are you...
Tch! Toshi, that idiot!
I'm cumming! I'm at my limit!
I-I'm getting there too!
Henmi-san! Henmi-san!
Tch! Who's that, now of all times?!
Shut up!
We're in trouble!
Oh, it's you again?
That punk Toshi got all fired up
and went to see Ryota on his own!
Oh man, what'll I do with that idiot?
That's on him. I did warn you two, didn't I?
Please! Come with us, Henmi-san!
Don't be ridiculous!
When Ryota's involved, you stay out of it!
Don't say that! Please, Henmi-san!
Is Ryota really that tough?
Of course! Biker gangs from all over Japan
challenged him, and nobody could touch him.
Then we don't stand a chance.
So give up, wontcha?
No way we will.
I heard he's got a sworn
younger brother he dotes on.
Yeah, the leader of Sally Crown,
Takashi, right?
What if we take that guy hostage?
Yeah! Let's do that.
Then Ryota won't be able to act.
A hostage, huh?
All right, let's give it a shot.
OHNO AUTO SHOP
Hey, Takashi!
Oh? B-Boss!
How's my car looking?
It's fine. I'll have it done by evening.
I've got a date tomorrow,
so make it perfect, okay?
Don't worry. Go do your job.
You've got passengers waiting.
Uh? Yeah...
Well, just leave the car to me.
Come on, hurry! Get going!
What are you doing?
Right, right, we're going.
All right, then.
I'll bring it by tonight.
If he's that worried,
he's really fired up about tomorrow's girl.
What's that about a girl?
Yo.
The hell! Yuki?
You're always wandering around.
Do you even go to school?
Takashi's girlfriend
Yuki...........
I do! Twice a week.
Meanwhile, you're still fixing
Ryota's car for free, huh?
Shut up!
It's silly. Just because Ryota helped you before,
you're acting like his lackey.
Maybe you secretly like him?
Ah, how pathetic.
And here I was thinking
the leader of Sally Crown was my man...
Wh-Who's your man?!
Don't decide that for me!
Ouch! My stomach hurts! It hurts like
I'm about to miscarry Taka-chan's baby!
All right! I got it!
Once it's fixed, I'll take you out, okay?
You say that, but honestly,
you couldn't be happier I came.
"It'll be free today."
Isn't that what you truly think about?
Ah, you're blushing!
I hit the nail on the head!
Oh, geez! Pervert! So you still
don't have a woman to sleep with!
Shut up! I shouldn't have to pay
every time if it's with you!
Why, you...
Ugh, pathetic!
Raping a girl at such a young age!
I-It's not that!
Hey... That tickles!
T-Taka-chan!
Yuki!
Taka-chan, I'm coming!
Hey! Hide, Yuki!
Just do it! Go hide now
if you don't wanna get gang-raped!
What the hell?!
Don't park that filthy car in a place like this!
O-Oh crap, there are three of them?
Hey, aren't you too cocky
for someone who has to fight alone?
What?! Who do you think you're talking to?
You prick...
Asshole!
Why, you...
Stop running and come at me already!
Hey, friend, do you even know how much this hurts?
And you just swing it around willy-nilly.
Take this!
Taka-chan...
Ryo-chan, you're in the fast lane today.
Am I?
You've polished off a whole bottle already.
Oh, it's quite all right.
Huh? Why are you in uniform?
Duh, I'm still on duty, remember?
What? You're working on Sunday?
Bingo! There's a bus parked in that alley.
With passengers?
It's nothing. They're probably just killing time too.
More importantly, wanna have some fun on the second floor?
Geez...
What are you thinking?!
Sober up and get going!
You're hopeless, I swear.
I'll die. I'll just die!
I'll crash into a soapland and die!
This is hopeless.
Ah! He's here!
Takao-san! You said it was just a little errand,
so where've you been for forty minutes?
I'm gonna be late getting home!
Shut up.
I said I'd drop each of you off at your place.
After making us wait 40 minutes, that's it?
Yeah, exactly!
Fine, fine, I'll give you a free ride too.
Whatever, I know.
I never wanted to be rolling
in my bus on a Sunday as well.
I've got the reputation of Rolling Ryota to uphold.
Bikers............................................................
Yoshimoto Kattobi Ma-kun
We could go grab a bite here, right, Yoshimoto-san?
Yeah.
HAMBURGERS
U-Um, if you park your car there, the bus...
You could board your fucking bus from anywhere.
O-Oh no...
Huh? Who's the dumbass
that stopped in a place like that?
Yoshimoto-san!
D-Damn it! He did it, didn't he?!
H-Hey, wait!
All right! Go ahead, get on!
HAMBURGERS
You bastard! You rammed our car.
Fuck your "Get on!" You get off, you idiot!
HAMBURGERS
What? You telling me to get off?
H-Huh?
Fine by me!
HOLY FUCK
What's with that attitude?! You're not getting away with just the repair bill, you punk!
Dumbass!
Biker
........Koji the Crossdresser
Wh-What are you doing, Yoshimoto-san?!
You shut it too!
Oh, so sorry! He doesn't know any better,
so please let it slide, yeah?
Ah, did your bumper get dented?
If it did, I'll pay for it.
Good. I'll let it slide this once.
Just make sure you never park at a bus stop again.
Got it. We'll be careful from now on.
Takao Ryota...
Can't believe that guy's a bus driver now.
Guess we'll have to think twice
before passing any buses from now on.
Anyway, I'm going home now.
You guys take care too.
Easy for Yoshimoto to say,
since his car didn't get totaled.
But me?
My beloved baby just got rear-ended!
Whoever did it,
we'll just pay him back in kind!
That's right! No way we're letting someone
trash our ride and walk away!
You know what they call me?
Kattobi Ma-chan!
Yeah!
Hot stuff!
Let's roll, Koji!
You got it!
Oh! So you wanna play?
Fucker! You smash into our car
and just grin about it?!
Stop right there!
Stop, or I'll make you stop!
What are you on about?
You want me to ram you in the ass
because you're a fucking pansy?!
What did you just call me, you boor?!
Oh, now I'm mad!
How's that?!
Damn, he dodged them all.
Y-You idiot!
How do you miss something that big?!
You think this is a game?!
But... Um, you see...
You... Y-You jerkface!
Got it! Nailed the mirror. The mirror.
Idiot! Don't get happy over that!
Aw, fuck, I'm getting dizzy...
I just can't trust you for anything!
We'll charge him head-on, bunt-style!
Now that's gutsy, Ma-kun!
Kamikaze move.
Let's see if he's got the balls to take it!
Y-You bastard!
He's not turning!
That guy's out of his mind!
He's looking down on us
because our car's small!
Here he comes again!
When did he catch up?!
He's totally after our asses!
Hey, you!
Here comes the Okama Thrust!
Ah, here he comes!
Too rough, I hate this.
Step on it and lose him!
Idiot! I'm flooring it already!
Really?
What now?!
Th-That's right. That guy's gotta be
the infamous Rolling Ryota.
N-No way!
Ah! I'm telling you, it's him!
What's wrong, Koji?!
I just remembered.
R-Remembered what?
If Rolling Ryota's after your ass,
your youth's officially over!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
There's no saving us now.
The only way to appease that guy
is to ditch the car!
That's why all the old-timers
ride bicycles now.
I totally couldn't do that.
HOLY FUCK
No way!
I still got 32 payments left on this car!
You think I can afford to ride a bike?!
Stop!
R-Ryota-san, help!
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
Taka-chan got taken by the Panthers gang!
The Panthers?
They said you have to come
to the Arakawa riverbank by seven, or else!
I wonder what they want.
Please, you have to go!
If you don't, they'll dump
Taka-chan in the river!
Even if you say that, I'm still on duty here.
Don't go playing the diligent employee now!
Toshi, what time is it?
Way past seven already.
Guess even Ryota's lost his nerve,
being outnumbered like this.
Don't be stupid!
The boss ain't like you punks!
What was that?!
Then maybe he ditched you already, huh?
Fine by me.
Then you can join
the trash floating in the river.
Boss!
Hi! Still at it?!
Ryota...
You showed up, you bastard!
Come on, knock it off already!
Another detour?
A regular ticket won't cover it.
You owe us a commuter pass now.
Man, passengers sure talk tough these days.
I don't feel right...
Boss! Not now of all times!
He's drunk! Don't hold back!
Flatten him, bus and all!
What the hell?! What's going on?!
No! Help me!
I can't tell what's happening anymore.
All right, now.
Ah, whatever. Floor it!
Yeah! That's my boss!
Even drunk, he's still got it!
Boss! That's enough! You did it!
Boss!
OHNO AUTO SHOP
Tch, in this state,
I can't work worth a damn.
Unbelievable. I sure have one helluva boss.
He can't even tell friend from foe
when he's hammered.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Our talk show tonight welcomes the bus driver
who wiped out an entire biker gang.
Takao Ryota-san! Welcome!
I'm Takao, the enemy of biker gangs.
How's it going?
You sure pulled off something incredible.
You fought off twenty bikers, didn't you?
Yeah, I was desperate, honestly.
They had me cornered,
no way to escape.
All I could think about was the passengers' safety.
But with opponents like that, well...
I had no choice but to take drastic action.
And you ended up turning
twenty vehicles into scrap metal.
That's quite a skill you have!
Well, driving's my profession, after all.
How about a drive together tonight or tomorrow?
My...
You're quite a people person, Takao-san.
Oh, not really...
I underestimated you.
What can I say? Put a beauty in front of me,
and I've got to make a move.
After all, no man worth his salt goes
for the main course before the aperitif.
Why the hell's the boss
getting all the glory?!
We heard that biker gangs
have been stirring up a lot of trouble.
Any thoughts on that?
Yes. Drivers should always follow the rules,
irrespective of their allegiance.
Reckless bikers don't deserve
to be behind the wheel.
H-How dare he...
Spoken like a true bus driver.
Your professional discipline
made that act of justice possible.
Well, you could say that.
That fucker!
We're not letting this slide!
We'll roll again next time!
His voice
Sounds dry now
When it came to loving
He got lazy
There are seasons
But he can't see them
Poison runs
Through his heart
If he could live
Without getting hurt
Life would sure be
An easy gig
But justice
Always comes swinging hard
And the Earth
Must be sick, for sure
My job
Is to do justice
To sing songs
In the far corners of the Earth
I'll stay free
Until I die
In this corner of the Earth
I'll sing my songs
Translation &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
MartyMcflies
anonymous