I never had a mole on my neck.
Th-Then, the kid in this photo...
Hibino Aya
...is a lookalike.
Protagonist: University Freshman
Terayama Suekichi
I-It's a different person?!
B-But how...
Attorney
Tachimi Tadanori
There goes...
...my inheritance.
450 million!
DaNCE till Tomorrow
Orphan Fansubs presents
It's been 49 days since my great-grandfather died.
Maybe that one?
Doesn't seem likely.
Y-Yeah.
Moles from childhood
can disappear over time.
So perhaps it was you, after all?
I wonder...
What are you two doing?
Ah, no... We're...
More importantly, didn't this house change in the meantime?
Granddaughter of Terayama Daikichi
Sue
Y-Yes.
The way our world works these days,
when vying for inheritance or anything else,
the loudest contender usually wins.
You're suspicious!
A-Are you...
A specialist in tasteful interior design.
A highly renowned daughter
of the loudest family.
That's right.
This is me.
So that's how it was?
What about it?
Then, were you on good terms
with great-grandpa?
I wouldn't go as far as that.
Though we did have a lot in common,
as fellow misfits.
Still, no matter how I look at it,
this seems like a boy's picture.
I changed a lot, didn't I?
Back then, everyone said I was the cutest tomboy.
Better tell me!
Why are you asking me all this?!
W-Well...
I-I was curious about what sort of things Daikichi-sama did during his lifetime.
Suspicious.
Look, you're a little too precocious
for a primary schooler.
Except I'm in middle school now!
It's kinda refreshing, actually.
Now I can safely quit university and focus on the troupe and my part-time job.
Then I'll proceed to become a producer of musicals that will conquer the world.
World-famous Terayama
Huge Broadway Hit
Even if we assume that,
Daikichi-sama pronounced your name pretty clearly.
Wasn't he senile?
I'm home.
Ah, welcome back!
Did you find the child with a mole?
It's none of your business!
More importantly, why this feast?
Freddy-kun said you looked
depressed for some reason.
Yes, here.
It's my country's cuisine,
just what you need for stamina.
Suekichi's Freeloader
Freddy
But hey, the will has your name on it, doesn't it?
Listen, you...
Oh, it's a little spicy
but actually quite good.
Do you eat this every day?
No, no! My country, my family poor!
This yum-yum is a feast for special occasion!
You could make really good money
and live rich in our country.
That's right! I have zero money now.
Still, I'll be working hard, starting now,
to become a moneyed man.
"He has zero money"?
Hibino, did you pay
for the ingredients?
No. Freddy-kun procured it all himself.
Yeah! I found it over there, so I took it for myself!
You can buy many-many stuff
with Japanese money!
I only left it there yesterday.
Why'd you take it?
It was supposed to last us for ten days!
I don't really understand Japanese, dick.
Sounds to me like you've acquired more than enough of it!
Ow, dick...
Want me to lend you some?
That's not what I'm getting at!
But you could still use it, right?
Oh, will you really bankroll me?
Hibino has thoroughly
outsmarted me once again.
Lately, I feel like
my bald spot is growing.
Your breakfast is ready.
Where's Freddy?
He went job hunting.
"I'm tired of being broke all the time," he said.
So he can be conscientious too?
History knows many cases like that.
During the Sino-Japanese War,
you know that Japan did nasty stuff to the people of Southeast Asia?
Way worse than what's happening between Iraq and Kuwait.
Don't you mean the Pacific War?
As I'd expect of Suekichi-kun,
the university student!
She's horny again?
D-Don't you need to leave for your part-time job?
Are you taking a day off?
Y-You're right.
What?
Seaweed and pickled radish​?
All the stuff I can't stomach!
You'll only get balder
if you talk like that.
Here, I'll put on some medicine.
No, it's because you're getting in my hair!
Ah, what nice weather!
I do love a warm Sunday.
Why are you still following me?
I've got nothing better to do, remember?
Suekichi-kun, you know,
I was just about to tell you...
Then, you spent those 5,000 yen
on medicine and food?!
You should appreciate my concern
when I buy stuff for you.
I can't even get
to my part-time job now!
Wanna go pick up where we left off?
Don't be silly.
Can't be helped. Want a loan?
Tsk...
So you have a day off.
How long you gonna hang out here?
Terayama-kun, we're short-staffed,
so we'll be in deep doodoo if you give all your attention to your girlfriend.
I wasn't doing anything like that!
Short-staffed?
I see, I see! You're stuck in a foreign land
where you don't know anyone?
How very admirable!
Terayama-kun, isn't that a good story?
My, I have a soft spot for such stories.
I just can't help crying!
Are you really sure about this?
This kind of energetic young men
is just what our store needs.
So will you really be able to work
until 5 AM, starting now?
Isn't that better? Higher hourly wage.
Good for you, Freddy-kun.
All thanks to you, Aya-san.
All right, then.
First, when a customer comes in, greet them with a wide smile.
Got it. Greet them with a wide smile.
Dick!
I thought he'd say that.
Huh?
You forgot to pay your electric bill?
I'll go pay it now.
Ah, wait!
Would you prefer to live
in the dark until next month?
I also bought dinner on the way.
The total here is 21,657 yen.
I never asked you to buy
anything like that!
You don't want dinner?
The electricity will be
back on tomorrow.
Say, aren't you supposed
to enjoy eating more than that?
How can I enjoy it at all?
Huh? Is it just me, or did your bald spot get bigger again?
Look!
Don't pluck it!
I guess losing the inheritance
came as quite a shock, huh?
Good boy, good boy.
At last, it's just the two of us again.
In that case, let's relieve our stress!
You don't see me as anything more
than a sex object, do you?!
Aren't you the one
who sees me that way?
You're wrong.
What am I to you, then?
The inheritance receiver Suekichi-kun.
Why are you still going on about that?!
Just kidding! Do you really
doubt my love?
Where is that "love"? I don't see any.
There is love! Right here, here!
My, you young beast!
Look how it perked right up!
Why, you...
Huh?
The gentleman has woken up?
It's 3 o'clock?
Tachimi-san, I don't think
I can help you anymore.
It would be a mistake to see
this issue so simply.
After all, we're talking about
an inheritance of 400 million.
What should I do about that now?
You got Sue. Just approach her.
I'm sure you two can work it out.
However, upon closer scrutiny of Daikichi-sama's will,
Sue-sama's name does not appear in it, even once.
That's because he was probably senile!
If I choose Sue-sama
as the beneficiary,
the will won't be executed for at least ten years.
Naturally, I wouldn't want whatever
course of action I elect to harm you.
Therefore, would you please let me
leave this matter undecided for a while?
Okay.
Of course, I'd rather you not divulge this matter to anyone else.
All right. But that means I can't quit university just yet, doesn't it?
Correct. If possible.
Up I go!
Hi!
I missed my train.
Can I stay overnight? Please?
Ah! I wrote the wrong number again!
Look, I came all the way here, so this isn't the time to be glaring at numbers!
That's not cool.
Shut up!
If I don't finish this, the company's next performance won't stand a chance!
Then, I'll make it stand...
for you!
Stop being so forward. I'm busy!
Then, should I stop?
I don't mind you continuing, actually.
Damn it!
Ah! There we go...
The account book...
Gotta finish it first, after all.
No, you don't.
What are you doing, you sex maniac?!
I'm feeling lonely.
Let's take a bath together
to cheer you up, like newlyweds!
Just who are the newlyweds, may I ask?
I can't be doing this now.
Wait!
Why do you have to go collect the money when it's so late?
Any other time,
nobody would be home!
Ah... Money! I just need to raise money!
150,000?
I'm that much behind?
Month after month,
everyone runs away from me.
But this month,
I'm getting you to pay up!
I don't have what I don't have.
Then, how do you suppose
we can rehearse
after they boot us out
of that cheap theater?
L-Listen, I understand...
Troupe Member
Ikezu Daisuke
If you do, why aren't you paying what you're supposed to every month?
That's why I'm working part-time!
You've got some nerve to collect money right here, at my sacred workplace.
'Cause this is the only place
I can catch you!
Where do you go to stay
every single night?!
Hey you, noisy guy. You two smell of the same brand of soap.
You just had sex, didn't you?
Y-You've gotta be kidding!
Bingo!
So you did?
Yeah!
I'm serious!
Man, you really are one dull guy.
Ikezu-san, you don't need
the role, do you?
In any case, right now I'm penniless!
So wait a bit, dammit!
By the way, Aya-chan.
Our Suekichi in good shape?
Been pretty shapeless lately.
This has nothing to do with you!
Seems like you hoarded a lot here.
H-Hey!
Terayama, do you have
any idea what time it is?
2:47 and 30 seconds. 31. 32.
I came to collect your share!
Wait-Wait-Wait!
Oh? Isn't this a burglary?
I'm doing this for the troupe!
Now we'll still have access
to the Toyota Theater.
Still, there's one more
problem on the list.
It's morning already.
We did it three times, then walked all night. How come you're still so chipper?
"As long as people have purpose in life,
no mountain is insurmountable..."
What?
Really! Falling asleep here,
of all places!
I'm sorry! Please give me
a few more days.
Tickets for the upcoming
performance are sold out.
You said you'd be sure to pay!
You still owe me for printing posters and fliers for your last performance!
That's why I'm asking
for a few more days.
Haven't I warned you over and over
that a marginal troupe like yours
can't afford all those
extravagant costumes?
And yet, didn't you say, "It'll be all right," every single time?!
I'm sorry! Our next performance
should be a big hit.
It'll rake in the dough,
so I'll pay you back afterward!
Hey, boy, you think you can make a buck with a play?
Yes. Shimomura-san's play is special.
Even that's possible.
It'll be a success for sure.
But until that happens, we're getting by
with part-time jobs and the like.
MONEY
Long time no see.
Hey, young man!
H-Hello!
I thoroughly enjoyed
your play the other day.
It was a sight to behold.
Wh-What a coincidence,
meeting you here and all.
The theater's on the second floor,
and my office is on the third.
Y-You've got a point there!
I guess it wasn't
a coincidence at all, then!
Are you busy?
Y-Yes. Well, I'm actually up to my eyeballs in money matters.
Money?
W-Well, I-I'm collecting the dues, a-and...
L-Long story short,
it's like collecting debts.
Well, that's kinda
how I spend my days.
I see. Collecting debts, are you?
So you're doing the same thing as us?
By the way...
Y-Yes?
Why don't you leave it to the pros
to handle this kinda thing?
Th-The pros, you say?
At this rate, if we don't
collect the needed sum,
the troupe will inevitably disband.
Well, here goes nothing!
P-Please do it!
Theory of Drama
"One's acting depends
on his own experience?"
Theory of Drama
Want me to give you
an interesting experience?
You're too young to be reading this kinda stuff!
Wh-What's the meaning of this, out of the blue?!
The show must go on.
For that to happen, someone has to pay!
Hey, guys!
Incredible fervor!
Ah! Terayama!
Hey, young man.
Is this enough to cover his share?
Y-Yes.
A Loving Hand for Needy Children
DONATIONS
A dead end. Is this guy
a volunteer or something?
The needy child he's talking about is himself.
We don't know if he's just making ends meet or working part-time like this.
Can you make living at it?
Who knows?
A Loving Hand for Needy Children
DONATIONS
Thank you, dear.
A frog! Frog!
DONATIONS
We're here to collect your share.
R-Ribbit...
Someone's at the door.
Well, go see who it is, then.
We're at your place!
Are we really?
Sheesh! Who could it be?
Come on, it's broad daylight.
Hey there, Ikezu-san.
What's with "Hey there"?
Didn't I pay you yesterday?
Yes, but not all of it.
You should know better than to bother people basking in the afterglow of sex.
What about all the other guys
who still owe you?
Actually, I've already
collected most of it.
No way you did!
Everyone in the troupe
says they're broke!
Been a while.
You gonna do it or not?
Why are those guys here with you?
They're helping our troupe out.
Why are you shooting the breeze?
See? You had money!
So how much did we collect in total?
Well, somewhere in the ballpark...
Why are you hiding it?
No, I'm not hiding it. It's just that this money is important for the troupe!
You think you can keep it all?
Give it to me now !
This money is important to us.
Chief, here!
What a pitiful sum.
Can you really stage a play with this?
No matter how pitiful, it's important! We need it for the play! Give it back!
Watch your hand, or it'll get cut with something metal when we return it.
You can't just ask yakuza to work for you
and get away with it for free.
Is that clear?!
Y-Yes!
Well, I'll go easy on you.
That much should do.
Here, your share.
O-Only half...
If you're being so hard pressed for such a paltry sum, look, we can negotiate.
Y-Yes?
Your girlfriend, that minx Hibino.
If you give her to us as collateral,
you can ask me for any sum.
W-Well, Hibino's not really my girlfriend.
If so, that's a shame.
Well, good luck with your play.
After the settlement of accounts,
it was 600,000 this time.
The total deficit through the previous performance was three million.
Presently, we're over 3.6 million in the red.
Why did you go to the trouble of gathering everyone to report something like that?
Because of "something like that,"
creditors flock to the rehearsal room every day!
If this continues,
we won't have a next performance!
Isn't it common for troupes to keep going while three or four million in debt?
Except the size of our troupe
isn't proportional to that debt!
And we won't get any sponsors
until we become bigger, either!
That's easier said than done.
Look, if I perform more than four times a year, I'll lose my part-time job.
I think it's a good opportunity.
Why don't we take a break and
use the time to make some money?
Besides, I thought it's a producer's job
to reduce our expenses.
It's naive to think we can't get sponsors
because we're a minor troupe.
Sheesh! You can't hold Suekichi-kun
responsible for everything!
Aren't you spending too much on sets?
We should focus more on the actors,
put on simple plays.
Bondage Horse Troupe Director
Shimomura Masami
What's the point of bringing that up now?
I gotta get to my part-time job soon.
Something's wrong with all of you!
You care more about your jobs
or saving money on sets!
You're treating the theater like a hobby!
But the hard fact is,
we don't have any money.
All right. As far as money's concerned,
I'll try to scrounge some up.
A week from now,
we'll have another meeting.
Meanwhile, get your priorities straight.
I'd take three million today
over the phantom 450 million someday.
Should I borrow money
with Hibino as collateral?
Those yakuza are after Hibino!
Think I'd let it slide?!
But those guys are yakuza, after all.
Yoohoo!
Is the troupe strapped
for cash big time?
Yoohoo. It sure is. Who told you?
Ikezu-san.
Blabbing about everything again!
I can get you like a million
or so, if you want.
How come you have so much money?
I'll lend it to you.
No interest, no collateral.
Investing in me is a fool's errand.
But you have an inheritance to your name, don't you?
If you don't lose your courage,
you'll still get about half of it.
You're still on about that!
There's no way you'll ever be resourceful enough to own a detached house in Tokyo.
I can't imagine living in this cramped one-bedroom apartment
for the rest of my life.
Who said I'm gonna live with you
for the rest of my life?!
I'm leaving.
Oh, by the way, Ikezu-san said he's quitting the troupe.
Internally, the troupe is a steaming mess.
I can't deal with that,
so I'm leaving for now.
What will you do after you've left?
I don't feel like performing for any other troupe beside Shimomura's.
I'll go home and live off my parents for a while.
For a while?
I'll be sure to pay my share later.
We can agree on that, right?
But listen, if you leave,
the troupe will come apart at the seams!
It's already coming apart,
even without me leaving.
Ikezu-san!
Good morning.
Is that all we got?
Y-Yeah...
I think I managed to scrounge up
about a million or so.
Although my parents grumbled about it.
Is that so?
So it's just the three of us?
Everyone must be late!
That's why I said
you shouldn't come either!
Perhaps it's high tide...
My parents gave me quite an earful.
"How long are you gonna keep working on that?" and such.
But stopping now would be quite regrettable.
Wouldn't that mean everything
we've done up till now was for nothing?
Still, if you're always in the red,
what can you do?
You don't need to say anything here!
I'm sorry. She tagged along again
because she had nothing better to do.
But Aya-san's not an outsider here.
There, see?
The three of us are still
two million in debt.
Scraping together two million
for the next production
is beyond our power.
We could recruit more members for the troupe.
But the deficit will
just keep snowballing.
I was right. Resigning is
the only sensible solution.
Wait a minute there!
Yo!
H-Hello!
Are we seeing theater artists having another interesting meeting?
Right... We were just about to...
By the way,
my connections in the neighborhood entrusted me with this.
Right...
We're here to collect.
This time it's for business.
I'll make you pay back every penny.
You're in charge of collecting money
from troupe members and paying off debts.
I was hired by your creditors.
So I'm in charge of collecting
the debt from your troupe.
We play more or less
the same role, don't we?
Y-Yeah...
But why is my only choice
to go with you?
When yakuza go outside to collect debts,
the cops freak out about it.
So we need an indebted sucker with us to blame!
You two keep silent, you hear?!
O-Okay...
Industry
Promotion
Hey, doesn't this count as kidnapping?
Industry
Promotion
N-No...
Hey, you bozos.
Why don't you offer
our guests some tea?
If possible, I'd actually prefer coffee instead.
A strong one.
N-No...
Come in!
Welcome back, boss!
Welcome back!
You fellas go line up
over there for me, will you?
Line the fuck up!
O-Okay!
As a yakuza, can you really talk
like that to respectable people?
I see you're as assertive as always, sis.
Still can't hold a candle to Aya Dragon, though.
I'm not "sis" to you!
I have a name, Hibino.
Would you keep silent
and listen to me for once?!
The reason we got you together was
to inquire into your financial plans.
F-Financial plans, sir?
We're also offering a variety
of lucrative part-time jobs.
We can always negotiate
a deal to alleviate your debt.
Some deal. Women join massage parlors,
and men sell themselves in okama bars.
Massage parlors?!
Okama bars?!
First, we'll taste you ourselves!
No!
Hibino! Shimomura-san!
Shit!
I'd love to add you guys to my harem!
And then you kick the bucket from AIDS.
Or become a lifelong meth addict.
Yakuza always follow
the same pattern with their victims.
H-Hey, Hibino...
Sister, you really oughta quit
reading such weird magazines.
Am I wrong, though?
Today's yakuza follow the law strictly.
Even if we stuff you all in concrete,
nobody's gonna squeak about it.
You cracking that kind of corny joke
is what gets the cops on our tail.
I-I'm sorry.
You heard it, everyone?
This was merely a joke.
O-Okay...
That said, we'll have another meeting tomorrow.
And if I were you, I'd try my damnedest
to get the money by then.
B-But if we can't get it after all,
what'll happen to us?
The young lady over there
knows all about that.
She can tell you what happens.
This whole brouhaha is
your collective responsibility.
If anyone runs away, we'll chase them to the ends of the Earth.
And then, once we catch them...
Let's just say, we'll have our fun then.
Well, that's about it.
Anyway, if we don't get our money back,
we'll take that assertive gal
and this middle-aged lady as a collateral!
Middle-aged?
And then we'll make you work your asses off for us!
All right! We'll get the whole sum by tomorrow!
You'll get back every damned penny!
You're so badass, Suekichi-kun!
What should we do?
Terayama, you were the one
who blurted it out!
We need 2.6 million by tomorrow, right?
I can't ask my parents for any more!
Don't you even look at me!
I have only 3000 yen
to last me until next month!
But then... Then!
You agree to the yakuza doing whatever they want to Shimomura-san and Hibino?!
I never said that!
It's all right.
It's all right with me.
If it's for you, Suekichi-kun,
I can do whatever it takes.
H-Hibino!
Cut! End of love scene.
In any case, it falls to Aya-san and me
to donate our bodies to the cause
so you guys won't have to work yourselves into the ground.
I'll do whatever,
even if it's a slightly dangerous job.
Let's go there and make money!
Th-That's right, Shimomura-san!
Let's do it! Whatever it takes!
Terayama! Didn't you switch to Hibino already?
Come to think of it,
the master at the host club I know
said they could use more staff.
Host club?
I ain't doing it!
Only ugly old hags visit those.
Ikezu-san! Now's not the time to be picky about methods!
Welcome!
We got all the best men in here!
Yes, the best men!
Respectable ladies!
All-you-can-drink one-hour specials!
All-you-can-drink for one-hour!
Madam, welcome!
My, you boys are so cute.
Are you new here?
Yes, I am, ma'am.
Are you a virgin?
Of course not.
You're cute, though.
But perhaps this big boy here
is more capable when it comes to sex?
S-Sex?
You guys need money, don't you?
Master told me all about it!
Well, I won't spare any of it
for the one who satisfies me.
The money.
Ikezu-san, stay strong please!
No way!
I've never been with an ugly girl
since high school!
This isn't the time to be picky!
Would you prefer getting murdered by yakuza? Now, now!
Come closer, boy.
Okay...
Terayama! Save me!
Ikezu-san!
Terayama, hey!
Stay strong!
Open up!
Me too?
Me too!
Good, good, my boy!
M-My, you're good.
All these new hosts...
It's for the troupe!
Y-Yes... It feels good,
but please do something about that mask.
Ribbit, ribbit...
Yes!
It's for the troupe!
Host clubs sure are
profitable, aren't they?
But we're still 1.6 million yen short.
How can we collect it by tomorrow?
I can lend you one million.
One million won't change anything.
It will. We'll work something out.
Hibino!
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Tomorrow will be the face-off with the yakuza.
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
Loan Contract
I, Terayama Daikichi,
borrowed 1,021,657 yen
from Hibino Aya
Terayama Suekichi
This might actually be our last time.
from Hibino Aya
Hibino, are we going to die?
Just kidding! You should trust me more.
That's pretty slutty of you.
Wh-Why are you here?
I thought it fishy that you were hanging out with the estate executor, Tachimi-san,
so I conducted an investigation.
By the way, what about this face-off with the yakuza?
Jeez! That's really none of your-
The mole kid?
Let's get back to the topic.
My investigation showed that great-grandpa's considerable fortune
disappeared into thin air
at some point.
Th-That's...
Of course, I'd rather you not divulge this matter to anyone else.
Why are you asking me that?
As if I had anything to do with it!
That's yet another mystery.
However...
You have something against children?
What are you saying?
You don't mind a fellow great-grandchild moving in with you, do you?
Are you stupid or something?
Hey, what's she talking about?
I'll give you one warning.
You'd be better off not tying yourself to a middle-aged gold digger
for the rest of your life.
Now then!
What was that?
Hey! Let's freshen up
and continue where we left off.
I don't feel like it.
But come on, I'm still so wet! Look.
Hey!
It's not the ti...
Let's try once again, okay?
You trying to kill me?
Come on, what's the problem?
I'm a goner already!
But don't forget. This belongs to me.
Or are you going
to ignore your creditor?
What do you mean,
"This belongs to you"?
I'm saying I took it as a collateral.
For my million.
When did that happen?
Just now.
Didn't you promise me a loan
with no interest and no collateral?!
That was the old offer.
You demon.
Then, give my million back.
You think you can find
the rest of the sum tonight
and protect me and everyone
from the yakuza?!
Stop!
Ah! Sorry.
Maybe I should return to the country?
Why the sour face?
Long time no see.
You don't seem very impressed.
Terayama Daikichi
Great-Grandfather
I got used to it.
I guess I've lost my impact, huh?
Jeez!
Aren't you supposed to be haunting someone else?!
What are you talking about?
The child you wanted to give your inheritance to is Sue, isn't it?
Ah, you mean this?
When you've lived for a century,
be it one year ago or ten years ago,
Suekichi or Sue doesn't make much difference. You get it?
That's so irresponsible!
A human life is full of hardships.
You're the source of my hardships!
But I'm pretty sure I'm your benefactor.
Benefactor?
They say, when you're young,
you bring all your hardships on yourself.
Besides, you have so many friends
to share your hardships.
That is your true lifelong treasure.
My lifelong treasure?
Compared to that, isn't receiving, or not receiving, my inheritance just a trifle?
Ah, h-hold on, grandpa!
Trifle, trifle, trifle...
Hey, wait!
This is getting more and more confusing!
A  A  A  A
I mean, with a head like that,
you won't be getting any clients in a host club or an okama bar.
Hibino...
Besides, fully shaving it like this
will heal your baldness sooner.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Don't tell me, this wig too...
You wanna go to a face-off
with yakuza with a bald dome?
This brings the total to 1,047,600 yen.
Did you bring the money?
Wh-What's going on?
You trying to lock us up?
My greetings.
My greasings.
Formerly known as Aya Dragon
of the Shooting Star Family,
I am a gunman of the Shooting Star Family, Aya the Kid!
So you came after all, assertive sis?
We won't stand for you
continuing to make fun of us!
Silence.
So... what is your business here today?
The Bondage Horse Troupe's debt.
I'd like a temporary extension for the rest.
Here, dick.
It's not enough.
Are you kidding-
We're answerable to the yakuza neighborhood association!
And debt collecting is the primary source of income for that neighborhood association!
We can't let you off for the rest!
I never said we wouldn't pay.
I'm just asking you to wait a little longer,
out of respect for this tattoo.
Does that mean I get
to keep the collateral?
Let's go!
W-Wait...
Hold it!
Yes, hold it!
All together.
We'll answer the call of the stage
and protect the Bondage Horse Troupe!
Ribbit!
You've got some nerve saying that!
Even if we die!
Dick!
They wouldn't come out to play!
Means we've won the duel!
But will this really be enough?
It oughta be fine.
Meanwhile, put your hands up and surrender.
They're returning fire!
What should we do now?
That's why I said it wouldn't work.
Ah, no helping it.
At this point, we gotta fight to the end.
At least we'll be together when we die?
Y-You've gotta be kidding!
Quack!
Ah, dick!
Shimomura-san!
The time had come to settle this duel.
I'm prepared to forgive you if you become my woman!
You ever seen yourself in a mirror?
They got me!
They got me...
Theater sure is a fun pastime!
You must've been paying attention
to see that we were firing blanks!
When did you realize?
We're the pros, remember?
Make sense!
Boss is too good at playing along.
At this rate, he'll never be successful collecting debts!
I guess he wasn't cut out to be a yakuza.
This was a special exclusive performance
by the Bondage Horse Troupe!
Did you enjoy it?
I did enjoy it.
It was as if I'd become
an actor myself.
Suekichi-sama!
I-I got word you were dueling with yakuza,
and a shootout broke out.
Are you all right?
Why are you here, Tachimi-san?
I told him.
Wh-What are you talking about?
It was just a simple prank, right?
Are you lying to me?
You dunce!
It was a rehearsal for a play.
Not something to worry over!
So you were just rehearsing a play?
Who might you be?
Ah, a thousand pardons.
Here's my card.
A-A lawyer?
None of us here is b-breaking any law!
No, I don't doubt it.
By the way, who are you?
I'm sorta like a patron to these fellows.
So that's how it is?
I must thank you for looking after Suekichi-sama for me.
Nice to meet you.
Tachimi-san, your head...
Oh, ah! This...
I'm not used to wearing hats,
so I accidentally took them off together.
I must also apologize to Suekichi-sama
for causing him trouble.
Come on, sweeties!
What are you doing?
Let's all pretend we're in a Western for a little longer!
This time, I wanna be wearing a red dress!
I'm sure Yul Brynner here
would become great friends with you!
Look, you!
My, we three are such great buddies!
I'm delighted!
Hm, what a sweet butt!
Huh? What's going on?
Here, that's enough.
Huh?
Did I do something?
Ah... No, nothing!
Well, I'll let you get away
with it for today.
We're leaving!
Okay!
By the way, kids, if you go around telling folks unnecessary things,
I'll be shooting with real bullets next time.
We know that!
See you.
Now I have the evidence.
Suekichi-sama, I again urge you
not to succumb to desperation.
In addition, as I've said
many times over,
you should not get too close
to that woman.
O-Okay...
Let us go, Sue-sama.
I'm not a baby. You don't have to escort me everywhere.
You're not a grown-up either.
I'm glad it went well.
Yeah...
You don't seem cheerful, though.
Eventually, I'll have to find the money to pay you off, and the yakuza too.
Pardon the intrusion.
W-We've negotiated a deal on the debt.
I'm Munakata Aya's husband!
Munakata Aya's...
Aya?!
Last night, you've got into
my wife's pants, didn't you?!
How do you plan
to compensate me for this?!
A-Another yakuza?
No! Give me back my normal life!
Translation
Translation Check &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
Collectr
ics-
Nemesis
anonymous