Protagonist: University Freshman
Terayama Suekichi
My dad's grandpa, that is,
my great-grandfather, passed away.
Because Dad was too busy,
I had to attend the funeral on his behalf.
This story starts the morning after the funeral.
Because I drank like a fish
at the post-funeral banquet,
I woke up the next morning dehydrated, as often happens with hangovers.
My head's splitting!
Hey...
Hey, could you move your leg away?
S-Sure...
Um... Have we met somewhere before?
You don't even remember me?
Divorcée
Hibino Aya
W-Well...
You remembered?
N-No.
Hey, you have a bald spot.
You animal...
That was how it all started
for the two of us.
DaNCE till Tomorrow
Orphan Fansubs presents
AKUMU   SALARY LOANS
TOYOTA        THEATER
Uh-oh.
Phew.
Indeed, the yakuza...
are human trash!
Good. That's where it fades out.
Now, we should proceed from act two onward.
Bondage Horse Troupe Director
Shimomura Masami
Good morning!
Good morning, Suekichi-kun.
Advanced ticket sales?
Yes, sort of.
Emergency Exit
Suekichi! The director told me.
A woman answered when she called you.
Emergency Exit
Anyway, you been to school today?
I-Ikezu-san, please don't
talk to me like a parent.
Emergency Exit
A parent?
Troupe Member
Ikezu Daisuke
So then, you're serious
about dropping out?
I'm right, ain't I?
Bogged down in theater,
neglecting your studies...
You're making a total mess of your life!
Right, Sue-chan?!
I haven't even notified
the university yet!
Quit it! Quit this damn student bit!
Without a purpose in life, you'll spend four years twiddling your thumbs!
When you find work, you'll devote yourself fully to the job!
Both your wife and
children will shun you!
You'd die from overwork by age forty!
Is that the life you want for yourself?
Sue-chan...
Ikezu-kun.
Yes?
Ikezu-kun, please act like that
when you're in your actual role.
Okay.
Huh? The previous performances
have left us that much in the red?
I still owe 70,000 yen
for printing the fliers.
70,000 yen?
I'm sorry.
I'm not trying hard enough.
No, it's not that.
If everyone had paid their shares,
it wouldn't have come to this.
Not so fast, Ikezu-kun.
Oh my...
You haven't contributed your share yet!
I'm sorry!
When I find a good part-time job,
I'll pay all of it! Okay, Sue-chan?
We need money.
We need so much money!
Maybe I could win the lottery?
Um...
Something come to mind?
N-No, it's... about your morning call.
A woman answered the phone.
"Suekichi-kun is blind drunk,"
just like that!
And then...
Suekichi-kun did so many dirty things to me while he was drunk.
No way. I've been yearning for
Director Shimomura all this time!
And then Shimomura-san,
of all people...
What's the matter? Let's go already.
I'm sorry.
You must be really busy because of all the work I threw at you.
No, it's fine. I was going
to quit university anyhow.
I'm glad I managed
to enroll after a year,
but university has been
somewhat boring lately.
I went to a funeral yesterday
and saw the face of a dead man.
"Everyone will die someday."
Since then, I can't get that thought out of my head.
If I'm going to die someday, I'd rather spend my time doing what I like.
I'm considering burning
my bridges with the university
and devoting myself to the troupe.
Didn't I tell you before
to say goodbye to your uni?
Going there only decays one's soul!
It decays them all, I tell ya!
Seems like he has a very deep grudge against students.
Ikezu-kun's girlfriend recently dumped him for one.
You too! Because you're always worrying about wasting your time there,
that bald spot will never go away!
Give me back my hat, please!
Pardon the intrusion.
Welcome back!
Morning girl!
Morning girl.
As for me...
Per our agreement yesterday,
I have come to discuss the execution
of the late Daikichi-sama's will.
Attorney       Tachimi Tadanori
What's this about?
So you can't remember, after all?
Attorney
Tachimi Tadanori
Then, let us take a look at this video.
It was recorded a week before Daikichi-sama passed away.
In his waning years, Daikichi-sama was quite a multimedia maniac.
Terayama Daikichi's Will
Hey, Suekichi. It's been a while, hasn't it?
But you know, by the time you see this,
I'll have departed this world.
My funeral will be filled
with people I don't know
who've come from all over, craving my riches.
Well, it'll be a festive gathering, at least.
Great-Grandfather
Terayama Daikichi
Of course, not a single one of them
bothered to come see me
while I was still alive.
My solitude would've been complete
if not for a young girl
who used to look after me.
Please watch the following
reenactment video to understand.
Beauty and the Old Man
Director    Terayama Daikichi
Starring    Matsushita Kimiko
The next part is largely irrelevant,
so I'll fast forward through it.
No, please let us see it.
As you wish.
One day, I was sunbathing on my veranda, as usual.
Hello.
Oh? Oh ho?
I'm from "Naku Cosmetics."
I live in this house alone.
I've no use for cosmetics.
My... You must feel awfully lonely,
living by yourself in such a big house.
After that, I passed the time talking
with her whenever she stopped by.
And then, one rainy day...
He even hired a famous porn actress for this!
That's pretty elaborate!
When I opened the door...
Grandpa, please let me take shelter from the rain.
Oh my, you're soaking wet.
Please come in.
I don't want you to catch a cold,
so here's my gown. Put it on at once.
Thank you.
You can stay in that room.
Okay.
H-Huh?
Amazing!
An interesting flick.
From that day on, she'd stop by daily
to put my house in order.
A beautiful, young woman.
I enjoyed my life and felt
rejuvenated every single day.
Gulp.
Beautiful.
Youth is something that money can't buy.
G-Gulp...
Whoa! For the first time in 25 years!
Grandpa, if we do this,
we may injure your body.
That's what I'd expect
of Suekichi-kun's great-grandfather.
What's that mean?
I was intensely enthralled by this woman.
I became completely oblivious
to everything else around me.
But at some point,
she abruptly stopped coming.
Then, one day...
I learned that the police had arrested her.
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
Metropolitan
Police
Department
She approached elderly men who lived all alone and had lots of money,
captivated them with her figure,
and then stole their valuables.
Still, I don't hold a grudge against her.
That woman gave the final joys of life
to an elderly man with no future.
So I decided to give part of my inheritance to her via support for public welfare.
The End
That was pretty chivalrous of him!
But what does this have to do with me?
Wait for part two.
Suekichi, you were the only one
who came to my place
to play with pure feelings.
It seriously helped
loosen up my stiff attitude.
Even now, I can close my eyes
and remember the hills and streams.
But I'm pretty sure I only went
to play at great-grandpa's place
when I was in elementary school or so.
That said, I don't have
much longer to live.
And so, on the occasion of my journey to the netherworld,
I've decided to give you a little present. Please accept it, will you?
Daikichi-sama had been putting this together secretly for many years,
using profits from his real estate business.
His stamp collection is a bonus, with a piece of land.
It is currently valued at approximately 450 million yen.
4... 450 million yen!?
That was what I told you
as you were trying to slip away
from the funeral yesterday.
No wonder he forgot.
When you come to someone and suddenly say 450 million, it feels unreal.
We could really use
the help of a sponsor.
We need money.
We need so much money!
S-So does that mean I can use that money however I want?!
Well, regarding that matter...
That's what I thought, but it feels boring just to bless you like that,
so I thought I'd put
a condition on it.
I know!
Sue must graduate properly from university,
find a wife, and become a full-fledged and functioning member of society.
Until then, hold on to it.
Great-grandpa always did like to throw in a last-minute zinger like that.
Then... Then, you'll hold on to
the 450 million yen until then?
Yes. Until then, I'm in charge of keeping it safe as the executor of the will.
Therefore, your sister should not rely
on the inheritance for now.
S-Sister?! I thought she came with you!
Doesn't this person happen to be your younger sister?
That...
...is to say...
Who on earth is this woman?!
I'm pretty sure you were
at the funeral, weren't you?
My name's Hibino Aya.
When Grandpa Daikichi was married to his third wife,
his mistress gave birth to his fourth son, who would later become my stepfather.
Long story short, I was just one of those distant relatives that swarmed the funeral.
Actually, I was there because
I tagged along with my parents.
That means you overheard my conversation with Suekichi-sama at the funeral?
Don't slander others like that!
You were the ones who showed up there
while I was just sobering up!
And you gained Suekichi-sama's trust for his inheritance?
Then... you only slept with me
for the money?!
Excuse me, what?
I just saw that Suekichi-kun
was too drunk for his own good,
so I offered to escort him home!
Which one?
This way...
And then, should I even start
on what Suekichi-kun did to me?
I'll only say it once.
I ain't no cheap broad
who sleeps with men for money!
But from the way
you talked about it...
It must be for the money.
Fine, then!
Don't believe me and see if I care!
You lewd bastard.
You were lively enough last night, Suekichi-kun.
W-Wait!
Huh? Where'd she go?
I advise you not to divulge this story to anyone else.
I suddenly felt like I was
the protagonist of some story.
However, in my room was one proof
that it wasn't a dream:
a business card saying "Tachimi."
...Aosaka
University
And that's why I started attending classes again.
...Aosaka
University
Then, the next few days just flew by.
I was busy getting ready for the troupe's upcoming performance.
TOYOTA        THEATER
Good morning!
Hey!
Advance tickets selling?
You're late, Suekichi-kun.
The rehearsal is already
over for today.
O-Okay...
So? Been busy lately, haven't'cha?
Say, Suekichi-kun, why are you going to class again?
Th-The end-semester test is coming up.
If there's one thing I hate,
it's university students trying to get into the theater.
Always carefree, despite living off a parental allowance!
You can't reason with them.
They're naive! They think theater is a walk in the park.
Except a certain student is paying for your drink!
What I'm saying is, I don't want you
to become that kinda disagreeable fella.
Know what I mean?
L-Look, I have my own reasons
for attending!
Reasons.
A woman?
I-It's not that.
Oh, I see!
You finally gave up on your hopeless yearning for Shimomura?
S-Speak for yourself, please!
Ikezu-san, why are you following me?
Well, I was hoping I could get dinner at your place.
You know that I don't have any money either!
If you need dinner, why don't you go to your girlfriend's place?
Why are you so prickly about it?
I'm not particularly prickly.
It's just that I prefer
solitude sometimes!
No, I'm not buying it.
There's a woman, after all.
Ikezu-san, you have a one-track mind.
Did you have sex already?
I know you did, you sneaky rascal!
Is she a student too?
An office lady?
Ah. Don't tell me she's a nighthawk?
I guess you just won't go away, will you?
I wanna know what kinda woman she is.
Oh, give it a rest already!
Phew! And there's the proof.
Ah! Good morning.
"Good morning," my ass!
Tell me why you're here!
Well, I climbed a tree and
came in through the window.
That's not what I asked!
Now-now-now-now.
Mighty pleased to meet you.
Ah! Nice to meet you.
You come with me!
Sue-chan, you little...
Beneath that innocent exterior,
a horny skirt-chaser!
No, I'm not.
It's fine, fine. I know I'm a third wheel,
so I'll go to Nanko-chan's now.
Sue-chan, don't overdo it.
That would be harmful for your health.
It's a misunderstanding!
Who is that guy?
"Who is that?"
Who are you, more like it!
Barging into someone's home like this...
I told you. I climbed a tree and came in through the window.
That's not the point!
I figured that a poor student living alone
would probably feel awfully lonely
on this cold, windy winter night.
So your older sister should come over and make you dinner. There.
I wonder if that's true.
You should learn to accept
others' kindness honestly!
That's rich from you,
talking about honesty!
What do you mean, "older sister"?
We're the same age, right?
If we compare life experiences,
I am the older sister here!
Besides, I've got nothing
better to do on my day off.
I'm not a plaything for killing time!
Rather than idling my evening away at home,
I thought, "Why don't I do it
with Suekichi-kun?"
That's the power of youth!
An immediate reaction.
You can't toy with others' bodies!
Oh, hey!
If you hang around out there,
you'll catch a cold, Ikezu-san.
Ah, you've got a point.
Oh? You have quite a knack for this.
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
Here, let's drink to it.
Cheers!
Don't hold back,
and eat until you're full.
Y-Yeah.
Well, I'm stuffed. Stuffed!
Ah! Our legs touched.
Didn't you just stretch yours?
But say, that inheritance of yours
is 400 million, right?
If you had 400 million right now,
you could buy a house with a yard
anywhere in greater Tokyo.
Isn't it about as much as an ordinary office clerk earns in his lifetime?
The last train is leaving soon.
Don't pretend to be asleep.
Go home now!
But won't you feel
lonely again if I leave?
Go ahead.
Turn off the lights.
Don't you feel like this is happening too fast?
Sometimes, that's just how things are.
Do you dislike me?
Not necessarily dislike...
Then what's the big deal?
Ah! Not there!
I feel it!
No!
I'm coming!
What'll we do about contraception?
Oh my. There's a condom right here.
You're right! I wonder why.
Maybe Ikezu-san dropped it?
That's it. Gotta be it!
Damn thing.
What's wrong?
I see! That's what this was all about!
You wanted to bear my child,
to chain me with child support
for the rest of my life?!
How'd you ever come up with that?
It's gotta be a misunderstanding!
I had no idea there was a hole in it.
So it was your condom, after all?!
Hmph. Of course I brought some condoms.
Oh? Is that so?!
So that was your plan all along?!
Feed me, make me drink, and get me ready for this while I'm drunk!
Why do you keep
making accusations?!
Shut up! I said go home,
so get lost!
You're too damn loud!
Pretending to cry won't
get you anywhere!
You're strange, Suekichi-kun.
You only talk about money, money, money.
Doesn't that make you the same as all those relatives, just craving riches?
Those words brought me
back to my senses.
Hibino Aya. I don't know who she is
or where she came from.
And yet, she has this mysterious allure.
So we're doing it now.
You shouldn't think I was fooled by a woman's tears.
Still, if that's how our love story happens to start, it's fine by me.
Before I knew it,
that's how I came to feel.
From then on,
Hibino Aya started frequenting my apartment like a street cat.
TOYOTA        THEATER
So, bro...
Yes?
Are you the one in charge of the play?
N-No.
There's a constant racket
coming from your place lately.
You're a public nuisance.
Okay, we'll be more careful.
If not, you'll have to compensate me handsomely.
Take care!
Scary...
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
February 2 - 7
Obakuro Toyota Theater
Our performance is scheduled
for March 2nd, right?
What are you saying?
This says February 2nd, doesn't it?
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
South
Post
Office
Ah... After paying for these postcards,
I have nothing left to live on this month.
1,500 postcards! They printed them all without you checking even one?!
That's what happens when you trust a student. They can't focus.
Take responsibility
for your own mistakes.
I'll be watching you!
How can I make ends meet
for another two weeks?
It's in my room.
You're here again?
Welcome back.
What, it's just you, Tachimi-san?
I know!
Please give me an advance on the inheritance!
That is impossible.
Huh? Why?
Do not give him any financial support until the inheritance happens.
This was also included in his will.
More importantly...
I think that you should remember
to lock your windows.
Though it helped that
it was open this time.
Well, no matter. I have important information for you today.
Investigation Report
My investigation has showed that
no person named Hibino Aya exists.
That is the gist of it.
Is she still visiting your apartment?
Y-Yeah.
And are you still in a relationship?
R-Relationship?
What do you mean by-
Are you shagging her or not?!
Yes.
I don't know who she is,
but she's clearly using her body to get at your inheritance.
She's a pro.
It's a trick from a pro's arsenal.
Pro at what, exactly?
Anyway, I'll try to find
a way to stop her.
I would also ask that you not show her any mercy either.
O-Okay...
With that, I will take my leave now.
What exactly did he come here for?
And like this...
Ah! You...
Dick!
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
Hibino!
Ah, this is Freddy-kun.
Nice to meet you.
Seems like he's from Southeast Asia.
I found him by the roadside,
so I brought him along.
He has nowhere to go.
Hey... Hey, you...
For grins, I also taught him that everyone in Japan says "Dick" as a greeting.
Listen, you...
Dick!
What were you thinking, exactly?
I still have work to do today, you know!
Work?
With this?
I ask that you not show her any mercy either.
Come on, tell me!
D-Don't come close, you vixen!
What are you saying?
Look, standing straight down there.
But...
Don't worry. He's sleeping.
Huh?
Suekichi-kun, are you there?
D-Director, welcome!
I hope I didn't wake you up.
N-No, please come in.
Sorry for what I said earlier.
Maybe I went a little too far.
I would have come to help you sooner,
but I had work left to do.
Hold it. Why do I have to hide?
H-Hibino!
Oh my, so I interrupted something, after all?
N-No, it's fine. Th-This girl here was just helping me out with some-
What was I he-
Oh? What's going on?
Oh! A new friend! Dick!
Director for a troupe?
I'm sorry to ask you to help with something irrelevant.
She doesn't actually mind.
So you're working at a theater, Suekichi-kun?
Yes. He helps our troupe
with production.
So does it pay well?
You can't make a living in the theater.
Then you're probably
working a second job?
That's right. Nearly everyone does.
Even so, I like the theater and...
No sleeping!
Right... Freddy, bring the ones that you erased, will you?
Sure, dick!
Girls sure have lovely faces
when they're sleeping, don't they?
Howdy! My, how you've grown.
It's me. Don't you recognize your great-grandpa's face?
D-Don't tell me you're...
Right, a ghost.
N-Nonsense!
I don't believe in ghosts and stuff.
Believe it or not, here I am,
and you can't prevent it.
Cretin! I'm not Dracula!
This means you still have some strong attachments to this world?
Not at all. I just thought I'd come see how you're doing.
Well, as you can see,
my life is a mess, thanks to you!
I've got this crazy girl all over me,
and I can't even quit college!
Sue, my boy, you don't want the money?
Well, it's better to have it than not...
Maybe you hate women, then?
Well, if I said I did,
it'd be a transparent lie.
Why are you complaining, then?
You've settled down pretty well and even have two women serving you.
W-Well, it's not exactly that.
This is the one that
put you under a spell, right?
You can take a quick peek.
No touching, though.
Ah! Grandpa, stop this right now!
Why did you even come here?!
J-Just a dream?
Oh? Hibino?
Oh, dick!
It's you, Freddy?
Huge.
Somehow, we managed to correct the invitations in time.
AKUMU   SALARY LOANS
TOYOTA        THEATER
But then, one of the actors broke a leg near the park,
AKUMU   SALARY LOANS
TOYOTA        THEATER
so we had to find a replacement for a major role.
AKUMU   SALARY LOANS
TOYOTA        THEATER
Hello.
You came to meet me?
With this, we can rent some extra costumes.
But how did you get this...
Don't tell me, did she enter the "massage" business?
You idiot. This isn't dirty money.
I asked for an advance on my salary.
I guess you really do love
the theater, Shimomura-san.
Don't we all? We couldn't do it if we didn't love it.
Theater's not a lucrative occupation.
Isn't it the same for you, Suekichi-kun?
Huh? Yeah...
I know. We should let you play a major role too.
What? Me?
You don't like acting?
Uh, it's not that I don't like it...
I think it'd be good experience for you as a producer
to try acting at least once.
Okay...
Try your best. I'll be doing my best too.
Well, see you!
Are you going home?
Starting next week,
we'll rehearse day and night.
I gotta make some cash while I can.
And there's the advance.
Take care.
Thank you.
I think you'd better give up.
She's the Nervous Nelly type.
You let yourself into my apartment without asking again!
So you're going to try acting this time, Suekichi-kun?
That's what I'm stuck with.
Anything for Shimomura-san, huh?
Mind your own business!
See you.
Wait a minute.
Right after talking to another woman like that,
you're starting something
with me again?
Buy a ticket.
AKUMU   SALARY LOANS
TOYOTA        THEATER
I beg you to stop! I have
a wife and children and a 60-year-old mother.
Right, that's your cue.
H-Hold it, ribbit!
Come in more slowly.
It's here.
Ah, Ikezu-san, I was looking for this place.
Is Suekichi upstairs?
That's an amazing makeup scar!
Almost like the real thing!
It looks perfect.
You're living the role.
You're like a real yakuza!
I am a real yakuza.
What do you want?
Wow! So cute.
C-Cute?
Suekichi-kun, could you do the ads soon?
Sorry, I'll wrap up here right away.
'Sup?
How did you find this place?
It was on the postcards
I helped you fix the other day.
I came to see how it's going.
We're busy here.
Don't get in the way.
Ribbit!
He was complaining about us
being too noisy even before this!
What should we do?
You bastards, that was the last straw!
Do you value your life so little?
Take responsibility!
You can't talk your way
out of it forever!
The director is currently out
at a meeting.
You're noisy from the morning on!
The traffic in and out makes
my customers avoid the place!
Great, Ikezu-kun! Really convincing!
Like a professional!
Ah? That woman again!
Shut your whore trap!
Huh? A real one?
Th-The production is running behind,
and tomorrow is opening day, so...
I see. I just had a funny idea.
Tomorrow, my boys will line up at the entrance
to make sure that nobody
comes to see your circus!
Anything but that, please!
I ain't messing around!
What should we do, Suekichi?
Wish someone would tell me that...
We gotta consult the director
and do something about it.
We're in serious trouble.
Would they negotiate if we apologized?
And we don't have any money.
Still, at this rate...
He wasn't just making
an empty threat.
Fine. I'm going.
We have all the props
we need right here.
Hibino, those guys are yakuza!
If I die, Suekichi-kun
won't get laid anymore.
I'll bring Freddy along.
In we go, Freddy.
Dick!
Dick, dick-dick-dick...
AKUMU
Salary Loans
Come in!
Benevolence
I am not a customer.
You assholes! Where are you from?!
Benevolence
We are meeting for the first time.
I am Aya Dragon of
the Shooting Star family.
Although I am still a greenhorn, sir.
Please change your dick!
Benevolence
Ah, damn it. Did you come here to make fun of us?!
This man is in training,
so please forgive him.
Dick?
My visit today to your premises
is an apology visit for
the Bondage Horse incident.
All right. That apology's
gonna cost you.
No, we are here just to talk.
You think talking's gonna enough?!
You humiliated the boss!
On top of that, business has tanked!
Don't you know that you should at least show some respect?
Without mutual respect,
we're all as good as dead!
It's the same with actors.
On stage, actors put
their lives on the line.
If they're not convincing,
they're as good as dead.
What's all this bullshit?
You're making it hard for our customers
to come borrow money!
We're a respectable institution!
Oh? Like, sweet and creamy?
That's a dessert!
You just keep your mouth shut!
Scary.
It seems the boss ain't gonna forgive you,
Benevolence
so stop wasting our time!
Go home...
Benevolence
Stop this endless whining already!
Whining dick!
We owe a debt of gratitude to the Horse.
I, Aya Dragon, would go as far as risking my life to protect them from you.
She really is living the damn role.
I didn't know Hibino
had so much courage.
Think we'll believe your shit?!
Didn't I tell you to stop whining?
You wench!
My head... My head...
Benevolence
Boss, are you all right?
Oh my.
Shiny.
My, Aya Dragon-san has so much courage.
It's a waste that a woman got it all!
Oh no! Don't look!
Don't look or I'll spank you butt!
The boss wears a wig?
Without it, he's an okama!
Oh no! Don't look.
I can't let you see me. No!
Well, I suppose I can stand it
for one more day.
However, I'll come see your play,
along with a bunch of my boys.
And if it's funny,
I'll let you off the hook.
Then, will you buy 20 tickets from us?
All right. But what you just saw
must stay in this room.
Benevolence
If he doesn't quit being an okama...
...he can't be a yakuza.
Thanks for your business!
Oh! They're back.
Excuse us.
AKUMU
Salary Loans
Th-That was exhausting.
Can't take it... No, can't stand... Dick.
And that's how Hibino's big act saved the day then and there.
Still, I couldn't sleep from worrying about opening day.
TOYOTA        THEATER
And then, it was opening day.
Are they here?
What should we do?
Will they leave
if we don't come out?
Just go give them some hearty laughs.
Like that, with a bang!
Listen, you...
They bought tickets,
so they're customers.
For now, let's just think
about the play, all right?
It's getting crowded, so please fill up the seats from the front!
This good man asked you to move up,
so get up and move already!
Well, I'll go take my seat
in the audience.
What if he recognizes
you from yesterday?
Not after the amount
of makeup I used. See ya!
You never know!
He's forgotten all his lines
right off the bat.
That idiot!
Ikezu-san! How could you forget all your lines already?
D-Dummy! I didn't forget them!
I was waiting out the timing!
Then get it together
and start again!
At least he managed to get some laughs out of them.
We're pathetic.
Th-There's no one here?! Tsk!
Die now!
Why, you...
Ribbit!
Ah... I-I'm sorry!
Thrust from your hips.
You can't kill a guy like that.
I-I'm sorry!
Almost time, Suekichi-kun.
Your turn to go on.
R-Right.
I-I beg your pardon.
Suekichi-kun came up with a great ad-lib right away!
Didn't he just trip?
Suekichi-kun, your lines. Lines!
I-Indeed, yakuza are human trash!
Boss!
My legs went numb!
They love it!
They think the yakuza
are part of the play!
Why are we acting like fugitives?
You wanna take a dive in Tokyo Bay or what?
Ouch!
You shouldn't use strange exits.
Ah... You see, um...
I-It's just that...
Today's performance...
It truly moved me, like nothing else has in a long time.
I was really pleased to see that your troupe consists of gifted actors.
I don't quite get it.
Did he like it or what?
Yeah.
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
In any case, I was relieved when we managed to conclude the run safely.
Well, Hibino played a big part too.
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Final
day
"Arriving at Kinta Okumon"
Bondage Horse Troupe Presents
Meanwhile, Hibino remained the same as always.
Seriously, nothing beats
a beer after a bath!
Use a glass, at least!
Don't you have any womanly
modesty at all?
Hm... I don't.
Wanna do it?
Tachimi-san?
I hope you don't mind me...
I see you haven't severed
your ties with this woman?
U-Uh, no, no!
Um, today is special, because she helped us out with the play.
Well, so be it.
Today, I came to show you
an album that Daikichi-sama
entrusted to me
while he was still alive.
I have no other use for it, so...
Ah! Suekichi hasn't changed at all since then!
What do you mean?
Oh?
What's wrong?
He has a mole on his neck.
I never had a mole on my neck.
Th-Then, the kid in this photo...
...is a lookalike.
I-It's a different person?!
But how...
There goes...
...my inheritance.
450 million!
Translation
Translation Check &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
Collectr
ics-
Nemesis
anonymous