Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
What a nice melody...
Amazing!
Nothing less is to expect from a first-class world-famous
pianist's performance. A bliss for the ears.
As soon as the concert is over,
countless banquets await her.
Not only the way her arms sway,
but her whole style is top-notch.
Really... Don't you have a more important
editor-in-chief business?
Well, it's just a diversion...
I'm done writing!
Finished... already?
Piano concerts tend to captivate one
without even noticing...
Hey, did you know? Turns out pressing the piano keys
requires a remarkable strength.
Therefore, pianists fingers are dexterous
and hands are firm and steady.
But her fingers look so slim and feminine.
You'd never tell!
Well, all the more surprising this pianist
contacted us herself.
Namely, the Turning Gears magazine.
A ticket?
She invited us to her concert,
taking place on the ship!
Well, seems like we're to join a high society soon.
Still, why pick such a peculiar venue for a party?
That I wonder myself...
What do you care about the details?
If we are welcome, we are not complaining.
Let's just accept her hospitality.
Which reminds me, Ginya,
you're free this Sunday, aren't you?
Yeah...
What is there to hesitate about? Such a bonus from the editor is to be accepted without a second thought.
Bonus, you say?
Our invitation allows for 5 people to enter.
Episode 4
Melody
For now, only the editor and Ishibashi decided to come, and then there's me...
With two more people...
Party on board a ship?
Technically, I'm taken along just to fill the gap...
And I'm also allowed to join?
Indeed! Mainly - because this time
I'm taking you out not at my own expense.
Why, of course!
I knew it all along!
Regarding this Teresa, the pianist who invited you...
She is from Spain, ain't she?
Master, you know her too?
I saw her on TV on Channel 23.
And her performance is damn fine. I'm telling you!
With such face, you're versed in classic piano?
Sounds fishy.
Do I look that philistine?
By the way, Master should also come. We still have one more vacancy.
No no! I'm not much of a Hearty
nor a fan of banquets, so I better refrain.
Moreover, if I yield and agree to come,
you'll make fun of me again. Can't afford that.
In this case,
the last spot remains vacant...
Well, who is this one more person you invited?
A secret.
My, you don't know either?
Far as I'm aware, it's some young girl.
Soon we'll meet her and know for sure.
Here! I am here!
Yo! Did we make you wait?
Your seat is there. In the back, back!
They're so... familiar.
What kind of relationship they have? Any idea?
But parties require dresses,
and I only have my school uniform.
It's fine, fine. The invitation says no dress code is applied,
so nothing to worry.
No more hesitation.
Hurry up and hop into my car!
You're as cheeky as ever, brother!
But I'd never think Ginya has a little sister.
I am Mai. Nice to meet you.
We are glad to meet you too.
Yuri and Ginya having a date?!
Well, well, don't be so nervous, Oumi.
They're having anything but a date. Just attending a show
and a dinner party on the ship, nothing aside that!
Still... A dinner party is a big deal,
especially - with Ginya!
The one living on cheap bentos
from convenience stores!
Surely, in her heart, Yuri never wanted
to accompany Ginya to such a place...
I see, see.
It's Yuri's sympathy.
You get so carried away talking about Yuri...
You were this aroused and erratic just yesterday.
It's great to be young...
I can't comprehend it myself, Master...
It's not like I desire to attend this dinner party myself.
Though I'd be way more comfortable without Ginya there.
So that's the case. All the more clear
why she agreed to go so willingly...
Damn! How did he dare to invite Yuri!?
Ginya is not even a human! Bloody animal!
Hey, hey! Aren't those your precious children?
Shit! I wanna go there too!
First of all, to everyone who managed to attend
Teresa Sam N'Kota's special party,
celebrating her visit to Japan, thank you very much!
Our honorable guests may proceed onboard.
Although we differ in our suits only,
I still feel completely out of place here.
Incredible!
Never have I seen that kind of luxury!
Hey, Ishibashi, Yuri,
shall we try everything?
Please.
Thank you, thank you!
Beautiful!
This is all on your brother's courtesy.
It's unbelievable how tangible his work gets sometimes!
Not every time it results
in visiting such a splendid ship.
We parted some time ago, so I live with my step-uncle now. I wonder if he minds.
A step uncle?
I may be calling him uncle,
but he is like a father to me.
Albeit we're not even blood related.
Back then, brother chose to stay in the city
where he is comfortable.
I don't think it suits him.
Hence I have reasonable concerns.
That is why I'm relieved to see you tend to him
and I'm grateful!
Here, have some, have some.
What happened? You look bored.
You didn't happen to develop a seasick?
I don’t understand it one bit.
What's the point inviting us to this kind of party?
You really are a curious one.
They say excessive anxiety makes your sake taste bad.
Who is it?
This one is Teresa herself.
Teresa Sam N'Kota.
She is so unbelievably beautiful!
Now I see her pretty face has nothing to do
with her recognition as genius.
She fixed a solo concert onboard a ship.
It must be absurd expensive!
To say the least...
Where's the editor?
Actually... Restroom is taking him longer than planned?
Teresa sure was kind,
and I never regretted attending this banquet...
Moreover, I'm even more convinced now -
such flawless play is a true art onboard a rocking ship.
Pachislot machines on the deck!
Pachislot machines on the deck?
Why, of all the places?
That is something I would like to know...
Any ideas, Ginya?
What kind of ideas you expect me to utter?
The Turning Gears magazine, are you?
I hope today's cuisine
meets your tastes.
Teresa Sam N'Kota!
Mr. Otonashi Ginya, aren't you?
Yes...
Can I help you in any way?
One of your recent articles
piqued my interest.
While reading your article,
I felt as if I was reading my own mind.
Do you play pachislot yourself?
Yes.
I wonder in which way these fingers
press the machine buttons.
The pachislot rhythm is similar to the piano rhythm.
Don't you think piano and pachislot are akin?
I checked your fingers to make sure of my suggestion.
Would you care to reciprocate?
That's what pachislot rhythm is about.
Would you do me the honor if I challenge you?
Challenge? Me?
Let me state the rules specifications.
Special identical pachislot machines
are installed on the deck.
Neither of them has a time limit.
Instead, the victor should manage to hit the big first.
Finally, we have a whole ship of spectators.
We're to be exhibited like in a gallery. Any objections?
Ginya...
I agree. Let's fight.
Hey, Ginya, is this really okay?
She is much more used to such conditions.
While you are just a novice pachislot journalist.
Not even a real slotter!
All you know is bare theory.
It's obviously insufficient for the victory!
But if you lose,
the whole Turning Gears magazine is also...
Teresa is an unmatched pianist.
But an excellent slotter at the same time.
I knew it the moment I touched her finger.
That's why however big the bets are,
I can't turn down Teresa's challenge!
Moreover - she challenged the whole
Turning Gears magazine today. So I must accept it.
Brother?
And now, on Miss Teresa's request,
we begin the additional special program.
The showdown will now take place
against the Turning Gears' representative, Otonashi Ginya.
In addition, for your convenience,
the game is broadcasted on a large screen behind you.
Whoever hits the big first - wins...
I need to get used to the drums speed faster.
It's rocking...
I see... That's the point of the ship.
Although docked, it still rocks on the waves.
This is one hell of inconvenient.
Are participants ready to begin?
Yes.
In that case, start!
Well, the battle began! Which one will hit the big first -
will it be Teresa? Or else... will it be Otonashi Ginya?
Started with the Neo!
Keep it this way, Ginya!
Mr. Editor, is brother winning this?
No... That's still unclear...
Damn! I only get Small Factors!
What?
Teresa plays with her eyes closed!
But how does she...
Is she planning to rely on blind luck only?
Teresa is already running a significant streak!
Can you play with your eyes closed?
I had no idea it is possible. Editor?
She plays exactly the same way as with piano,
letting the body follow the rhythm.
Her ears tell her about the machine's state
and when to press the buttons.
Damn it!
Keep calm, Ginya!
That's the way! Ginya has almost hit Riichi!
Alright!
Crap!
He missed!
His finger slipped off due to the ship rocking.
Ginya, pull yourself together!
You will win if you calm down.
It's no use, I can't hit it!
Sometimes it's strong, sometimes it's weak.
But a constant rhythm is inherent even in the waves.
It's no use opposing the rhythm.
Just like... playing the piano!
Success! Teresa's first Riichi is out!
She takes advantage of the wave pattern!
Brother...
Otonashi has also closed his eyes!
Rhythm, you say?
I need to catch that rhythm and move with it.
Great! Brother is winning!
He combined three titles before Teresa!
No, wait... He did not.
A Regular...
There it is! Miss Teresa's Big!
The game is concluded!
I'm smashed.
To pieces.
Acknowledging one's defeat is important,
but wasn't it fun?
I won today only thanks to this rocking ship as a handicap.
This time the ship served me a home field.
But next time I hope to face you on even grounds.
Well then...
It's about time we leave.
Shall we go home, Ginya?
That was so humiliating.
I feel sorry for Ginya.
He'll be fine.
He's my brother after all.
That's right. Ginya won't get upset
over one loss, however devastating it is.
What an unusual paper airplane you have...
I have not folded any since childhood,
so I may have messed it up.
However, it flies well enough, so it's fine.
You don't think you lost
only because the waves were rocking the ship?
Teresa allowed her keen senses to drive her.
She followed her own rhythm all along.
Meanwhile, your conviction of only one legit way to victory led you to defeat.
Led me?
That's what differentiates the winner from the loser today.
All experienced slotters come up with their own
style of play, which they stick to.
You know a lot about how to play pachislot right.
But that knowledge stands in your way to victory.
At some point, I even believed
that you could actually win.
As a writer, you should not run from this defeat
for the sake of good articles.
That is the only way your articles remain sober.
Besides, won't it be nice for Turning Gears
to have a man to stand up for it?
Brother.
Unfortunate, isn't it?
Yeah. One hell of unfortunate.
But more than that, I experience some kind of refreshment.
Refreshed after being beaten?
That taste of yours is something.
Brother, don't you think you grew through it?
Mocking me again?
I didn't mean any mockery!
Then, it's the effect of today's hard work.
Have you ever had it easy?
I may share it with you someday.
You'll be surprised.
There is nothing else to surprise me!
Ginya! We're going home!
Coming!
Mai, let's race!
Wait, brother!
Brother, you cheat!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
History.
Memories.
Hatred.
Past.
Slotter.
Next time:
Future.
My finger will
stop the time.