Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
You have 1 new unread message.
It's Yuri.
My Hokkaido employment matter has been settled.
Tomorrow,
I'm coming once again to Tokyo
to vacate my flat.
You have been the most caring up until now...
So thank you for everything.
Yuri...
Is it really better this way,
Sakura?
Episode 22
Incandescence
Align to the Sakura bloom!
I'm going ahead, Otonashi.
Otonashi is putting up quite a fight!
Still, Daiba is unaffected.
Just what you'd expect from a King's battle.
Can't take my eyes off.
It really is better this way.
Intermission?
I understand.
With half of the battle behind,
we are now entering an hour-long intermission.
Intermission?
What would you like to drink?
Some cold water, please.
Will bring right away.
Daiba...
Don't waste your time.
Right now, we're supposed to rest our bodies.
Okay.
Ginya.
Oumi?
You've become quite formidable.
Great match.
I'm finishing the rest of it in one sitting.
Daiba should too
be ready to carry it to the finish.
Stay sharp.
Then Daiba stays sharp too.
Most certainly!
Mr. Otonashi...
A special supply from Mr. Shibaura
has been delivered to your room.
From Master?
Roger that.
Then, I'll head to the waiting room.
This sure will help regain my spirits!
I think I'll go get some rest
in my own room as well.
Daiba...
This fight is between me and Otonashi.
Don't you obstruct it ever again.
Daiba!
Daiba collapsed on the floor!
But why?
Daiba...
I don't need help.
I'll go get some rest there.
Spirits!
10 more minutes.
Where's Daiba?
Haven't returned from his seclusion yet.
I see.
Then, I'll just wait here a bit.
I guess, Daiba too
is completely cool and collected.
3 minutes left.
Please return to your seat.
No need to hurry like that.
Until Daiba returns, we can't start anyway.
I'll go check his condition.
No one is allowed into the waiting room -
Daiba's request.
Still...
I will go.
Ain't that fine by you, Mr. Dealer?
However...
Ginya...
Daiba?
What's the matter?
It's almost time.
Sure, sure.
And now, we will resume the match.
I still plan to win, Daiba.
Just what I was hoping for.
Show me what you're worth, Otonashi!
A clean cut!
Have you seen it?
No... He aligned it in a blink of an eye!
Is that the Finger of God's worth?
Daiba is amazing, just as always!
Otonashi is steadily falling behind!
Now he is playing to his true ability.
What a curious feeling.
Not a hint of fear in me now.
Somehow, Daiba's devotion is rather comforting.
Here I go, Daiba Ryo!
I can hardly believe it...
Otonashi is starting to catch up!
Such an impressive momentum!
Is this...
the fight Ryo yearned for?
Not just yet, please!
Daiba!
Ryo!
Step off!
That's what I'm here for.
The reason is malignant intracerebral tumor.
A life-threatening condition.
I'm sorry.
I had to keep it a secret until now.
Owner?
I will reiterate what I said before.
If there's any danger,
the match should be called off.
Therefore, I ask you to call the match off at once.
This is my verdict as attendee.
If this keeps up,
Daiba is beyond saving.
The ER team has arrived.
I'm taking Daiba with me.
Hands off!
I'm not...
going anywhere!
What are you trying to do, Daiba?
The match is not over yet.
Nonsense!
I would never concede to such thing.
Aoi...
Ryo...
Otonashi.
Otonashi Ginya is here?
Otonashi,
I need you to walk me back to my machine.
Daiba!
What are you talking about, Daiba?
In that condition...
The car is ready.
We can now transport the patient.
Please proceed.
I have already arranged it with the hospital.
Now, Daiba.
Please step away from him.
Ryo.
I can lend you my shoulder.
Owner!
I'm sorry.
We are resuming the match.
But what about your promise?
You should keep burning in Slothium,
Otonashi Ginya.
You should keep fighting!
Ginya,
let's get going.
Otonashi Ginya!
He can no longer be saved.
Rather than die in hospital,
he would die here!
We're sorry to have kept you waiting.
The match will now be resumed
between King Daiba Ryo and General Otonashi Ginya.
Start pressing, Otonashi.
Don't hold back.
It's no use...
I can't press.
All that pachislot...
what purpose does it serve?
It never made a single person happier!
Enough already.
I can press no more buttons, Daiba.
You must go to the hospital.
You mustn't die!
Not you...
This is what I chose myself.
Not because it's the right thing to do,
but rather because you can only choose one.
I don't get it.
Just so you know,
I didn't choose pachislot.
Otonashi Ginya,
it was you who chose it.
Ginya.
"Daiba dies either way?"
You dare to call yourself a doctor after that?!
I'm done with the Slothium.
I'm not playing pachislot ever again.
I see.
If that's your wish.
A long time ago,
Ryo told me this:
I myself only live in the present moment.
And then...
It's our perception
that constitutes the present.
By piling up perception after perception,
we build up our own present moment.
Then, from it, a future is born.
For me, it's this way, too.
Even after Ryo dies,
I will remain faithful to this conviction.
Did you...
really have no regrets, doing this?
What's going on?
Otonashi's retirement means Daiba's win.
Don't be stupid. Otonashi has higher score,
so he'll be declared winner.
Hey, what will become of the match now?
Just put it frankly already!
You no longer have to keep going, Daiba.
I made it all the way to here.
However, Fushina,
have I managed to get close enough to you?
It's over already.
This is my business only.
Man must decide by himself
on a place to die.
Daiba is recuperating already!
Where the hell is Otonashi?
There's no point anymore, Ryo.
It's all over with Slothium!
You will remain the Ultimate King for eternity!
Not yet.
The match is not over yet.
I will overthrow Daiba.
Let's roll, Daiba.
Step down, please.
This fight is between me and Daiba.
Ain't no one can get in our way.
Daiba...
I am...
For future's sake, I'm going in.
Fine by me.
Maybe Ryo was right when he said,
he is to become much stronger.
On my part, I just envy those two.
Since the beginning of match,
8 hours have elapsed.
Update on the current scores:
Ultimate King Daiba Ryo - 22 785 coins.
Challenger Otonashi Ginya...
Caught in a sieve too fine-grained for me
Now I cannot move, not even fall down into your spot
Not one hint of human left, I'm but a walking empty corpse shell
And along with me, a bunch of others born just to get robbed
And it won't be long before they come for me
I'm running helpless through the quicksand
Playing with scabs, trying to peel them off
Here and there, neglected idols are all around me
While painting them all with meaningless colors, I offer a prayer
The longer I go on believing in it, the more it becomes the truth
Until it shatters to pieces small enough to escape the sieve
And I guess they've finally come for me
Now I too walk the road without an end
At last, falling down to your place
Time is breathing.
We clash.
We overlap.
We make history.
While time is breathing.
Somewhere inside it,
memories are engraved.
Final episode:
Time
Your way of life
is that of a shooting star.