Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
This game's winner is...
Haneda Takeshi.
Well, well. Isn't that Otonashi?
Episode 8
Bewilderment
He is... my dad.
Slotter's life is in fingers.
Morning!
Guess you're not showing up
carefree as usual.
Of course you are not.
You are too concerned
about why did your father abandon the family.
And is he really that vile a person.
But by a cruel irony, you ended up
following the same path as the father.
Is something wrong, Master?
You don't usually sigh that deeply.
No.
Nothing whatsoever.
That's strange.
Speaking of strange,
Ginya is also acting a stranger.
He hasn't shown up here a single time recently.
What could have happened to him?
One's contents are vast
and cannot be filled with loneliness.
Even if you try sustaining such a life,
the hunger will bring you back soon enough.
You think so...
So be it.
Master, it's about time I go.
Thanks for your work.
I'm off!
Yuri!
Oumi?
What a coincidence.
It must have been fate that drew us here,
what else can it be?
I feel like Big Bonus
has suddenly been bestowed on me.
Really? Because on my side it very much feels
like an intentional calculation.
Well, I've not been doing
enough exercises recently you see.
I need to burn a lot of subcutaneous fat.
Is there a better place than a gym to do so?
That's the sole reason why I turned up here.
One way or another, it just turns out
Yuri is working here as well. Who would've thought!
Subcutaneous fat, huh?
Yes! Shall we start?
What do you mean?
No way! Aren't you the most
renowned instructor here, Yuri?
And this one here is in a dire need of a coach.
Aren't we the mates by nature?
Coach?
Yes. A Coach.
You are bound to devote today to me alone.
So? Is it intense enough?
Not... yet. What's more important,
what are your plans for your next day off?
Instead of talking,
take a tighter grip.
Sure!
Say... Yuri...
Is your weekend schedule very tight?
Raise your legs more!
Okay!
Right, to make your abdomen stronger,
you have to raise your whole body.
I'm off!
Oumi?
I cannot thank you enough for today, Yuri.
Oumi... Are you feeling well?
It was Yuri's coaching
that stunned me.
So I thought I should do something
to repay to you for that consultation.
To me?
By the bayside, there's a pleasantly vibed restaurant
serving french cuisine.
Unless by any chance Yuri
prefers japanese cuisine?
So...
Yuri?
There's one place I'd like to visit.
Would you care to accompany me there, Oumi?
Without a second thought!
I'll go wherever Yuri says!
Whether it's the edge of the Earth or a cozy hotel -
everything is OK with me!
I said you can go wherever...
But you chose this?
Yes! For the first time ever,
I wanted to visit a parlor.
If you say so...
Yuri.
Pressing buttons blindly won't do.
But then...
It's alright.
Let me show you.
You're such a lovely child.
Something wrong?
No... Instead, Yuri,
try pressing them now.
You don't mind?
The right timing decides everything here.
Just watch carefully on the spinning drum.
Try to notice big red Sevens as they are passing by.
It's easier once you get used.
Okay, now try to adjust to the timing.
Hit it!
That's right.
Now just do the same with the right button.
Hit!
Just one more left.
Watch closely as it spins.
Feel the timing for the Seven.
Tap... Tap... Tap... Hit now!
I did it!
Three Sevens!
You really did!
Don't you think you have a hidden talent for it, Yuri?
Do I?
Alright!
So what do I do?
It really...
hurts.
Why does it distress me so much?
Ginya, little Mai will also be living
together with us from now on.
That's right. The time is ripe for us
to finally start being a family.
What about mom?
For now, we have to part.
However, you can be sure that mom
is always looking after you two from the heavens.
Since that day we have been raised
by our aunt and uncle.
Hey, mom, which man is our real father?
He never showed up - neither when Mai was born
nor when sister Sakura was dying.
He was a vile man.
But he was duly punished for abandoning you two.
He died too.
It took no more than 3 months
after my sister's death.
Kojiro can in no way
be considered a vile man.
What on Earth is going on?
Our piblings never ceased talking
about how vile our father was.
Master, in turn, claims
our father was a sound guy.
Neither strikes me as a person telling lies.
What kind of work was he doing? What kind of father
he was? I never had any chance to find out.
The only thing the aunt ever told me
is the most digestible one - that he was a vile man.
But then, there's the Master.
It hurts...
Where is the truth?
What is it with that punk?
How should I think of it?
My father might as well still be alive.
And I... I'm alive, aren't I?
Why am I being such a laughing stock?
Not taught to apologize
for bumping into a person, are ya?
Say something, you brat!
I'm telling you,
the youth has no idea of decency these days!
Indeed they don't!
At least look me in the eyes when I'm talking to you!
You play pachislot with a deep hatred.
Daiba says...
he can see that inside my heart.
What a punk!
Now he is assaulting us without warning!
See what happens
when you underestimate a salaryman?
If you ever forget what a cruel place world is,
we're here to remind you!
Hey, don't you think he had his lesson?
Well, he's unlikely apologizing,
so maybe we call it enough?
What a gutless scum.
Hey, who wants another drink?
Me...
Pachislot...
Dad...
Do I really hate it?
This place...
Is someone there?
Well, guess who decided to wake up.
Oumi? But why?
That should be my line.
Why would Ginya
be lying on the ground in such a place?
I applied all the treatment available.
But you still have to stay in bed for today.
I appreciate that a lot.
The hand is not injured,
that matters the most.
As a matter of fact,
yesterday I went on a date with Yuri.
That was when I saw Ginya
loafing by in the downtown.
I thought I'd go find you later
to brag my accomplishment.
But then I found you unconscious
in some backstreet.
I heard you have lost,
Ginya.
I don't claim to know
what exactly is going on for you.
But I don't understand it at all.
If you keep it this way,
you are bound to keep losing.
You know it better than anyone.
Slothium does not tolerate such ineptitude.
Here.
It was in your postbox.
It's from Slothium.
Most likely, a schedule for your next game.
That is exactly
what Oumi would have said.
One can see with a bare eye that fighting
in such condition will only lead to a beating.
The same pachislot
that my dad has so much to do with.
I'm not going there.
I will no longer be fighting in Slothium.
Is that so?
I guess it's irrevocable since you decided so.
Ginya...
You are my most precious rival.
If there is a way, I don't want you
to get off the track that miserably.
He didn't show up today either.
I wonder
what could have happened to that guy.
In the end, I...
am going
essentially the same way my father once went.
With pachislot...
What is it so interesting about pachislot?
She has the point...
In pachislot...
Keep it this way
and you will lose again.
I should stop.
That's right.
It's the best for everyone's sake.
That is the only way to end suffering.
Once and for all.
Shit!
Shit! Shit!
What the hell
am I doing this for?
Game is concluded.
Today's game winner is Oumi Shunichi.
Ginya...
Are you worried about Ginya, Master?
Oumi?
You think he will come?
Naturally, there is a good chance he doesn't show up.
However...
However?
I'm not forgoing the hope.
Either way, we can't do anything but watch how he copes.
Shall we make a bet?
Whether Ginya shows up or not.
That won't do.
Why else do we come here?
To find out for certain, without guessing.
But if we did, what would you bet on?
I see.
Hey, Dealer!
Isn't it time already?
I don't want to come here another time!
We've been waiting long enough.
Well then...
Ginya understands that as well.
If you skip a prescheduled game
without particular reason...
A penalty follows -
a complete reset of all of your previous progress.
You start from zero again.
In worst cases,
one's license gets withdrawn completely.
Ginya, which answer are you going to give?
All we can do is wait.
After all, we don't know the answer yet.
Game starts in 5 seconds. 4... 3... 2... 1... Start!
Ginya...
As expected...
Will you come to Slothium in that state?
No... Will you run away from the fight?
Hey, is that... The Otonashi guy?
Otonashi Ginya?
Did he show up the last minute?
I knew he was gonna come somehow, told ya.
But can he really turn the tables?
Well, we're about to find out.
No, this time he is determined.
Mr. Otonashi.
My bad.
I got lost, but I hope I'm not too late.
Ginya...
I cannot be terrified
by the sight of the machine forever.
At least for now,
I should be able to do it...
To fight my opponents!
To keep fighting
because I have to win.
Let's do it!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
My father's other side.
Eyes of savage.
Boxer.
Kasamatsu Ryu.
Akira.
Sweet child.
Next time:
Pro.
My finger will
stop the time.