Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Dad...
Instead of tending to us and our family,
dad preferred to design pachislot machines?
Such a thing... Such a thing!
Episode 11
Days Gone
Impressive...
Ever since the match started,
this guy have not stopped once in 30 minutes.
It would take him just 5 more to win.
We have seen his games before.
Shit... Shit, shit! Shit! Shit!
Game is concluded.
The winner is Otonashi Ginya.
Note, that the current Otonashi's victory
in just 35 minutes has set a new record for Slothium.
What is he doing now?
The game is already over.
Dealer?
My heartfelt congratulations.
Well, what a bummer.
That felt like one hell of a weird game,
even though I inadvertently won.
Daiba?
Have you seen what just happened?
How I fought?
At this rate, you'll be getting
a challenge from me in no time.
You're overvaluing me.
I'm not to remain the Ultimate King for the eternity.
What do you mean by that?
If you go on pressing buttons this way, no matter how many times you challenge me, it is all in vain.
You're being the usual you,
pressing buttons with anger and hatred.
It's only natural, you had no trouble
seeing through my heart's mood once again.
But can it be due to you
pressing the buttons with hatred as well?
Me?
You should be.
I know pachislot allegedly killed your best friend.
That's enough to hate pachislot!
Do you think so?
I will pray that you
do not lose your next game as well.
What's up?
Did you come back to vex me again?
Do I really vex you that much?
Where's Yuri?
Doing deliveries?
Nope.
Doing pachislot with Oumi.
With Oumi?!
Oumi kept obstinately vexing her with invitations.
Cafes, leisures...
Well, all kinds of things.
But recently, Yuri embraced pachislot,
refusing to accept his courting any other way around.
Does it bother you?
Not at all.
Say, Master, can I still vex you with a question?
I knew it!
Those two's rapprochement does bother you after all?
Another thing! That's not what I wanted to ask.
Tell me about Daiba Ryo.
Daiba?
From what you know of Daiba,
what kind of person he is?
If only I knew what kind of person he is...
But I can't have any idea
what was this guy before coming to Slothium.
Something wrong with him?
Well, if only a smidgen.
I just don't get it
how come he doesn't hate pachislot.
That's how it looked like at first.
That was Daiba's deal.
When he first appeared at Slothium,
it was like he is fighting a swordfight. That's what I'm told.
Here, have my brand one.
As soon as I abandoned my hatred,
I could see the light.
Master, we're back.
You have to forgive us.
Yuri's self-indulgence carried her away.
Today is special. So, how did it go?
Were you victorious?
Winner, winner, chicken dinner!
I'm telling you, Yuri has everything it takes
to become a first-class slotter!
Master, let me handle this.
You finally came, Ginya.
Your pachislot addiction is getting out of hand!
Why are you being so ablaze about it?
There's nothing of the kind.
I'm not ablaze.
I guess Ginya can't stand the sight
of me and Yuri finally having a date?
A date?
Am I not allowed to enjoy pachislot?
I didn't say you can't...
Is it only allowed for Ginya?
Unlike Yuri, I am not playing it for fun!
Ginya, you do not enjoy pachislot?
You press the buttons with anger and hatred.
I do... I do...
What's the matter?
Ginya, are you experiencing a slump?
I mean, people say novelists have periods of slump
sometimes, when they can't write a line,
be it even a mere article.
And with Ginya's miniscule brain,
slump is only natural.
Who did you call miniscule-brained?!
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
It can't be helped.
It can be mitigated
by going shopping with me tomorrow though.
To carry my bags around, naturally.
I will happily join you for a date!
It's no good to go on dates every day.
How about you go to work for a change, Oumi?
Okay...
Ginya, we're good to go.
It's decided then.
Master, I'll do the dishwashing.
Please, you have to tell me.
After his best friend's death,
what became of this Daiba guy?
If only I had any idea myself.
All I've heard was
that weird Double Pachislot-Suicide rumor.
There should be something else concerning Daiba!
That is, unless he coped with his hate for pachislot.
But was it really possible in his position?
Did you meet Daiba somewhere recently?
No...
Hiding the sensation.
Ginya, you are almost a real reporter now.
Well, it's not...
I don't know much about Daiba,
but I can remember one thing.
What is it?
People say he was smiling.
Smiling?
When Daiba first saw Fushina dead,
Fushina's face is said to have been grinning blissfully.
Why won't you inquire
in the Toto University yourself?
There's a good chance you stumble upon someone
who was attending the same class as Fushina and Daiba.
That's it!
Thank you, Ms. Ishibashi!
If you excuse me!
That's one excited departure.
All the tea stalks are standing!
I came here again, Fushina.
Faculty of Electronic Engineering
Are you that reporter for the magazine?
It is me. Otonashi Ginya.
So it's you, huh...
What is it you want to hear about, then?
The new negative resistance superconductor?
Or is it the chemistry
of organometallic vapor deposition?
Now that is troublesome.
You didn't bother to study the subject
prior to the interview.
I can't waste my experiment time on you.
Well, gonna get back to it.
Just a minute more,
Professor Umeyashiki!
Not a Professor, but the Assistant.
Then... Can Professor Assistant Umeyashiki
tell me about times of his studentship here,
when he was a classmate
of Mr. Daiba Ryo and Mr. Fushina?
Daiba? Fushina?
Those names bring back so much memories!
If those two were still here,
both would have already become professors by now.
So, are you saying they were both that excellent?
Daiba and Fushina were two geniuses,
equally eligible to be the faculty's number one.
They were rivals,
but also best friends at the same time.
I could be trying my best studying
and still remain below their ground zero.
They were often helping me out studying.
Yes, I remember that time...
In various kinds of the recoil response,
the electrons wavelengths arrange by layer thickness
and come into superposition
in the artificial crystals of superlattice.
Hey, Daiba, are you in there?
My hands are full, open the door.
What? Is that you, Fushina?
What is all of that?
The pachislot gainings.
I can't eat it all by myself, so treat yourself.
Come in.
This is all from pachislot?
I solved your supper problem for today.
We're having an exam coming.
Sure you want to spend every day playing pachislot?
I also snatched Daiba's favorite cheese.
Thank you.
Our preparedness renders it already over.
Thus, until the exam day, I have nothing else to do.
Thanks.
Geniuses can omit preparing for exams?
Wish I could someday say such a line on my account.
Too bad that genius is only passionate about one thing.
Is pachislot really that exciting?
It may seem primitive at first glance,
but on the inside, pachislot really is rich and in-depth.
All it takes is just some spinning titles
and a bit of luck.
It even has its own philosophy.
In a way, it gives me the religious vibes.
With time, I will certainly unravel
the essence of pachislot.
You're overdramatizing again.
You can try and see for yourself.
Either way, pachislot is a whole lot of fun, Daiba!
There's no way you're not enjoying it!
After that, we haven't seen him for a while.
We found out Fushina bought a pachislot machine though.
Fushina! You have not been coming to university lately.
What are you doing?
Just a little more.
I will show you everything just a little later.
Just a little.
That was the last time I saw Fushina alive.
His death was a shock to everyone.
Soon after, Daiba transformed as well.
Transformed?
Into this.
He stopped attending the university,
spending his days in the parlor.
A gossip sprout at that time,
that he destroyed god knows how many stores on his way.
Dear customers, we appreciate your lasting fidelity.
After a long break, our store will be reopened on the 10th of this month.
And then, Daiba went...
Well, that's about as much as I can tell.
I don't have any idea what happened after that.
Fushina,
do you remember?
I hated pachislot,
vowed to take my revenge on it.
When I found out about Slothium,
I entered without a second thought.
I'm going in, Fushina!
Why?
Why won't you align!?
Game is concluded.
This game's outsider Daiba Ryo
has lost his privilege to fight for a Knight's title.
Damn!
I'm sorry, Fushina.
I don't think I will ever succeed in avenging you!
You should enjoy it, Daiba.
If you play with hatred,
you cannot unravel the essence of pachislot.
Try enjoying it, more.
Pachislot is a whole lot of fun!
Fushina...
I have always wanted to see it
the way you saw it.
But alas, it does not seem I have much more time left.
That is why
I must do whatever is still in my power.
That's the way I felt when I was young.
I hated pachislot.
Yes, Otonashi.
Yuri?
Behind me...
Sorry for the wait!
Well then, up to carrying some bags today?
I figured so.
So, where to?
Follow me and don't ask.
Sure, sure.
I remember what you taught me once,
and I know, I should convey it to him as well.
Are you serious?
You know it's a parlor, right?
Of course!
What about the shopping part?
We'll get everything here.
Come on, you kidding?
You promised to accompany me, remember?
Come on in.
What are you afraid of?
Go ahead and teach me to adjust my eyes to the timing.
That's unfortunate.
Go on, Mister Ginya Windmill.
Okay.
Then, let's begin with the basics.
First, try to aim for that red flashy Seven.
Okay. Here I go then.
Watch closely.
Do it now!
I did it!
It's just a simple Small Factor.
Guess that overreaction cannot be helped.
Now!
I won again!
Ginya, how do I aim for the Big now?
I wouldn't call it aiming...
It is rather a matter of luck.
When you play, you kinda do a lottery draw.
How, then?
The machines usually have
from 1 to 6 settings for that...
But even the most lavish setting for this machine
has a chance of just 240 to 1.
Then, I have to play no less than 240 times?
That's why I said
it's a lottery draw inside the machine.
Then, a pro and a rookie have the same chance.
Yuri, this one is a secured forerunner.
I did it!
Ginya, it's a Big. A Big!
Then, try not to miss the Small Factor.
You grasped the timings from earlier, remember?
Yes!
Yuri, you seem to be really enjoying it to the full.
However, when Daiba appeared at his third game,
his eyes were completely different.
I have no way of knowing what caused that change.
What's with that fella?
Did he give up before fighting?
Daiba's face was never the same since that time.
His way of pressing pachislot buttons was joy-fueled.
Until then, I have never seen such a play.
Ginya?
Is something wrong with you?
Not at all. Why?
That pattern seems somehow odd.
Wait... Yuri, that's another secured forerunner!
Is it?
Wanna try?
I did it! It's a consecutive hit, a Renchan!
Ginya, V!
We have won a lot. A lot!
Hey, do you know?
Why did I suddenly become so keen about pachislot.
I guess...
Because you enjoy it?
So that's how you see it.
But I thought I became so keen about pachislot...
In order to cognize Ginya's feelings.
I wanted to understand how Ginya feels about it.
But I couldn't understand it.
Even if I personally enjoy it,
for Ginya it's a whole other thing, it seems.
Ever since he started playing pachislot,
Ginya changed completely.
He became anxious, sorrowful.
Seemingly oblivious to very concept of joy.
If it goes on this way,
it feels like Ginya would only stray further away from us.
Thank you.
And sorry for borrowing you for today.
But it was still fun.
Spending a day with Ginya.
Yuri...
Time left: 30 minutes.
Shit... Am I going to keep on losing?
Damn. At this rate...
Daiba...
With hatred alone, you can't win in pachislot.
Ginya, you don't enjoy pachislot at all?
When Daiba first found Fushina dead,
Fushina was said to have been smiling.
I have never seen someone pressing pachislot buttons
with such a joy.
At this rate, Ginya will probably
end up somewhere far away.
I am not...
I am not going anywhere.
I am here for good!
Regardless of my father,
I have a life of my own.
That's why, here and now,
I must conquer my own place in the sun.
I am not going anywhere else!
You have regained your composure.
After throwing away the hatred,
you saw the light.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Destiny.
Rival.
Soul.
Mirror.
Life.
Sakura.
Connection.
Next time:
Bonds.
My finger will
stop the time.