Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
He has a Tenpai already!
Tenpai = 2 "sevens" aligned; effectively the same as Riichi Eyes or Scissors
Alright, I got it.
Imbecile! Shouldn't have been pressing it!
You can't press properly even with "Eyes" in front of you!
Sorry.
In a tag match, you have to follow the partner you teamed up with into all the ups and downs.
Episode 17
Person on my Mind
Even if you’re adroit yourself,
you can't exert any power on them.
Now it's Tenpai for the other side!
The right one can be slippery...
Is it one tempo faster than the others?
Now!
Faster!
What was that for?
Showing off how lucky I'm feeling today!
Ain't that one was a good omen?
I thought it was one tempo faster,
yet you aligned it nicely anyway.
Yeah, I guess so.
You're starting to make some allowances
in the way you press the buttons.
I can't afford to lose in a place like this.
After Oumi did so much for me.
I will hand in the resignation from Slothium.
Why did Oumi do this, all of a sudden?
If you excuse yourself losing in such a place,
a dream of challenging Daiba Ryo will remain a dream!
Fight with everything on the line!
Throw your everything at me, unrestrained!
Oumi went to such measures just to help me fight Daiba.
Where did this come from?
Move aside!
It's my turn!
Even if you lose, you still stay in Knights.
But my ass will get kicked from Generals!
I'm nowhere near losing yet...
Shut the fuck up!
You can't win for toffee with that way of pressing!
But I...
Nice, nice!
That's a nice omen.
The prime reason for bands break-up
is members becoming bad buddies!
The two that cannot concert their opinions
can never play a good concert.
Long story short, the other guys
ain't having a good game today.
Maybe it's time to swap here as well?
I guess.
Daiba, I'm winning for certain here,
whatever it takes to fight you sooner.
Akiyama Chika
Coach Akiyama?
The memory of that time you had to give up,
to abandon your dream of becoming an athlete
because of that injury right before the tournament,
even to this day,
it pains my heart vividly with remorse.
A more prodigious athlete than anyone else,
and also with a huge love for rhythmic gymnastics -
you're the only such person I know,
therefore I ask you this.
I have no doubt
that you would make a magnificent coach.
I'm aware that for the time being you're working hard to qualify for an instructor already.
Therefore, please give it a good thought.
I'm sorry to trouble you with my personal affairs,
but I'm getting married.
Yet wishing for the gymnastics club of our alma-mater to thrive and prosper, I'm writing this to you.
Coach Akiyama is getting married...
A gymnastics coach in my alma-mater?
The practices were always grueling,
but that still was a really fun time.
Remaining time: 3 minutes.
It seems, we can win even making some allowance.
Even I can only do that much to catch up!
Shit! It was all your fault!
But I...
Game is concluded. Winner team -
Ken Hayashi & Otonashi Ginya.
Be noted, the next General-Knight castling match
will be held between today's two winners.
Which means, we are enemies from now on!
Nothing personal, but I'll be the one basking in the spotlight in the next match. It's not your turn yet!
Be sure to live up to that conviction next time we meet.
I'll go further and smash
that self-confidence with my stick!
Don't disappoint me, will ya?
This is a battle!
No child's play!
Like I said -
I want you to hit me with everything you got.
Fight at earnest!
You can't possibly know it, but Oumi entrusted to me
fighting you for him as well, Daiba.
We both challenge you now.
Throwing away my current job as an instructor
is a hard choice to make,
yet it's tempting to see amazing players
brought up by my own hands.
Coach Kamoi, huh?
Wouldn't it be nice
to push the youth towards their dreams?
Also, if I tell them I'm returning to suburbs,
mom and dad would surely be delighted.
Dream.
Ginya...
Still 4 o'clock? Though it's a little early, maybe
I'll stop by a parlor for an interview on my way home.
Ginya, you feel like joining me?
I had plans for today.
Though once I'm done with this, I'm free tomorrow.
Can it be because of a date?
Of course not.
Well, whatever.
Work hard, everyone!
That's a no way to go.
You should ask her out every once in a while.
Girls abhor it when you neglect them.
So you were perfectly aware of it after all.
If you want me to persuade him to change his mind,
I will have to refuse.
No,
I know trying to persuade Daiba
is a nonstarter at this point.
What is the matter then?
I wanted you to allow me
to attend Daiba's match.
His match?
If there's nothing else I can do as a doctor,
I will at least do this.
I wish to see to it
that Daiba carries on fighting till the very end.
But the Slothium rules do not allow other players...
My withdrawal notice.
Please accept it.
I implore you,
I know you can arrange that.
Was delicious!
Ginya!
Yuri?
Today, at 6.
I'll be waiting, in front of station.
Today at 6?
This is so sudden,
I'm already busy for today.
I need to tell you something important.
We absolutely should talk it over today!
If you have some errands to run today,
I can wait until you're finished.
At what hour you think you can do it?
Assuming the match starts at 5 and lasts for 2 hours,
I guess, it's around 7 that I can leave from there?
I may get bogged down somewhere on the way,
so let's make it something like 8 PM.
Understood. Then, make sure to show up at 8 today
under the clock in front of station.
It's important, okay?
I'll try.
I wonder what is it so important
she wants to discuss.
I can't afford worrying about Yuri now.
Until the match is over, I have to focus entirely on the match.
For today's match, a new machine
of Slothium's original design, Goldracer, would be used.
This machine comes
with a new service function called Gold Time.
New machine?
I wonder if you can navigate that machine
to the multiplier the usual way.
It seems 150 000 multiplier combinations
are available on it.
Today I have a heavy metal mood!
With a bulldozer beat,
I'll stomp you into the ground!
It's as I said before.
No way I'm losing here!
The match starts in 3 minutes.
Be noted, today's rules are:
200 as initial capital, 5000 as the goal.
5000 as the goal?
Isn't it supposed to be a 2-hour fight?
I'll wait for you, however long.
Whatever.
I just have to get this over with as soon as possible.
5 seconds left.
3, 2, 1. Start.
The duration of the Gold Time
depends strictly on player's luck each time.
You mean there's no telling when it ends?
If it goes on forever, won't it pile up enough
to let a player score 5000 with one hit?
Still, if it ends with one game,
it would cause a huge shock.
Otonashi pulled a Big already!
Go for it, hit Big!
Show us the power of Gold Time.
While it's still on.
The Gold Time lottery has a high chance of 50% to activate
at the moment of completing a Big.
So it's just one in two times
and you never know whether you draw it or not.
But if you draw it,
it may decide the match's outcome.
Eventually, you have to complete the big.
Big's conclusion.
Come here, my Gold Time!
Got it! Gold Time!
Maybe I acted a bit too overbearing on him. Still...
So soon...
That's it!
A Big is on the way!
What...
Lessgo, lessgo!
Time to outsrip him in a blink of an eye!
Is it...
The two that cannot concert their opinions
can never play a good concert.
Is he playing a concert
in duet with machine?!
This way we'll stomp him at once!
I still don't know how to put it. To tell him
"I'm returning to countryside" and be done with it?
Ken's Gold Time bonus is still active.
Just as I thought,
the Gold Time is astonishing!
Yeah, it makes the confrontation so much hotter.
Gold Time, huh?
Nice, nice! This is the tables-turning tune!
Keep this up and we're in the money!
Well he said he might arrive a little late, didn't he?
Can't be helped.
I guess I'll just wait and see until 9.
Ken is having a Renchan of Gold Time at this point!
If this keeps up,
he's going to get miles ahead.
No way. At this rate, I'm never winning!
Every fight you engage in from now on
is a challenge to the dream.
So fight with your everything on the line!
Oumi...
If you are to lose in a place like this,
the dream of challenging Daiba Ryo will remain a dream!
Believe!
You are still to become so much stronger!
That's right. Not giving up until the very end.
Fighting while putting my everything on the line!
Therefore I ain't giving up!
Nailed it!
It's way too late now!
The Goddess of Victory favored me already!
Big's conclusion...
Come, Gold Time!
Otonashi entered the Gold Time too.
I wonder if it's not too late.
Amazing!
That's a sight to behold.
To reduce a gap between us,
I have to make sure to collect every multiplier.
Assuming each game won adds 10 to the score,
I have to play 100 games to score a 1000 more.
There's no telling
if I manage to keep up with that timing.
Scheming to catch up with me by raising the speed?
Very well, let's race!
Too bad for you!
I'm almost at the goal!
Impressive!
Both trying to squeeze dry their Gold Times!
Not giving up?
Not giving up until the very end!
What?
Shit... I'm just one game away from the victory!
Like hell I'm losing!
I need to score just 15 more. Stop!
Gold time, don't stop!
Stop! Stop!
Don't stop. Don't stop!
Stop!
Don't stop!
I guess the errands
are taking him somewhat long.
Yo! Lady, you alone?
How about we go pass a glass or two?
I'm here, here!
What? You were waiting for someone?
Move it, move it.
There's another one.
Told you we should approach her first.
Well you never shut up about girls!
Let's go already!
Maybe I'll wait and see
for just another 30 minutes?
Rain?
Just 10 minutes more.
We need to talk this over today.
Just today.
That boy sure was playing on a razor's edge today.
Are you really saying he is just lucky?
Luck is also a part of skill.
Otonashi Ginya,
here's to your overwhelming luck.
Otonashi Ginya is such a stupid ass!
Yuri, I'm sorry.
I'll be sure to wait long enough.
Otonashi Ginya
is such a stupid ass!
What is it, lady?
You ridin'? You not ridin'?
Excuse me, what time is it now?
11:59.
He came!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Dream.
Maze.
Confession.
Regret.
Hesitation.
Believing in Ginya.
Next time:
Yuri
My finger will stop the time.