Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Closed for stocktaking
Right, right...
Yes, I see now.
Those machines are more sophisticated than I thought...
I was damn sure
they are nothing but interior...
Is this Riichi Eyes?
*guaranteed bonus in next roll
Has he been here for long?
Yeah... For longer than he should be.
Now, now, now!
What?
You spend the whole morning loafing.
Isn't it time to work?
Wrong! I brought the manuscript to editor in advance.
Not bad, not bad.
By the way,
how come you're playing pachislot for hours now?
It's just so that I could write
a really comprehensive article.
But since when are you taking
such a keen interest in the article?
It's only natural.
Since I now know about Sloth...
What was it about the sloth?
No... I just meant to say
that I'm a slow starter with unfamiliar topics...
Don't wanna editor to scold me any more
for being superficial.
Ginya is a slow-starter?
Sure you're not trying to make an excuse
for being easily distracted?
Well, I wouldn't say I'm always like that.
Hello?
Editor summons me?
Episode 2
God's Finger
Declined?
You mentioned only general details, but no insides!
No specifics of the process!
General details?
You've always taken up the cases with ardour before,
although you're not fond of publicism.
But until you learn to get to the essence,
the dream of becoming a novelist will remain a dream.
Even after rewriting the same article for a millionth time.
Pretty much what you're doing now.
Well, I'll leave you to work.
Been a pleasure seeing you.
Ginya...
Any idea why he bumped you again?
No, not at all.
Then it's complicated...
Is there something that distracts you?
I wouldn't exactly call it distraction...
Pachislot just turned out to be kinda exciting.
That's the point.
Explains your lack of success in Pachislot magazine.
The machines' technical specifications are important,
but until you let the joy of the game embrace you,
you're doomed. Don't you agree?
In other words,
articles need more solidity.
If you're not interested in the subject,
neither is the reader.
Ginya...
If this goes on,
you'll lose your employneck.
Give up?
After I've already put so much effort into it...
...Lose your employneck.
I can't even go spin some drums!
Yuri will be worrying and complaining
that I slack off again...
Obviously, I can't find this solidity
anywhere else but in Slothium.
I hoped to see noble warriors
fighting for the champion's title there.
But now, having seen it myself,
I can't be sure of anything...
Ginya? Gin...
I always thought of pachislot
only as of a blunt game for over-aged morons.
But that time... In Slothium, when I became a play member myself and got involved in the the game,
I didn't even notice how I got obsessed with pachislot.
I forgot about everything else.
It was the first time something had me
that fired up.
Don't you think you get carried away too easily?
Got carried away, huh?
Ouch!
Come the damn on!
The manuscript was rejected?
Open
But it's okay,
boss rejects whatever he considers imperfect.
Yuri is being too worried about one loafer.
I see.
You sure he didn't reject it out of his bad mood?
Have you seen Ginya recently?
Yes, just now on my way home.
Maybe he took my prank to heart?
Nonsense! Take offense at jokes and withdraw
is totally not like Ginya.
Yuri, time for you to go.
I'm off.
Yuri works part-time at a gym now?
Striving to be a sports instructor,
she always dreamt of becoming.
So it's practice in advance for Yuri?
Well, master, take care!
Sure, see you tomorrow.
Do your best!
Isn't it great?
Seeing one fulfilling a dream.
Why are you speaking of that
as if you don't have a single dream yourself, Ishibashi?
Sure I do, at least one.
Although now I'm an ordinary office clerk as well,
in fact, I would sincerely like to be a reporter.
"Gym" and "jimu" (office work) sound alike
I wish to write about what I see with my own eyes,
tell people about it.
That's why I'm so worried about Ginya's article being rejected. Master, what's your dream?
Dream, you say? Once upon a time, I had a dream
that I had the determination to never part with.
What about now?
To support the youth's dreams -
all that's left for me now.
Still, it seems to me,
you're not telling the whole truth.
Something in this gloomy master's look betrays
a dreamer in him, even though he won't let it surface.
My God, it's so late!
If you see Ginya,
tell him I stopped by to wish him luck.
I look like a dreamer
who forbids himself to dream, huh?
Damn it... Maybe I just wasn't born Japanese
to understand them.
I tried my best,
but there's no use crying over spilt milk.
The first thing tomorrow I rush to Slothium.
Only in the heat of the game, my luck can be fixed.
For I am a pachislot-reporter!
Going to Slothium
first thing in the morning?
I'm running low on the advance payment.
The tournament schedule is drawn up by the authorities,
such are the rules. Here.
Slothium prohibits training games.
Only actual matches are allowed.
Then they better send me this schedule sooner.
Why are you so impatient about getting there?
I'm not impatient.
I just need to get there.
Ishibashi came through here.
Yuri is also worried about you.
I let you see Slothium
just so you could write a fine article.
I didn't expect pachislot to infatuate you that much.
I understand.
I understand it all, but what can I do?
The game ignited me to the core before I could notice it.
This is beyond my will.
What am I doing wrong?
I'll never get it by myself...
Good morning everyone!
Morn...
What's the matter, youthful one? Was one rejected manuscript enough to make you that gloomy?
Don't talk nonsense!
Where do you see a hint of gloom on this face?
Your nail, it's broken!
It's nothing serious!
No way!
Disinfection is required!
No need, no need!
I'll be fine...
No way! How can one be working as a writer
with a wounded finger?
Here, have one.
No matter how small the wound is,
all of them should be tended to. Right?
Thank you...
Open
Then I think I'll go...
Where to?
Interviews, interviews!
Ginya...
Reckon he will be even more absent-minded now.
All he has on his mind is the game.
"There is one place called..." Oh damn, no good, no good.
It's not an article about Slothium only.
Yes, yes.
Yes, it's Otonashi.
Yuri?
I wanted to invite you to lunch tomorrow.
In a restaurant.
A restaurant...
For real?
Do you mind to lunch with me?
I don't!
I don't mind, not one bit!
Then, at 1 pm in front of the station?
At 1 pm in front of the station.
Promise to come?
Sure thing!
Tomorrow, please come sooner!
I wonder what should I eat?
A hamburger? No, a steak...
The restaurant oughta be the unusual one...
To Mr. Otonashi Ginya
"Members Tournament - Round Two."
No way! An invitation from Slothium!
Let's see. Begins on April 18th at 1 pm...
Are you goddamn kidding me!?
No matter how small the wound is,
all of them should be tended to. Right?
Yuri, I feel so sorry for you.
There's no telling if he'll make the right choice...
You will be more beautiful than love itself...
You, too, had to quit gymnastics once
due to a minor injury...
You will be more beautiful than love itself with Miake jewelry
To leave the athlete's path behind.
Give up the desired fate and live a worldly life.
The today game's rules are as following:
initial score - 200 points. Final score - 2000 points.
The game starts in five seconds...
Four seconds... Three... Two... One...
Daiba...
Is he interested in member's tournaments?
Maybe in some of them in particular?
He looks at this rookie guy...
The game has just begun...
I mustn't be hasty now!
What's taking him so long?
Will he actually come today?
Got it!
Riichi Eyes!
But which one of them?
Look..
He's more collected than the last time.
It's getting hotter up here!
Let's do it!
Unsheathing your favourite weapon? But...
The number you have dialed
could not be reached...
Right now!
Gonna hit Big!
What?
Why has it stopped?
What happened?
What's that?
Blackout?
Has Otonashi's machine got unplugged?
Are Slothium rules that strict on the participants?
Why is that?
Why was only my machine unplugged?
Is there no justice in Slothium whatsoever!?
Quiet, please.
The Game is still going on.
The accident that happened to Otonashi Ginya
has induced a stop command.
But nothing has happened to me!
This is nothing...
Just a scratch!
Slotter's life is in his fingers.
Please follow me at once.
But... what about my game?
Otonashi's progress is suspended.
You will be scored with "No game."
You can replay the current match another day.
Now, this way.
Hey, wait...
That's it! Big!
I'm in the top now!
What a surprise... Slothium's building is equipped
with such an exclusive first-aid post...
In high-level games, the physical and mental state
of the participants is subjected to severe stress.
Still, it's not a reason to make the full-arm X-ray.
At times, even the marginal case can be life-threatening.
Life-threatening?
The bone is intact. Still, I suspend you from the game
for two days. Take care now.
Take care now.
Thanks...
Life-threatening high-level games...
What's this all about?
Mr. Otonashi,
I hope your injury wasn't too serious?
What about high-level games, huh?
What kind of institution is this Slothium anyway?
Having my nail slightly peeled off,
I get an X-ray, and the game rescheduled!
The schedule will be rearranged for you.
You'll be notified. For today, you are free...
Then just tell me!
What is my level?
Come on! Here and now! Please!
Are you sure you want to know it?
What's the deal with you?
Only rogues sneak up on people
in that shinobi manner! What are you, a cat?
Mr. Daiba hasn't done anything to you.
What are you up to?
You are... just a newcomer,
recognized by Slothium as one of its members.
That's all you need to know.
The thing is... My passion for pachislot
was first ignited here in Slothium.
Although I don't understand why. But that's why
I came here today - hoping to find the answers!
But as I feared, I flared up in excitement again.
Before I realised it,
I got carried away.
So I wanted to see you, whose rank is superior!
Not only that,
I wanted to play against you!
Until you grasp the local rules, our showdown is impossible. Consider this my request.
Incredible...
What you wanted to understand
is Slothium ranking system.
Keep in mind, the administration wants the system
to remain obscured from the public.
I know how to keep secrets, my man...
Excellent.
In that case...
Ordinary challengers recognized by Slothium
comprise the foundation of the pyramid - the Members.
Members' count is 298...
This is my current rank, I reckon?
Then, exceedingly successful members get promoted.
They are assigned the rank of Knights.
Next, skill plus manner, followed by the special
personal exam, get you the promotion to General.
Finally, the one crowning the pyramid is King.
King?
The best of the best.
Then, this man...
Is the Ultimate King. After becoming a knight,
he hasn't lost a single of his games.
He was destined to hold this title.
King of Kings. Daiba Ryo.
With his power, one can even arrange matches
on his own, irregular, rules.
It was that man...
The Ultimate King!
It's really something! Can you believe it? There are
as many as 298 people like me, and I'm one of them!
Slothium is, in fact,
a considerable enterprise!
Huh? Are you not in the mood?
I tried to talk sense into you, Ginya.
Talk sense?
Good grief.
You have your head stuffed with pachislot now.
No wonder, master!
Do you happen to know Daiba Ryo?
Sure I do!
He's the Ultimate King!
I knew all along he's not some layman.
I can't imagine how strong he is.
Now I'm even more determined to meet him!
Ginya...
Yuri!
Was it fun, playing pachislot?
Well, no...
That was quite fun for me though.
While waiting for Ginya, I had some time to imagine.
Hey, did you know?
Women tend to dislike the guys
who don't keep their promises. But you know...
What I dislike even more is people forgoing the dreams.
So I don't hold any grudge.
Now then, my work is over for today. Later.
Yuri... Wait! I'm sorry!
Yuri...
You rarely see her so upset.
Did you screw it up?
I'll surely... make amends somehow.
I did my best,
but Daiba Ryo's name is not mentioned anywhere.
What damn kind of person are you?
I both let Yuri down
and failed to make any progress with my work.
Slothium, huh...
Alright then!
Where else can I start my quest?
Don't you know when to stop!?
If you keep bothering us,
you will lose your membership and get kicked out!
Let me go! I just want to see Daiba Ryo,
what do you care about that?
You again?
Daiba!
I know the rules forbid me to play yet.
Daiba, I only want to watch you do the play!
To see your game!
I have some time to spare.
Follow me.
Daiba...
I'll settle it with the owner later.
Let him go now.
What's wrong?
Trembling already?
This is a special hall for General and above games.
General and above?
The initial score is 300.
Game will last for 5 minutes.
For a rule-violator like you are, I can't spare more
than five minutes. The choice of machine is up to you.
The limit is 5 minutes. Need to score as much as in a full-weight game. I was given a chance... I'll seize it!
First, gotta get a grasp on the machine.
Shit! What's the deal with you? I still haven't won
a single time! How's Daiba... What?
Why is Daiba frozen in such a daze?
Why does he not move a bit? Is this the guy called the Ultimate King? He hasn't stopped a single drum yet!
Wait though, I got it...
While I'm rushing headlong with full-weight bets,
this guy is acting carefully, saving all the coins!
What Ultimate King are you then?!
Daiba has finished only 3 games so far.
Keeping this pace, he hopes to win by the score!
Two minutes left.
I just need to hit one good Big!
Damn it! Small Factor, Small Factor...
Nothing but Small Factors!
And this guy...
How is this guy doing?
From now on you'll see,
it's not about techniques.
Otonashi Ginya, I believe,
Lady Luck has abandoned you forever.
Not a single one of your drums
will have seven on it anymore.
On the other hand,
I'm Luck's favourite.
I'm driven by her.
Nonsense! He barraged the buttons and hit Big...
Is this what the Ultimate King's finger capable of?
Time's up.
If you excuse...
Before I leave,
will tell you just one thing.
If the slotter's heart depths are filthy,
his game is also bound to be filthy.
What's wrong?
The reel is still spinning.
Daiba... Ryo...
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Fingertip.
Throbbing.
Titles.
Conversation.
Doctor.
Next time:
Palpation
My finger will
stop the time.