Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Free lap! Splendid! I want you to know, sweetie,
right now you're shining brighter than ever!
Game is concluded.
Winner - Oumi Shunichi.
That's it!
Oumi won again.
Now it's my turn.
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
Did it!
Final score - 2064 points.
Daiba Ryo.
Somewhere in the depths of your heart,
you sincerely hate pachislot.
You say I actually hate pachislot?
Why would you suggest such nonsense?
I have no reason to hate it.
And to prove it to you...
To fight you as soon as I can,
I must keep winning!
Episode 6
Spark
One of our instructors went on a sudden hiatus,
and tomorrow is my day off...
That's why, even though tomorrow is Saturday,
wouldn't you be so kind as to replace them?
Tomorrow you say?
Yes... I'd ask someone else,
but no one else is free.
But I have not yet attended courses
on healthy breathing...
Running properly is not such a big deal.
Would a cafe owner allow a day off for you?
What now? I'll have to manage this place on my own
this time? Don't worry, it's not a problem.
See you.
This girl is doing fairly well.
A worthy adversary for us, it seems.
Oumi, you plan to watch it until the end?
Not at all, I was just waiting for you.
I wanted to celebrate our recent conquests.
Well, what do you say?
I'm fine with it.
But I came here on bike...
Game is concluded. Winner - Yoshino Sayaka. Final score: 2061 points.
Then, how about dropping at my place?
You can stay for night. Won't have to worry about driving drunk.
Great idea!
So that's it.
We're both one victory away from the Knights.
If it goes well for you,
I won't have to regret losing that time.
If I had been more careful then,
I could even get promoted before you.
Nothing personal, you know...
It's nothing.
I'll catch up soon enough.
Not gonna happen. Sorry, but I'm not stopping any time soon. I will go on winning until I'm at the very top.
That is easier said than done.
The hottest clashes seem to happen
on the borders between classes.
Borders between classes?
Yeah. Like between Members and Knights.
The difference in power is apparent then.
In fact, the first real difficulty is the knights level,
and not everyone can withstand it.
Not everyone?
Yes, which only makes Daiba Ryo more ominous,
since this guy went through 3 of such promotions.
Daiba Ryo did...
Well, on the other hand,
it makes the road more interesting.
To the one reclining in his throne -
the Ultimate King.
What's the matter, Ginya?
To be honest, I was even thinking
about taking his place.
As well as your humble servant.
I can already see!
Right, right, how dare I, your majesty?
Let's drink to it!
Good morning, Yuri!
Sorry! I have to manage all by myself now!
Where's my rice omelet?
How unusual...
Yes?
Ah, Yuri?
What? Yuri?
It is so. Right now, Master is having
unbelievably hard times all by himself!
Wow, really? Ginya, please!
Since I couldn't come today, please help out Master!
Let Oumi Shunichi handle this!
Why is this womanizer also there?
Hello?
Hanged up.
Welcome!
We are glad to see you in our cafe!
Here. Please, have a sit.
Will I see my sake today?
Yes, yes. It's on the way.
I didn't ask for a coffee...
But our coffee is the best one around!
You must try it, as Shibaura's special brand!
Who else ordered a rice omelet?
Here!
Two more spaghetti sets.
But no coffee.
Yes, on the way!
Thanks for choosing our place!
We'll wait for you again!
You've done well.
I could use one of these.
Until you two showed up,
it was beyond saving today.
It was Yuri who asked us to help.
To please Yuri, I'm willing to do anything.
Except she asked me only!
Besides, don't you have to be in the hospital?
Nah. I already called it and asked for a day off.
That's why this whole day
I'll dedicate to helping Yuri.
You know I don't pay barely as much as the hospital?
I don't need any money from you.
Yuri's love for me will cover all the bills.
I'm afraid, I don't even have that much.
Everyone goes nuts their own way...
Who is it? Yuri?
Hello?
Oh, editor?
What, just a boss?
Hurry up talking to him! Hurry!
Again, not a single one is good?
That is usually the case,
but not this time.
Then... Should I rewrite?
Teresa sure has peculiar hobbies,
and pachislot is just a subject for us.
But only a pachislot fan would enjoy your writing.
We, in turn, want Teresa's fans to also buy it!
Worst of all, time is running out.
Tomorrow noon is the manuscript deadline.
Tomorrow noon?
You have to think of something new until then!
Understood! You can count on me!
There will be no more customers today,
you can leave it to me and head home now.
Thank you, Master. I was the one asked for help,
but Oumi did most of the work ultimately.
It's nothing.
Working here was kinda fun.
And I also got to wear another kind of apron.
But most importantly... Yuri will now know
how responsible and practical I am.
After all, she had no such opportunity before.
Opportunity?
Yes. Ever since you want to know,
this fortuneless girl never had my phone number.
Wait just a minute. I'll make the bitterest coffee
for the doctor so that he finally wakes up.
Wait, you don't believe me?
I'm serious!
What's so funny?
What do they like so much about this ordinary game?
Yuri!
Yo!
I thought you'd go straight home.
I was too worried about the cafe.
So thank you both for today.
It's alright, alright! To help Yuri,
I'm willing to go through fire and water!
That's right!
I wanted to give you my cell phone number.
We managed by ourselves today,
so have a good night.
You two can also go now.
From now on I can handle it alone.
Alright! Why don't we go
to a French restaurant then, Yuri?
Well? I want to treat you!
We could...
We should! Alright!
But we won't. Ever since I came here,
I want you to teach me to play pachislot. Well?
Yuri, playing pachislot?
What kind of weird suggestion is that?
It's nothing,
because with Oumi Shunichi
debit, credit, and bed it...
Right! I'd love to bed this knowledge in you!
What about Ginya? Well? Will you help?
No, Ginya is out of question.
He is too preoccupied with work.
I see then.
Good luck with your work.
See? First, we add coins.
Then gently shake this lever. And press the buttons.
Wow, cool!
Then, now it's Yuri's turn!
I put coins in this tray...
Now try to catch the buttons' timings.
The bonus set is conspicuous one, so aim for it.
You mean those sevens?
Now!
Damn, I missed it.
No, no. For a first game,
this is an amazing result.
Really? Great. Then, let's try one more time!
You are a born slotter!
Yuri, incredible!
It's not like that...
No, I really think you have a talent!
I didn't do anything special...
Master, actually,
I think I'd rather finish at home. See you.
Do your best with the manuscript!
I will!
The music, in fact, consists of only seven tones.
But by intertwining them in a complex pattern,
you create a beautiful symphony.
In pachislot there are also 21 titles on each reel.
And given that there are three of such reels,
potentially you can get more than 9000 combinations.
In other words, pachislot is a decent cultural leisure
that makes people's hearts happy.
But... what else can be said beside that?
Wait though... Last time, Teresa seemingly
said something important to me. What was it...
"Something about pachislot and piano rhythms..."
Good luck with your work. Yuri.
Yuri?
Yuri!
Thank you, Yuri.
What a pleasant surprise!
Yuri, pachislot of all things...
What made you suddenly change your mind about it?
Just Ginya not being himself because of it.
I couldn't help wondering what is so exciting about it.
Good morning everyone! I have it, have it!
Yuri, for your deed, thank you to the deep!
I want a coffee, a hot one.
No need for bitterness. I have already woken up.
Coming.
By the way, did you also stay up late yesterday?
I got bored soon.
Got bored, you say?
"You're so clever.
My little naive prodigy girl...
Come on, cling on to my chest
in a gesture of gratitude!"
What's gotten into you?
It's Oumi. Five minutes into,
he won't stop babbling, neglecting pachislot completely.
"Ode to Joy! Sing it with me, thou!"
Like this?
Yes. He was so distracting
I couldn't track any numbers.
Oumi is at his best!
Next time I will teach you myself!
Just when did you take that many pictures?
I may be just a clerk now,
but I actually wanted to become a reporter myself once.
I'm experienced in both trades... Yeah.
Well, Ginya.
This is something printworthy.
You really think so?
Yes, well done in such a short time.
You did a great job of capturing Teresa's charm.
Thank you...
You probably underslept.
Go home now and have a good rest.
Willingly!
Slothium calls!
It's an important game for promotion to Knight.
I can't let myself be weak.
Whatever happens today,
I have no right to lose!
Today's rules - starting at 200 points,
victory at 2000.
The participants may now
seat before the machines of their choice.
This one! For some reason it appeals to me.
That one?
What? If you're still alone,
you can sit next to me.
What's the matter with her?
Such a pushy woman...
If you're not into me,
sit somewhere else.
But choose carefully who you start the game with.
We can flirt later, okay?
Flirt with me?
Is Slothium a dating agency now?
Not in the mood, sorry.
Well, best of luck and stuff...
Playing next to the refined man
might increase my chances of winning.
Wait a minute, boy!
Game starts in 30 seconds.
Nighttime writing has its downsides.
How can you be yawning that wide, darling?
Are you not nervous at all?
I am Sayaka.
Nice to meet you.
It's mutual. I am Otonashi Ginya.
Otonashi Ginya...
What a mature name you have!
Well, thank you.
Why is this crazy woman following me?
Otonashi...
You don't mind a female company, do you?
The fight is about to start.
Game starts in 5 seconds.
4 seconds...
3... 2... 1... Start!
Our Father, who art in machine, hallowed be thy play;
thy Small Factor come; thy will be done on reels as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily Jackpot;
and lead us not into the miss, but deliver us from bad titles...
Our Father, who art in machine, hallowed be thy play;
thy Small Factor come; thy will be done on reels as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily Jackpot;
and lead us not into the miss, but deliver us from bad titles...
What's going on?
Why can't I score anything?
Since I made it this far,
I have no choice but to drink and calm down.
Refreshing!
Pressure. Pressure...
Hey, darling!
Otonashi Ginya?
Otonashi!
Don't you think it's predetermined,
regardless of our play?
No... I don't think that's the case...
It's the first time I'm seeing someone
chatting so casually amidst the game.
What is on her mind?
Damn, missed!
I knew right away,
you're dandy a man, aren't you?
When this game is over,
you think we could go on a date?
Sayaka is not in the mood
to give this guy a single chance.
Otonashi is her favorite one for this game.
I wonder how will Sayaka approach him...
Well, the pot-bellied one
seems to manage without her interfering.
The guy survived last qualifiers by pure luck.
Does he have any chance of winning today?
Tch... A misfortune.
That is one very ungodly machine. Right?
Now... My Small Factor game strategy
is slowly but steadily starts paying off.
That's the way!
So what do you say?
Hey, hey. What do you think of my proposal?
A date. I'm free for the rest of the day you know...
What is going on inside her head?
Missed again...
Almost pulled it.
Listen, you!
Don't talk to me until the game's conclusion!
My, why are you so harsh all of the sudden?
Take it easy, remember to have fun.
It's just a game.
It's the first time I have so much trouble focusing.
Hey, hey. Hey, Otonashi Ginya!
What do you want?!
Tell me, darling, do you have a girlfriend?
Did you come hear to talk heart to heart?
Quit fooling around!
You can't be sulky all the time.
Tired of sitting...
Now what?
Will she ever settle down?
I need to focus, the game is on!
Such a trifle won't distract me!
Well, how it is going?
Neither the fervent prayer, nor the sincere devotion, nor the play in the Lord's name... Does not help.
I see... Hey hey, how about you?
For the love of God, don't come over here...
Can't be helped if you don't want me to.
I'm sure you'll have more luck next time.
That's the case... That is just her strategy.
She is disrupting other players' paces!
Have you regained your confidence?
Looks like he cracked Sayaka's trick.
No, nothing is decided yet.
Otonashi is still well behind her!
Did he manage to disengage?
Okay... One more time!
A Big...
Congratulations, Otonashi.
It's a Big!
I knew it.
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya. Final score...
Then you just press the buttons one by one.
The order is up to you.
Wanna press them in reverse — do reverse!
A reverse order works as well?
Yuri, you have such a pretty face!
I understand. I have a face of a person
savvy in game's rules, isn't it?
Wow! Bravo, Yuri!
Your insight never ceases to amaze!
Yuri, try the reverse order!
It's fun to look for new paths!
New paths?
Yuri has no way back now.
What do I do to get a lot of coins at once?
Well, first of all,
try hitting Ichi!
Not Riichi?
"Riichi" is a mahjong term.
In this case, should I add one more every game?
Bravo, wonderful!
No need to yell like that...
It's an impressive collection for one man!
Yeah, there are machines from all eras.
What exactly do you need those photos for?
Pachislot history booklet. Once Ginya is back from his day off, I will task him with it.
And I'll make sure Ginya doesn't slack off with this one.
So many memories!
I used to play on this model a lot in my young days!
Yeah, truly, so much memories!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Photo.
Paper airplane.
Shinbashi Kojiro.
Master's past.
Memories of mother.
My recollections.
Next time:
Suspicion.
My finger will
stop the time.