Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
I got it!
You still adhere to that manner of pushing?
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
In addition, with this victory Mr. Otonashi
has earned the right to be promoted to Knight.
I did it!
Daiba...
Have you seen it?
Episode 12
Bonds
You are still winning merely by force.
If you don't come soon enough...
Such high spirits.
Did you hit Big after Renchan?
In that terms, you can say it's ten Renchans at once.
You won that much but took no prizes?
No... About that... I didn't.
You didn't...
Were you actually drunk when it happened?
Well... Sorta...
It's still a long way off.
By the way, any progress with development history materials?
All the materials relate to a certain period, so arranging them proved a bit tricky.
Are you stuck figuring out the relations?
That sheet is what I came up with.
I see. So it's between generations 1.5 and 2?
I understand.
You covered 23 manufacturers here?
Let's see where your quest for knowledge brings you.
Okay. Got it.
Nothing at all?
I don't think a coffee shop owner
has such a dire need for materials on pachislot.
I can't cover all the manufacturers after all.
Have you already asked the Doctor?
In Oumi's storage room, there are only models of under 10 years old. It's generation 3.
I'm home.
Welcome.
Yuri...
The reason I became interested in pachislot
is to cognize Ginya's feelings.
But I just can't understand.
As much as it is fun for me,
I don't think it's the same for Ginya.
Somehow, this way,
I'm only straying further away from Ginya.
Dear guest,
is there something on my face I need to know?
Not at all...
How about taking a day off today?
I'd like to give you another lesson.
We couldn't get any food the other day.
I'm already scheduled for today.
Tomorrow?
Part-time job.
The day after tomorrow?
I can't say what happens the day after tomorrow.
I see...
Are you mad?
Not at all.
Should I be mad about something?
No... I just... thought you could.
In that case you have nothing to worry about.
I don't think I quite do.
Unknown caller
Yes, this is Otonashi.
It's Daiba.
Can you talk?
How come you have my number?
Your resolve to play against me
is still unswerving?
Of course, it is! Did you finally feel like facing me
after seeing yesterday's game?
Yesterday's game?
Well, you could say that.
Will we have one game?
It depends on whether the owner allows it.
However, we should do it before 23rd.
When I have the details, I'll call you again.
Just a minute more.
Can I ask you a favor?
A favor?
Your villa from back then,
can you give me an interview there?
An interview?
I want to take pictures of the machines.
If you will just take photos,
I don't mind one bit.
Preferably, I want to do it ASAP.
Then, tomorrow at 1 pm, I will be waiting at the villa.
When are you planning to get the owner's permission?
Permission has just been granted.
I can finally play against Daiba.
This time, I must win at any cost!
What was this all about -
the yesterday's game and facing you?
Yesterday in the parlor I played against a guy next to me
and he happened to see that.
That's why he is facing me next.
I interviewed this guy previously.
He also has a friend collecting lots of old machines.
I'm not lying, that's how it really is!
Did someone say you are lying?
Oumi?
I'd like you to also bring me to that villa.
As your kindred spirit,
I should by all means visit it.
I can't do that!
It's a private exhibition.
Not happening.
Please don't ask for such things.
How can you say that
after what I just heard?
Then just forget what you heard.
Master, put it on my tab.
Don't leave just yet!
What was that?
He wanted to eat together with us, didn't he?
Yuri, how about you eat a dinner together with me, instead?
Let me think...
I like this.
For real?
For-re-al.
Master, we will have two rice omelets.
A Dinner Set.
So that's what you mean...
Daiba?
Up to this point, it was generation 1.5.
Not a lot of it was preserved.
Further down this row,
it's generation 2?
No, it's generations 1 and 0.
Generation 2 is on the other side.
Generation 2 release followed a profound revision of standards, persisting up to this day.
Most of them look like the contemporary designs.
Is it the end of generation 2?
From here on it's generation 3.
Still, that friend of yours sure is fond of his omnipotence.
Such a vast collection.
Actually, this is the Slothium owner's villa.
Slothium owner?
I believe, this will be remade into museum
and put on exhibition.
So did you get permission from owner?
Our game is appointed at 5 pm tomorrow.
Tomorrow at 5 pm...
I look forward to it.
So do I.
Well then, shall we head home?
Thanks for your time today.
Is it...
This feeling...
I had it only once.
Cherry Blossoms at Night
It really is.
Is something wrong with Yozakura Ichigo?
The last time we came here,
it caught your attention as well.
Yozakura Gen 1?
Do you know who designed this machine?
The designer is Shinbashi Kojiro.
Shinbashi Kojiro?
It's here...
My father's work in such a place...
What is all that ghost machine bullshit.
What is that Yozakura Ichigo thing!
Dad...
Is he familiar to you?
He is my dad.
Shinbashi Kojiro is your father?
In order to finish that machine,
dad abandoned our family.
Fushina, don't you think it's one amusing kink of fate?
This boy was in relation to Yozakura Ichigo all along.
That is the reason
he cannot lift that burden off his soul.
Drinks and snacks are at your disposal.
Please help yourselves to it.
Let me announce the rules
of the current special game.
You will receive 50 starting coins.
Those may be replenished up to 10 times.
Time limit is 12 hours.
12 hours?
You have any problem with that?
No. It's OK.
For the duration of the game,
no one except the three of us is allowed to enter.
I appreciate that.
Then, let us decide on the machines.
My opponent can choose of his own accord.
The game starts any minute now.
I will be playing against you today
with all due earnestness.
Hit me with your best performance.
I do that every time!
Every time's not enough.
Game starts in 5 seconds.
4. 3. 2. 1.
Start.
I must certainly win!
Now!
That's the way.
If I keep it up, I will hit you hard.
I have a Renchan.
By the sounds of it, you're doing good.
How is it going on your side, though?
I'm just warming up.
The night is still young.
Alright...
This is perfect.
This is how I'm gonna win.
You're not catching up on me this way.
He left the office early,
so I was sure it's for a date with Yuri.
Date, you say...
At what time did he leave the office?
About 4 in the afternoon.
Must be playing pachislot somewhere.
About that, he has indeed been busy lately.
Looking at Ginya, I think
there is nothing else in his head besides pachislot.
Can't be helped. One does not write an article without extensive knowledge of pachislot.
I just don't get why is it imperative to become obsessed with pachislot.
Is playing against others also required to write an article?
Against others?
He is competing against others in pachislot.
Right, Master?
I don't know much myself, but he competes with his friends in who carries out more foods, I believe.
Then that's the case.
Rest assured, this is all for the sake of a job well done.
Alright, I have this one!
Bar screwed me.
I believe you are already past your peak.
Not quite. I am just approaching it.
Good night!
Cretin.
Crap...
Why did I start losing?
What in the world is wrong with you?
You are trying to storm it by force again.
But instead of fighting the rough waves,
the sandy beach flirts with them before returning them to the sea.
Sandy beach...
It's over.
Do you want to win?
Yes.
You are facing the endless rough waves head-on
trying to stop the tide.
Every time storming it by brute force.
Until one day the waves crush you to pieces.
Sandy beach does the opposite to the cliff.
It never tries to stop the waves, playing with them instead.
It lets the waves caress it before returning them to the sea.
In accordance with your heart, machine can either become a devil, or a kindly goddess, smiling at you from heaven.
In other words, pachislot machine is a mirror
reflecting the slotter's heart.
Mirror, reflecting heart?
I need to focus on the game!
Shit...
Why do you keep sabotaging against me?
Quit sabotaging my game!
Please don't do that.
In such a state, the goddess
will never bestow you with a smile.
What can you know about it!?
Fuck!
Mirror, reflecting heart...
In me...
Somewhere in my heart, dad...
I don't want to hate my dad.
That is why I had to turn my hatred towards pachislot.
I had never felt any kind of hatred to my father in the first place.
I still have 2 hours left.
Never give up until the very end, right?
Now that at least resembles the sandy beach.
What is it...
I feel?
Daiba, pachislot is a whole lot of fun.
Fushina... is that
what you have been seeing as well?
Game is concluded.
The winner is Mr. Daiba.
That was a fairly enjoyable game.
Can we play against each other again?
If you keep winning and climbing up to me.
In other words, it's up to you.
Certainly.
I look forward to it then.
This time...
I can't know for sure
if I loved my dad or not.
But if he is still alive,
I want to meet him.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Sound of the waves.
Grudge.
Memories.
Seashore.
Family.
Mai.
Next time:
Older brother, younger sister
My finger will
stop the time.