Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Episode 13
Older brother, younger sister
Should I really...
Burglar!
No I'm not!
Mai?
Brother?
It's so unusual of you to pay us a visit.
Yeah, sorta kinda.
Did you need something from uncle and aunt?
I don't need anything in particular.
Those two are both coming late
from school retraining courses today.
I see.
Busy as always.
Going back?
I'll come again some other time.
Wait a minute!
We're going shopping.
I'm cooking the dinner today.
You'll eat with us, won't you?
Don't know if I should...
It's good, all good.
We haven't been hanging out as siblings in a long time.
There, there!
Ever since he started playing pachislot,
Ginya changed completely.
He became anxious, sorrowful.
Oblivious to the very concept of joy.
If it goes on this way,
Ginya would only stray further away from me.
Yuri.
I don't mind if you leave early today.
Say, Master.
In your opinion,
what do I look like to men?
What do you mean?
For instance, you think it's all cool
to leave me stood up?
So that's what bothers you? Yuri, you found some bozo
who dared to leave you stood up?
Can it be that time with Ginya...
There was nothing of the kind.
Yeah, if you say so.
Come to think of it,
I remember Ginya repenting that too.
He said he is very sorry for what he did to Yuri.
I think it was an open-hearted apology.
It's a lie...
Isn't it?
I guess I just have no luck with men.
But maybe I should really rethink Ginya's case.
Hey, what did you want from our piblings?
Ah, about that...
Yo! Mai!
How is your dad's condition?
Thanks to everyone's care,
looking better already.
Something... happened to uncle?
While moving stones in the garden the other day,
overstrained his back.
He was alright, wasn't he?
Recovered already.
I see.
Why, isn't it Gin?
It's been a truly long time!
I heard you went to Tokyo University.
It's great to see you're doing all right!
More or less...
You shouldn't worry your dad and mom
by spending so much time playing!
By the way, Mai.
We're still pickling out pickles,
but maybe you want some?
Dad can't live without those pickles lately!
Didn't come?
Yes.
Otonashi Ginya did not show up today.
Ginya knows he is allowed to practice in Slothium
for promotion to Knight games and higher, doesn't he?
There is no doubt about it.
It is adumbrated in the match date notification, explicitly.
Tomorrow is his first title challenging game.
Where did you run off to, Ginya?
I hoped to find him here
after failing to do so in parlor.
Will you be in condition to win if you don't prepare?
Ginya?
Attaway, attaway.
My luck is improving steadily.
Splendid!
What is so splendid about it?
I nullified the series of Riichi Eyes
by a following Renchan!
What an eccentric way of pressing buttons!
Nonsense!
What the hell is this guy?
Who there?
My bad.
To peek at someone's practice,
you need a ticket you know.
I didn't really mean to peek.
I'm just impressed by your manner of pressing. That's all.
You're much nicer a guy
than what rumors say, Oumi-chan.
How do you know my name?
There's nothing my fortune-telling can't figure.
Fortune-telling...
Then, you must be that guy, Occult Kanpei!
Won't you mind not calling me
by that nickname anymore?
Okajima Kanpei
is my more commonly used name, you know.
Relying solely on jinx and fortune-telling,
you always put up quite a fight.
Remained undefeated for a long time.
And I feel that tomorrow
I'll be in perfect shape as well.
Stars aligned and my biorhythm is steady.
My tomorrow's opponent
is doomed to just serve me a foil.
An unfortunate fellow.
Had you been my opponent,
you'd think just losing is a favorable option.
Where and what are you up to, Ginya?
New shop opens at 7/5
From 2 dresses - sale
Hey,
you never told me what you came here for.
Ah, no, there's nothing at all.
We both know it can't be nothing.
You came all the way home after all.
Whatever. Don't tell me.
Not like it matters now.
Say...
Suppose dad is still alive...
He can go to hell.
Don't wanna see him.
For me it's opposite.
Fibber.
I understand it like no one.
No use fooling me, bro.
Hey,
you remember?
The time we ran off from home.
Hey, if we already have dad and mom here,
why do you wanna go look for dad elsewhere?
The one I'm looking for
is yours and mine true father.
True father?
But didn't he die?
Our true father.
That's what mom said.
Idiot! Don't cry!
Don't you dare crying!
Stop crying I said!
Don't cry...
Idiot.
You didn't have to cry then.
I didn't know any better.
I still remember how firmly we were scolded after that.
Since then, you didn't ever drop another word
about our real father.
Say,
as for the current us,
we already have dad and mom, don't we?
That's just our Otonashi uncle and aunt.
Stop putting it that way!
Whenever I talk to you,
you seem to need to point that out!
I don't want to have a brother
that keeps denigrating them like that!
Think and look for yourself, Mai!
Both me and you ended up here
because of our pops!
No matter how many times you call your aunt "mother!"
For how longer will you keep saying that?!
You're making me worry about you!
Weren't they caring enough for you!?
But rest assured.
He was duly punished for abandoning you two.
He died soon as well.
Sorry.
In that case...
In case our true father really is
still alive and well and you get to meet him,
brother, what are you going to tell him?
Are you going to tell him
all your grudges for abandoning us?
That is quite
wrong.
Bro... Brother, I'm speaking to you!
Wait! Wait I said!
Got carried away earlier.
Will you forgive me?
I should be one saying that.
What are you folding?
Kojiro used to fold them for you every now and then.
- Hey...
- Say...
What is it?
Nothing at all.
What kind of person our true father is?
Gotta be a mighty kind fellow.
Is that why you wanna go meet him?
But didn't he die?
You can't meet him.
He didn't!
Mom said he is dead already.
Don't call her mom!
But mom is mom, isn't she?
That'd be weird.
It's nothing weird!
Actually, Mai would rather wanna return home now...
I don't mind now.
Father really is alive.
When I was entering high school...
Mom decided it's time to tell me.
She said we should rather forget
about how she told us he died.
You...
Why did you keep it until now?
Well... I'm your sister after all.
I know how my brother feels
and try to be mindful of that.
Certainly, had I known that,
I'd not give up back in those days.
I know, right?
I managed easily to get over father and move on.
But in your heart,
his place is probably much more deep-seated.
When you dropped out of university halfway through,
dad and mom told me this:
"Eventually, we failed to become a family for Ginya.
We fed you those lies
to help you forget that man sooner.
But perhaps, he returned to Ginya's heart,
hurting him only the more."
You really wouldn't want the truth about your father.
Please understand, Ginya.
But after seeing you today,
I think there's more to it than just an old grudge.
You can go meet him.
I don't mind now.
You should meet him, brother.
You've...
grown up so much.
I'm 17 already.
I have long buried the child in me.
Buried the child?!
Don't you mean...
What are you thinking about?
Of course I didn't do anything of the kind!
You're dumb as nails, bro!
It's your fault!
Well then.
We'd better be heading back now.
Lest I'll not be able to prepare dinner in time.
I'll carry the shopping bag.
Thank you!
Huh?
It's the same as the one the principal folded.
Won't even eat with us before returning?
I'm glad I got to hang out with you today.
Thanks to this, tomorrow
I'll be fighting with a clear mind.
See you.
Brother!
So self-willed.
Fighting?
Who are you going to be fighting?
Otonashi you say?
We'll see if he's in the mood.
No, no, I'm told Occult Kanpei
has his luck in zenith today.
Either way, this should be
the first interesting match in a long time.
And now, we proceed
to the Knight's title challenging bout.
Going already?
Today's match I should,
by all means, see with my own eyes.
It's not just the today's one.
You do it every time.
That Otonashi Ginya
seems to always be on your mind.
It's as though you fell in love.
What now?
Won't even answer?
I am forever in your debt,
Aoi.
Not something you'd expect Ryo to say.
You think so?
Ryo...
Ryo. Ryo!
Ryo... Ryo!
In the title challenging bout, one side is the defender,
and the other is the challenger.
It is decided by a one-on-one battle.
Now, participants are invited to pick a machine.
Hold it.
Today, this seat is reserved for me.
My compass pointed to it, you see.
Yours is over there.
Today's lucky colors are
red and purple.
Lucky item is... snakeskin wallet.
You never know how it may help you.
It's been a long time without Kanpei's occult gimmicks.
Time limit for this bout: 2 hours.
It's always exciting to see,
which kind of occultery he uses this time.
3...
2...
1...
Start.
A multiplier.
It's only natural.
Because you don't align your target
with the Bar Wind.
Bar Wind?
For the moment,
Bar Wind blows towards the Small Factor.
No wind is blowing
towards Big Factors now.
Therefore I only aim for Small Factors.
There, see?
Are you stupid?
The hell are you talking about?
You know no shit!
Can't even heed humbly to someone's advice,
calling them stupid instead?
Then, how about I prove it
with the next one?
I'll win the next one my own way!
Ain't no one is telling me what to do!
My, is that so?
Well, I did my best to teach you some wisdom.
What? Why does he press it like that?
I press "Max Bet" 3 times,
because I have a hunch it's a lucky number.
See?
Bullshit!
The Occult Battling Style
seems to pay off splendidly.
Ginya keeps making a fool of himself because of Occult Battling Style.
He cannot press the buttons his usual way.
I don't believe it.
I would never believe it!
Now! Riichi Eyes!
Alright, seeking Riichi Eyes.
There! Watch and learn!
The Bar Wind changed it's direction. Then, I'll alter my aim as well.
From Small Factors,
I'm realigning it to Riichi Eyes!
There, got it!
How is this a Riichi Eyes?
Red on the right, gold on the left -
the omen of Big!
I could be fighting like this all day long!
See?
It's the first time
I'm seeing that kind of Riichi Eyes.
It's Riichi Eyes
only this guy hits.
Secured! Renchan!
Catching your breath after establishing a Renchan?
Renchans expire, you know.
I can decide for myself.
We decide nothing.
Everything in Destiny's hands.
Destiny?
The Fate!
Ryo...
Ryo!
Why is it happening?
Why did my Renchan streak break?!
Told ya -
Destiny!
It's a Fate's play.
You can't go against the Fate.
Fate?
You say everything is in Fate's hands?
So it decided I should lose?
After that exhausting battle of pressing buttons
Daiba spent with me, I have to lose? Here?!
Fate...
Remaining time: 30 minutes.
You shittin' me!?
To honor Daiba's effort,
I cannot afford to lose yet!
Useless!
Your fate is already beyond salvation.
Got it! Riichi Eyes!
Just some death throes.
You can catch as many Riichi Eyes as you want.
Without a Big, it's pointless.
What?
Bullshit! That shouldn't be possible!
Remaining time: 5 minutes.
How?!
Your fate has already been decided!
Let me tell you.
That Fate guy
doesn't decide shit!
You carve your own way through!
You took the rose-tinted glasses off my eyes!
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
In addition, with this game,
Mr. Otonashi is getting promoted to the Knight.
Secured it!
From now on, I'm one step closer to you,
Daiba!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Letter.
Paper plane.
Reunion.
Mother.
Pops.
Next time:
Backbone.
My finger will stop the time.