Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
That kid...
He won, you know.
Please arrange a car.
You shouldn't...
It's not like usual you.
You're so into him.
I'm jealous of this kid, even.
He will eventually become
dozens times stronger than me.
Episode 14
Backbone
Bronze-Silk Dream
To Mr. Shibaura Futoshi
Tokyo, Nakano Ward, Fujigasa 110
All that's left now is to refurnish the hardware.
Yozakura.
The name for this series.
He used to cherish you once.
As a man too.
Do you still resent me, Kojiro?
A'morning!
How's it going, how's it going?
Why so sullen a face?
A letter?
Don't tell me, it's a love letter, isn't it?
Don't talk nonsense. Just a note from a friend.
An old-time one.
I wonder if it really is!
Did you sleep well last night?
I sure did!
Like a log!
Speaking of, thanks for yesterday.
It was a treat from Doctor.
He was mighty happy,
with your promotion to Knight and stuff.
Oumi, I wonder how he is doing.
He sure was thoroughly boozed yesterday.
To Mr. Shibaura Futoshi
Tokyo, Nakano Ward, Fujigasa 110
About that...
It arrived yesterday.
It's a letter from your pops.
To Mr. Shibaura Futoshi
Tokyo, Nakano Ward, Fujigasa 110
Master is not as easy one
to catch red-handed after all.
But if you occasionally receive a love letter,
it's no big deal showing it to others.
Ginya, you'll have to figure on your own
what to think of Kojiro.
But let me tell you just this.
In what I said, there was no lie.
I see.
Welcome to our place!
Yuri?
I guess, you must still be mad at me...
I still am.
But with so few regular customers,
we can't really afford to alienate any.
Not even me.
Because treating them with a smile
is good for business.
What are you up to?
The usual thing?
Dear customer, did something stick to my face?
No, nothing.
But say...
Don't tell me...
You made up your mind to treat me to dinner?
Sorry, today I'm...
Then, tomorrow?
I'm sorry, Yuri.
On the 23rd, I'll be away.
It's really important.
Is it? Well, can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
But once I'm back,
I'll treat you to dinner at once.
Can you at least...
Tell me where you're going?
To settle one old score.
Settle the score, then?
What is this pretentious wording?
What's the matter, Young Doctor?
Mr. Gen?
Not feeling well?
Your face is so pale!
Just a hangover.
That's a no-way to go!
You have to take a better care of your body!
My bad.
Is that...
What is it there, Doctor?
Excuse me.
Why did Daiba come here?
Will you let this kid meet his father?
That is the matter he should decide himself.
When you meet him, what will you do?
Nagasawa
Thank you for coming!
Say, Yuri...
Yes?
Yuri, you...
You like this fellow, Ginya?
As for me, I like him.
Though I can't know
what becomes of this guy later on.
For some reason, I have faith on Ginya's account.
Okay.
Nagasawa Station
Guess I was a bit too naive...
Of course it won't be that easy to find him.
Shinba—
Shinbashi Koketsu
Look, look.
There's someone using payphone in this age!
Did he lose his cellphone or what?
Still looks rather young, in his 30s.
I know, right? Really!
Fools! It's not about a cellphone!
Hey, hey, ladies!
You happen to know the guy on this picture?
Is this some perverted kind of pickup?
His fly is open!
I'm out of ideas.
What did that mean?
It was too rash to come unprepared after all.
Hey, let me do it just for a short minute.
But we'll be in trouble...
You don't have to worry about that. It's okay.
But what if someone comes in?
Don't worry.
We'll be done in no time.
Young Doctor! I...
Thank you.
No running in the hallway!
Shunichi?
I want you to tell me about a patient
by the name of Daiba Ryo.
Medical chart?
Had to do a bit of cajolery to extract it.
Well, I don't think I can help you...
This photo is from 17 years ago,
so he probably looks rather like a grandpa now, I think.
This thing is not serial.
I have never seen it. When it comes to pachislot,
I'm quite a connoisseur, you know.
Eventually, this one
never made it to production.
It's from early generations, right?
Must be Unit 1.
It felt so great to press buttons on those!
Well, I'll ask people around
about this machine.
Ah, no. It's not about the machine...
Have you tried asking
in the police box across the street?
About this person. If he lives around here,
they must know something.
Excuse me...
No alms for runaways.
For me?
It's not like that!
You see, I'm looking for a person.
That's better.
Where were you yesterday around 3 PM?
Yesterday? Lemme...
In Nagasawa, in front of the Station, I think.
We received a report,
the perpetrator features are just like yours.
What do you mean?
A molester.
Me!?
Under the pretext of showing some photo,
he approaches high school girls.
Then all of a sudden drops his pants.
Hold it there!
I never dropped my pants or anything!
They all say so.
Just what the hell did I got myself into?
In the hypophysis,
there is a malign tumor of significant size.
Without a detailed checkup,
I can't tell more than that.
The danger is significant as well.
Shunichi, what is your exact relation to him?
The woman accompanying him
also asked his case to be kept in a low profile.
This morning, he sneaked out of hospital
without permission.
Sneaked out?
Just what kind of man is he?
He manages to keep going quite well
even in that condition.
You feeling better?
Today it's such a nice weather.
I think I'll go out to do some shopping.
You want to eat something specific?
Ryo?
I see. Your real father then?
However, we don't have anyone
named Shinbashi Kojiro in this area.
As far as I can tell.
That's unfortunate.
But I'm sure I've heard it somewhere.
Actually, yes.
The fraternity in the neighboring city.
Fraternity?
Mr. Daiba?
Take care of the car.
Okay.
But... Today's matches have not yet started...
I know.
My seat is not taken, is it?
Yes.
I'll wait there.
Mister Kojiro!
You learned to fold it yourself?
Look how it goes!
No way, no way it ever goes this way.
That's how you do it.
Were you sent here for anything?
Anything?
You need help with some matter?
No...
There's nothing of the kind.
Sorry I interrupted you!
If you excuse me.
That was...
My pops!
Uncle...
Where is dad?
Fraternity?
You shitting me!
He let mom die alone!
Sakura!
Mom's name...
At that moment, dad...
Where is dad?
Don't! You shouldn't let him in!
Dad came to the hospital!
Why, then?
Why didn't you come in and let mom see you?
Why?
With your own actions,
you brought such deep wounds upon everyone!
Fraternity
Now, now.
Everyone, gather up for dinner.
Let go of me, you!
Like hell!
Come on, head inside and wash your hands.
Today's battle between Knights
will start at the prescheduled time.
Pleased to meet.
You act just like those previous weaklings.
I can smell at once
whenever I'm dealing with the small fish.
Too bad for you.
But speaking frankly, today,
I totally don't feel like losing to the kinds of you.
And now, we are proceeding
to begin the battle between Knights.
Game starts in 10 seconds.
5 seconds.
3...
2...
1...
Game start!
What?
Bullshit!
Daiba,
Before long, I will knock your door!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Truth.
Full name.
Decision.
Stubborn.
Obstinacy.
Life.
Next time:
Chart
My finger will stop the time.