Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Episode 9
Pro
Ginya's pressing timings are still not good enough.
He is in a hurry to catch up for his lateness.
It's victory or resignation.
That imperceptible hesitation in your heart
is what messes up your timings.
What are you trying to keep by yourself?
Ever since I was a child,
I have been constantly hearing that my father is dead.
But the truth is,
all these 17 years he has simply been missing.
Which means he very well may still be alive.
And if he is still alive, at least once in a lifetime,
I must find a way to see my real father with my own eyes!
Right...
I am now in Slothium.
This very moment, I must fully concentrate
on the battle right in front of me.
Otherwise, I can't move on.
Let's do it!
Otonashi is starting to pick up the pace!
This is finally getting exciting!
Zeroing in. That's the way!
Well, it's not enough to turn the tide.
Just don't give up the hope...
That's right.
Disengage completely
and let your determination do the thing.
Don't fall out of the flow now.
I got it!
A continuous bonus!
Beautiful! Go, go, Ginya!
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
He did it!
From game to game,
you are playing hit-and-miss.
But for now, that's about it.
In addition, Mr. Otonashi will be granted an advantage
in his next promotion match for the Knight title.
Congratulations.
Oumi? Master, you watched it as well?
Your last minute appearance agitated everyone.
That was a spectacular clutch.
Just your thing.
Didn't expect this myself.
I challenged my luck today.
We can give you a ride to the cafe.
How about it? Wanna celebrate with us?
Sorry, but I'm heading to the Spinning Gears.
Then, see you later.
Oh, Ms. Ishibashi?
Doing overtime?
Already finished.
Is there a reason you come at such hour?
No, not in particular.
Let's see... We have our files
on pachislot designers right about...
No. 28 of the previous year.
That's our Ms. Ishibashi.
Essentially, a living directory.
How rude.
I'm not that limited you know.
Though to be fair, there are plenty of corporate secrets
that are not to be published.
Data of zero value, you know.
Zero value, you say?
What exactly you look for?
About 17 years ago, Shinbashi.
Forget it. There's none.
Know anything about that Shinbashi?
A machine designer, probably.
No longer in active service, I bet.
Designing only attracts young men.
Those who are older tend to retire to management.
So, wanna get a round?
Oh, right, you're driving a bike.
Later then.
At times she's nice,
at times she's ice.
In this sunset...
I played one day when I was a child.
Dad...
Just a dream?
I remember so little of my whole childhood.
Can this photo be the reason?
Are you awake, Ginya?
This is the second time, you know.
What?
That deep sigh.
Is your contents' wallet filled?
You look ravaged.
Ravaged? It's not really that bad...
I'm not amused!
What are you trying to hide from me?
I'm not hiding a single thing from you!
But it's so late!
I gotta work, work!
Well, it was tasty and stuff.
Usually he cleans the dish out
as though it was just washed...
Something definitely happened.
He must be going nuts over pachislot again.
I can feel something weighting his shoulders.
Master, you think he is acting weird too?
Yuri...
There's more to it than writing issues.
Something troubles him.
Good morning!
Welcome.
That'll come in handy.
But that's...
Yuri's coffee is perfect!
Can have a refill?
Here. Master?
For the moment,
this model is number one in demand.
The game has become more intense than ever.
Say, the business demands
shift with incredible speed, don't they?
The developers barely manage to catch up!
Figures.
Speaking of which, does the name
of designer Shinbashi ring any bell for you?
Shinbashi?
Let's see... I can't hear any.
If you say so...
How old is this gentleman?
Well, about 50 or so.
50 years old designer?
Designing the new models
only attracts young men.
This work is on the leading edge
of high-tech after all.
Older ones usually retire to management.
If my dad is still alive, even if retired from engineering,
he should still be involved in pachislot business.
This might help me cheer up a little.
It's pretty crowded in here,
but I already fancy it.
He's fast...
I've never seen such a finger wielding.
With swift and decisive movements,
he lines up the titles.
And still, however swift he is,
the firm steadiness
is apparent in his movements.
What an amazing sight he constitutes.
I got you!
He hit it! Even in such places
there are awesome slotters!
What the hell is this man?
That man's eyes.
They are piercing you through.
I've never seen that before.
They are not like Daiba's eyes.
They are aiming for something.
No... Those are eyes that can stab a man
in the most cold-blooded fashion.
Those eyes...
The eyes that are used to hating people!
What's that? A dustpan?
Whatcha looking at?!
Is that yours? One should not leave a dustpan
in the middle of the road.
One should walk around it and you're stupid!
What did you say?
I recognise this one...
Do you like boxing?
I peak hate it, you dumbass!
That was nowhere near cute.
Rising Sun Cafeteria
Come to think of it,
I haven't eaten since the noon.
Welcome to our place...
It's him!
What's the matter?
Sup, halfling.
Uhm...
Did this child bring you trouble somehow?
Not at all.
Glad to hear then.
Thank you.
Minor.
Akira, you can't say such things
to our customers.
It's rude.
I don't care!
You have to forgive him.
Since recently I have to look after that sweet child.
You have one busy grandchild.
He is not my grandchild,
I'm just doing a favor.
But don't get me wrong,
my own grandchildren are just as sweet.
Please call me when you decide what to eat.
Okay.
I wonder what should I try in this ramen house...
No wonder at all,
it's ginger pork.
Is it ginger pork?
Then, I'll have pork on rice!
Cut it out, hey.
It's the ginger pork day.
One ginger pork!
Coming!
Here you go, bon appetit.
Smells great.
Let's eat!
Damn, so hot!
Hey, I'm hungry here.
Minor!
If you say so.
Thank you.
I'm Ginya by the way.
Otonashi Ginya.
Ginya?
Cool name, right?
And Akira's surname is...
Kasamatsu.
Kasamatsu Akira then?
It's a good name too. Not as cool as mine though.
It's times more famed than Ginya's!
Kasamatsu...
Some talented singer I reckon.
Impressive.
Dumbass.
What? He's famed, right? That'll do!
That won't do!
Dad!
Well, dad, did you win?
Let's go home.
It's that man again.
The clingy one is Ginya.
Otonashi Ginya.
I have to apologize for earlier.
Kasamatsu.
You have to excuse my son's coarseness.
Dad, you know him?
We're going. Thank you.
Bye-bye!
Don't forget to take a bath!
We'll see you tomorrow!
So it was that man's child.
Are you acquainted to Mr. Kasamatsu?
Seen him in a parlor once.
Akira's face...
is shining whenever he sees his father.
He is a papa's boy.
He misses his mother a lot
though she's long gone.
Can you really blame him?
He doesn't have a mother?
If I knew more, I'd tell more.
Tomiko! We need your help with the washing!
I was just gossiping with this young chap here.
How much I owe?
That would be 680 yen.
Let's see. Six hundred and eighty yen.
It is that man again.
He was a boxing champion once?
As a junior lightweight,
he had a comparatively successful career.
Kasamatsu Ryu (Tsutsumi Gym)
A signature Razor Jab!
Kasamatsu... Ryu.
Tsutsumi Gym.
I was I child once too.
Although not quite as cute.
Give it back! This is mine!
You have to return it!
Take it away!
Dumbass!
As a product of the lonely childhood myself,
somehow I can tell we are similar.
You like boxing?
I hate it the most, dumbass!
That kid.
He is so much like me.
That won't do at all.
Mr. Kasamatsu?
Has he not retired from boxing long ago?
I hate it!
Mind if I sit next to you?
You're so keen about it,
you start as soon as the parlor is open.
Mr. Kasamatsu,
you were an incredible boxer, didn't you?
It's all long past now.
I see. And that speed.
It's like a Razor Jab reborn.
With precise, steady movements and a shrewd eye,
you deliver a punch full of pure instinct to your enemy.
Capture the rhythm of your opponent
and then impose your own pace upon him.
This can easily be applied
to catching the machine's rhythm.
Impressive technique only worthy of a pro.
Are you looking for a fight with me?
Fighting you is clearly a suicide for me.
However, I'm also keen about pachislot,
and would like to learn from you, Mr. Kasamatsu.
You want to challenge me?
You don't mind?
Whoever hits more in 10 minutes, wins.
Ten minutes?
But if I win, you shut that mouth of yours
and get it as far away from me as feasible. Deal?
Sounds fair to me.
Let's start.
Did this man
never forget a thing from his boxing youth?
He is still training as a practicing boxer.
I've heard it helps them
maintain the body even afterwards.
What's the matter?
Want to give up?
Mr. Kasamatsu,
you don't actually have
any regrets about boxing, don't you?
Why so?
That's what Akira said.
"I hate boxing more than anything."
However children tend to say things
which are opposite to how they really feel.
"Love" will be "Hate" in Childish.
I've had enough of your snooping!
I'm just trying to feed my son Akira!
That's why I'm playing pachislot!
This is my life, and mine only!
This is what you're getting next time!
I'll mess you up!
Akira.
I know you have a dream in that little chest of yours.
And I understand it.
You have every reason to call me a dumbass
for being that unduly nosy.
But I saw how your face changed.
Are you ready to go to the extremes
in all of your undertakings?
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Sweet child.
Setback.
Road to the champ.
Akira's feelings.
Kasamatsu's hesitation.
Hope.
Next time:
Father and Son.
My finger will
stop the time.