Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
My old man...
turned out to be alive.
What? Why are you telling me this now?
I have become a participant for Slothium.
Slothium? What now?
What is this thing?
It's a place where I fight.
This fighting too...
What the hell is this all about?
Well, in this place, there's a
slotter under the name of Daiba Ryo.
This man is referred to as "Finger of God."
He's a man wielding a great technique.
My heart gets extremely agitated
from just watching Daiba press the buttons.
So I want to fight Daiba myself.
Until I turn white ash,
I want to burn hot and bright, fighting him!
What is it?
Nothing.
Turns out, you've been fighting
in some place I never heard of, Ginya.
Me or Slothium -
which one is more important?
Those are...
Not subject to comparison.
All the parameters are different...
I understand.
But I want an answer - what if you had to choose?
Both are important to me!
I care for Yuri more than for anyone!
If so, don't go there!
Episode 21
Yozakura
But I was pretty sure, the deadline is...
I know it's the day after tomorrow,
but I suddenly had other plans.
I won't be lenient
just because you handed it in early!
I never expected you to.
Editor Hino.
Isn't that a rude thing to say to Ginya
before you ever read it?
Right! Read first,
complain afterwards.
I get it, I get it!
I'll make sure to read it too!
Ginya,
for a quick word.
What happened to Yuri?
Well...
When I went to "Bronze Dream," I was told she returned to the countryside suddenly. It had me a little upset.
Did you two have a quarrel?
It's not about a quarrel. Rather, just...
The question of the day is,
do you like her?
You do like her, don't you,
Then it's a piece of cake.
Just go ahead and be open about those feelings.
Go ahead
and be open?
Alright! Ginya, it's "OK!"
This feels great!
I'm glad we took a detour!
Promise to fetch me tomorrow morning too!
Yuri...
Kamoi Yuri
Between me and Slothium,
which one is more important?
Missed calls:
Otonashi Ginya
To me, both are important!
I know that my future lies with you.
If so, don't go!
Please!
I care for you
sincerely and with all my heart!
But right now,
I need to complete the conquest!
Both are truly important to me.
But right now...
Right now, only today's battle...
Come, Otonashi Ginya!
Bronze Dream
Master's omelet rice is superb after all!
Master,
no free service today?
I was just about to offer it.
Here you go.
That's better!
A raw egg is consequently
the superior source of raw strength.
I'm overflowing with strength!
Save the demonstration of strength
for the time of the battle.
You don't have to tell me.
Today, I'll make sure to win this.
Good bye.
Ginya...
Slothium...
All the fights until now... Everything was for today.
For this one today's fight.
Something I have been yearning for.
Otonashi Ginya,
If it's against you,
I know this would be the fight of my life.
Confrontation of the century.
I'll get to witness it in detail
with my own eyes.
Challenger's Waiting Room
King's Waiting Room
In a few minutes, we are starting the match between
the King Daiba Ryo and the General Otonashi Ginya.
Like it or not, the King Daiba always wins.
The rules are: starting score - 50 coins.
You don't know what you're talking about!
The challenger Otonashi has a huge momentum.
Upon the expiry of 12-hours time limit,
the player with the highest score will be declared winner.
Momentum alone
is not enough to surmount God's Finger.
Barely made it in time.
Challenger's Waiting Room
It's your time.
Alright, let's do it!
King's Waiting Room
If you don't mind, could you go ahead?
I'll catch up with you soon.
As you wish.
How are you feeling?
If only I could,
I'd feast my eyes forever
on your sweet face.
But now, it's elsewhere where I have to go.
Ryo!
I am truly grateful for all you've done.
Ryo...
Challenger's entry.
Challenger - Otonashi Ginya.
Records: 19 matches, 18 wins.
Currently, on the streak
of 15 consecutive wins.
The King challenger's path of just 18 victories
is the shortest one in the history of Slothium.
Alright, I'll show you all a truly ultimate match.
And now, time for King's entry.
King - Daiba Ryo.
Currently, on a streak of 32 consecutive
successful title defenses, the Ultimate King.
You, people, are happy out there.
In a matter of minutes,
you'll get to see a genuine battle of life and death.
Yet I'm the one even happier than you are,
for I'll get to play a main role in that battle.
Hail fellow well met, Otonashi Ginya.
My long days of yearning
for this moment are over.
At last, I get to fight in Slothium
while sharing the ring with you.
My delight is limitless.
Ditto for me.
You attention to the middle, please.
We are introducing the machine
that'll be used for today's match.
This machine is the logical extension
of an original phantom design from 15 years ago -
Yozakura Ichigo.
What?
Yozakura?
By letting the same staff extend the development,
it has been given a modern installment -
Yozakura Seven.
They unearthed Yozakura?
Dad's original design.
The most appropriate machine for the cause.
In addition, for this match only,
alongside Dealer,
a special attendee will be present.
Why... Oumi here?
Special attendee?
Oumi, how come?
Couldn't help the urge of watching
the showdown of the century from the best seat.
Oumi...
If the owner permits it,
there's nothing we can do.
However, I don't want you
to interfere with the course of battle.
I understand.
Is that why he did all that for me...
Fight with everything on the line.
Throw your everything at me!
If you excuse me.
Still...
Still, the moment the battle is over, if need be,
by brute force, I'll have you undergo the checkup!
Only after the battle is over.
Hope you remember that.
Doctor is a special attendee?
The match is starting any minute.
The challenger should now choose a machine
and get seated.
Match starts in 5 seconds.
3... 2... 1...
Start.
Come at me, Otonashi Ginya.
I will, Daiba Ryo!
With a final challenger.
And with Yozakura.
What more there is to wish?
Keep cool and keep going, Ginya.
Ryo...
I feel that I'm starting to understand now.
The dad's idea behind Yozakura.
The idea behind bestowing mom's name
upon this machine.
Is this...
No doubt about it now -
this is our Yozakura.
A spellbinding sakura whirlwind.
It all resulted in a great machine.
Somehow, I knew you'd be rapt with it.
That Yozakura...
Appearances changed,
but it's still your heritage.
Kojiro...
Daiba Ryo, your reign as the Ultimate King
ends today!
Only if you manage to beat me.
I will be the one winning this.
So once I'm at your King's...
Once I reach the Ultimate King's throne,
I'm deposing you!
Sorry to disappoint, but this dream of yours
has no chance of getting fulfilled.
It's my own dream,
so I'll fulfill it with my own hands!
Then it's my own duty
to prevent that from happening.
All this time, I have been fighting to topple you.
My finger will stop the time!
Falling down sakura, blooming sakura -
both are exquisite.
We are about to find out
which kind of sakura you are.
Unsheathed it!
God's Finger!
Is it Renchan?
Don't get impatient, Ginya!
Shit...
Like hell I'm gonna lose!
Both play with an immense determination.
If this keeps up, he can...
He can win safely.
That's it! Look at me!
What?
This is the genuine life or death fight
I was longing for.
They truly are on even grounds.
Even their timings for hitting Big are nearly the same.
Up to this point,
Ginya has been fighting on par with this guy.
At this rate, if all comes together with all,
he can really get to Daiba's...
I owe it to everyone of them
that I was able to come that far.
Thus, the only appropriate answer
would be winning this battle!
I won't lose!
I don't consider losing an option either.
I will thank you for bringing me up
all the way to this point, by defeating you!
Stick to that conviction until the very end.
Come at me, Otonashi Ginya!
Incredible...
Too incredible, even.
At this point, doesn't matter which one wins.
Until the very final roll is played,
I won't take my eyes off.
So true!
Such match is not something you see every day.
Not again!
Return to normal now...
Ryo...
I beg you!
Daiba!
Just a minor seizure.
Ryo...
I must be the only winner!
Caught in a sieve too fine-grained for me
Now I cannot move, not even fall down into your spot
Not one hint of human left, I'm but a walking empty corpse shell
And along with me, a bunch of others born just to get robbed
And it won't be long before they come for me
I'm running helpless through the quicksand
Playing with scabs, trying to peel them off
Here and there, neglected idols are all around me
While painting them all with meaningless colors, I offer a prayer
The longer I go on believing in it, the more it becomes the truth
Until it shatters to pieces small enough to escape the sieve
And I guess they've finally come for me
Now I too walk the road without an end
At last, falling down to your place
Daiba Ryo.
Murasame Aoi.
Oumi Shunichi.
Otonashi Ginya.
Next time:
Incandescence
My finger will stop the time.