Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Game is concluded.
Tell me, as a slotter,
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
how did you manage to pull that 180 turn?
I'm still the same person.
It's just that...
I came to seeing the truth of my heart
clearer than ever.
No more than that.
Truth of your heart?
Yes, exactly.
From now on, as Daiba Ryo's recognized adversary,
I'm going full steam ahead!
Episode 15
Chart
I know I should respect one's privacy!
But I can't stress this urgency enough!
Just tell me where to find Daiba Ryo!
Master Oumi...
I didn't mean this.
The matter seems really urgent.
If I happen to come across Master Daiba,
I will pass your plea to him.
Please do.
Working hard, aren't you?
Yo! Working hard as well, aren't you, Yuri?
Yes. Taking my life seriously.
While we're at it, Ginya,
have you settled that score
you were going out to settle the last time?
Settled.
Well, relieving to hear.
I see.
So you met him after all.
Nah.
Merely saw him from a safe distance.
Well, does it mean you're convinced now?
Dad retired from pachislot completely.
Instead, now he runs a place called "Fraternity."
Fraternity
I see.
Master...
I guess I was an urchin of a kid after all.
Took you long enough to realize.
Rude.
What's the matter with you two?
You aren't being bad kids, are you?
Nah, if only a little.
Actually, Ginya has grown up
this wee bit since when he was one.
Just that little?
An ordinary person can grow twice as that
by just sleeping overnight, don't you think?
Except we're not talking stature.
I understand that.
I understand.
You look much livelier.
Speaking of,
Oumi also didn't show up here on 23rd.
But well, unlike a certain monsieur, I'm a grown-up,
so I don't dwell too much on it.
I think so too.
Surely, he'll show up tomorrow
with the usual livened looks.
In the hypophysis,
a large tumor is present.
Without a personal checkup,
that's all I can tell.
Certainly, a perilous condition.
I have reasons to think he is an old pal of yours,
therefore, let me be perfectly forthright.
He needs to undergo
a detailed checkup as soon as possible.
Yet despite that,
he sneaks away from the hospital.
What is he even thinking about?
Daiba Ryo, where did you run off to?
You must call me
in the shortest term possible.
Is that so?
Dr. Oumi is still working?
Well, that's fine too. Thanks.
He can be diligent too.
No wonder, since Oumi is a heir to this hospital.
He must learn how to run it well..
Well, I too, must get a good grip
on my pachislot work!
You've finally passed through that long tunnel.
Good morning, Ryo.
Maybe you should try sleeping in a bed for once.
- I'll be now preparing...
- No need to.
Please spare me your excessive solicitude.
I got my hands on some freshly squeezed milk.
We haven't had milk tea in such a long time.
I love the vista this place allows you to see.
While watching a big waterfall, I sometimes fall
into the optical illusion as if water is flowing backwards.
Water should by all means be falling down,
yet it climbs up instead.
Same for this place's vista.
It's supposed to change a little bit each time.
Yet I'm still looking at exactly the same vista
as many years ago.
Owner.
I'm sorry, but the only thing I keep in my head for now,
is the two characters for "Game."
Ryo...
Owner.
I'm sorry, but the only thing I keep inside my head for now,
is the two characters for "Game."
It's me.
Please ask the R&D department chief to hasten up
the completion of new machine by all means necessary.
Owner's decree.
I'm no longer asking.
Impressive report, innit?
It takes a lot of effort to collect that much.
Even Generation 0 is present!
I'm even still struggling to believe.
I know, right?
I stumbled upon one influential collector!
Who was it? Can you bring him here?
I need to know him too!
I'm sorry, I've not yet
been introduced to him myself.
Only condition of our cooperation
is that his name remains undisclosed.
Interesting. However, as far as his contribution goes,
I feel obliged to reward him.
Please rest assured
I'll take care of this.
Here, coffee.
Tx.
But what an exhaustive congregation!
Like a guidebook on development history!
Alright, Ginya!
Put together a rough summary!
We'll make it a special issue!
Okay!
That's a huge success, Ginya!
Uh-huh. Also include the correlation between this
and socioeconomic changes.
I can smell human drama too.
Some dirty laundry of developers and engineers.
Oh by the way!
What became of that coffee shop Master from earlier?
- Well, about that...
- If special issue reception is good,
might as well publish it as independent mook!
Sounds great!
Percase, we'd raise enough for a hardcover!
- Say, aren't they overreacting?
- Should be great! It it great! Dandy!
Start by outlining the structure.
But you'll need a quieter place to think it through.
Agreed.
The deadline is 5 weeks!
Affirmative!
Daiba really bailed me out with this collection,
though I would have preferred some more time to process it.
Huh?
Which reminds me - Daiba never attended to see me fight
my two last matches, if not more.
Perhaps, even in this terminal case,
his condition can still be relieved.
One way or another,
why Daiba Ryo keeps ignoring me?
He doesn't fret over a thorough checkup, does he?
From now on, I'll be advancing
by leaps and bounds, Daiba.
I feel like I'm breathing down your neck already.
Dr. Oumi from pediatrics.
Mr. Daiba?
I need to tell you something.
I'm glad you've finally came here.
I was told you're being persistent
about meeting me.
Mr. Daiba...
I'm sure you are yourself
well aware of the matter at hand.
Let's hear it.
Mr. Daiba, please don't play dumb!
Have collateral symptoms began kicking in already?
We should start the medication now!
Now, I'm waiting for one man,
climbing frantically up, until he reaches my spot.
Otonashi Ginya, isn't it?
An outstanding contender is on my doorstep.
Grand showdown is imminent.
Are you telling me to throw it away?
Are you placing a showdown above your life?
Precisely so.
Oumi, the death of our universe, what would it be like -
have you ever wondered about something like that?
For me, the answer never became apparent.
However,
when I combust my life to 100% of its capacity,
I feel like I'm starting to see some parts of it.
Mr. Daiba...
- Still, that's...
- People...
No,
I, in particular, take into account
neither my life's longevity nor its shortness,
but how well I made use of available resources,
when assessing its completeness.
If you excuse me.
But...
But the instant the showdown is over, even by brute force,
if needed, I'll make you undergo a checkup!
Oumi, what lies ahead of you
is a whole brilliant career in medicine.
Still, at this rate...
Today's battle of Knights:
Otonashi Ginya vs. Kisaragi Annie.
Time limit: 2 hours.
The participants will compete
for who acquires the most coins.
Now, both sides
are invited to pick a machine.
What's the deal with him?
And here I was thinking
the previous occult jerk was a pansy.
I guess straight guys
never get promoted to the Knight here.
The victory is not decided
by how well you can wield coins.
How does it help
to cope with this place's pressure?
Daiba...
You've finally come.
As for now,
you are the only thing in my sight.
I will keep on winning!
And so, I will reach out to your level in no time!
Game starts in 5 seconds.
3...
2...
1...
Start.
That coin-wielding
doesn't seem to be of much use.
Though his finger-wielding is elegant,
and rhythm is refined.
Regular.
That's not half-bad.
Well, here goes my turn too.
After escaping the tunnel,
which road will you choose?
Will you be marking time in hesitation?
I'm keeping a close eye on you.
Kisaragi nailed Big at once!
How will Otonashi answer?
Can really tell it's a knights' battle.
His score is already impressive.
However, this is a 2 hours long game.
I can wait for a better opening.
Otonashi Ginya.
He doesn't look anything
but a commonplace youngster to me.
He has a potential
to become times stronger than me.
Ryo...
Should you betray the hopes Ryo pins on you,
I won't ever forgive you.
Aight, attaboy!
Look!
Otonashi is catching up by entering a Renchan!
Alright! Continuous multiplier is mine!
Annie Flash!!
She's doing it! Annie Flash!
Why, a woman after all.
What is it about me being a woman?
Explain yourself.
I didn't mean to offend you,
accept my apology.
Now, why don't we enjoy the game?
Your strategy is disgusting!
With your ad hominem invectives,
you are trying to detune my concentration!
But isn't that precisely
what you were trying to pull yourself?
With that Annie Flash gimmick.
No, not just with that.
That performance during the introduction too.
Your finger-wielding.
It was different from that of a man.
However...
You don't enjoy pressing buttons.
You push yourself forcefully into the battle,
you condemn yourself to suffering.
Isn't that so?
Why do you keep saying some hooey?
I too, until a little while ago, thought I'd never be able
to escape that same kind of suffering.
Same kind of suffering?
A certain person told me once,
"If a slotter's heart is dirty,
he can only show a dirty a game."
I thought my devotion to pachislot to be pure and unreserved, but my heart was obsessed with a completely different thing.
I had to grow aware of this obsession
and look it directly in the face
to start seeing the truth.
What's the matter?
Your hands are not moving.
Don't quit the game halfway.
Since I... Since I was in my infancy,
I have been brought up as though I was a boy.
I was the 4th of my siblings, all of whom were girls,
but my parents' only desire was to have a son.
That is not your fault.
I understand it!
But...
I had to really become a boy,
as per my parents heart's desire!
I grew to adhering to that role.
I didn't want to be in any way inferior to men.
Ms. Kisaragi,
as a lady, you are much more fascinating.
That is my opinion.
And I would go as far as saying,
such is the opinion of everyone here.
Ms. Kisaragi,
next time you get to fight here,
do it in your true form.
In your woman form, if you would.
Naturally, just because you're woman
doesn't mean others would make allowance.
I could ask for nothing better.
They say suffering fuels the growth to adulthood.
You really are out to the light of day.
Otonashi Ginya,
I'm waiting for you.
Daiba, just a little more.
In just a little more,
I'll catch up with you.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Doubt.
Determination.
Challenge.
Company.
The time remaining.
Next time:
Sworn Friend
My finger will stop the time.