Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
That time, I saw it, clearly.
Is this how Fushina has been seeing this world?
Back then, what was it Fushina has been seeing here?
Will I manage to find my own path to that place?
Ryo...
Whatever the place you're aspiring for is,
I want to climb there with you.
Episode 18
Yuri
Alright, that's good enough.
Though the data and specs explanation is still rather weak,
you excelled in getting across the new pachislot aspirations.
Thanks a big deal!
You're slowly starting to get a good hand.
Well, the man should feed himself
with his hand only, isn't that so?
But where's the fun in that, Ginya?
Ain't that nicer to have a girl do it for you?
Oh, I see where this is going!
In your case, it's Yuri. Isn't it?
Huh? It's someone Amy knows too?
And it's one very adorable girl.
Right, Editor Hino?
She's nice, alright,
but you should still keep your work neat!
Naturally!
Well then, if you excuse me!
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Your article the other day
enjoyed a rather warm reception.
Maybe a little premature,
but here's a bonus!
For real?
Make sure to treat her to some exquisite dinner.
Will do!
Now if you excuse...
Oh, sweet youth.
True. I wonder when the days
of my sweet youth will start too.
Amy, why won't you make love to me then?
Making little ones as a housewife
is not my thing.
Oh my...
Is this Coach Akiyama?
Kamoi speaking.
It's about that coach affair
from your letter the other day.
Eventually, I made up my mind to...
Yes. Still...
Yes.
I'm sorry to have bothered you...
Coach went to all that trouble just for me.
Yuri!
Otonashi Ginya's stupid ass.
Look. It's one of those rare days I'm loaded.
So, what's your program for today?
It's an auspicious day on the horoscope, and unfortunately, it would appear I have nothing else to occupy myself with.
Why don't we go somewhere then?
Can I consider this an invitation for a date?
As you wish, M'Lady!
It's been such a long time.
Going out for a date with Ginya like that.
Lately, all you ever live for is pachislot, Ginya.
Hey, you wanna go over there too?
Huh? I'm sure we came to here before as well.
Let's see. Last time,
we turned right on the corner here.
Then, to the left,
then the straight path and up the stairs, and...
That's it! This way.
Yuri, here! Here!
Ginya!
Wait! Wait for me!
Really...
Oh my.
Returned to childhood already?
What in the world is he trying to do?
Ginya!
Ginya?
You're not supposed to escape by yourself.
Yuri!
Here, here, here! Up here! Up!
Keep going straight this way.
Then, on the second corner, turn left.
And after that, take another left turn.
- Next would be acute right...
- Idiot.
All right...
It fwies!
What are we riding next?
Don't know...
Hey, Ginya, maybe that's enough of amusements?
Enough already?
I've had some thorough fun already.
And besides, there's something
I wanted to have a quick word about.
Wanted to have a word?
Will I
still be able to fight then?
Sorry. It slipped my lips before I knew it.
Please forget it.
Ryo...
In that maze earlier, had you escaped in under 20 minutes,
we'd have gotten a prize.
What are you saying this for?
So, what did you want a word about?
Maze.
That was underwhelming.
Ginya kept running away alone,
far ahead of me.
Not that much of a big deal.
After all, that's what mazes are for.
Just in a maze, you say?
But you know,
that way we're both getting lost.
Should I take the other way on just one corner,
you can no longer wait for me,
and I can no longer chase you.
Today's Yuri acts somehow very odd.
Ginya is the one acting odd here.
Me?
Right. "Me."
All day long.
Here, your coffee.
Black just like you asked for.
What is this thing you're writing? A novel?
Impressive!
What is the story about?
Advancing steadily towards your dream?
That's such a cool idea!
My name - Otonashi Ginya.
Mine is Kamoi Yuri.
Once you're done polishing it,
let me read it too, okay?
No problem.
Albeit I haven't really written
a terrible lot of anything yet. But still...
Thanks.
Then, I'll become the very first fan of it, okay?
It's a promise then.
The very first!
To be honest,
my favorite Ginya is the one from those days.
Completely different person from now's.
You think so?
It is so!
Totally odd!
Then maybe it really is so.
It's because my old man
turned out to be alive.
In Slothium, I came across an unexpected trail to my father
being alive, though I've always been told he's dead.
Dad is still alive, you know.
You can go meet him.
I don't mind.
You're the one who should go meet him, brother.
Can I help you with anything?
Dad was alive and by all means well.
What? Why are you telling me this now?
Well, I signed in as a Slothium participant.
Slothium?
What now? What is even this thing?
The place where I fight.
That fighting too...
Just what is this all about?
What do you mean, Ginya?
Ginya, what in the world are you saying?
In this Slothium place
those called "Pachislot-Aristocrats" -
the best of the best slotters,
picked from all over the country
risk their lives in fierce battles
on secret arenas of that institution.
I'm one of those fighting there.
Fighting there?
Also, in that place
there's a slotter under the name of Daiba Ryo.
That man is a wielder of an astonishing technique
called the Finger of God.
Yuri,
have you ever been engulfed in this irresistible heat
straight from the bottom of your heart?
- I—
- For the first time in my life
this heat is so intense in power.
From just watching Daiba press buttons,
my heart heats up to red-hot.
I want to let it ignite,
fighting Daiba.
To turn into the white ash,
burn my everything fighting him!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Turns out you've been busting your chops
in some place I had no idea about, Ginya.
Shall we head home?
Bronze-Silk Dream
Oh hell, my bad.
Hey there!
Master, coffee.
You are Otonashi Ginya, aren't you?
Who is this pops?
Beats me.
Must be one of your acquaintances.
Young, young man!
You sure take a good care for your body, don't you?
What's this? Please hold it to yourself!
And firstly, pops, who the hell are you?
Oh my, my bad.
I beg your pardon.
Usually, nobody cares for my name
so people just call me Professor.
Professor? Then, what is your business to me?
For now, I didn't want anything in particular from you,
but rather to just meet you and look with my own eyes.
Think of it as nothing more than a zany pops' whim.
It's "chun-chun" then "totin-toton"
into "tsun-tsun," I think?
Hey! Just because you're young, doesn't mean
you can make it through our world with determination alone!
Well, I will bother you no more.
Hey, master. Can I ask you to present this coffee
to the young man as a treat from me?
The heck was that pops?
I wonder. Here, coffee.
You sure filled it to the brink.
It's a coffee on another's expense.
Make sure to drink with gusto.
Will do!
By the way, where's Yuri?
She was not feeling well,
so she called me earlier to ask for a day off.
I see.
That's odd.
She looked mighty healthy yesterday.
You told her, didn't you?
I wanted Yuri to understand
why am I being the way I am now.
Somehow, my conscience weighs on me
for staying silent this long.
Today, I'm playing my first one-on-one match
against a General.
Now...
Ginya.
No...
Forget it.
Don't screw up.
Will do!
Ginya, I don't mean to reproach you
for giving out Slothium to someone else.
After all, you did that
because you were concerned about Yuri's feelings.
And now, we proceed to the match for General's title
between Otonashi Ginya and Kasai Hajime.
I hope for a heated fight.
It's you...
We meet again, young man.
Before we proceed to fighting,
let me tell you just one thing.
The essence of pachislot is probability and data.
And, of course, the timing.
Once I succeed the current King on his post, I'll make sure to eradicate any counter-scientific tactics like that of yours.
Slothium will become a ground of methodical battle, where you can only defeat an enemy with a logic-based strategy.
You're getting ahead of yourself!
I'm not losing today!
My, my. Such a young man acting like an old guard,
rejecting the idea of a warrior that can lose.
And now, we are ready to start the match.
Participants are invited to pick a machine.
A youngster packed with energy versus
a veteran professor. Which one you think will win?
Game start: 5 seconds.
3, 2, 1.
Start.
There we go!
Don't even need to rely on arbitrary things
like the ability to stop the reel on the right title!
What are you trying to do?
Please be quiet, I'm doing the math.
This condition is vital for approximating my ambition!
Alright, done!
Click and click.
Calculated using maths!?
In this life, there's nothing
statistical math can't predict!
That is our Professor!
If Daiba has God's Finger,
Kasai has God's Brain!
Think I'll lose?
Little do you know the Goddess of Victory favors me!
Yeah, yeah!
Yet another unscientific fallacy!
You've made it pretty far, haven't you?
Ginya.
And now, as soon as the bonus game ends,
the probability of the Gold Time starting...
He's at it again?
1/504 multiplied by 1/2, add 1/504.
This gives us...
Got it! Math pays off.
What?
Put a strain on your head while still alive.
Especially so while you're young!
Lest your brains go putrid!
My very nature opposes the idea
of such man being worth of fighting Ryo.
Only God decides who is worth fighting.
Shit! Shit! Shit!
What was it about your Goddess of Victory again?
Did she happen to go out for refreshments today?
Shut up! You're so obnoxious!
You're not used
to showing respect for elders, aren't you?
Bear no regrets,
Yuri.
Nailed it!
This marks the beginning of my catching up!
Not so fast.
As per my reckoning, the probability of Gold Time
starting for you after this roll...
equals zero!
What the hell?
After all, the existence of a tactic surpassing the God's Brain
remains an obscurantist speculation!
Once I depose Daiba and succeed him in King's seat,
I will retrain you too, as a prominent prospect.
Whether I like it or not, it appears the old chap would end up being more worthy of fighting.
You should keep one thing in mind.
The decisive factor,
unbound by any category of reckoning -
the existence of genuine strong-willed people.
That's it! Bonus Game is finished!
Show up, Gold Time!
What?
Just like I told you - equals a plain zero.
But the problem is not even your usual
succession strategy.
Otonashi Ginya, I know rumors are not liable
to sprouting out of thin air.
Just a fluctuation in luck.
When it goes up, I'll outstrip you in an instant!
Fluctuations are but artifices, produced by people collecting data, intended to explain statistical exceptions.
Therefore, in a machine, merely picking random
numbers indiscriminately, there's no place for fluctuation.
Look, that gap is nigh overwhelming now.
Seems like you can't win with youth alone.
You're telling me one can secure the victory
with just math and data analysis?
Base one's play on calculation alone?!
Like hell!
You are dead wrong,
Professor!
Reducing pachislot to mere math and data?!
If that's the case,
why am I getting so excited about it?
What is that?
That's it!
Gold Time, begin!
That's some steaming nonsense!
To enter the Gold Time with such measly score...
Nonsense... Nonsense. Nonsense!
It's a lie. Just a lie... A lie, isn't it?
This equation... With the equation for victory,
my designs are crumbling too!
The insolence! Otonashi's raw ability to stop the reel
is defying me blatantly! Show some respect for the elders!
Kasai Hajime
Otonashi Ginya
Processor Kasai.
It seems he made a typical mistake
of not trying to grasp pachislot past the surface level.
Whilst the insides of it
can only be comprehended by senses.
How come... How could you win
with just your youth and without pondering?
'Tis what that Victory Goddess of yours is for?
The one smiling down on me
ain't no Victory Goddess.
But instead, my own Goddess!
Now I won't have any regrets about it,
Ginya.
Caught in a sieve too fine-grained for me
Now I cannot move, not even fall down into your spot
Not one hint of human left, I'm but a walking empty corpse shell
And along with me, a bunch of others born just to get robbed
And it won't be long before they come for me
I'm running helpless through the quicksand
Playing with scabs, trying to peel them off
Here and there, neglected idols are all around me
While painting them all with meaningless colors, I offer a prayer
The longer I go on believing in it, the more it becomes the truth
Until it shatters to pieces small enough to escape the sieve
And I guess they've finally come for me
Now I too walk the road without an end
At last, falling down to your place
Wind.
Dream.
Man.
Woman.
Time.
Wavering.
Heart.
Next episode:
Parting
My finger will
stop the time.