Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Yes, Otonashi. Ah, the editor?
Transcribing Miss Teresa's tape right now. Almost done.
Yes, it's all alright. I'll be done in no time.
So, if you excuse me...
The first-class pianist enjoys pachislot in her free time. Ain't that peculiar?
Miss Teresa, what are your
personal sensations towards pachislot?
As I told you before, I believe that the piano rhythm
and the pachislot rhythm are the same thing.
Everyone has their own unique approach to pachislot.
Do you think otherwise?
Teresa plays the machines
as though they are piano.
Oumi treats the machines as human beings,
inspecting and talking to pachislot.
In pachislot, there are truly as many ways to play as there are men. This game is that profound.
Everyone strives to reach the pinnacle of pachislot-mastery.
And the one occupying this pinnacle now is Daiba Ryo.
The Finger of God wielder
and a man who perfected the pachislot.
I must, at any cost, rise to Daiba Ryo's level
to show him once and for all!
Damn, what am I doing? I have to finish in time
to make it to Teresa's extra concert with Yuri!
So, what if you master pachislot too well?
What then?
Should I truly master it,
even death will no longer frighten me.
Episode 5
Future
Master, is Yuri around?
She's off to Miss Teresa's extra concert with Oumi.
With Oumi?
Thank you.
Still, seeing her concert in person
is terrific every time.
That's what I think! Her music is so good
at making women cry. It's perfect!
Well... I didn't mean that...
Anyway, thanks for inviting me.
I'll return that after I wash it.
That's no problem at all.
Are you going to the gym now? I can give you a ride.
I believe the subway will do it faster.
Thanks for everything today.
Yuri...
While being serious and courteous,
she remains tender and sensitive...
Patience, Oumi!
For a first date, it's a huge success!
Damn, too late after all?
Wait though... Oumi should be on a car...
I can still catch them in the parking lot! Aight!
Miss Teresa, where are you planning to go now?
Next up is America.
After that I'm going to Europe.
Is it true that in your spare time
you like to play pachislot?
My... So you already know?
How could we not...
Can I not be interested in something else besides music?
Especially since combined,
those two activities create a great symphony.
Every pachislot reel has exactly 21 title on it.
Since there are 3 of these reels, it's easy to calculate -
the total possible number of combinations is over 9,000.
Getting the whole ensemble to play in one rhythm is tricky,
but isn't it a great way to hit the Big?
...Or a great way to play a concert?
Right. It's the same thing.
In other words, pachislot is kind of cultural leisure
that pleases the hearts of people.
Pachislot is a cultural leisure you say?
Ah, Ginya! Did you come to see the show?
Alas, I didn't make it in time.
It's fine.
I'm still glad we met.
Deeming pachislot a kind of a cultural leisure is a good point. I'll add it to my notes.
Sure. I expect you to write a good article.
Ginya, you aren't upset about losing to me, are you?
Well, to be honest, it was embarrassing.
But for some reason, I also felt refreshed.
So it helped you to refresh?
Up for a revenge already?
Yep! We'll definitely do it
the next time you are in Japan.
Ginya...
Yes?
The way you press the buttons and the way you write your articles radiate the same kind of ardor.
I'm almost certain, if you'd play more from your feelings,
I would've had much harder times winning.
But at that time, you were too astounded by my way of pressing the buttons,
never managing to regain your own rhythm.
It heated you further up,
causing you to rush and make mistakes.
As a result of his inability to catch neither the rhythm of the waves nor the rhythm of the machine, Ginya lost.
However, you must not forget - that ardor of yours is bound to become an incredible weapon later on.
I'm looking forward to our next meeting. Bye!
Take care!
Wait a minute!
What is it between you and Teresa?
What are your claims on her?
No, it's...
We just played pachislot once, that's all...
Wait, you! What's your name?
He certainly gave Yuri a ride to the gym.
Slothium's call!
The promotion game between the four members begins shortly.
Starting score - 200 coins.
The first one to score 2000, wins.
5... 4... 3... 2... 1... Start.
That young man made it to the fourth round after all.
Are you talking about Otonashi Ginya?
I wonder if he wins and gets promoted to knight today.
It seems to me
that the miniskirt will seize the victory.
Daiba...
Ultimate King!
Why is he here?
Which reminds me, since the appearance of this newcomer, I see him much more often.
I noticed it too.
But you should not forget - your ardor is bound to become
an incredibly powerful weapon later on.
Don't rush... Otherwise,
I'll miss a good chance.
Missed!
Now, I'll get it!
Now! Riichi is on the way!
Wow...
Crap!
The glasses guy got carried away
and lost concentration.
It's over for him.
Look! Another Big for the miniskirt!
The rookie is completely out of shape.
Before hitting at least one Big,
he'll run out of coins.
I can't hit it...
If you had played using your feelings,
I would have not won that easily.
But at that time, you were too astonished with my way of pressing the buttons, failing to regain your own rhythm.
That heated you further up,
making you hurry and make mistakes.
Don't rush... Calm down!
Rhythm... My own rhythm!
Got it! Rhythm. My own rhythm!
That's it! Way to go!
Game is concluded. The winner is Otonashi Ginya.
Final score is 2014 points.
You hit some pretty good Bigs today.
However, it was a no way to press the buttons.
If you abuse luck, it will run out very soon.
Otonashi Gin, I'm pleased to see you heeded my recommendation.
Daiba Ryo?
"Tomorrow at 1 PM..."
What could it mean?
What's here?
You'll see soon enough.
This place belongs to one of my good friends.
Zero to latest -
machines of all generations presented here.
So it's not Daiba's collection?
I don't collect things myself.
You don't want to be anything but slotter?
For a slotter, pachislot machine
should not exceed the mean of playing and having fun.
I see. So that's the approach you developed
through the years of playing.
I'm not enjoying it the way a usual fan would.
It helps to remain collected in the heat of battle.
If you intend to be a successful slotter in Slothium,
you need to know the secrets of the pachislot machines.
Knowing the mechanics and history
is not barely enough.
"If the slotter's heart is filthy,
filthy is his game," isn't it?
One way or another,
that's one impressive collection!
What is it?
Found something interesting?
Nothing of the kind!
Are you interested in this machine?
No, it's not that...
If I recall right,
only three of those were assembled.
Interesting...
It has never been in use, never seen the light of a parlor.
It's a ghost machine.
Ghost... machine.
Lots of inventive and creative designers
took part in creating it. It was devised with passion.
Yet not a single Parlor ever exhibited one.
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Let's go then.
Daiba, aren't we playing one of those?
This is where the pachislot machines are being collected.
We can find a better place for playing.
Your method of pushing buttons has a flaw.
Flaw?
You play pachislot with a feeling of deep hatred.
Hatred? On the contrary, I'm sort of addicted to pachislot! It makes my blood boil! But the hatred?
Being agitated while playing is normal.
It's just that you sometimes manifest other emotions too.
You think so?
In Slothium you always play as though you are throwing yourself off a high cliff into the raging sea.
You face this sea and its endless stream of cruel waves head-on.
Trying to prevail through force and persistence.
I just really want to win.
Is it wrong thing to do?
One day, this cruel sea
will mercilessly crush you against the rocks.
Then what do you suggest?
A sandy beach?
This beach is the antipode
of the cliff you're jumping off.
Instead of fighting the cruel sea,
the beach plays with it.
He gently meets the waves lashing him,
and then turns them back.
I understand.
But there's also...
How the slotter acts in such situations
depends on his heart.
Depends on the heart, huh?
Are we going to the game center?
Is something wrong with game center pachislot?
No, it's just that only kids play it here.
Pachislot in the game center allows everyone
to genuinely enjoy this game to the fullest.
I heard the parlor machines
have somewhat harder settings.
That is one more measure
to make it the most enjoyable for visitors.
Everyone does whatever he wants.
Are we really playing in a place like this?
How inconsistent of you. Aren't you the one
craving to fight me again, regardless the conditions?
I am. But there are reasons...
Let's get to business then.
But I meant in Slothium!
I'm not planning to ever fight you in Slothium.
Is it Slothium or the game center,
isn't it all the same for you?
What are you trying to say?
Are you still willing to fight?
I heard you. Let's do it!
The initial score is 500 coins.
The first one to hit the Big, wins.
Shall we start?
In Slothium, he may be the Ultimate King.
But here and now, Daiba is the ordinary slotter!
I will win this!
Daiba... Even in a place like this,
he remains collected.
Here goes my first Small Factor.
I won't miss this one.
Of course I do.
It's just a game center pachislot!
I can't let myself be defeated here!
You are constantly rushing head-on,
fighting the seething sea face to face.
Trying to prevail by brute force and persistence.
At one point, this cruel sea
will mercilessly crush you against the rocks.
The beach is the antipode of the cliff.
Instead of fighting the cruel sea, the beach plays with it.
It gently lets the waves roll over,
and then turns them back.
You play pachislot
with a deep feeling of hatred.
He already has the bonus flag?
It's over.
Did you want to win?
Yes...
Your demeanor
reminds me of myself when I was young.
I also had to overcome my hatred at first.
Only then the road to the King was revealed to me.
To become a slotter one has to be rich-hearted.
We'll meet again.
One must first overcome his hatred
to find the way to the King?
What could you mean by that?
Such an inexplicit guy...
Finally writing your own novel?
What's this? Only devised the characters' names so far?
Ryo Daiba
Daiba Ryo?
Is he the hero of your last investigation?
Where could I have heard this name?
Do you happen to know him?
Double Pachislot-Suicide!
Pachislot has already driven someone to suicide?
About ten years ago, when I myself
was an article writer for a magazine.
In one of our interns' articles,
I happened to see this name.
And the headline was...
Right, I remember it:
"Times" publishing House
"An elite university student
commits a double pachislot-suicide."
Publications Archive
Found it!
An elite university student commits a double pachislot-suicide!!
What was the cause of death? Only we have the key to the mystery!
It happened on the seventh of March.
Famous student of a prestigious university
was found dead in the dormitory of Toto University.
An interesting detail is
that they found him in the pile of electronics.
Fushina Manabu was cuddling
his favourite pachislot machine even after death.
His best friend Daiba Ryo discovered him first.
The deceased appeared to have had
a cardiac arrest due to overworking.
No other causes of death were found.
A subsequent autopsy also found nothing.
How did your best friend die?
There must have been something
getting on his nerves lately!
It was pachislot! Pachislot was what took the life
of my best friend and a promising scientist!
Daiba entered the pachislot world
to avenge his best friend...
Could this be the secret
behind the Daiba's God's Finger?
You play pachislot while hating it.
Inside my heart, there are no secrets
to make me hate pachislot.
Miss Teresa, Oumi... Each one of you, albeit in your own fashion, tries to achieve the perfection in pachislot.
Win and rise to me.
I will keep winning. You'll see what I'm worth.
My path lies to the King's throne!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Contender in love.
Contender in game.
Rival.
Heat of battle.
Heart treatment.
Next time:
Spark
My finger will
stop the time.