Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Dammit! Small Factor, Small Factor, Small Factor only!
At this rate...
And this guy.
How is this guy doing?
You'll find out yourself now
no technique can help you.
Otonashi Ginya, I believe,
the goddess of fortune has left your mortal life.
You won't see a single drum
with "seven" on it from now on.
What I do is opposite - I attract Lady Luck.
I'm her favorite.
What just happened?
I have to go.
If you excuse me...
But before I leave,
I will say just one more thing.
If the depths of the slotter's heart are weak,
his game will be weak as well.
What's wrong?
The last drum is still spinning.
Daiba... Ryo...
Episode 1
Windmill
And now, let me give the floor
to our weather forecast host.
Right! Thanks a lot, colleague!
Today I have a bunch of good news for all of you!
Not again... I overslept!
I doubt we might hear something better today,
than the fact...
Publishing house "Spinning Gears"
Good morning everyone!
You're late.
My bad.
Ginya, I understand that what I'm saying
might sound empty to you,
but if writing articles takes you so long,
why not use a fax once in a while?
No word processor is needed. No PC is needed.
Just send the article out and mind your own business.
Neither a word processor nor a PC
are in my possession.
And that's what I'm saying.
You won't need any of those.
That's whatcha mean...
Does it really bother you?
Gin...
You better listen to boss this time. We don't look forward to working till the last minute here either.
We should budget a fax for you sometime.
Besides, what a poor handwriting you have!
Is it that bad?
You should be more self-confident!
There's not a single subject
that is out of Ginya's competence.
The audience loves him too.
Right, Kawato?
Yes, yes. Can't argue with Amy here.
Fan mail is usually torn apart after his writings.
Yet, an article written by an aspiring novelist
remains a novel anyway...
I can't call it high-quality journalism.
But the housewives seem to enjoy it.
How long in the faculty of literature again?
Two years, then I graduated myself out.
So you're not familiar with the tabloid-style...
Well, I have some ideas of it...
But for now, what do you think?
I say OK. We're publishing this one.
Much obliged!
But wouldn't you be so kind
to pay me in advance for the next article?
Again and again,
you ask for it every time!
What's more important, the next article will be
an unusual one. Come a little closer...
Did you know...
I overheard one spicy conversation the other day...
Apparently, in Japan, there's a place
where the best national slotters gather.
To determine the Number One among them,
they play against each other.
However, maybe it's just a rumor...
And you want me to find this place?
Or prove it doesn't exist...
Still, at least half of this story is positively true.
Would you rather try to find it and write about it?
We compensate any expenses you suffer.
Now I'm in trouble. Just what have I got involved in?
A minute out of the office, and I'm lost already.
That's right!
That short old man might help me out...
Greetings!
She's doing deliveries.
Yuri.
No...
I understand it perfectly.
You couldn't care less about my coffee.
You can only come here to see her, Ginya.
What makes you think so?
It's not like that at all...
To get master's coffee,
I'm ready to drive through the whole city.
"For the coffee," he says! What an insolent fellow.
Have you no honor at all?
Have you had breakfast?
When was the last time you ate?
At five... PM yesterday.
What else did I expect...
You always forget basic things.
That's right...
How is your job these days?
Well, little by little...
Little by little, he says...
Well, good luck with it anyway.
Pachislot, right? But what a pain... Why is it me who has to mess around with pachislot, why me?
Welcome back, Yuri!
Good morning.
Working hard already, young man?
Sure! With my spine!
What's this?
A free gift from a local supermarket.
A windmill, huh...
Brings memories.
Say, brother, where does the wind come from?
From the mountains?
From the sea? From the sky?
From everywhere.
But what matters, Mai, is where it starts.
I believe it is blowing straight out of our hearts.
Straight from our hearts?
And then it makes the windmill spin?
I wonder what color my heart prefers the most?
Is it the color of the beautiful sky, blue?
Is it the color of flowing clouds, white? Or maybe...
Is it bright red like a burning sunset?
Is it bright red like a burning sunset... Huh?
Something's wrong?
Yuri, which color do you choose?
Blue.
Alright...
What?
You can see the color while it's rotating?
Generally, this is the essential ingredient
of playing pachislot. Here. Your rice omelet.
Essential ingredient?
What do you mean?
The key is holding your neck straight.
The essential ingredient is moving your eyes instead.
I always knew you are also a pachislot Master.
That's yummy.
Speaking of yummy,
there's that one rumor I heard recently...
I know that there's a place
where the pachislot Number One is being determined.
Do you know it, by any chance?
No idea.
How unfortunate... But then,
what for do you have all these toys here?
Operational pachislot machines. In that kind of adult facility, they look a little out of place...
Ginya...
Are you sure... you should write about pachislot
with that kind of attitude towards it?
This is my job, so I have to.
That's not what I wanted to say.
Without experiencing the fun of playing it to the full,
can you write a really high-grade article about it?
No way. Impossible.
I can't stop it in the right color.
Ginya's eyesight is much more agile after all.
And yet, I'll say the same thing I said before.
Until you understand what is good and bad about this game, you won't write a comprehensive article.
Forget it.
But I...
Sometimes, it's just better
to continue dreaming of becoming a novelist.
Pachislot might turn out to be a phenomenon
you are unable to comprehend yet.
Well, what's the point of saying this? I'm not the person
to teach you how to write. I believe it's a big deal.
It was delicious.
Don't give up, young fellow.
I won't, aging fellow.
So it was beyond your power after all...
Keep looking. This rumor couldn't have appeared out of nowhere. There is no smoke without fire, you know.
We have no other assignments now anyway.
Continue your investigation.
I did everything I could...
Maybe I'm just too young to understand.
Am I not destined to ever see
the battle for pachislot Number One title?
Still, if it really exists,
I positively want to see it on my own.
That'd be good.
I'll try again!
Where there's a will there's a way!
Here.
I hope I survive till the paycheck...
So, how is it going?
Dead end. In a week or two,
finding something except dead ends is impossible.
It's never too late to give everything up!
But think about it yourself,
all cats are gray in the dark.
Especially when they exist in rumors only...
None of the places I've been to
seemed to be even close to it...
Ginya...
Will you come with me?
To the place you are looking for. "Slothium."
Slothium?
Master! You knew it after all! So unfair of you!
And I was wondering why you look so smug lately...
Slothium is a place...
Where slotters who dream of becoming Number One
compete against each other fairly.
Those who succeed become pachislot aristocrats.
However, you who dreams of becoming a novelist,
will hardly ever understand such an inferior dream.
Those childish guys...
Those pachislot aristocracy fellows...
To understand them, one needs a heart.
Keep that in mind.
Thus, no wonder this society is semi-secret.
Even close friends are treated coldly.
Makes perfect sense.
Dear Shibaura Futoshi,
we are glad to see you again.
Today I'm bringing with me one guest
willing to watch the game.
Name please.
Otonashi Ginya.
Use the monitor presented
to type in your name, please.
Right, right...
Mr. Otonashi Ginya, your registration is now complete.
Please proceed to the main floor.
What it this facility?
Some kind of underground villain base?
Ginya. This way.
Yeah, on the way.
One hell of a luxury club!
That's how they do stuff...
And the game is on, on!
This is your member card.
Sit wherever you like and make yourself comfortable.
Thanks. But I'd rather go see it from inside.
From inside, you can see things a lot better.
I beg your pardon, dear guest.
You will have to wait for the next match,
starting in an hour.
It's fine, fine.
I just stopped by to see it in person.
You don't have to worry about me.
But... Wait... Wait, please...
What is this fellow doing there?
I haven't seen this man before.
What brought him there?
Who is it?
Does he own a registration card?
A minute into,
you are already the center of attention, Ginya.
First one stopped...
Quit distracting me!
How did you get here, kid?
I am sorry...
You have intruded on our battlefield!
It's no place for wandering kids!
Wandering?
Well... I said sorry, didn't I?
People here are too serious about the game after all...
Even though I apologized, some are still mad.
Shut up, will ya!?
What are this guy's intentions in there?
The hell you've done this for!?
Listen here, brat!
You have invaded the sacred place where we dream and live!
Apologize right this moment!
If you hadn't thrown a coin at me,
I might have agreed to make an apology.
But not now,
when you've already made your choice.
You should know one's fate may be decided
by a single coin.
But your deeds now
are not suitable for a real dreamer.
What...
People who dream of becoming Japan's number one slotter are bound to be gifted with some nobility.
That's what I was hoping to see here.
But I only met a bunch of inept pseudo-dreamers.
In the end, I couldn't find a single adult
who'd be worthy both in this game and in life.
If you excuse...
You think this is just an unsophisticated game?
Why don't you try it yourself then?
But I...
Our system has your name registered
as a game member, not a spectator...
Mister Otonashi Ginya.
Each machine in Slothium is regularly serviced
so you can choose freely.
This particular game has started
with a hundred coins on each score.
The first one to score two thousand points
is declared the game's winner.
You're a kid. Kids are always cheeky at first,
but I'm used to shutting them up with one "Big."
I can even allow you to start with about 370 points.
I agree.
Let's give him the idea once and for all.
You say the way we play for the dream is wrong.
Let us see the right way then.
Now, this is getting interesting.
I wonder how will the young blood act now.
Ginya...
I accept the challenge.
He accepted it!
Now I am interested too!
The young man looks reckless,
but will he also be prompt?
Any ideas about what method is he planning to use?
I like him!
Can I still change my bet to the boy?
New faces are present.
Daiba... Ryo...
Ginya...
Why is it happening?
Why won't it work?
He is about to be silenced for good...
I'll make this pretender of a man understand
that Slothium does not tolerate the light-headed play.
Such a defeat will make the best teacher!
How did it happen? 4 left?
This is the boy's first game!
I reckon you regret changing the bet.
I can't lose!
No way in hell!
Go for it!
Why did he not give up yet?
He is done for, that's a plain truth.
Red, red, red, red...
Red!
The last one...
A final Big!
He's still trying!
Is he really that thickheaded?
Guess we'll never find out who he is.
Young men are so unreliable these days.
There is just...
one left.
I can't make it...
Ginya's eyes are so much more agile than mine.
Is it bright red like a sunset?
Just one last chance left...
On this windmill...
I place the bet!
Red... Red...
Red!
Red!!
From such a situation,
you could find a way out.
However, will your luck continue
to help you out like this in the future?
That's the way!
A series! Renchan!
But how?
Was he able to handle the Big too!?
Why it's "Bar!?"
Got it!
I got "Big!"
It's over... Though, to be honest,
I was already feeling my ass fried.
The game is concluded.
This game's winner is Otonashi Ginya.
The final score is 2035...
Otonashi Ginya...
I'll remember this name for now.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Slothium.
Ultimate King.
Daiba Ryo.
Miraculous technique.
Next time:
Finger of God.
My finger will
stop the time.