Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoded by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Episode 19
Parting
Today's the day I'm not showing up late!
It's from Slothium.
The next match for General
is in 10 days!
Just one more match to fight Daiba!
Daiba Ryo, just you wait for me!
Yes, Otonashi.
Yuri?
I'm awake.
Meet me outside in 5 minutes.
This feels great!
I'm glad we took the long route.
Ditto.
I like how this wind smells too.
I sure wish I could feel this kind of wind every day.
I can make it happen!
I know I did the right thing by declining.
You said something?
Give me a promise for tomorrow's morning too.
OK! Let's gallop it a little, shall we?
It seems, today it's going to be hot too.
How ungracious of you, Master!
You alright, Ginya?
Ouch... Sorry. Sorry.
Really, Master.
You should be more mindful than that.
I was lucky to be in Ginya's care, but with someone else,
that would've destroyed your shop's good name!
Yuri, why are you putting it this way?
Well, because it is this way.
I thought it was just hot this morning,
but the reason is this way.
Even the Master is saying it's this way?
Then I will be this way too!
One Morning Set, please!
This way, after all?
Bronze-Silk Dream
Your "Morning" is ready.
Coming now!
Now... Is that Riichi? Alright...
I'll get you like this!
My... Why did I even bother.
In 3 days, I defend my King's title.
If things go favorably,
my next match will be against Otonashi Ginya.
Ryo...
Ryo!
Ryo seems
to have grown so faint...
Spinning Gears Publishing House
For crying out loud,
I throw up my hands!
Without warning,
they passed 3 more advertisements to me.
I'm not getting paid for this!
What is it?
Oh my...
What is it Ginya scribbling here? The speed
at which his hand moves is like that of a savvy writer.
Incredible concentration.
Has he caught fever or something?
Here.
2 pages done.
Now it's yours to check.
Fine, but if you cut corners because of the hurry,
I'm not being lenient.
No typos or misspells so far...
You sure?
The pacing is also orderly.
Can it be...
You "OK" it?
Gimme a sec.
Until I read it to the end.
The closing conclusion is articulate too.
Also, quite engaging on the very first look.
Thank you!
Then, I'll leave you at that.
What about the next topic?
I'll show up the other day!
He put it together in a little more than 3 hours.
Incredible concentration.
Ginya sure is one hit-and-miss fellow.
Let's see, let's see.
Come to think of it,
it felt like he's fighting some huge pressure.
I wonder if something happened.
He, who can concentrate,
is never coming late.
That Ginya fellow is probably struggling
to overcome a demanding work assignment.
He didn't broke any promise this time.
Yuri, you can be dismissed now.
It's time, Yuri.
Okay...
Till later!
My, my.
She seemed much more spirited just this morning.
Come to think of it, Ginya too...
In some imperceptible way,
he had a different look in his eyes.
Can it be because of a difficult match in Slothium?
I'm still getting distracted
by the surrounding noises.
This won't suffice, Ginya!
Concentrate your senses more,
cleanse your mind.
Daiba's defense of King is scheduled for the 5th,
while Otonashi's match is on 15th.
15th?
Then, we'll rush Otonashi Ginya's match
to 3 days from now and hold it as a double match.
We have already notified them
according to current schedule...
Then, do it under the owner's fiat.
Sure, if that is your wish.
For now, I exhausted my options for facilitating it.
Another one from Slothium?
Schedule alteration notice?
In two days,
a double match coupled with King's defense.
Ten days sooner than planned?
If I win this match,
do I get to challenge Daiba?
And this...
I'll be waiting tomorrow too
- Yuri
Yuri...
What in the world could have happened.
In my experience,
there has never been such a drastic change yet.
Above all, the slotter has to adjust
his life circumstances to the schedule.
But how am I to enhance my concentration then?
Mr. Otonashi Ginya?
For Dr. Oumi?
Young doctor is on a business trip
for academic conference.
Oumi is really devoting his life undividedly
to the medical practice.
Especially since that time.
If you excuse yourself losing in such a place
the dream of challenging Daiba Ryo
will forever remain a dream!
That time, in order to make his retirement from Slothium worth it, Oumi bet his everything on this one final battle.
You should, by leaps and bounds,
rush straight up to Daiba Ryo's spot!
But more than words that encouraged and empowered me, he transmitted this pulsing passion straight into my chest.
Ginya,
before finally retiring from Slothium, I tried my utmost
to transmit as much of this message as possible.
There's but one thing I'm asking of you.
Be in a hurry, Ginya.
There's no longer any spare time to stand idly.
It seems both Oumi and Slothium
are trying to rush me, for whatever reason.
I'll be waiting tomorrow too
- Yuri
The number you have dialed is either out of reception zone
or the device is out of power.
I'm sorry, Yuri.
By all means, I really want to investigate it.
It's as though even the Slothium itself
is trying to rush me.
If possible, even by just a day or two,
I myself desire to fight Daiba sooner. However...
Mr. Otonashi does not have a match
planned for today.
Please check with the schedule.
How do I even approach this?
Yuri must be sure be mad.
Broke the promise to come to work together
on the second day.
Of course he did.
Somehow, whatever I start,
I leave it half-done.
Ginya's stupid ass.
Even having realized it now, I still can't change a thing.
I can only invest all my power in one battle in front of me.
For now, no other options.
I signed in as one of the Slothium participants.
Slothium?
That place houses a superb slotter
by the name of Daiba Ryo.
Fighting that fellow is,
for the moment, my dream.
Dreaming about fighting someone...
Yuri?
Ishibashi?
What happened? Just now, you had a face
like you were about to throw yourself over.
As a matter of fact, I...
I pondered over my major decision.
"Do I pick the job,
or do I pick the man?"
This fellow sure is doing fine.
He also does a good job lately.
A man in such a period
is enjoying his prime years for making love.
It's as though he is glowing.
You can be confident in him, Yuri.
I have to make sure
to win today's bout.
Yuri.
Yesterday...
I'm sorry.
Going somewhere?
Sort of.
To Slothium?
Today I'm having an important rank-up match.
With a man by the name of Daiba?
No. But if I win today's match,
next on the line will be Daiba.
I'm told Otonashi Ginya's schedule has been altered.
What about that?
If the queue is sped up by a great extent,
I fear it may disorder his concentration.
You think Otonashi Ginya
is of that capricious type?
I get your point.
The man you saw a prospect in...
Hey, answer me in all earnestness.
Me and Slothium -
which one is more important?
I can't...
Not comparable.
The gauges are like heaven and earth.
I know that much. Yet if you had to choose,
which one would be your answer?
Both are of importance to me!
I care for Yuri more than for anyone else!
Then don't go there!
Please...
I have been thinking of retiring from Slothium.
After that time, right?
Since when you first met Otonashi Ginya.
Yuri, hear me out! In Slothium,
people who recognize me as a full-fledged...
People, who recognize me as an opponent worth fighting,
are waiting for me!
That man was fighting foolhardily,
intending to subjugate the machine itself.
Right...
Like as if he was tilting violently at windmills,
akin to a Don Quixote.
So it was you who turned this Don Quixote
into a full-fledged warrior?
I thought, "That youngster has all it takes to later give me
a once-in-a-lifetime fight worth burning my life in."
Otonashi Ginya is going to meet all my expectations.
No, he will outgrow the most optimistic of them.
I used to play a rogue before, but with his fiery passion,
this man made me grow to recognize myself as his rival,
so I want to answer appropriately
by throwing in all my might!
Soon enough, I'll get to fight him.
Such thoughts
make my soul tremble in excitement.
To bring your life
to a fulfillment?
Right.
An undeniable sensation
that outshines everything.
I don't get it!
I just can't...
Yuri!
Yuri, I just truly wish for you
to understand my feelings!
Please.
Give me your trust and wait a little more!
And now, between the Ultimate King Daiba Ryo
and King challenger Celestial Junzo,
a King defense battle will be held.
In addition, two B-Block members will fight to qualify for challenging the King next - Otonashi Ginya and
Jackie Lee will take part in Generals' match.
Within the double match ruleset,
those matches will receive a simultaneous start.
A double match, huh?
Somehow, we'll have to keep an eye on both.
Game start: 5 seconds.
3, 2, 1. Start!
So much!?
Look! More Gold Time for Otonashi!
Skyrocketing into 5000 is viable now.
Whaaa?
He insane?
This exceptional double match is astonishing.
King is defending his grounds
as the next challenger is being decided.
My heart has been pounding all the way.
The true opponent in my scope, Daiba Ryo,
is you!
Otonashi Ginya, by emerging here,
you changed me as well.
I'm alive...
I have never yet felt so alive in my entire life.
I know, as long as you feel the magma splashing,
confined to the insides of my body, you will win this bout.
He unsheathed it!
God's finger!
He's on Renchan!
Gold Time Rocket
is leaving the atmosphere here, too!
Do it, Otonashi!
Daiba, I'll be arriving at your place in no time.
I have climbed to the summit!
Otonashi Ginya, I have long been waiting for a chance
to burn my life out unreservedly, fighting you!
It's soon enough now.
It seems Otonashi cares not for the enemy in front of him,
focusing on fighting Daiba instead!
The same is true for Daiba.
It's as though those two are in a King's battle already!
Otonashi Ginya,
you have to win and advance.
And if you don't...
Ueno Train Station
Game is concluded.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
Thus, he earns the right
to challenge the King next.
King's Battle - winner - Daiba Ryo.
This makes 32 consecutive successful title defenses.
Daiba, at last,
I can finally stand before you on equal grounds.
Your endeavor is worthy of my salute.
Well, this just means in the next match
I will be fighting you with all my might.
I'm determined to beat you thoroughly
and beyond recognition.
Daiba, I can't help but to return those words to you,
exactly to the letter.
Next departure - 20:18 to Sapporo
In a moment, the limited sleeping car express to Sapporo
departs from track 1 of Hokuto line.
Ginya...
Now I cannot move, not even fall down into your spot
Not one hint of human left, I'm but a walking empty corpse shell
And along with me, a bunch of others born just to get robbed
And it won't be long before they come for me
I'm running helpless through the quicksand
Playing with scabs, trying to peel them off
Here and there, neglected idols are all around me
While painting them all with meaningless colors, I offer a prayer
The longer I go on believing in it, the more it becomes the truth
Until it shatters to pieces small enough to escape the sieve
And I guess they've finally come for me
Now I too walk the road without an end
At last, falling down to your place
Things I desired.
Things I asked for.
Things I gained.
Things I lost.
Things I believed in.
Next time:
The Night Before
My finger will stop the time.