Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Episode 20
The Night Before
Step by step, I get closer.
Daiba, I'm heading for your spot!
Now, to top off the evening...
Cheers!
Hello?
Hey, Ginya, what happened to Yuri?
I'm asking,
what the hell happened to Yuri?
What are you talking about, Master?
You haven't heard a thing
ever since you two split up?
Yuri did something out of line again?
She hasn't shown up yet.
And it's well past her regular hour to start the work.
Hour to start the work?
Well, she may have just overslept today.
If that was the case, I wouldn't have minded.
Still, usually, I'd be able to at least contact her somehow.
Now I can't get through,
not even to her cell phone.
You're just overthinking it.
Anyone is subject to oversleeping and absenteeism.
I would have thought so too,
had our world been prevailed by the likes of you.
Well, anyway, if you learn something,
give me a holler, deal?
So early, so redundant...
Can it be...
Two new items.
Hello. Is this you, brother?
Staying up late at night again? Gosh...
At least, take your meal seriously! I know you hate carrot,
but it's not a reason to leave it on the plate!
Also, you're getting sand for bones
if you don't drink milk every morn!
You always dine someplace else, don't you?
Every once in a while,
cook yourself, even if it's just rice.
You should at least be able to make boiled spinach
or some stir-fried vegetables!
Lest you end up on a vitamin-short diet again.
You should realize it and be inventive on your own!
But if that's all,
I'll call you some other time.
Good bye.
End of message.
Yuri!
Shit!
Not a single time until now
I had this kind of feeling!
I misappreciated having her near me,
as just a natural order of things.
But now she's gone.
For the first time, I realized.
I have been...
towards Yuri...
so inattentive.
Has Yuri...
Really been always feeling this way
while waiting for me?
She was to that extent anxious about me...
And yet, I...
Otonashi Ginya's stupid ass!
At last, you've completed your ascendance
all the way up here.
Otonashi Ginya, you managed to put up a fight,
far exceeding my estimations.
That's the only way
you might have at least a chance to beat me.
Or is that another groundless worry?
After all, you won your way through to here
at a pace dwarfing my boldest estimation.
Even if I'm silent about it,
I'll be in my prime condition, applying finishing touches.
Despite all...
I will be the one winning it!
My determination...
My determination will fend off the illness
for the time being.
I won't give in!
Not until I fight Otonashi Ginya!
And you are...
I believe, it's the first time we meet in person,
Otonashi Ginya.
First, let me congratulate you.
That was one fine match.
My name is Murasame Aoi.
The owner of Slothium.
- And how can I help the owner...
- Today,
I'm here for one special task.
To Mr. Otonashi Ginya
Is this... from Slothium?
It has been decided. The day for the score-settling
showdown between you and Daiba Ryo.
Between me and Daiba...
Please accept it.
This is a written evidence
of the Ultimate King challenging you.
Put up a good fight!
With your everything on the line.
Because if you put up a half-assed fight,
don't expect me
to ever forgive you!
You were chosen for this!
By the man wielding the Finger of God.
By the Ultimate King,
as the ultimate challenger.
A chaser, huh?
Too bad, I have quit chasing already.
It's important to have a good night's sleep.
That exact line,
I wish I could somehow propagate to him too.
Truly...
Truly, a walking corpse, who put his life on the line -
once he accomplishes this,
what the hell is he waiting to happen?
Right, Ginya?
I've been waiting.
As well, as been longing for it with all my heart.
To Mr. Otonashi Ginya
This one battle.
Why though, to me,
Slothium... No, pachislot in general
brings people nothing but misfortunes?
Because of it, dad lost touch with us.
Oumi seems to have gone cold too.
And then, Yuri as well.
Yuri!
What have I...
really gained?
What have I been pursuing?
When I first tried pachislot,
what happened to me?
Stop! You shouldn't let that man in!
I am retiring from Slothium.
Good bye.
Did I really have to lose everything I had?
Wrong.
It didn't just deprive me of things.
After I got engrossed in pachislot...
After I started fighting in Slothium,
I gained something as well!
The chance to meet this motley crew of rivals.
Or this feeling of accomplishment,
untranslatable into words.
Daiba Ryo
has been waiting.
Daiba is looking forward to fighting me!
Therefore, I too
must look forward to it!
Today, my every thought
is directed towards fighting Daiba Ryo.
With more passion than for anything else,
I live for that fight only!
Unabated in looking forward,
we enter the showdown for Slothium's #1.
I will fight with my everything on the line.
And then...
I win!
Nothing is as endless as the everlasting sky
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
For long enough, the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
But even if you get hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
But how I loved you before, I love you now just as much
Hokkaido, Sapporo 20-264
Kamoi Yuri
It says Yuri returned to her hometown.
She won't be back here any time soon.
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
I see.
At any time, I want to keep in touch
Even while asleep, I want to watch over you
Much more than that,
I want to get to know you better
In all honesty,
the more I give it a good ol' thought,
The lyrics come out terribly off-spot
On Saturday, I walk down through the pouring rain,
Shivering and stooping, all alone
But even the chill,
even this bitter chill
In a little more, just a little more,
The stream will wash it all away
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
At last...
Tomorrow.
And then I win!
Useless!
I can't sleep a wink.
It's time.
Thank you for all your trouble.
Ryo!
You must win.
As the one who always wins, Daiba Ryo!
Ryo...
It's me.
Shibata from the engineering department.
I know this is some unfortunate time to call.
Nevermind.
How is it looking?
Did it. Conducting the last minute shakedown.
Then a hotchpotch of other tests, and we're ready in time!
That means...
Yes. We're making it in time
for a Daiba-Otonashi showdown.
Thank you...
Nevermind it.
It's thanks to you that the machine we developed
for a battle of the century will receive an explosive debut.
Like a dream come true.
You still have my gratitude.
It may very well turn out
the perfect machine for this battle.
Now it's completed, Yozakura Seven.
Caught in a sieve too fine-grained for me
Now I cannot move, not even fall down into your spot
Not one hint of human left, I'm but a walking empty corpse shell
And along with me, a bunch of others born just to get robbed
And it won't be long before they come for me
I'm running helpless through the quicksand
Playing with scabs, trying to peel them off
Here and there, neglected idols are all around me
While painting them all with meaningless colors, I offer a prayer
The longer I go on believing in it, the more it becomes the truth
Until it shatters to pieces small enough to escape the sieve
And I guess they've finally come for me
Now I too walk the road without an end
At last, falling down to your place
The supreme.
Challenger.
Completion.
Victory.
Next time:
Yozakura
My finger will stop the time.