Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Episode 7
Suspicion
I'm sorry. We have this training
so early in the morning because of me.
Why, I am doing it for my own sake as well.
Sooner or later,
I'll have to earn my own Knight promotion.
What?
After getting me a knight promotion,
you claim to actually be training for yourself?
That's what I said.
Besides, this is a pleasant walk.
Don't you like it too?
Indeed.
At night...
I'm training even harder than that.
You do it even at night?
Naturally.
The next game is just around the corner.
All I do is training.
It seems you are only satisfied with perfection.
Please enjoy your stay with a fresh coffee
Coffee - 400
Omelet rice - 680
Toast (with salad) - 500
Neapolitan (with salad) - 680
Welcome.
Since when you two are concerned about being fit?
We exercise a lot these days.
Yep. Writing is a tiresome manual labor.
It requires a lot of training.
Master! We'll have two "Mornings." With milk.
With milk? Don't you know my coffee
is supposed to help you wake up?
I managed it myself already.
Besides, with milk it seems more nutritious.
Yep! Milk is required to build a strong body.
Well, well.
It's good to care about you body.
But it’s the brain where the fat tends to accumulate.
Yuri...
Relax, relax. Just kidding.
Still, you two are somehow weird today.
On the other hand, you are always weird.
Yuri...
Just kidding, just kidding. Relax.
What exactly is this?
Photos and materials
related to pachislot development history.
Everything from generation zero
to the latest models is covered.
Yes, here you go.
Even the ones that never made it to the production line are featured.
Are we making a new series?
For now, just start working
on whatever you come up with.
This time we have a lot to sort out,
so you can look at the materials yourself.
The "Bonus" is active.
Understood.
Can I ask you a favor, Ginya?
Sure!
Please check the reader's enquêtes for today, will you?
Sure.
How many thousands are there?
It's 2600 sheets.
I'd prefer those number in coins.
Come
See
Conquer
This place does not go easy on visitors.
That's the point.
It's perfect for our training.
Let's do it!
number of Bigs 000
number of games 000
Today's
Yesterday's
You kiddin...
Today's
Yesterday's
number of Bigs 000
number of games 000
For real?
All the machines here have a factory data reset!
No way to pick from this variety.
What are we talking about?
Aren't we the proud slotters of Slothium?
Congratulations!
Look, even a grandma is able to hit Big here.
If you turn down a place like this,
how can you expect to defeat a Knight?
Touché.
To give this place a chance,
I'll start with 5 test games.
Let us proceed.
You don't have to be afraid of me.
You're on it again?
Start with speaking to a machine?
Yes, cause pachislot is a living being.
I'm not gonna lose!
So am I.
I can hear it clearly.
Your heartbeat.
What, a Bar scissors?
My eyes won't fail me!
Aiming for a Bar!
It was a secured Big!
Let's give it another try.
Right...
Now, a Big!
Secured!
I can hear it.
Your neighbor's delight.
Now, it's your turn to shine!
Yes, that's the case.
You are desperate for a good slotter!
Alright, I will give you the help you desire!
You don't seem to have any diseases.
Now, spread your hands wide
and jump straight into my warmest cuddle!
That's it. You are maturing.
Your body is thriving!
No way!
Of all the prize balls won today,
those guys took 83 in just 8 games!
Easy settings are only for getting used to the machine.
Hard settings are for seasoned players.
Indeed. By the time you get accustomed,
the match is already lost.
I see now.
Umei, memo, memo!
That's interesting!
Another Big!
That sure was a fine game you showed us!
True, so true! Especially with our hands
full of those bonus souvenirs!
I can already see my grandson's happy face!
You don't have to bother thanking.
It was a training after all.
That is indeed so.
Then, Ginya, I'll see you tomorrow.
So we will see those young men tomorrow too?
Naturally.
It's a training after all.
Then, we look forward
to seeing you tomorrow as well!
Naturally.
It's a training after all.
Chief, did you hear what this guy just said?
The customer is king, I guess...
Here. Any progress yet?
This is all just a bit messy.
That's the deal.
The editor-in-chief has been collecting those
in utter chaos it seems.
Wow, amazing! Take a look at this, Ishibashi!
What a peculiar one.
It has 5 reels! But why would they need so much reels?
If you need anything, ask me.
There's another box in the storage room. Good luck!
Understood! So this one is related to the
generation zero stuff. But what about that one?
Thank you,
Fushina.
Did you eventually manage to acknowledge
your hatred's true identity?
I told you not to follow my footsteps.
Hurry up and climb up to me your own way!
Say, editor.
Where did you take this photo?
Is something wrong with it?
- No... But what does it have to do with development...
- Emy! Can you make me a coffee?
...and master?
He certainly looks similar to the Drum Master.
A famous machine developer quits his job
to travallier as a coffee shop master you say?
I'm out for a quick interview,
if you excuse me.
Maybe this smells like an interesting article.
Greetings!
Ah, forgot something?
Better yet!
Yuri, you should see this!
It's a scoop, a scoop!
Should I be interested?
It's a pachislot scoop after all.
It's fine, fine! Just take a look at this photo.
Ain't that spicy?
Let's see...
Is this...
The young Master?
I know, right?
And this - it's a pachislot machine, isn't it?
You don't see photos like this very often.
That's why it's gonna be
the next Spinning Gears' exclusive pachislot front-pager.
Because I found this among the raw materials.
So you're busy as always.
Yes! Keeping myself busy.
Well, anyway, I was just planning to ask you
to enlighten me on that matter,
Mr. Shibaura Futoshi.
Yuri, it's almost gym time.
You're free to go now.
Right.
Then, Ginya, good luck with the interview.
If you excuse me.
Thanks for your work.
Ginya...
We may still have customers.
Come after the closing.
Understood.
In that case, see you tonight.
Well, well, Mr. Shibaura.
Ready to tell me the story?
Before that, let me see it once again
so I can recall properly.
So many memories.
It was 17 years ago I think.
I knew it. It was Master after all.
Somehow I knew it the moment I saw it.
That accounts for your familiarity with the Slothium.
On this photo, we are...
still in the age when you can live
fueled by nothing but dreams and passion.
We attempted on creating a machine
of a brand new kind.
A new kind of machine?
The ideal machine, that is.
In other words, the one on this photo...
I can still remember it clearly even to this day.
That was one truly happy period.
Want some?
I'm driving a bike you know.
I see.
Ginya, you've become quite good at those gimmicks.
Gimmicks... What do you mean?
I was willing to tell you whatever I know myself.
However, I was also hoping
you'd help me by complementing the story.
Complementing?
With that paper plane at least.
This one?
I took those at the same time.
This one doesn't have Master in it.
And this is... Mom?
Then... This one... is me.
And the man next to you
is my associate Shinbashi Kojiro.
A co-developer of that machine.
Shinbashi Kojiro... Shinbashi?
Exactly. That is your father.
Father? Then, Master and my father
have been developing a pachislot machine together?
Exactly.
So Master have been working on it
from the beginning?
No. I helped building it
but only in the final stages.
What a shame.
That's how you see it. But from my perspective,
it's not a good occasion for chit-chatting.
I'm happy anyway since you agreed to talk about it.
Besides, no one told me anything about this guy before.
That paper plane...
Kojiro used to make those for you
every now and then.
Don't you remember at all?
I don't remember.
I do remember how to fold it myself though.
Say, Master.
We had my sister's photos in plenty
ever since she was a toddler.
But not a single one of me
before I'm 3 years old.
So among those,
there's gotta be a lot of pictures of him.
He was a vile guy, I'm told.
My guess is, our piblings despised him so much,
they didn't even want to keep his photos.
Ginya...
Even the mom's photos were not spared.
We only had one.
And a Buddhist temple photo at that.
Because of this man, our mom is now
one sheet away from living in our memory only.
He seems pretty vile a guy.
It is indeed so that Kojiro didn't make it in time
neither for Sakura's childbirth nor for her deathbed.
Didn't make it in time?
Have you just said
he didn't make it in time?
Then, dad was trying to come?
He never showed up — neither when Mai was born
nor when sister Sakura was dying.
He was a vile man.
But have no worries —
he was duly punished for abandoning you two.
He died as well.
Just three months after my sister's demise.
Ginya.
Kojiro can by no means
be considered a vile man.
You can see it yourself on the photo,
where Sakura has your little sister inside her.
Just take a look.
Both Sakura and Kojiro
are smiling sincerely and happily.
Of the dead, say nothing but good,
isn't that so?
Of the dead?
Kojiro you mean?
Yeah. Immediately after the mother's demise.
This can't be true.
After Sakura's death, we've been developing
the machine together for at least a year more.
Then,
my father can still be alive?!
Master!
Please tell me what you know!
My father...
15 years ago we finished developing the machine
and I could finally retire from pachislot.
When I decided to visit him again some time later,
the place was already abandoned.
From then on,
we both had our own careers to pursue.
However, I've never heard a word of him being dead.
I'm certain, out there somewhere,
he is still kicking.
My father is...
still alive.
My real father?
Turns out you didn't die after all?
Even to this day,
you never tried to tell us you're still alive...
Why are you still breathing?
You never even tried to come and see us!
Good morning!
Today seems to be a very nice day!
Let's see what we have
in coming broadcasting schedule.
Morning! I'll have one.
Oumi, are you alone today?
My counterpart deserted me.
Taking a one-day break?
Probably playing pachislot somewhere again, doesn't he?
At this hour, nothing is open yet.
I see.
- Master, have you seen Ginya since...
- Oumi, are you good with milk again?
Definitely!
Just don't make it too light.
Roger.
Father was developing
pachislot machines for some reason.
The very things
I became so keen about in Slothium.
My dad...
No use. It's turned off.
Now that's peculiar,
seeing Ginya go AWOL like that.
He's home, I guess.
Ginya? Ginya! You there?
Last one...
Just because I won yesterday,
doesn't mean I'll prevail today.
Wise words one can use to redeem his defeat.
Umei, memo, memo!
What of it is true?
And what is not?
Today is the day of the game.
Wasting another one worrying will get me nowhere.
Any minute now, the most prominent members
will compete for a Knight title in a promotion game.
It's finally happening. Our most recent members
are about to enter the life-changing fight.
Who do you expect to win?
Otonashi has been riding the waves
quite well lately.
Game starts in 5 seconds...
4...
3... 2... 1...
Start!
Otonashi. Otonashi!
What is it? What's the matter?
Excuse me, Otonashi...
What am I doing, goddammit!
Hey, hey. Is this Otonashi guy okay?
Has he lost his nerve
because this game is different?
If he is alive, can my dad still
be working with pachislot?
What happened?
Is he sick?
What is he doing?
What in the world happened to you?
What is it to me, even if dad is still alive?
Why do I keep getting that feeling?
Have I not got over it a long time ago?
Am I really that vulnerable a man?
Damn!
What's going on?
How did it happen?
Did he become too agitated?
Why, if you were alive... Dad... Shit!
Mom was laughing... Dad too... And me...
Why were everyone laughing
with such happy faces?!
He is a vile man.
Shit... I don't get it.
Where is the truth here? Where is the lie?
Hatred is overflowing your body.
It's over for you.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Memories.
Reflection.
Hesitation.
Prostration.
Debility.
Next time:
Bewilderment.
My finger will
stop the time.