Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Encoding by hSa
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
As a doctor...
As a man...
What should I do about it?
Daiba Ryo,
have you really come to terms with such fate?
Ginya,
are you really the man
Daiba Ryo would put his life on the line for?
Episode 16
Sworn  Friend
Good heavens.
Aside from mayonnaise,
there's nothing but some sprouted onion.
Mayonnaise it is then.
Yes, yes.
Who could it be?
Oumi?
What brings you here at this hour?
Well, nothing special.
How about that?
Wanna join me for a drink?
Most certainly.
I'm sorry and stuff.
I barged in completely uninvited.
No, without a supply of foods,
I'd be in much more trouble.
Well then.
To the meeting.
How times flies...
You still remember?
Our first ever battle.
I remember it, and vividly at that.
Of all places,
I'd never expect Oumi to show up in Slothium.
Oumi?
Now, relax and take it easy.
I am going to inspect your condition thoroughly.
I knew it! You have a volvulus!
How can that be...
At this rate, I'm on the my way to losing!
Yes, that's the perfect way.
'Tis was one good battle.
That naive boy then,
now you are a Knight.
It was but a stroke of luck then.
You really think nothing but luck is involved?
No, what I'm talking about is not the battles.
It's about the people.
About what a luck it has been for me
to meet Daiba and Oumi.
Should I believe
you're thus obliquely confessing your love?
Where the hell did you get that idea?
I guess not.
Jokes aside, though,
Ginya, actually, you're...
No, nevermind...
What was it?
You are even weirder than usual today.
Why do you
keep fighting in Slothium?
Why?
Well, about that...
You do it to fight Daiba Ryo.
But that's why
you also need to hurry the hell up.
You don't have as much time
as you'd probably like to.
Had it not been for my rivalry with Oumi,
there wouldn't have been current me.
I should probably be upfront with you
and say thanks.
Ginya...
Just as I thought,
it's a love confession after all.
How many times do I have to say it's not!?
Ginya's path lies towards the world
far beyond my scope.
You keep on growing
at the most unimaginable rate, Ginya.
So much, it even spurred Daiba
to put his own life on the line.
I daresay he made fighting Ginya
his raison d'être.
They gravitate to each other,
though each one only attracts another in order to fight him.
It's like they pull one another
by reeling in the thread of fate.
Ginya is like a carp trying to climb up a waterfall,
beyond which is the promised land.
But to do that, he has to turn into a dragon.
Only by fueling it with his own life,
Daiba Ryo manages to keep that fire going.
I will hardly ever rise to either of their roles.
Impressive!
He is trouncing him hard.
Otonashi Ginya again?
Ever since he became a Knight,
his games become less and less a hit or miss.
If this keeps up, he'll approach the Generals
before you can say Jack Robinson.
True.
You are indeed less hit-or-miss now.
Still...
It is apparent that you lack any ferocity...
This overwhelming power
that Daiba Ryo endows himself with by burning his life.
Alright...
If this keeps on, Daiba Ryo...
No, if this keeps up, you may not even get to him,
leave alone defeating.
For Daiba Ryo and Ginya to have an ultimate showdown,
Ginya will have to sweep through the General ranks.
And to do that,
he cannot afford getting defeated even once now.
Is Ginya really the receiver of Daiba Ryo's,
the Ultimate King's heritage, of his whole life?
Ginya,
can you really dash all the way up to Daiba Ryo's spot
without even once being stopped in your tracks?
I see.
I have to take the initiative myself.
For me, getting even close to either Ginya
or Daiba Ryo is out of question.
Still,
if I manage to show him
even a fraction of Daiba Ryo's soul,
he'll learn to detach from everything,
he'll learn to fight with everything on the line.
I should be able to teach him that much.
I'm ready.
Thanks.
It's nothing, customer is king.
What is it, Master?
Did something stick to my face?
No, that is not exactly the case.
Still weird.
Well, Master is always this way,
so we'll let it slide.
And you always feel
like blurting some impertinence.
Hurry up finishing.
Guess I should.
Oumi?
Ahoy, Oumi.
Been a little while.
And what was it that made you pull
such intimidating a face?
True.
Ginya, I need to engage
in a conversation with you.
What's with the formal demeanor?
Uhm,
Oumi?
Oumi...
It's the first time I'm seeing Oumi
with that kind of expression.
Ginya,
I ask you to fight me.
What do you answer?
What are you talking about?
That fighting thing or that demand for answer...
Ginya!
I heard you.
I accept.
Tonight, at 12PM.
This is the place.
Then...
Hey, Ginya.
What in the world has gotten into Oumi?
I wonder...
I wonder if he ate something weird again.
Something weird?
Like a lunch box far behind expiry date.
I doubt it...
Suit yourself.
It's all as Yuri says.
What in the damn is he thinking?
Alright.
Kept you waiting?
No.
A dedicated parlor just for us, huh?
A little favor from an old acquaintance.
Just for today, it's all ours.
Somehow, it changes the mood completely.
Now, let's get started.
I have already chosen the machines.
We'll have even conditions.
Ginya,
chances are, this would make
a concluding battle between me and you.
Tonight I'm throwing my everything at you.
Therefore, Ginya,
I want you to fight at earnest too.
Start.
Forgive me. Even if you'll think of me as a brute,
I intend to push you to the edge.
That's it!
What? Though we're just getting started,
you nailed jackpot already?
Oumi is not being his usual self.
He dropped any foreplay, proceeding straight to palpation.
Also, his threat earlier
and this self-exhausting manner of pressing the buttons.
Yes, it's almost like...
he is fighting the God of Death himself!
I see. But you're not in perfect health yet.
I'm sorry.
All right...
That's a good child.
Thank you.
Riichi Eyes? Again?
Whatever! I can do it too!
Alright, Riichi Eyes!
There! Nailed it!
Yes... That's the way, Ginya.
Oumi?
Oumi!
Don't come closer!
We're amidst the fight.
Not some frivolous frolic.
Remember what I said?
Because I'm throwing my everything at you,
fight me at earnest!
What is this pressure...
What in the world has gotten into Oumi?
Resume the play,
Ginya.
This kind of pressure.
Where have I...
That's right!
Daiba Ryo...
It's the same as when I fought Daiba!
There's one thing I need to pass to you.
I am absolutely obliged to pass this to you.
You will be growing all the stronger.
The fight you found yourself in
is a challenge to the dream!
The fight with your everything on the line!
If you allow yourself to even think of losing to me now,
a dream of challenging Daiba Ryo will remain a dream.
Believe!
You are still to become much stronger!
My everything... on the line...
Exactly.
This kind of magnificent fight
is not something one can devise on the whim.
Exactly.
Everything I have, I will throw it at Oumi.
That's what Ginya ought to do.
That's what Daiba Ryo's rival ought to do!
Thank you, Ginya.
No, it was me
who learned the most from this.
Really?
Then I'm free of any afterthoughts and regrets.
I will file in the resignation from Slothium.
But why...
Maybe when you rise to a Knight...
No, to a General!
No need to.
It's settled already.
Oumi...
Ginya,
I will say it just once again.
Thank you.
Don't you lose, Ginya.
Dash through every obstacle
straight up to Daiba Ryo's spot.
For the moment,
he is still second in my list of targets.
Still, huh?
That sounds so much like you.
Hurry up, Ginya.
There is no longer any time to loiter.
I hope I conveyed to you all that I intended to.
Well, one way or another, do your best from now on.
In my stead too.
Okay.
Please take it seriously, Ginya.
The time left
is considerably less than what you'd like to have.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
To come.
To not come.
Phone.
Promise.
Rain.
Next time:
Person on my Mind
My finger will stop the time.