Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Bye-bye!
One is strikingly cheeky,
a wannabe grown-up kid.
One is striking you with his eyes,
a devoted slotter father.
Those are both so difficult to approach.
As though they are one.
Father and son, huh?
Episode 10
Father and Son
Prediction guide
Weekly horse racing bets
Weekly boxing
Data room
Kasamatsu Ryu's title match
Tragic  accident
Immediately before the match!! Fracture in the right leg
Tragic accident
Excuse me? How did a pachislot magazine reporter
end up investigating boxing?
Well... Different things have intertwined.
Whatever.
There was a lot of ridicule
about that title match of Mr. Kasamatsu, born 1973.
Kasamatsu Ryu - the Invincible!
By that time, Mr. Kasamatsu was popular for his intention of becoming world-famous.
Kasamatsu - King of the Rookie!
By that time, I was still fighting in the 4-round league.
I remember those days clear as a day.
I say, it happened
4 days before his title match, didn't it?
A car accident.
Since his debut, Kasamatsu Ryu
kept winning with a thrust of a steamroller,
eventually becoming East Japan's rookie star,
entering the rankings.
He was determined to maintain that momentum
to conquer the Japan's title.
However, during a routine roadwork,
he got a ligament rupture in the car accident.
Kasamatsu Ryu's tragic accident
Title Match - Hopeless!
Kasamatsu Ryu - Unrecoverable!?
His boxing career seemed by all means over.
Kasamatsu Ryu's retirement for rehabilitation.
Kasamatsu Ryu's comeback
From despair, he is reborn
From the state which seemed hopeless to any,
he ascended again, in spite of all ridicules.
Kasamatsu seemed more fearless than ever
after those two years,
making this time the most productive in his career.
It's for my son.
So, the main factor
in Mr. Kasamatsu's miraculous comeback is...
Well, it is Akira.
The prime reason for me to keep winning...
In that case, your next title match...
Yes. I'm winning it. Certainly.
For my son Akira, that is.
Dad... The best in Japan.
That's enough.
You move well, Ryu.
I can see all of his punches.
And my reflexes are perfect, boss.
You came a long way. Don't you think
it's about time you finally become a champion? Hit!
Okay!
What is it...
What is going on here?
Idiot, start moving!
Use your goddamn legs!
He is coming!
Look out!
What... is going on?
My leg... won't move an inch!
Old wound strikes again!
Honey?
Just a dream...
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
You wake up screaming almost every night now.
I'm sorry.
But tomorrow I'll put an end to it.
I will win.
To quit this circle of self-destruction.
For you. And also
for that little one.
I'll go get some fresh air while running.
Honey...
Bell... Bell... Bell...
Replay... Replay... Replay!
I can see you.
I will be alright.
Watermelon is next.
I can see you.
I see your every move.
Which punch will this guy try next?
I will win!
Ryu! It's only round two!
Move it! Move, goddamnit!
I must... I must... defeat you!
I can see.
And I will...
I will...
Win this!
You're gonna lose!
Dad!!!
Yo, Akira.
Ginya?
You eat here today as well?
I wonder if the rest of the food here is good as well.
Welcome!
I'll have special fried oysters with a big rice.
Okay, okay.
One of special oysters!
Coming!
Akira is hanging out here every day?
He is in our custody here.
While that riffraff is having his fun in pachislot.
I've heard about it.
Mr. Kasamatsu was once a mighty fellow, didn't he?
In the old days, yes.
But it took him one title match lost
to run out of steam completely.
He neglected the trainings completely -
pachislot, pachislot!
His wife also grew cold on him
and left the family.
So Akira is forced
to spend his lonely days like this.
Ryu used to constantly claim to do it all for Akira,
but the truth is -
has he really done something good for Akira?
But he did not retire yet, didn't he?
He is still boxing to this day,
trying his best, I thought.
Who knows.
Even if he does, it's no better than quitting.
I, for once, have not seen Ryu
training a single time lately.
Have you not?
It's a shame, he was really gifted.
I'd never act this was in his shoes.
Nevertheless.
A guy like him is not supposed
to end his path in this miserable way.
Chef...
Ryu, for how many years, exactly,
have you been a boxer?
Nine years.
I see. And how old were you
when you started?
Have we not discussed this
enough times, boss?
I know I have been advised to retire.
If I go on barking in vain like that,
I'll have no future aside from being an underdog anyway.
Are you... Really thinking of it this way?
Because that's how it is!
Ever since I lost that title match.
You have never been subjected to unfair matchmaking.
And you have never been seen as an underdog's either!
All of this -
merely a product of your low spirits.
What I'm trying to say is,
I understand your feelings perfectly.
Very well,
point out what's wrong with me then.
If you can't tell me more than that,
I'll have my leave.
All in all, how many comebacks have you already had?
If you excuse me.
Do you ever feel lonely?
It's because your father is a boxer, isn't it?
This father of yours... you love him?
You love your current father,
or your old days' father?
All the same.
They are both the same person.
Dad will be dad.
Say, Akira.
Akira, do you know where does the wind come from?
From everywhere.
However, it's the depths of my heart
where it starts.
Say, Akira,
why don't I give you a piggyback ride.
What are you doing?
Ginya, stop, you hear me?!
It’s so embarrassing!
It's fine, fine.
Put me down I say!
- Quit fidgeting!
- Embarrassing!
You okay?
It hurts...
No, that took too heavy a toll on my tallness.
You got what you had coming!
Only thanks to someone's dumb fidgeting!
A father, huh?
All in all, how many comebacks have you already had?
Why did he have to lie to me?
You're here after all.
You again...
I was looking for you.
A pro boxer, Mr. Kasamatsu Ryu.
What is it again?
Once more,
I want to challenge you to a game.
Not happening. In contrary to you,
I play pachislot for fun, not for fight.
For fun?
You're not a child
to be playing it for fun, aren't you?
What?
Leaving things half-complete
is only excusable for children.
As well as using pachislot
to escape the responsibility for giving up boxing.
Asshole, what do you want?
If you want to prove me wrong,
accept my challenge, Kasamatsu Ryu!
And if you lose, you quit pachislot forever!
The hell...?
Dad.
Akira?
So, what do you say?
Let us hear your answer,
Mr. Kasamatsu.
You'll have it.
I agreed to bother to come,
but I can't help wondering where to.
As soon as Akira saw this place,
he figured it'd be the best possible ring for us.
Ryu = Dragon
The first one to score three Bigs, wins.
Whoever loses, never plays pachislot again.
Is that fine with you?
Then, let us get started.
Akira.
Ready...
Start!
Dad...
Just as I thought.
That speed and nimbleness of eyes.
Seeing such a slotter outside Slothium
is not something you do on a day by day basis.
But that also means
I have no excuse to lose to him, whatsoever!
What's the matter?
Where did all that recent cockiness go?
What?
It's just as I said.
We're not playing games here.
Dad...
Dad, win!
One more left.
Whoever hits Big first, wins.
Okay...
I got it!
The first one to stop a reel, wins.
That's it.
I've had enough of his trickery.
Damn. It's fast.
I will win and shut that brat up!
I'll get this one.
What?!
Missed?
Is this for real?
Why in the world does goddess of victory
hate my whole existence this much?
Please, don't forget what you promised us.
Do not lose!
Dad, do not lose now!
I absolutely cannot see dad
losing again!
Akira...
You just...
Akira.
We don't have to continue.
The answer is already apparent.
Isn't it, Mr. Kasamatsu?
Well then.
Dad...
You will have to forgive me, Akira.
Dad!
For some time, you'll have to do without treats.
Hope you're okay with that.
For you and me,
some dark times may be coming soon.
Therefore...
It's completely fine!
I won't complain! Not once...
But I want just one thing...
For you to give me a promise.
A promise?
Just once more. Once more, I want you
to step into the ring and piggyback me.
I want you to give me a piggyback!
Fine. I heard you. I'll do it.
I'll do it!
Can you promise me?
Yeah. Naturally!
Give me a promise!
I promise!
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
Death of a friend.
Hatred.
Voice of a friend.
Objective.
My bewilderment.
Next time:
Days Gone.
My finger will
stop the time.