Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
Thank you.
I'll make sure to treasure it.
Hey, the sea breeze is drying, isn't it?
Here's to the beginning of our new life.
I'm sorry, but it's still too rash
to merge our two lives into one.
Ryo...
Turn the yacht around.
What are you saying?
Knight's title requires me
to always arrive on time now.
Ryo!
Look at me!
Me, who you used to love with your whole existence!
Between me, who used to console and bolster you,
and pachislot... which one is more important?
Answer me.
Answer me, Ryo!
Because your own parents abandoned you,
you've grown callous to others' affection!
But even so, my love for you is genuine!
Daiba Ryo, if there's still
any human-loving heart left in you,
you owe me an answer!
You are obliged to answer!
You can't rely on me
to act forever as your spiritual father.
Spiritual father?
You are disgusted with your father
having god-knows-how-many mistresses.
Yet you always end up trying to bind people
to yourself with father's money.
It's about time you start walking
your own path with your own legs.
I will do so too.
To the place where I'm alive -
Slothium.
Episode 23
Time
Five years ago,
I succeeded my grandfather,
becoming the owner of Slothium.
I wanted to see with my own eyes as you wander alone
through the wasteland to meet your fate.
However,
I figured it out right away -
we are two disbelievers in the eternal love,
cut from the same cloth.
And now, I'm wandering
through that same wasteland myself.
Ryo...
What lies ahead of this place...
What lies ahead of my life...
For the sake of future...
Look, neither can break away from the other.
It is an even battle again.
Superb!
What am I even doing? At last... At last, I was given
a chance to put into practice my resolve to fight Daiba.
Aligned? However, even now,
I still can't see a thing beyond this line.
Pachislot machine, Yozakura Seven, Slothium,
I won't spare my life to get the answer!
To pull it out of you, even by force!
Hey, the Ultimate King
can even press with his eyes shut?
He really does!
But how can that be...
Can't see. Even when I combust my life
to 100% of its capacity, what lies beyond that line...
Why so?
This manner of pressing
is different from Daiba's usual.
What happened there, Ginya?
Must defeat... Must defeat Daiba!
For now, I have no other means
for answering Daiba, but to win.
What kind of thoughts is Daiba having,
pressing the buttons now?
Daiba doesn't look my way anymore.
I'll make you turn your face to me
once again, Daiba Ryo!
What's going on...
Ryo, who desired so much to fight Otonashi
doesn't even look his way now.
Doesn't ever turn to him.
It feels like Ryo is going to some place I don't know,
to some place away, out of hand's reach.
Otonashi!
After this one, start building a Big!
Ryo...
Pull Ryo back to reality,
Otonashi!
Owner, get yourself together!
What happened?
I wanted to see it - Ryo driven to the life's edge.
But now... Now...
Ever since I first met Ryo,
I should've gone upfront about it. Why did I...
Why did I ever greenlight such a match?
Owner...
Don't get closer... Please...
Don't look at me!
Please don't run away, Owner.
No, Aoi.
The duty is yours to witness, until the conclusion,
the fight between these two men!
It's no use covering your eyes.
The clatter of their fight would still reach your ears.
Should you cover your ears,
you would still smell the fragrance of their fight!
Should you try to repulse it with your whole body,
your heart would still feel what's going on.
Both you and me came to this fight
perfectly aware of it.
What I want to see, what I want to learn,
where I want to go...
After making it this far,
why do I suddenly feel lost?
As the Ultimate King,
I had to defeat numerous rivals along the way.
What am I looking for
in this final battle of my life?
We'll see.
What... What is this light now?
Ryo!
What happened, Ryo?
Otonashi Ginya, you were chosen
by the Ultimate King himself!
Align the Big now! Please!
It should be easy for you!
I just want Daiba...
I want Daiba to return to reality!
Ginya understands that too, Owner.
You're not the only one in agony now.
That's not what I mean!
Haven't you noticed?
Ryo is fighting
in a whole another world, alone.
The place that he yearned for
is a completely different battlefield!
Hey, don't you notice
something bizarre in Daiba's appearance?
What is it?
He is laughing?
Ginya, you're the only one
who can pull Daiba back to our world.
I see it...
Alright, Big!
Nailed!
Sakura?
Right now, I heard it clearly.
The sound of your burning life.
The sound of burning life?
A warm, gentle and embracing motion.
Just like the depths of the sea,
it's quiet and docile.
And yet, immense in strength.
Unbinding.
Originating from the Earth's womb,
just like magma.
A potent motion.
Now I heard it too.
This sound that a life makes
came clearly to me too!
This is the sound of Daiba's life burning!
Thank you.
That's a relief.
Daiba...
Some things are once-in-a-lifetime.
Like our meeting.
No, everything up to this point.
Time will always be the same.
Time is continuous,
forming an endless flow of time.
Occasionally, times intersect,
creating history.
By shredding the past,
we create the future.
This fight of ours
also exists on the intersection of times.
Still, though it saddens me,
this intersection is only transient.
Because time is not something you can stop.
In that case...
In that case, I must exceed my limits to stop it.
By burning my everything
inside this one moment, my...
My finger will stop the time.
Daiba Ryo, your capacities are well and truly
beyond any ordinary man's.
As well as those in your possession, Ginya.
The sound of burning lives of those two
reaches me even down here!
It heats me thoroughly, to the very core!
You once told me this,
In a country, spared by wars and revolution,
what is this place where men
can fight with their lives on the line?
In all my time,
I never looked at the opponent I'm fighting with.
No, rather, even to this day,
I just never cared enough to go out of my way.
However!
What a willpower, even in his condition!
Ginya, I had to realize it with my own heart.
It's good, just being able to fight you like that...
No, I'm happier by just thinking
how we got to experience the same moment together.
The time...
One is powerless to stop the time.
But this one moment I'm living through
together with Daiba...
Once in a lifetime... The answers
to everything I have ever lived for, are here.
Once in a lifetime...
What me and Daiba have once met for
is this one fight!
It's why I met Oumi,
why I met Teresa...
It's why I had met, but also parted
with all those people.
Everything was just for this day alone!
That's right, Otonashi.
Everything I have or ever had...
No, I'm throwing at you
even more than that! So you, too...
I'm savouring it, Daiba.
This one moment!
From approximately 8000 winning combinations...
I'm aiming for one and only,
just for this moment's sake!
The reason the two of us had met...
Was for this one,
once-in-a-lifetime battle!
Look! His reels are exactly like Otonashi's!
Can it be...
They are aiming for the same pattern after all!
This time, it's Daiba who is chasing Otonashi.
Can you even believe that?
Astonishing.
This can't be a coincidence.
Both are aiming for the same titles!
Remaining time: 1 hour 30 minutes.
Daiba!
Is that how much strength he needs
to endure the pain to fight me?
Worries aside, keep going forward, Otonashi!
I know I should, Daiba.
That's better.
Remaining time: 30 minutes.
Update on the scores:
King Daiba Ryo - 45 678 coins.
Fingers too...
The thumb is going numb already.
But considering what Daiba is going through,
this is bullshit!
Challenger Otonashi Ginya - 43 569 coins.
What's the matter?
I can't see your hand moving.
The only thing I stop today is time.
And I'm not yet finished!
Exactly.
Not quite yet!
Now, secured it!
Remaining time: 1 minute.
Update on the scores:
King Daiba Ryo - 51 366 coins.
Challenger Otonashi Ginya - 51,381 coins.
With a lead of only 15,
Otonashi is going to win!
It's not about winning or losing anymore.
Whichever way this battle ends!
This life...
My life...
Accept it,
my companion,
my rival!
Remaining time: 10 seconds.
Saved by the bell of a time limit, Ginya.
Update on the scores in a recent game:
Challenger Otonashi Ginya - 51 396 coins.
King Daiba Ryo - 51 381 coins.
Winner - Otonashi Ginya.
This marks the beginning of Otonashi Ginya's reign
as the 52nd King.
This was close...
Nail a Big at such a climactic moment...
Daiba, you are, well and truly,
the man wielding the Finger of God, after all.
I'm still ages away from surpassing you...
The time has...
Ryo... Wait, Ryo!
Don't go away! Stay by my side like this
a little longer! Please!
Don't go away all by yourself, Ryo!
Look at me!
Aoi, I'm grateful for keeping up
with all my selfish antics for so long.
Now it's my turn to be selfish.
You're past the Slothium chapter.
But you don't have to turn away from me.
Let's keep going together, from now on, too!
All right.
But right now, I want to savor
those little last moments of my supreme bliss, alone.
That would be my one final selfish antic.
Please call for my car.
The time has...
"The time has..."
What in the world did Daiba
mean to say by this?
Daiba, while I was fighting you then, certainly,
the time has stopped.
Ginya...
Daiba is...
What's the matter?
What's the matter, Ginya?
Daiba is...
Daiba, since then,
many moments have passed.
I have made history many times.
Please enjoy your freshly-ground coffee with us
Murasame Building Demolition Plans
Moment:
"The Legend of Shooting Star -
The Man Who Bent the Time With God's Finger"
Otonashi Ginya
Thank you for enduring this show with me!
This was a bumpy ride, but I regret nothing
See you in parlor, pachislot cowboy
Yours truly, Perevodildo