Gin
The Pachislot Aristocrat
—
A study in srt by Perevodildo
Nani mo nai tadatada tsudzuku sora
Nothing is endless as the everlasting sky
Nani hitotsu te ni todokanai yōna
Nothing out there that is out of my reach
Ano hi no biru no sukima kara mieta gaitō ni
Tonight's streetlights in between buildings sites
Are too bright on me
Watashi ga nanimonona no ka tte
For so long I
Didn't know who I am
Utau koto wa nanina no katte
What songs I sing
And what songs I sang
Ano hito ha ai o kuretakatte shiritaku mo nai
For long enough that the one offering love
Doesn't want to know me now
Demo itamunara kono itaminara
But even if you're getting hurt,
Even if it hurts a lot
Mōsukoshi mōsukoshi itai gurai ga ī
In a little more, just a little more
This pain will turn to joy
Kirainara kirai to ima kotoba ni shite
Say you hate me, say all you want
Your words don't frighten me a bit
Mienai ashita o koko de owara sete
Cause if you do, your tomorrow,
Unseen before, will die for good
Demo an'nani aishita kon'nani aishiteru
But how I loved you before,
I love you now just as much
Sono shiawase no hitotsude ī oboete ite
And how sincerely happy we were in old days
I will never forget
The editor rejected everything again...
"Those manuscripts are poor even as a fiction" huh?
Until now, I was hoping to see your style improving,
but you don't seem to even try.
Yes, Otonashi.
Editor?
Then, with this interview...
You give me another chance?
Can you assure me this one
won't become another manuscript I reject?
At this rate, you'll be fired soon.
Isn't editor being too harsh on Ginya today?
With his attitude, this is to be expected.
The name is Oumi Shunichi. Be aware,
the person bearing this name is unique in a way...
Oumi Main Hospital
He postulates pachislot machines alive?
Alive, you say?
Episode 3
Palpation
Young Doctor! Young Doctor,
would you like to dine with me?
He has already promised me!
Why don't we go driving instead?
Come on...
Young Doctor, we still should drink together...
Doctor! You are so unreliable...
Fine, fine. One at a time.
What's with this guy?
Now, now. We should get back to work.
Come on. On our ways.
Otonashi, the chief physician is ready to see you.
Please wait at his office.
I wonder if he is a spoiled person...
Please wait for him on that sofa.
A chief physician a pachislot player?
Have we met?
I arranged an interview with you.
Turning Gears' reporter Otonashi.
"Turning Gears?"
Frankly speaking, never heard of such a magazine.
It's still a small magazine, you know...
No, no, no problem. If my next dissertation
is of your interest, it's my pleasure to tell.
Your magazine is bound to grow big this way.
Dissertation...
Have you already composed its plan?
Have you read the dissertation summary
prior to the interview?
Yes. I happen to see some of your ideas
as extremely unique.
All accepted by public nevertheless.
I see... Should this mean such ideas
are recognized warmly in medical society too?
What do you mean?
What do I mean... You got me here.
This, of course! This one.
Massage with fingers?
Massage... Is not precisely the thing...
Somehow it feels like
we're not on the same wavelength.
I'm going in. Apologies. I made you wait.
Weren't you looking for me, Otonashi?
Shunichi?
Old man, you're here?
Pachislot!? Shunichi! Is this how you waste your time
when not courting nurses!?
I'm not over yet!
Hey! Shunichi!
I was hoping he'd be away past noon.
I was just hoping to interview you,
neither is happening.
Then, let's do it in my mansion.
It's just two or three minutes away.
Young Doctor!
If my AWOL is discovered, we'd have trouble.
Let's hurry.
However, you seem to be terribly popular here.
This popularity is just a consequence
of being heir to the hospital. Bothersome at best.
Only women like my mother appeal to me.
Anyway, grandpa is still lively.
Meaning that I'm not getting any peace soon.
Though I'd like to be mistaken on the latter.
For how long have you been playing pachislot?
It's eight years already.
Then, it was when you were 13?
Doesn't matter.
Hurry up inside.
Right... Thanks for the hospitality.
Can we finally begin the interview?
No, before that,
I want to show you this room.
Now, now.
Come, come. Here.
Amazing! Such an extensive collection
is not to be seen every day!
This is nothing.
It still lacks a lot of cool machines.
What are you planning to do with it?
I'm checking her current condition.
She's a child, particularly capricious.
A child?
They are children, living beings.
When playing, one should consider their condition.
Take their mood into account.
So, pachislot are alive. Is that it?
You are not someone's pet robot, aren't you?
I, for once, can agree with one thing - the better you treat your surroundings, the better it performs...
Right. The same goes for pachislot.
The way you touch the buttons defines the outcome.
I see now...
I think she's in a good mood now.
You should try and hear it too.
Can you hear it already?
This kid's mood.
What do you mean?
Nothing but reels spinning motor reaches my ear.
Well, too bad for you.
Only by throwing away the bias
of soulless pachislot machines, you can hear their pulse.
This is the sole way to understand a child's mood.
Hence, the only way to ensure hitting Big.
Care to prove your certainty
by hitting Big right now?
Just look closely.
Are you serious?
Can't this machine be simply out of service?
Not. Not this one.
Something is perturbating her.
Can't we just never mind it
and begin the interview?
Now, girl.
I expect a fine combo from you.
Oumi!
I got it!
You are the reason.
This girl is too shy to let me win in front of you.
Yes, yes! This was the case all along!
He sure likes his bets.
I hope you have made up with Ginya
and hold no grudges.
What do you mean?
I'm a little worried
he did not show up neither yesterday nor today.
Pachislot, isn't it?
It's more important to him than keeping a promise to me.
For the sake of writing the manuscript
that won't be rejected that is.
If he is preoccupied with a Pachislot article,
could he unconsciously get fully engaged again?
In that case, it should be no less than a column.
If so, I can understand.
The last matter I'd like to know.
To you, Oumi, what does pachislot stand for?
Personally to me, pachislot
is a living being.
It can be your gentle lover
or a shrewd loyal friend.
Or, of course, a capricious child.
It manifests in the most diverse forms.
Once you get to know them better, the machines repay your tender attitude with a big bonus.
After that, nothing else excites you more.
Think this makes for an answer?
Yes. An exhaustive one.
Thanks a lot for your time.
You should stay a little longer.
This time I'll surely hit my bonus.
No, really gotta leave.
It's lunchtime already.
Wanna get some sushi?
I haven't dined yet too.
No, I'm used to dining in a specific place, you see...
Really? Because of good cooking?
I guess, yes...
Then, I will also give this place a try.
You sure it's fine?
Oumi Main Hospital
- I won't, I won't! No syringes, never!
- Hiroshi, don't run!
Wait just for a moment.
Wow, stopped crying already...
Pretty impressive.
Mama! The Young Doctor said they will do it
the special, totally painless way!
My, isn't that relieving?
Thank you so much!
Bye-bye!
See you!
What exactly is this special way?
Medical confidentiality.
I cannot tell you this much.
We're off! Please buckle your seatbelts.
Such a natural and ingenious form.
An elegant color scheme! She is beautiful in every way.
I hope someday someone
would praise my coffee this way.
Do you mind if I check her from the inside?
If it's your heart set, sure.
Not only appearance, but insides are beautiful as well.
This is, without a doubt, a perfect machine.
Hey-hey, you shouldn't jump to such conclusions.
This was no flattery,
but my sincere opinion!
Oumi, I hope you won't solicit her
for your collection?
It's true I liked her so much
I would've moved heaven and earth to obtain her.
She is among a few astonishing machines
that one sees once in a lifetime.
But I see these children
are happy to remain in a place like this.
These children?
To remain in a place like this?
They are appreciated here by master and the playing
pachislot guests. It makes them shine even brighter.
I just have no right
to deprive them of such happiness.
I never regretted going here with you today.
Not only that I met a breathtaking machine,
I also had a delicious curry
and a fine coffee after.
Don't forget riding my bike for free.
Oumi, modesty is certainly not your forte.
People call such things a friendship.
You should try it too.
Can't argue with that.
I'm back!
How's work, Yuri?
You came after all.
Beautiful...
Lady, let me lend you a hand!
There's no...
Oumi, what's got into you?
Now, now. You're exhausted from work.
Please rest here.
Incredible. Those proportions! Not a single machine
can even get close to being so ideal. Perfect forms!
Once I saw these eyes' glow,
I knew right away this is a Premium Riichi!
What is he talking about?
Did I just hear the angel's whisper? This divine sound made my love burn with renewed vigor!
Who is this guy, seriously?
Oumi Shunichi...
A future heir to the Oumi Main Hospital.
So it entails... what?
Why is he grabbing my hands talking nonsense?
What an incredible purity...
This is the first time I meet a woman like you.
You should know my feelings are sincere!
Right now, my flag waves towards you!
A hanged flag = increased chance of good combinations
I understand!
I got you, now please let me go!
Really... If you hang out with freaks,
be so kind as to put them away from us!
Spare me the details
of who has the flag hard for whom!
Your bag! Yuri... Yuri!
What's the matter with you?
Never have I saw her so annoyed...
Is she master's daughter?
Don't talk nonsense! They're not even a bit alike.
Instead, would you care to explain what happened?
I just... thought...
How do I explain it?
Oumi, why don't we call it a day
and head home?
Leaving already?
Right, we're leaving!
Leaving?
We are leaving!
Master, put it on my tab!
As usual.
Be sure to come again.
Are they gone yet?
I wonder what this guy was thinking of.
Surely, he had in mind
some odd combination with you.
Here it is! Slothium's invitation!
Member's tournament, the third round's
date and time have been determined. Friday this time?
I wonder what opponent will I face this time?
Bienvenue!
Good day to you, Yuri!
Having a morning set?
Flag, hanged at morning
Yeah. Whichever that means.
Yuri, for how long are you going to play resentful?
I'm not in any way resentful, can't you see?
I'm very much content.
Let's get over it!
You'll see, next time I'm keeping my promise!
You're too light-headed for such promises.
But whatever. This time I'll believe.
Thank you!
Let's see... The title is...
Bienvenue...
Good morning... I came with a present for you,
my sweet honey.
You again?
Oumi?
Yuri, marry me!
You're too hasty with such decisions!
You know each other for less than a day may I remind!
True love cares not for the time passed!
Oumi... I don't claim to be an expert,
but shouldn't a doctor conduct a thorough examination
prior to cutting the patient's abdominal with a scalpel?
It's correct!
The same goes for our situation.
Before proposing, a few important steps are required.
Yuri still knows nothing about you, not a single trait!
I understood.
Yuri, please forget that I ever proposed to you.
Sure...
Instead, until Yuri wants it herself,
I'll look forward to it!
Say, how about we drink together? I know a fine place.
We'll enjoy a night city scenery with wine.
But... if it's just the two of us...
Then, Lil' Gin will make our third.
Lil' Gin, huh? I'm getting a -chan suffix on the second day.
What kind of man do you think you are?
If there are three of us, I might agree...
Really? Lil' Gin! My fair Ginya, Mister Ginya!
Will you be the third one drinking with me and Yuri?
I'd love to, but when?
I will only be free on Friday.
Friday?
How unfortunate... I have an important training operation appointed on Friday.
And I have... the manuscript deadline.
Well then,
I guess no one's going anywhere.
Damn it...
The initial score is 200 points.
The first player to score 2000 points, wins.
Players take seats in front of machines of their choice.
Oumi!
Ginya!
At least, I can show you today.
Machines really can talk to you if you listen well.
Yeah, sure!
Three minutes left.
There will be only one winner.
I look forward to ascertaining it.
No way I'm losing!
Starting in 5 seconds. 4... 3... 2... 1... Start!
Come on, grant me luck. I will examine your condition
thoroughly. I feel that you wanna grant me luck.
What's with this guy?
A weirdo one.
- What is his strategy?
- That guy is talking to his machine!
- He thinks it can hear him?
- Did you bet on him?
Bars again...
Not what I needed!
What's the matter?
Haven't you caught a cold?
If you get sick, I'm the man of an hour.
I'm the one with whom you can share everything. Now...
Now, remain still.
Let me finally hear your pulse...
No swelling.
The throat seems fine...
Hey, what the hell do you keep murmuring there?
I can't get my concentration!
It's alright.
You definitely don't have a cold.
By the way, isn't he a doctor?
Meaning he is doing the palpation there?
Touching the machines
is not prohibited, so why not.
You have the point.
Otonashi, today you look a whole different person
compared to the day you played with me.
However, there is still one fatal flaw in your play.
Right... What if...
You really have volvulus!
In that case...
What happened to him?
He'll regret spending coins recklessly!
Looks like the doctor is bound for home soon.
Unless he aims to be
the premiere loser, he oughta stop.
That's for sure.
Even red-only-seeking Otonashi has more chances.
Your game looks mediocre.
It's still too filthy.
You are such a good child...
Just marvelous!
Hey, look!
The doctor suddenly hit Big!
For real!
It's not over yet.
You shouldn't be selfish playing alone all the time.
Let us enjoy the game together.
Actually, the bonus strategy is in use again.
Do you think it might just work?
Otonashi's score rises slower than last time.
While the doctor guy scoring rapidly with a Renchan of three Bigs!
This one is mine too!
Can you outrun him with time?
This is growing interesting.
Right, right. It's alright now.
Nothing will hurt anymore.
How's that? I had to bust my ass this whole time
to somehow score these 1970.
Still, Oumi has almost bonus-caught-up with me.
Am I gonna lose?
Small Factor is okay...
I want a Small Factor!
Regular bonus!
Right. You're in great shape.
Hey, is this...
We may see the tables turned at the last minute!
If I don't score another 15, I'm done for!
The doctor's Regular bonus is over.
Who will hit the Small Factor first?
Okay, it's scissors now!
I got a little carried away with you...
Game is concluded. Otonashi Ginya is the winner of the game.
At least, I made sure you are perfectly well.
Oumi, pachislot is a living being.
I saw it myself just now.
Turns out you are a Slothium member as well.
Today's game was a great pleasure.
Next time I won't lose.
See you again, Rival.
Oumi...
Got it!
Looks like you got lucky this time.
The heavy rain is over now,
Shadows have ceased to roam,
Even summer itself has come to an end
Ame wa yande ita kage to aruide ita natsu ga owatte ita
My youth goes on, pushing me in my back with no rest,
And the scarlet sky will soon start pouring water again
Seishun ga boku no senaka o oshite akai sora utsuru mizutamari
With my leg in a clutch, suddenly the sky shivered,
So unawares, making such stupid look!
Ashimoto ga tora rete ite sora wa ureru bakaridatta
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
So it will remain forever,
As I will remain forever so!
Konomama de īkai boku wa konomama de īkai
So do we, the way we are now,
We surely will remain forever too!
Kimi to konomama zutto konomama de īkai
The strong.
The weak.
The stiff.
The supple.
The pianist. Teresa Sam N'Kota.
Next time:
Melody.
My finger will
stop the time.