Time stops as snow falls on the ocean
I embrace your slender shoulders
It's winter outside.
I can't see anything but your cute lips that I kiss
As we had seen, the attack that mobilized all resources of the underground army
ended in a spectacular debacle.
Miraculously, peace on earth was preserved.
And the sounds disappear in the distance
I guess you could say
we humans are a fortunate species.
Merry Christmas time,
in Christmas time everyone is like that
I wish you holy night and a kind heart
Merry Christmas time
When I see your tender smile,
I cannot help but love you
Seasonal greetings!
The End
Wait, wait! It's not over!
It's only the beginning! Yes, it begins!
Our town in winter is like a lonely star
Talk to me...
Ishii Hisaichi's Underground Men 2
Christmas Hades
Merry Christmas!
492 times!
Yes, please, here you go, sir!
Oh, thank you!
Thanks, really.
Underground Men Youth Organization Christmas Party
East
Representative's
Address
And now, one more...
Ritual stone.
That's a good one!
Good. Good.
General! We have a situation!
What now? Don't be a buzzkill!
The surface people
are also celebrating Christmas!
What?!
That's it! They'll pay for it!
All right, call up all the troops!
Yessir!
We'll see to it that the surface rats
don't get any Christmas!
All troops, set out!
Yes, keep going!
Yes, that's it! Go, go, go!
That great! Keep going!
Ouch-ouch...
Can't you please stop?
Ouch! Ouch! General, please!
Come on! Run!
Run! Run, you slackers!
We can't let those surface rats have any fun!
As the underground men continued their furious march to destroy Christmas on the surface,
in the depth of darkness, beneath the feet of underground men, the horrible, lowly men...
were sleeping.
Still sleeping.
But no longer.
Still not here?
Man, it's taking them so long...
Ah! It looks like our guys are back.
Where? Where, where?
The recon unit has just returned!
Allow us to report!
Dead head...
...A serpent blocks our way!
Huh? Serpent?
Oh, is it Maria-sama?
Is it this?
It's a pitcher for the Giants!
We trample over it!
What now?
Former professor at the University of Tokyo!
This time it's the ex-ex-ex-prime minister!
We step on it! We step right on!
Step on it, step on it, step on it, step on it, crush it.
Keep stepping! Yes, step right over all of them!
Step on it!
W-Wait, who might this be?
The president of Walkers.
What? Walkers?
Is that some fish store?
Should we step on it?
Wait! Of course not!
Not before we burn it.
Serves you right!
Yay! Presents!
Huh?
What the hell?!
How's this a present?
Everyone hold your breath and run by!
The furious march of underground men to destroy Christmas on the surface continued.
Meanwhile, in the darkness deep beneath the feet of the underground men,
the horrible lowly men...
were awake.
Good morning.
They were awake.
It's noon already.
Hole Digging
Wo-oh-oh-oh...
Happy, happy birthday!
Our Earth is
A lifesaver, a nice guy!
Let's gather everyone together
For a big, big carnival!
Even if you give in to despair
You can see good things if you look closely!
I'll give you
All the happiness I have!
From yesterday to today
Digging holes, digging holes!
Find some firewood
Before the sun sets
Let's call him too!
Hey come, come, come, come to house!
It's a new birthday for me!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go, happy birthday!
I have no words for you, but I have this song
The only language we understand is jungle dance!
Wo-oh-oh-oh...
Happy, happy birthday!
Let's sing together with the morning sun
Hey smile, only happy song!
Everyone's voices
Are rising too
Today is the new
Go happy birthday!
Your very own
New birthday!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go, happy birthday!
I have no words for you, but I have this song
We understand each other through the jungle dance!
Wo-oh-oh-oh...
Happy, happy birthday!
From yesterday to today
Digging holes, digging holes!
Find some firewood
Before the sun sets
Let's call him too!
Hey come, come, come, come to house!
It's my new...
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go, happy birthday!
I have no words for you, but I have this song
We understand each other through the jungle dance!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go, happy birthday!
Hole Digging
Birthday!
Advance!
We must have our own underground red-nosed deer too!
It's Christmas, so we have to catch one before marching out.
What's goin' on?
Excuse me.
Isn't that the red-nosed caterpillar?!
We'll harness it and use it to advance!
Excuse me.
Start moving faster, you idiot!
And don't ask us to excuse you!
Excuse me.
If you want to redeem yourself, keep going!
The Big Turnip
I wonder where the big turnip is?
Which of these turnips will grow big?
Those grownups only care about the price
They don't know how to simply live without worrying about what goes up and what goes down
I don't know!
I don't know,
Where is that turnip
The turnip that Tic-san gave me
Is guaranteed to grow big and expensive
But the guy who ended up buying it
Is trying to come up with an excuse
for why it's shrinking
I don't know!
I don't know,
Which one is going to grow big
Now you sing along too!
I don't know!
I don't know
I don't know...
Let's sing together, once more!
I don't know!
That'll be on our next album!
From the bottom of your lungs!
I don't know!
The back rows join in too!
I don't know
One, two, three, four!
I don't know!
The Big Turnip
I don't even know what I have anymore
Let's go!
Wait!
It's the lowly men attack!
Oh, dammit!
Idiots! Idiots! Idiots! Idiots!
We won’t just stand by and let them call us idiots!
We'll counterattack!
The lowly men are rude and stupid!
Everyday
I have different tastes in women every day
I have different tastes in men every day
I wear hair of different color every day
Everyday!
I live in a different house every day
I read different Manga every day
I watch different shows every day
Everyday!
I try to look busy
I look busy all the time
I smoke different cigarettes every day
I shed different tears every day
I smile... differently every day
Everyday!
I go to a different church every day
I believe in different gods every day
I believe in different Buddhas every day
Everyday!
I try to look busy
I look busy all the time
I'm so bored!
I’m bored to death!
Just as it was yesterday,
it's the same today
I'm so bored!
I’m bored to death!
Just as it was yesterday,
it's the same today
Everyday
I'm starving...
General, it's a river!
It's an underground river.
We're in luck.
Maybe there's fish in it!
All right! You go over there and check!
Yessir!
Right? Who's the great commander? Who?
General!
Got noodles here!
Underground noodles stream
Noodles! We got noodles!
Everyone, they say the higher you climb, the longer the fall.
But General, sir...
What is it?
Going downstream means going deeper underground.
Doesn't that mean we're only getting further from the surface?
Why didn't you say sooner, you cretin?
W-Wait! General, sir,
there's a waterfall dead ahead!
Wh-What?!
Are you serious...?
All troops, row upstream as hard as you can!
Do it with your military discipline!
Yessir!
Imbeciles! That’s not the kind of music to boost morale!
It's not the time for relaxing music!
You need to rally your comrades to get them moving!
We're sorry.
Yeah, apologies.
No! No, you don't understand!
It's too late!
Mommy!
Someone's left a present for us!
I'll make your one wish come true.
Then give me a Christmas present.
Very well.
Wow, I wonder what's in there!
I'll make your one wish come true.
Didn't you just jump out of the previous box?
That was Number 1, I'm number 2.
Give me a Christmas present!
Very well.
You again?
Yes. But that was Number 2, I'm Number 3.
Then give me a Christmas present!
Very well.
It'll be Number 4 this time.
Probably.
I'm Number 28.
Apologize for coming out with a different pattern, you asshole!
Sir, should we perhaps ask him where the fireplace is?
Oh, that's right!
You tell us where are the fireplace and the chimney that lead to the surface!
Very well.
It's a straight shot from here.
Even an idiot will find the way through.
Exit to the surface
Now she's no longer here,
but the alarm still goes off early in the morning
I've always lived with her,
Always fighting and always making up
I was always dreaming and feeling at ease,
I'm just a
Day Dream Believer, and she is a Queen
But that's a long-ago memory
Even as the sun sets and I sit at the table
Ah, now she's smiling at me
with her gentle eyes from the photograph
I was always dreaming and I was happy
I'm just a
Day Dream Believer and
she is a Queen
I was always dreaming and feeling at ease,
I'm just a
Day Dream Believer, and she is a Queen
I was always dreaming
and I still do,
I'm just a
Day Dream Believer,
and she is a Queen
I was always dreaming
and feeling at ease,
I'm just a
Day Dream Believer, and she is a Queen
Thank you for letting me
keep dreaming forever
I'm just a Day Dream Believer
and she is the Queen
Advance! Advance!
Get them!
Stop!
Oh, here it is! I-It's the fireplace!
The exit to the surface!
Hello!
All right, seems good!
All troops, go in!
Attack!
Let's light a fire...
Yessir!
Scar People
Scar! Scar! Scar!
People, number one is a hacker!
Director: Kazumi Nonaka
Scar! Scar! Scar!
People, number one is a hacker!
She's a wounded woman, I'm the abandoned man
And the hacker got burned
Don't touch that
Don't laugh at that
The more I look, the more I see
You can do it too
Don't touch that
Don't laugh at that
The more I look, the more I see
You can do it too
Scar! Scar! Scar!
People, number one is a hacker!
There's a scar on my face, and a burn on my heart
The hacker, poor fella, got burned
Don't touch that
Don't laugh at that
The more I look, the more I see
You can do it too
Don't touch that
Don't laugh at that
The more I look, the more I see
You can do it too!
Scar! Scar! Scar!
People, number one is a hacker!
People...
Stop it!
Scar!
Scar! Scar!
Wait, wait, wait.
OK!
All right!
The rest of the story is full of scars
Even if you get hurt, pretend not to notice
If you stop pretending, it'll hurt even more
The wounds of heart never heal
The nail that sticks out gets hammered down
But the nail that falls out doesn't get hammered
But the nail that falls out doesn't get hammered!
Scar! Scar! Scar!
People, number one is a hacker!
People, number one is a hacker...
Well, well.
Congratulations, congratulations!
General! We have a situation! They also celebrate the New Year on the surface.
Unacceptable!
The New Year belongs to the lunar men!
That's it!
All troops, march to the surface!
Underground Men 2:
Christmas Hades
Ripped & encoded by WOWmd
Translated by Perevodildo
Quality checked by True Noobow Gamer