Coward!
Compared to me, you're merely a mouse!
Somewhere in the infinite expanse of space,
there must be a civilization
advanced enough to defeat Gadzilla.
Find it and come back, Kenichi-kun.
Got it, professor.
Don't let us down!
Professor, I found it! A planet with a civilization that can defeat Gadzilla!
Oh, at long last!
It's the Kiris Planet of the Elmara Nebula!
They have a wonderfully advanced civilization.
Well done, Kenichi-kun!
Don't tell me this kid is all you found.
One sunny afternoon,
a postman was making his rounds.
Yamamoto-san, you have a registered letter.
Yamamoto-san! Yamamoto-san!
Yamamoto
Wh-What are you doing, Yamamoto-san?
You're gonna rip it away, Yamamoto-san!
And all the while we were doing foolish things like that,
deep underground, right beneath our feet,
they lived in perpetual darkness...
A fearsome band of invaders lay in wait,
secretly biding their time for the perfect moment to conquer the surface.
Yes, it is them—the...
The...
The Underground Men
Huh?
On the blue sea, there's a slow boat to China,
I'd love to take you to the land of dreams
Get you and keep you in my arms evermore,
Leave all your memories on the faraway shore
As we walk this road through the calm seas
With seagulls flying up above
On the blue sea, on a slow boat to China,
going to the land of dreams
Underground Men Supreme Command
Meeting in progress
What's on our agenda for today?
The harmful effects of dry cleaning.
Dry cleaning?
Who suggested that?
It's so obviously bullshit!
Silence!
S-Silence I said!
I said silence, can't you hear?!
It's impossible to hear anything!
Hey! Stop! Pipe it down!
Silence! S-Silence!
Silence!!
Why are there rocks falling from above?
Why do we have to live underground?
Why... Why...
We must break free from here!
To the surface! To the surface, after me!
You know, even if you command us to...
Shut up!
After me, everyone!
All right! Get the army ready to march out!
Yessir!
You surface-living rats, we'll show you!
You asked for it!
Following the strategy meeting, it was decided to launch a surface attack, and the entire Underground Men Army was mobilized!
Earth
What's the first army's composition?
It starts with the L*tus Sutra corps.
What's that?
Next, it's the M*slim corps.
And here comes the t*berculosis corps.
They don't look all that well...
Followed by the Al*ens believers corps.
Next, it's the timid regiment.
E-Excuse me?
S-So, h-how is your business doing?
N-Nice to see y-you here today...
Festival dancers regiment!
"Turkey in the Straw" dancers regiment!
Heroic Underground Men Army!
Now we're getting somewhere!
I like it.
Unit... stand still!
Here's to the Surface Invasion
Um... You'll probably manage... Probably...
Regardless, the decision to proceed with the surface invasion was made.
Everyone, attack!
Is that our strongest regiment?
More like the weakest one, sir.
Why did you mobilize all that rubble?
Damn it all!
Hear this, you surface rats!
You’re about to come face-to-face with the terror of the Underground Men!
I swear on me mum!
Thus began the terrifying underground army's offensive to conquer the surface...
Too late.
He's departed this world.
Blazes! Who's doing this?
Ah, leader, look at this.
He wrote something.
Wha...
He was trying to tell us who killed him.
Yes. What did he write? Let me see!
Yessir.
They got me...
There it is.
101 Ninja Marches
Part 1
Is the Iga Trio currently awaiting my command?
Ye!
Yes!
Yeah!
Assassinate Yamada Bizennokami,
the lord of the Yamamoto clan.
Ye!
Yes!
Yeah!
Get going already, you dimwits!
Okay!
Darling, please tell your ninjas to stop disguising as trees and stones in our garden.
I'm so tired of putting things back every time!
Don't get in my way!
My lord!
We have a situation.
The Matsudaira clan dispatched their ninjas to assassinate you.
L-Lord! The enemy ninjas
are coming for your life...
N-No, my lord, the enemy ninjas...
Oh no!
We are the Fuuma Trio!
I-It's strange, I can feel their presence...
Do you suppose they're still alive at the bottom of that ravine, somehow?
Ugh... Guys, it really hurts.
No, I mean it guys. Please.
Run! Run!
Hey you, get back here!
They're catching up!
You scoundrels!
Get back here!
Idiots! It's your own fault!
What do you know?!
Cretins! Cretins!
Who’re you calling cretins, you crab-hands?
Cretins!
But are you sure it is appropriate to stop for some soba in a place like this, Ring Leader?
Don't be stupid!
We already know where they're going.
Besides, you can't go to war with an empty stomach.
This Soba is just like what they cook on Mount Togakushi in Northern Shinshu.
We should try the ones from Satsuma,
with dried bonito and pickled kelp next time.
'Scuse me, but this soba is imported from Canada.
Only pickled in soy sauce, is all...
Thanks for the meal!
Excuse me, you wanted a shared bill with those gentlemen, correct?
N-No... I mean... Huh?
Whoa! It's the enemy! After him!
Hey! G-Get back here!
Bill! Pay your bill first!
Hey, wait! Bill! Pay your bill now!
Stop, you thieves! I'm already old and poor, but then you're also gonna rob me?!
You dislike the imported soba, huh?! But our home-grown variety is even more expensive!
I also have a sick wife to support, so I'm working myself into the ground every day!
I push my food cart by myself, and even in the freezing winter, I still have to go out.
It’s tough on my teeth and my health!
I can't get any fish at all, and you're asking for dried bonito from Satsuma?!
"Pickled kelp" my ass!
You think this is a 5-star restaurant?!
What's going on?
I'll fucking kill you! Hey! Stop!
It looks like we’ve kicked the hornet’s nest.
J-Just run for now!
It seems we made it here unnoticed.
Someone, dive into this dike and scout out the situation.
Yes, let me do it.
Thanks to intense training,
I can hold my breath for 30 minutes.
Oh! Quite impressive indeed.
Go ahead, then, Yadoru.
Yessir.
I can't dive! I can't dive anymore!
Yeah, I was expecting something like this to happen.
Get back here, you rogues!
Run!
No time to think!
Gotta go now!
Why are you here?
W-What's going on?
Hey, that thing is convenient!
It's as though it pulls us up automatically.
I ought to get one too!
You bastards...
Run, run!
Run!
Get back here, you crooks!
Cowards! These cowards are inside!
Hey, hold it! Who are you...
Cowards! Rogues! Die!
Next program:
Ken-chan the Searcher
Space Travel
Kenichi-kun, you must go there
and learn from the Natakio Aliens
how to defeat Medora.
Got it, Professor.
Don't let us down, Kenichi-kun.
Professor! I learned how to defeat Medora!
Ah, at long last!
So what do we need to do?
Do this!
Like this?
Like this.
You absolute imbecile!
Once again:
Ken-chan the Searcher
Space Travel
Even a monster such as Gemora
must also have a weakness!
Kenichi-kun, go there and find it!
Got it, Professor!
Don't let us down, Kenichi-kun!
Professor! I found Gemora's weakness!
Oh! At long last!
Gemora's weak point is right here,
between the two of its nostrils!
How's that supposed to help?!
You numbskull!
Take this! And this!
You're not treating me fairly!
And this!
Ready...
Go!
How's business going?
Well, we're managing
That's not even worth mentioning
I couldn't wait to see you again
Want to go to Doutonbori?
All the way to Nandacho
You came because you heard rumors
Because I can't go on
w-without you
Imbeciles!
We've got a war to win! Finish the tunnel at once! Get to work, you slackers!
Oh, this seems easy to climb!
The heavens are on our side!
E-Even the gods are on our side now, you hear?!
Let's go!
T-This is actually i-impressive!
Greetings! I hope you brought the offerings?
You bastard!
Get this dumbass out of the way!
All right...
If we all act together,
we'll move this stone!
Everyone, arrange!
R-Run!
To the right tunnel!
A dead end?!
W-Wait! H-Hey!
W-Why do you hate me so much...
Clinging to the ceiling to hide?
Just your average ninja.
Huh? He was actually here?!
101 Ninja Marches
Lord! Lord!
Part 2
W-We've got a situation!
The enemy ninjas have already infiltrated this castle!
Lord! You must evacuate at once...
H-Huh?
L-Lord?
Lord! It's not the time to fool around!
Get back here!
Run! Run!
We'll get you! Stop!
Clingy bastards. Take this!
Money!
Ah! Hold it, you! Stop it, you hear?
Thieves! This is mine!
Where are the invaders?!
I will use my spear to exact punishment on them!
Over there?
Maybe here?
Shit! I'll show you how scary the real men are!
I'll kill you!
You've got nowhere to run now!
Say your prayers!
Ouch...
H-Huh?
Hey, where is the boss's room?
Let's see... Oh? Huh?
Dumbass, dumbass, dumbass!
So they came!
The ninjas sent to take our Lord's life!
But his loyal servant Gyobu
won't let them pass!
Run!
Blow at the fire!
O-Okay.
Blow it out, you cretin!
Sorry,
I always do this when someone's watching.
What are you gossiping about?
You’re some of the most spineless ninjas I’ve ever seen!
Ring Leader...
Q-Q-Quickly, bring the water, somebody!
Run, run!
Hey! Who told you to run away?!
Whoa! Run!
Hey, you! Get back here! Will you abandon the castle along with your Lord that easily?!
Lord! Hurry up to evacuate, through here!
I'll kill you!
This is it! Get back here!
What was that just now?
Lord!
L-L-L-Lord! Lord, hey!
So bright!
Ring Leader, what do you think that is?
Is that... the legendary firebird?
So dazzling!
What's all the commotion about?
Idiots!
Idiots! Idiots! Idiots!
Get back here!
Stop! I'll get you!
That's enough,
Ken-chan the Searcher
Space Travel
Kenichi-kun, go to Gedzilla's birthplace,
the planet of Manachia.
You must find his weaknesses.
Don't let us down!
Got it, Professor!
And just like that, Kenichi-kun
made his getaway!
M-Marvelous!
Ouch!
Screw you!
Blame the ceiling!
Yeah! Yeah!
That's right!
That ceiling is our enemy!
All forces attack!
Go!
Don't stop at anything!
Keep going!
Show it! Bite into it!
Dig right through it!
Keep going!
Put your back into it!
Go! Go!
Don't stop at anything!
The only way to go is forward!
Yes, we're getting somewhere!
I-Is this what I think this is?
All troops, attack!
Isn't it touching?
I-I'm so happy...
W-Where's everyone?
What's going on?
Attack! Attack!
Don't abandon me!
Attack! Go!
I see a way out!
Hey! W-Which way now?
Yes, that way, it seems.
There?
Oh, there it is!
Attack!
Keep going!
Go!
This can't stop us!
Are you telling me the underground army is full of weaklings?
Attack, all troops!
Follow me!
K-Keep going!
K-K-Keep going!
We'll show them! Keep going!
K-Keep going!
It's going downhill next!
Advance! Keep going!
Get a move on!
K-Keep going!
K-Keep going...
Nobody can stop us...
It's going downhill next!
Go! Advance!
Don't stop!
Go! Go! Attack!
Go!
Keep going!
Go...
Down! W-We're going down!
Go! Keep going!
Thus, the conquest of surface, which previously united the underground army, took an unexpected turn...
Surface humanity was barely saved, and it was truly by a stroke of luck!
I wish I could come again
to your room
I want you to invite me
I love you
The painful passion
The red wine
We clink our glasses
Tears flow
Beautiful you by the crescent moon window
I hug you
I wish for something more
But we stop there
Thank you for those
pink sighs,
Yes, when you close
your two eyelids...
You're pleasantly warm,
You're tenderly soft
No need to say anything
or the happiness will slip away
I want more
of this paradise
While I'm with you,
no one can bother us
the rest of the world is not real
Cretins!
See you again...
I wish I could come again
to your room
It were the rumored Underground Men
Anyway,
blame the ceiling!!
to your room
I wish I could come again...
Bonus
Are you the dimwit from the peasants of the Yamada Village?
Raise your head.
I won't kill you.
O-Okay...
What the hell is that kind of face?
P-Please don't get angry, my lord.
I was born with this kind of face.
Idiot! I'm not angry.
I was also born with this face.
Vase...
For real now
The end
Ripped & encoded by WOWmd
Translated by Perevodildo
Quality checked by True Noobow Gamer
Underground men
aid
Christmas
Hades