Energy reaction detected
in Kanto Block B!
Current time is 15:23!
The space has started to warp!
Confirmed trail in the air above District 4!
Declare level four emergency!
The speed is abnormal!
It's a fusion!
So it's finally happened here.
Chou of Benten, you don't know when to give up, do you?
No matter what you do,
you can't defeat me.
Well, I'll commend your
fighting spirit, at least.
Headband: Unpredictable
That said, our fight will be slightly different this time.
At least he looks strong.
Don't cry this time!
Headband: Triumphant
Dekao! Go get her!
Let's go!
Rabbit Journal
Morning!
Geez, you're really keen on this.
Oh, morning, Miku.
Hey, instead of working on that,
let's go to this new hamburger shop on our way home today-
There's a fight!
Hey, Inaba's taking on Chou of Benten High School.
Where?
On the roof.
Th-The roof?
Th-This is bad! Mimika!
Sign: Class 2-B
Mimika-chan
Your strength's not bad,
but your speed isn't good enough.
Time to finish this.
Mimika!
Matogi?
I've got you now!
Crap!
Mimika!
Charge Charge Energy
I'm sure some power sleeps in me
To make my dream come true once again
Orphan Fansubs presents
Usagi-chan de Cue  !!
The days when we laughed like fools
The memories of crying till it hurt
If they were all lies
Then I'm sad to know I'm like that
I want to know when did you learn
Just to resign and step back quietly?
You Take Chance Game
Charge Charge Energy
"Something is different"
When you have that kind of feeling
Change My Destiny
People are always being reborn
Charge Charge Energy
I've been searching in my heart
For so long now, but it's not enough
Change My Destiny
When we fuse into one
That's who I truly am
So Inaba's body is like this?
Her skin is so plump and smooth.
Buy why did this happen?
I can't remember no matter
how hard I try.
Oh well.
Amazing! Inaba-san is great!
Great! Great!
Somebody help!
Stay away!
Well, if you put it that way...
Gramps!
You should check
if there's someone inside first.
Oh, I was careless. There's only
one lady in our house, you see.
Oh.
So, who's this girl?
Um... well...
Isn't she Mimika-chan?
Mimika...
Geez, Gramps. You have such
a bad memory.
Was she here all this time?
Yes.
I see. I see. So that's how it is.
That's right.
You never change, Gramps.
You shouldn't enter the bathroom without asking.
I've kept you a secret from my parents.
It's all right! I have these.
They emit special waves, convincing people there's nothing strange.
More importantly, have you
remembered anything?
I really don't know.
I can remember things clearly up until Inaba-san saved me, but...
While we were falling together,
I suddenly felt a warm
light enveloping me.
Wh-What happened to Inaba?
You want Inaba-san, not me!
No, by no means...
Really?
Y-Yeah.
Yay! Haru!
M-Mimika?
I got to meet my beloved Haru in a human form.
I'm so happy.
Mi... mika...
Um... well...
Hey! What are you two doing?
Miku.
I-It's not what you think!
There's a reason for this!
I know that.
It's Mimika-chan,
so you can't help yourself.
If not for her, I'd also...
Here you go. I brought you a change of clothes and some snacks.
Haru!
How long are you going
to keep that up?!
I want to keep doing this forever!
Haru! Haru!
No-o...
Look, you... You'd better really be Mimika-chan.
If you were Inaba-san,
I wouldn't let that slide.
M-Mimika. Y-Your ears.
They don't seem to work on Miku-chan.
But why? Actually, they don't work on me either.
Doesn't matter! Hurry up and get off him already!
I'm sorry, Miku-chan.
I'm just so happy when I'm with Haru.
It's all right. I don't really mind.
Wait! I didn't say start again!
Like I said, it's not what you think!
I'm not talking to you!
This is hopeless.
Haru!
Well, I'll go home, so...
Yeah... Right... It's dark, so be careful.
Oh geez... S-Stop it, Mimika.
I have strong points of my own, y'know.
Mimika-chan's so lucky.
She's alone with Haru.
She's finally asleep.
Okay.
But why did Inaba and Mimika fuse?
Oh well.
She fell off the roof but walked away unharmed, and that's what matters.
I'll think about it later.
But even though she can
send those signals,
I have to be careful.
For now, best not to show her off too much.
Yeah, I'll do that.
It's Haru! It's Haru! It's Haru!
She's so outgoing!
Way to go, Mimika!
Huh? Was she here all this time?
More importantly, is Miku okay with this?
Mimika will take Matogi-kun away.
You have the wrong idea.
We're just childhood friends.
But don't you and Matogi-kun
make a good couple?
That won't do. If the woman is serious,
the man must be flamboyant.
If the man is serious,
the woman must be flamboyant.
My parents are like that too.
There needs to be balance in the world.
Boys his age prefer outgoing girls.
They're easy prey.
Stop, I said. Mimika, that tickles!
That's true. Easy prey.
Hey, have you gained weight recently?
Sorry about yesterday.
I don't know what got into me.
I was a bit jittery about it.
Oh, those candies were nice.
Yeah, by the way, I heard
they built a hamburger stand
near the station.
Want to stop there on our way home?
All right!
It's finished.
Sorry, what were you saying?
G-Gulp...
Forget it. It wasn't important.
Haru! Let's go home!
Oh! You fixed the house
for me and my friends!
Y-Yeah.
Bye-bye, everyone.
I'm going to Haru's house.
Okay, let's go home.
Let's go home for an afternoon snack!
Afternoon snack?
You're right, we probably still have Miku's groceries from yesterday.
Gila Jello...
Gelato candy?
What's wrong, Miku?
Huh? Did you gain some weight?
Inaba... Mikami!
Boss!
What is it?
Headband: Afternoon Snack
Headband: Surprised
Inaba Mikami is alive?!
Even though I've already boasted to everyone about killing Inaba of Banzai, my archenemy!
Hold it!
Hey, Inaba, why the hell
do you look so perky?
Headband: Hold It
Dekao ended up in the hospital!
That's right! We'll do away with you today for sure!
Boss! That's Mimika.
As always, so cute!
What are you saying?!
That's Inaba, don't you see?
I-na-ba!
It's Mimika.
What is this?
Who's this little boy?
Shut up! Don't act like
you forgot who I am!
Headband: I'm Not Little!
Hello, kid.
R-Right... Hello.
Headband: Huh?
What am I saying?!
Headband: No!
Headband: Prepare Yourself!
Headband: I'm Coming!
Chest!
Headband: Oops!
Miku-chan!
Headband: Fortune for the Family
Tsk. I missed. But next time...
Wh-What's this?
Wh-What's going on?
So pretty...
Hey! We're withdrawing.
What? Why?
Let's watch a little longer.
I said withdraw!
Yes, sir.
Miku.
Haru.
Are you okay?
Yes.
You were worried about me?
Haru!
I was so scared!
Well, you can calm down now.
Oh, anyway, let's go in there. Okay?
Grand Opening!
All right!
Hey, Boss! Please wait!
Headband: Fortune for the Family
There's no doubt about it.
They fused.
Yay! It's brand new!
What's a brand?
Wow, they've built this cafe here.
Did you know?
No.
Haru! I'm thirsty!
Okay, okay.
Here, your healthy carrot juice.
Yay!
I don't have much money,
so I got us some cola.
Okay.
Haru got us the same drink.
Thank you.
Wow! Mimika has a different juice?
How nice! I wanna drink it!
Carrot juice is more expensive than cola, you know.
I want some cola too!
Just a little.
Mimika!
I'm sorry.
Oh no, it's fine.
It just spilled on the table.
I'll get some paper towels.
That wasn't very smart.
You could've just asked me to pass it.
But I wanted to try the cola.
I don't have any more money.
The cola went bye-bye.
Then have some of this.
Thank you!
Haru's cola. An indirect kiss...
Mimika-chan can do that so naturally.
It's nice to be her.
Oh, you really are dumb.
Your hands are all sticky.
Oh, Miku, sorry.
I'll take her to wash her hands.
Wash hands! Wash hands!
Okay, I'll wipe the table, then.
I guess it can't be helped.
Haru's her caretaker, after all.
I saw the fused specimen in District 4.
So... where is it now?
The evidence suggests she's currently residing at her classmate's house.
Then what is her intelligence level?
Seems rather high, but in the end,
she's still a rabbit.
A rabbit?
Yes.
How's that different from a dog like you?
A dog works for his master.
Don't take your eyes off
the fused specimen.
Yes, sir.
Do you believe we can rely on an agent like him?
He's bad at sniffing around.
A dog with a weak nose?
She's finally asleep.
Anyway, what happened to her today?
Maybe she should refrain from seeing people.
Let's not take her out too much. Yes, that's it.
It's the beach!
It's the beach? Rah, rah...
Me first!
What are you doing, Mimika-chan?
Inaba's butt looks unexpectedly good.
No, I mean that swimsuit on her...
Hey, Miku-chan! Don't laugh!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy!
Come to think of it, Miku and I have never been to the sea together before.
I never knew she was that womanly.
We've always been close,
but I never looked at her that closely.
She's actually quite shapely too.
Why is Haru standing still,
when the sun is so strong?
He should pitch the tent already.
I pitched the wrong tent.
Should we go?
O-Okay.
Are you all right, Miku-chan?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just stepped on a seashell.
Is something troubling you,
young ladies?
If you have a problem, leave it to us!
Do you need CPR?
Need some company to beat your boredom?
We're here to help you with it!
We're the Comforting Sinbads!
Nah, we're good.
Thanks for asking and all...
Not so fast!
Accept your fate!
You need saving!
Miku-chan!
How is this supposed to save me?
Don't worry. It's for saving us from our bursting...
Stop that!
Get away from her!
We're saving her.
You stay out of this!
No!
Stop it!
Then we'll rescue you first!
Sinbads!
Next up, artificial aspiration!
Final blow, emergency evacuation!
Haru!
I-It's so sad...
Now it's time for some actual lifesaving!
Who did it?!
Don't you know that the ocean belongs to no one?
Your vulgar behavior ruins
this beautiful beach for everyone!
Mimika-chan?
I-Inaba Mikami...
As you predicted,
the black rabbit came out,
Chou of Benten!
Headband: Good Work
I've been waiting for you, Inaba Mikami.
Headband: Professor All-knowing
No... The product of advanced fusion.
Then we'll have our fun now!
What?
Such a high jump, even from the beach?!
And that speed...
Because she's a rabbit.
Headband: The Red Comet
It's you!
Dekao!
I see! You've been discharged from the hospital.
Headband: Won!
Inaba Mikami, we have
one final card to play!
But it won't be like the last time.
After all, there's no roof
for you to fall from.
Now, it's time for revenge!
What are you doing?!
So you're a messenger
who's come back from hell?
Here's my revenge.
You're finished!
Okay! I'll borrow this.
That bastard. This time,
I'll punch a hole through him for sure!
Dekao...
Take this!
Headband: Mommy!
Who...
Mimika?
I-Inaba?
Inaba Mi...
You're awake, Haru?
Miku?
Where's Inaba?
Haru!
Hey...
Haru...
I thought you were gonna die!
Did you know? My chest was pounding!
Right here. Haru, feel it.
H-Hey!
I've been meaning to ask for a while.
What's wrong with you? Get off him!
Never!
Get off him!
Headband: Death of an Insect
Where did Dekao get a body like that?
I wonder...
N-No. He didn't get that body.
He was forced into it.
Then, I trust you to look after my girl.
Please rest easy, sir.
Of course. I'm well aware
of your school's reputation.
I'm not worried for her.
I'm honored.
Well then, I'll call the homeroom teacher.
The rest is up to you.
Yes, roger that.
We're putting great trust in you.
Leave it to me.
Oh, Koshka-kun, this way.
O-Okay!
Koshka-kun, this is your homeroom teacher, Yoshimura-sensei.
Nice to meet you!
Well then, let's go to the classroom.
Okay.
You're more precious to me than anyone
I can't say it well
So I disguise it with a smile again
I still can't understand
That strange flicker in your eyes
The more I like you, the more uneasy I am
I want to know why my heart does that to me
I put the pieces of my feelings together
Gently with these hands
Original
Subtitles
Translation
Check
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
C1 Anime
Perevodildo
ImAWasteOfHair
Collectr
anonymous
MartyMcflies
another anonymous
Next Episode
If you finished watching
the first episode...
Oh, you thought that Mimika
was the main character?
How silly. You're wrong.
The main character is m-e.
I'm the cute kitten, Koshka-chan.
If I get serious, I can kill that
stupid rabbit with one blow.
Just you wait, Mimika!