Blue Experience
Maybe this one?
No, this one is better.
Hm, I'm tired of this.
All right! I choose this.
It's not like I'm going
to show this to anyone.
There.
How come no man seems to notice
this beautiful body?
I think I'm more than ready.
Right?
Oops, I've no time for this.
Yeah! Looking good.
Heya!
So trendy! But of course!
My sense of fashion is impeccable.
Who am I kidding?
Bye, Mom!
Bye, Miki. Behave yourself, okay?
Sure!
I'm Miki. I entered college last spring.
Where am I going?
Just to work.
After all, I'm a hardworking girl!
I'm supposed to help the son of my mom's friend study during the winter break.
It's a single parent household.
And because the mother is too busy with work and housework to help her son study,
she asked me to help
her son with his studies.
No!
Oh dear, my boots got dirty.
Damn!
Hey!
Huh? No way!
Welcome.
I'm concerned that his grades
have dropped lately.
I have a guest right now,
so I'm counting on you.
Sure.
See you later.
"A guest," she says.
Is that what it's called these days?
I hate him.
Wh-What's the matter?
Nothing.
Just talking to myself.
I can see it's not "nothing."
What an unfriendly kid.
Oh boy, I'm bored.
Hey, you wanna see
something interesting?
What is it? What's interesting?
You'll see.
You have to keep quiet, though.
Oh?
Follow me.
Geez...
That brat.
Just as I thought.
What is it?
I-It's not scary, is it?
No, not at all.
Huh?
What is that?
What are you doing?!
Why, you...
Seriously!
Ow!
Geez...
Hey, Miss Miki.
Miki!
Huh? What?
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Do all adults do that?
Do what?
This.
How would I know?
Stop thinking about that
and finish your studying already!
You're blushing!
I knew you were thinking something like that too!
Come on, tell me.
Does it feel good?
Have you done it before?
Cut that out, or I'll get mad!
Are your private parts also yucky like my mom's?
Absolutely not!
Mine is still clean!
Hey, do you want to see if mine looks like your mom's?
R-Really?!
But you can't tell anyone about this, okay?
Yes, sure!
What if your mom comes in?
Don't worry. She won't.
When she has her "guest,"
she doesn't come here until 5:30.
Then we have an hour
and twenty minutes.
Make sure to look carefully.
How does it look?
I-It's a little different.
Different how?
Say it.
I don't really know how to answer that...
Look... Look closely.
I-I still can't see the shape.
It does look different from mom's.
No, you have to be more specific.
This is the outer vulva.
Then what's this?
Uh, well...
The inner lips.
They should be cleaner than your mom's.
But I can't really tell.
Everything looks all mixed up.
Here's the clitoris.
All right? You got that?
Mine isn't dirty like your mom's.
But...
Come closer and keep looking
until you can see the difference.
It's so wet that I can't see clearly.
Then go ahead and clean it up.
It's not something dirty.
But this is where your pee comes out.
It's all right.
But...
Hurry up. We don't have much time.
Now do it!
You're... doing well.
You can... You can stop now.
Yes...
But it's not a bit cleaner.
Actually, it's even wetter,
and I can't see anything.
No. Stop that.
Don't move your fingers! Stop it!
It's my turn now.
Huh? N-No!
D-Don't!
They might hear us
from downstairs if you yell.
Oh, it's cute.
Be quiet.
I'll make you feel good soon.
W-Wait!
Well? Did you like it?
Yeah.
See you.
Oh, I wonder why he closed the curtain.
That's strange.
Maybe so he could focus better?
If that's the case, I'm impressed.
It's a little earlier than usual,
but I guess I can take up some tea now.
Translation
Editing
Raw provider
Translation check
EROBEAT
Collectr
ProxyMan
Perevodildo