Original Work:
Shuuichi Shigeno
(Weekly Shounen Magazine)
Animation Production: Studio Pierrot
Me, a specialist rider?
That's right.
They're called the
Hagiwara Racing Company.
The races they arrange make us
look like amateurs in comparison.
And those Hagiwara guys saw your performance at
the four-hour race and want you all to themselves.
They want me?
What do you say?
If you really do want to get into the racing scene, I don't think this is a bad offer.
Does this mean my
dream will come true?
But on one condition.
Condition?
The thing is, you'll need to get
promoted to B-class before year's end.
But if you pull out all the
stops in the remaining races,
they can recommend you
get promoted to B-class.
And what's more,
Hideo "Pops" Yoshimura...
After all this time... my
dream's finally coming true...
Tomoyo! You seen
my Katana keys?
Aren't they in
the usual place?
Why else would I be askin'?
Now that's strange,
I always leave them around here...
Hideyoshi, can't you
just skip this morning?
I mean, I could...
They say, if you can't find something before
going out, it's God's way of telling you something.
Are you listening
to me, Hideyoshi?
Dumbass, that's
jus' a superstition.
Oh? Found 'em!
There they are. Must've
dropped them 'round back.
Right, I'll see you later.
Ain't nothin' to worry about.
Hideyoshi...
I don't like the color
of that sky one bit...
The mountain pass
sure is great, huh?
It's somethin' else, alright.
That said, this is it for me.
This is the last time you'll
ever race me on the pass.
Startin' today,
this highway racer's finished.
I'm joining the big leagues.
He looks out of it.
What's gotten into him?
Thanks for everything,
and see you 'round, winding
roads of the mountain pass.
Wh-What's with you?
It's called a handshake, Beanpole.
But what for?!
Don't you worry.
You're one weird dude.
Thank you.
What's gotten into him today?
Wanna go? We can
take it nice and easy.
Yeah, nice and easy.
You're awfully lively for
some rich, little upstart!
I'm gonna beat you
on the pass this time!
In your dreams!
Didn't we just pass those guys?!
They're so fast!
You tryin' ta get
yourself killed, dipshit?!
That got the blood flowing!
It's too narrow!
Stop, Hideyoshi!
Wh—
Someone wiped out!
I can make it!
What?!
PART II - SUZUKA CHAPTER
The Legend of Revving Engines
It sure is snowing hard, huh?
Guess I won't be riding any time soon.
That bike's the only thing on
your mind, isn't it, Hideyoshi?
Y'know, I heard there was a really
bad crash on that pass you drive on.
Some things never change.
There are a lot of idiots
on the road, after all.
If it's that dangerous there,
then maybe you should stop going.
I'll be fine.
Hideyoshi!
I... get kinda scared sometimes...
Especially when I'm waiting for you to come back from your morning ride... I just think...
I just think,
if something ever hap—
Tomoyo!
Let's go already.
Don't get so worked
up over nothin'.
Tomoyo, please understand,
I'm doing this for you.
What do you want?
What's with you?
Whatcha starin' for?!
Lookin' at you makes
me wanna hurl!
Who lit your fuse today?!
C'mon, you wanna piece of me?!
What? So that's
why you're all sulky?
You two belong in
kindergarten, that's for sure.
Gun! Hiro!
Come here, there's
something I wanna talk about.
You know about the 4-hour endurance race
held at Suzuka over the summer, don't you?
Yeah, and I know about the
8-hour race the day after.
What about it?
I was thinking of entering it under the Ichinose Racing Team.
You serious?
That's amazing!
D-Do you really mean that?!
Yeah, and I need
three more riders.
You serious about this?
We'll race as two pairs,
and I'll be driver number four.
Count me in! Even if I've gotta
work with that stupid beanpole!
What was that?!
Ya heard me! I don't jus' race
for fun like you rich kids!
Like hell I'm working with him!
Gun!
Please enter the
race, just this once.
Get up already.
Gun!
When did I say I wouldn't?
Goddammit!
What's with him?! I thought he'd rather die than do something like that!
I could never do that.
But he can do what I can't.
He was way more
into that than I was.
When I see how much
he really wants it,
I really do look like some
amateur doing this for fun.
Damn it!
The cold winter had passed,
and with that, a warm spring had arrived.
I really wish I had a bike license...
But my mom said...
Not on your life!
Only hooligans ride bikes!
Wait until you turn 18 and
get a proper driving license!
I can't believe her.
I even thought of
running away from home.
Honey! Ai's never coming home, and it's all because of the horrible things I said to her!
Yeah, it's all your fault!
If anything happens to her,
we're getting a divorce!
Ai, your mom was wrong!
I don't mind if you ride a bike or a tank! Please, just come home!
Or something like that!
But I still got a license
without my mom knowing.
You should've seen
the look on Gun's face.
Ta-da~!
It only took six hours to get here from Tokyo, but we're finally at Suzuka!
It's wonderful!
Suzuka Circuit is even
bigger than I thought!
I want each of you to practice
with your own goal in mind.
One more thing, we won't be measuring your times until this afternoon.
So, for the time being, none of
you will know how long you take.
But why not?!
That's just boring!
Trust you to object.
This rule was made
specifically for you.
By trying too hard to lower your time, your corner entries will suffer,
your bike will become unstable, your corner exit
will go to shit, and your times would just get worse.
I know it's your first time
at this kind of event,
and I know it'll
go to your head,
so, instead, I want you
to focus on your pace.
Okay...
Dumbass. You really thought
you'd post a time that easily?
Suzuka ain't that easy.
I can take him!
Ah... he's already gone...
What am I going to do with them?
I told them to take it easy on the first lap.
His time on the West course has improved by two seconds since this morning.
Come to think of it, Gun's been sticking
like glue to the guy in the white helmet.
He's trying to learn the lines
from a more experienced rider.
Ah, it's finally over!
We'll settle this later!
What's with that guy?!
Oh, yeah, he said he
had somewhere to be.
I'll go change,
be back in a sec.
S-Sorry!
N-Now what do I do...?
I-I saw it all... All of it!
Ah... I'm... I mean... I-I'm sorry!
I-I didn't know you
were changing in there!
I'll take responsibility, and I'll
do my best to make you happy!
I still have 21 payments left on my GP, b-but my
family owns a grocery store, so I've got a future!
I won't cause you any trouble,
so I'm ready to marry you.
Hiro, take it easy.
You don't need to go that far.
Just forget about it, you idiot.
I'm doomed...
Wh-What did you say?!
Hiro looked at Miyuki
when she was changing?
No way! You saw
the princess naked?!
Maybe he did a little
more than that...
I-I did not!
I'm innocent!
I didn't do a thing!
I really didn't know!
I sure as hell didn't touch her!
Dad, Mom, it's
been a while, huh?
Tomoyo is doing great.
We're still getting along fine,
so don't worry about us.
I was at Suzuka, and since
I was in the neighborhood...
I thought I'd best come
see you before I went back.
I didn't have time to buy you
any flowers, so sorry 'bout that.
What?! I got a flat?!
That's strange, how'd I get
one all the way out here?
Yes, this is the
Hijiri household.
Yes?
- Dad! Mom!
Dad!
Mom!
Well then, I gotta go.
Don't worry about
me on the way back.
I'm not the type of rider who'd have a
crash on the Tomei Expressway, after all.
I've been saying it's too cold out to be wearing
a short-sleeved sailor uniform for a few days now,
but now that the Sun's out,
you get reminded of how hot it really is.
Though, when the boys disappear,
we do something a little unladylike.
While summer was hiding behind the rain clouds,
we could tell it was just around the corner.
Gun!
You didn't bring an umbrella?
Nah, It wasn't
raining this morning.
Still, everyone knows to bring
an umbrella at this time of year.
The rain never
bothered me anyway.
If you're out on your bike in the rain,
yeah, it's no fun at first, but the drive home
feels much better when you're soaked through.
Hiro, say...
What'll you do
after graduation?
Let's see...
What should I do...?
Once we decide on our path,
it impacts our future, doesn't it?
Once we decide on something,
do we lose out on other choices?
We're to graduate next spring.
Mi...
We'll all go our separate ways.
If only time could stop...
Then I'd make this
moment last forever.
It's almost the big day, Hideyoshi.
That race has been the only thing
on my mind for the last six months.
I don't really know much about races,
but all that matters to me is that you're safe.
If your bike is maintained and you stick to the rules, safety won't be an issue.
If I perform well there,
it'll be my shortcut to going pro.
Hideyoshi!
Don't worry about it,
just let me do my thing.
Oh, the rain stopped.
Whoa, it's so red!
It's beautiful...
Summer's here already.
The center line continues
all the way to the horizon.
As you rest your chin on your hand,
I can't take my eyes off you.
So before you fall asleep,
please let me know one thing...
"Racers to starting positions"
Would you kiss me for
longer than your other girl?
Get a move on, #2 rider.
What was that?
Cause I'm #1, obviously.
They only brought you here to prop up the machine for me, dumbass!
Oh, is that so? Then
I'd better get going!
What are you doing, Gun?!
Oh shut up, will ya?
That little shit...
Only 40 more seconds under the scorching Sun
before the race is underway.
The light will turn yellow
ten seconds before start.
And then the signal will change to
green and a "go" sign will be raised.
The eyes of the
world are on Suzuka.
And now, second by second,
the start time is approaching.
Now, at last, only ten seconds left!
The signal turned yellow!
Drivers on their marks!
We have 60 vehicles participating today!
The light turns green and the
drivers make a run for their bikes!
Whoa, an accident just off the start line!
Down goes bike number 37!
The lead group heads into
the corner side-by-side.
In the lead, holding onto his
pole position, #1, Okamoto!
Now they're entering the s-bends!
Whoa! #3 makes a break for it!
Bike #3, who had been neck-and-neck with #1, makes an overtake and seizes the lead!
Our opening lap is as
intense as any sprint race!
As soon as they leave the cambered corner,
the top group will approach the uphill section!
And the competition for
the top is really heating up!
Having just passed through the Dunlop gate,
the top group is disappearing into the West course!
We're entering lap number seven.
No change to the top with bike #3, Matsui of
the Hamamatsu Racing Team, leading the pack.
Onto the second group:
Ooya on bike #2 and Onozuka on bike #5 are really fighting for their position.
Maehara on bike #34 seems to
have come off around Degner.
More info on that to come!
So, how's our team doing?
Right, Hideyoshi is in 17th, with a lap time of 2 minutes 38.16 seconds.
What about the princess?
Being measured as we speak.
29th place. Time is 2 minutes 41.25 seconds.
Do you think they're
a bit overpace?
Gun, how do you manage
to remain so calm?
Who said I was?
I'm dying to get out there.
If I don't get on that bike,
I think I'm gonna explode.
I don't care how fast these other guys are,
I'm not losing to any of 'em.
No changes to the lead with Matsui on bike #3 leading the pack into lap 12.
He just clocked in
another smooth lap!
My watch has a time split of
three seconds for second place.
As you can see,
he's gained a huge lead!
But #2, Ooya, is hot on his heels!
And Onozuka isn't far
behind on bike #5!
It's too hot... my throat's so dry.
I'd hoped the wind would
cool me down a little,
but with the heat reflecting off the asphalt, it's like I'm driving into an inferno.
It's a little better if
I stay beneath the cowl,
but it's still like I've been thrown into a frying pan where someone's turning up the heat.
It's hot... so hot...
Alright, get ready to swap drivers.
Ai, can you get the pit
sign out for Hideyoshi?
Sure.
Haga, get the charger ready.
Okay!
Hagino, the board!
On it right now!
And remember, once we're done
with Hideyoshi, it's the princess' turn.
Gun, are you ready?
I was born ready!
Leave it to me!
It's lap 18 and the leader, Matsui, on bike #3 is coming in hot to the pit lane.
Their bike will be refueled
and their riders swapped.
And Onozuka,
#5, isn't far behind!
As a result, the race leader becomes Ooya on bike #2, as he flies past the stands.
Followed by Yamada on bike #6.
Hamamatsu Racing Team's
pit work is as fast as ever!
And they're back on
track within five seconds.
Ibe, the rider
replacing Matsui, is off!
And here comes
Hijiri on bike #16!
Gun, keep it together.
I know, but I've been
waiting a long time for this.
Here, Hideyoshi!
That's payback from the start line!
That asshole...
Gun, what the hell was that?!
Oh, shut up!
You moron!
What are you two playing at?!
We're in the
middle of the race!
This is a great pace.
How can you not love it?
Charging is done!
Good. Hiro, get going!
Are you okay, Miyuki?
Thanks, I'll be fine.
The race has been
going for almost an hour.
And it's maintained its
sprint-race-like pace!
Bike #3, Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing is
in the lead and is entering his 23rd lap.
But Murakami, #5, from Suzuka Riding is about six seconds behind.
The lineup was just as we predicted.
But something's happening
in the second group!
A rider just clocked in a blistering
time of 2 minutes 35 seconds!
Ichinose Racing's #16 is really putting the pressure on the other riders!
You're so cool, #16!
The crowd's more excited to see
me than that reckless little runt!
Koma, on bike #16, just did a lap
faster than Ibe who's leading the race.
Whoa there! Bikes #11 and #50
collide on the entry to the chicane!
Will Koma get caught up in it?!
And he avoids them!
What's Koma's lap time
going to be this now?!
Koma's time just reported to us is... 2 minutes, 34.91 seconds!
He's amazing! He broke
the 34 second barrier!
That dude's crazy!
Who is that guy?!
Check the entry list.
It says Koma on #16.
That'd be the Ichinose Racing Team: Koma Gun and Hijiri Hideyoshi?
They're both only 17!
They're so young!
Wait, they're still
in high school?!
Now Koma's making a move
on Yamada in 4th place!
If you give him a target to
chase, he's unbelievably fast.
In other words, if there's nobody in sight, you can't light a flame under him.
Maybe that's why he can't
drive like this all the time.
Has he always had this level of insight?
Or has instinct brought him this far?
Whether it's on the pass or on the circuit,
chasing and then blowing past them is his style.
And when that happens,
he's insanely fast.
The guy's a natural sprinter.
Alright, Hideyoshi, we're
changing riders again. Get ready.
Alright!
The Suzuka Endurance Race is now so well
known that you can listen to it on FM radio.
Those who have an FM radio receiver with them, please tune in to 78 MHz.
Gun!
What's the deal with
you and Hideyoshi?!
It's not like it's saving us any
time in the pits, you moron.
That's just how I say hello.
Same goes for him too, I guess.
Good job. We're now running somewhere between 35th and 40th place.
Manager, what about Ichinose?
Ichinose? I think
they're sitting in 6th.
6th place?!
Yeah, they were even
in third at one point.
Those guys were?
I can hardly believe it...
Takanezawa, I'll be blunt.
Forget about them.
They're on a different level.
I don't wanna hear it!
So we're giving up?!
Just like that?!
You really think I'd let those
punks get all the attention?
Matsui from the Hamamatsu
Racing Team is still in first.
And Okamoto from Green
Grass is just behind.
Onozuka on bike #5 is in third, but Hijiri
on bike #16 is making use of his slipstream.
Oh? That one seems interesting.
That #16.
He's my sort of rider.
Bike #16?
Oh, you mean the other rider?
That stupidly fast kamikaze novice?
No, I mean the shorter
one who's riding right now.
Can't you see why?
Among the 40,000 spectators here,
how many do you think know what he's doing?
Five? Nah, maybe two or
three would be generous.
While they're polar opposites,
if those two geniuses are a team,
I think we could see #16 winning today.
That little shit
thinks he's so smart.
That beanpole's riding it too hard on
the engine, it can't take much more.
All I've gotta do is maintain our current position and not put too much strain on the engine.
I'm able to keep up with the bike in front at only 80% power.
I'm gonna preserve as much
of the engine's power as I can,
then it's all down to that beanpole and his explosive driving!
That's strange. The princess
hasn't come around yet.
And there's no way
she'd miss the pit-in sign.
Do you think something
happened to her?
Hey! Hey, you!
Are you okay?
Who's that guy?
What just happened to me?
O-Ouch...
Corner 130R.
That's right, I came off.
I've gotta keep riding!
At least your
bones are still intact.
Can you keep racing?
I don't know... it hurts like
hell whenever I move it.
And I've lost all strength in it.
I see.
Courage is needed to race, but a different kind of courage is needed to retire.
I'll respect whatever
decision you make.
You two just have to work
it out amongst yourselves.
Hiro...
Let's do it, Mi.
We'll adjust our time splits to
keep your driving to a minimum.
I'll give it everything I've got.
We're finishing this together.
Fuckin' dipshit!
Go die in a ditch!
What?! The tires are
worn down already?!
That beanpole's riding has
turned these tires to shit!
You can't be serious?! I bet everything I had on winning here today!
To hell with relying
on others after this!
I'll go pro my own way,
and I'll do it for Tomoyo!
But I've gotta win first!
Ichinose's bike.
Just who I've been waiting for.
These tires are done for! They're stopping me from going on the throttle out of the corners.
All because of his shitty driving!
What?!
Are you serious?!
It's over...
For both my summer...
And my dream...
It's the end...
of everything.
He crashed?!
Don't gimme that shit!
He's the last person who'd ever
do that! There's no way he would!
Ah, but still...
Gun, take it easy!
Hey, you!
Are you okay?
Don't touch me...
Don't touch me!
Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing Team is
the race leader going into the 69th lap.
Murakami, #5, is back in second, and Yamada is back in third.
Thank you.
And here comes Hijiri, walking
his bike around the final corner.
It's so heavy...
And here was me thinking racing bikes were
designed to be light, but it's so damn heavy...
That said, why...
Why are my legs
movin' on their own?
Even if I bring it back to the pits,
there ain't a thing they can do about it.
I can tell that much.
It's so far...
How come the pit
lane's so damn long...?
I can hardly even see straight...
Feels like my heart's about
to jump outta my chest...
I know I can quit now,
but like hell I'm gonna...
I'm sure that beanpole's
waiting for me...
And until he gets it,
there's no way in hell I'm stopping...
You can do it, Hideyoshi!
Hijiri, you're almost there!
Don't give up!
It's all yours...
Beanpole!
Yeah, it's mine alright...
You'll never believe it!
Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing has come off on the s-bends and lost his lead!
With this, Murakami on bike
#5 takes the top position!
Ai, when this race is over,
let's go to the beach.
Yeah, let's go!
Whoa! Koma's back in the
race after swapping in for Hijiri!
But with all the repairs,
he's a whole lap behind!
Ibe of Hamamatsu Racing also managed to drag his bike back to the pits!
Here come the mechanics!
What will they make of it?!
Don't push yourself
too hard, Princess.
Murakami leads into the 72nd lap and we've still got 44 bikes on the track.
The lineup of the top group
is really getting shaken up!
With injuries like these, I'll try to stay on course for at least 15 minutes.
Matsui on bike #3 is
coming out of the pits.
But he's more than a
lap behind first place.
And Koma of the Ichinose Racing Team is
charging down the main straight and after Matsui.
Though, since they've both had accidents,
they're both lagging behind the battle for first place.
Let's hope they give it
their all until the very end!
Not a chance. No way
they're gaining a whole lap.
But that #16 is crazy fast!
He's really closing
the gap on #3.
It's Mi!
Gun!
He carves through the
wind like nobody else can.
He was like that
back then too...
Some would say
you're born for this.
You've grown ever faster...
And you've done it
without looking back...
I never thought I'd be
able to keep up with you.
But I've always been
watching you from behind, Gun.
It wasn't love I felt
for you, but admiration.
For their final rider change, Suzuka Riding is
replacing Murakami with Onozuka, their ace rider.
Onozuka on bike #5 is now in the top position, and I don't think he's going anywhere.
Oh, wait! What's this?!
Matsui on bike #3 is in 7th and has just
clocked in a lap time of 2 minutes 33.84!
And Koma on bike
#16 isn't far behind!
His time is 2 minutes...
and 32.74 seconds!
He broke the 32 second barrier!
Wow!
Matsui and Koma are
exiting the final corner!
What's wrong with you?!
Why are you rooting for him?!
Are you really that stupid?!
What can he possibly do now?!
He doesn't stand a chance at catching up!
What's with this guy?
He's the one that made #16 crash.
Throw something
at him, will ya?
You idiot!
Who threw that?!
Please stop that! It's dangerous! Please stop throwing things!
With 40 minutes to go,
Onozuka on #5 enters his 83rd lap.
Matsui and Koma on lap 83 and have finally caught
up to Hanakawa in 5th place around the s-bends.
Matsui cuts in on
the cambered corner.
Damn it!
After overtaking Hanakawa on bike #7, Matsui
and Koma have once again climbed the rankings.
No blocks seem to
stop their combination!
That's Matsui for you! He cuts
past Gouda on bike #21!
Whoa! Matsui's gone wide
and Koma takes his chance!
And #16 overtakes #3!
That kid's got drive. Things
are really starting to heat up.
What?!
Ichikawa, if Gun keeps
the pace of his last lap—
He'll make his way
to the front again.
And #3 makes a break for it!
Damn it... I'll overtake you
as many times as I have to!
Even if he is a runt,
he still got the bike back to me.
He was battered, broken,
and could hardly breathe.
And you thought I'd run out of steam here?! No fuckin' way!
At last, Yamada in 3rd starts feeling
bikes #3 and #16 nip at his heels!
Both are trying to break into the lead with bike 6 between them!
Finally, they entered their 90th lap! With just
under 13 minutes until the checkered flag is waved!
Bikes #3 and #16 are closing
in on Shigeno in second place.
They're closing the gap
through the Casio triangle!
Now the three bikes are exiting the
final corner! It's anybody's game!
I'm scared... but
I'm not sure why...
This is amazing!
Nobody can keep up with
Hamamatsu on the back straight!
But #65 is still fast!
Last year, Shigeno on bike #65
had to retire after a crash.
But this year, he's aiming
for the championship!
The leader, Onozuka,
is 20 seconds ahead!
Oh, but here comes Koma!
He's giving it his all,
but he can't break out!
I'm not that easy.
Goddammit!
Next time, you're mine!
Whoa, Koma's
going in too hot!
What?!
It's a crash!
Wait, he regained control!
Now Koma's driving like a true GP racer!
In five minutes, the checkered flag will
fly for this four-hour life-or-death race!
The race enters its final stretch!
There he is!
No doubt about it!
That's #5 in first place!
Bikes #3 and #16 are really
piling on the pressure!
Bike #5 can already feel
them breathing down his neck!
No way!
Those guys are something else.
I can hardly believe it...
I can hardly take my eyes off them...
I can't believe how cool they are...
It's all or nothin'! How
much cooler could they get?!
The final lap!
Onozuka is making a break for it,
but Matsui and Koma are close behind!
I've come too far to
be overtaken now!
Their only chance
will be on 130R!
Whoever takes
the inside line wins!
Damn it!
You can't get much
more inside than this!
We're moments away from
seeing the checkered flag.
Who'll be in the lead on
the exit of the final corner?!
Will it be Koma, or Matsui?!
And #16's in the lead!
The sea! I can see the sea
just beyond the first corner!
My throat's so dry... it's killing me.
Matsui is attempting a breakout!
Will he manage?! Will he?!
Will it be Koma or Matsui?!
And across the line!
And that's all she wrote!
The winners are the
Hijiri-Koma pair on bike #16!
We did it!
The Ichinose Racing Team!
Way to go!
That was amazing!
Hiro...
This can't be real...
You're really somethin',
you know that?
A man among men.
Look who's talkin'. If you weren't
my partner, then we wouldn't...
be standing here right now.
I can't believe he'd say that... a man who'd
rather drop dead than give me a compliment...
He was a good guy.
Not the sort you'd
find anywhere else.
Why did I always
hate him so much?
He was the best guy I ever met...
Beanpole...
Beanpole, you've gotta
get faster than that.
Hideyoshi...
Hideyoshi... I'll get faster...
That's what you wanted, right?
I know what I heard...
Gun, you gonna enter
the final race at Tsukuba?
You'll have to for a B-class license.
I've already missed
the entry deadline.
Don't worry, it's been dealt with.
Hideyoshi said you'd probably
come around, so I signed you up.
He said that?
By the way, Gun, how about you ride
around on Hideyoshi's bike from now on?
It should be an easy fix.
No.
I could never do that.
Gun, what are you doing?
His blood, sweat, and
tears went into this Katana.
You think I could ride that?!
Gun, don't do it!
Nobody's riding it anymore.
This was the only thing
Hideyoshi left behind.
What will we say
to Tomoyo now?
I couldn't bear to let
someone else ride it,
but I also couldn't bear to see it gather dust in the corner of some garage...
It's better this way...
They can be together now.
It's all yours, Hideyoshi...
Not once did I manage
to overtake your Katana...
But you quit while you
were ahead, you dumbass...
With this, my memories
of you are gone.
I'll forget you in no time.
See you around, Hideyoshi.
Don't forget to give 'em hell!
Even if it's been raining all morning,
and even if it feels like it's
gonna be damp all day,
I won't let the mirror reflecting
my sleepy face go cloudy.
Don't go thinking I won't pick
out my favorite clothes!
My bobby socks and my
Mary Jane shoes...
always give me a spring in my step.
When a nice pair of red-calf
gloves fit you perfectly,
you worry more about your
looks than your feelings!
You're not going anywhere if you keep
your heart closed, so it's up to you.
My path ahead is uncertain, but I keep
walking as time won't wait for me.
I've always been afraid to disappoint.
But if I have the courage to face it,
my shyness and shame won't hold me back,
and I could throw away my old smile.
Because my new smile will finally be me!
Everything reflected in your eyes
can shine. It's all up to you.
Though my path ahead is uncertain,
just like the falling raindrops...
Never stop dancing in your dreams!
NONSTOP DANCER!