He's fast...
That runt's not fooling around.
This isn't working. Forget
overtaking him, I can barely keep up.
He always pulls
away on the corners.
Damn it! What
the hell's going on?!
I'm already riding on the limit.
So why can't I catch up?!
Crap!
That was one hell
of a crash, huh?
At least you're still in
one piece, Beanpole.
I see how it is.
Then lemme give you some advice:
your riding sucks.
What?!
I know riders can be clumsy, but if they end
up wrecking their bike, then they ain't shit.
I'm nothing like you
young rich kids!
I'd rather break my
neck than my bike.
With driving like that, the only time you'll overtake me is in your wildest dreams!
It takes everything you've got
just to not die in a crash.
That asshole...
The Legend of Revving Engines
The center line continues
all the way to the horizon.
As you rest your chin on your hand,
I can't take my eyes off you.
So before you fall asleep,
please let me know one thing...
Would you kiss me
for longer than your other girl?
Whenever you speed up,
you become like the wind.
And I can only ride behind you
when you're lonely.
You still keep your heart closed to me,
but one of these days,
I'll make it mine.
I can see your innocent
smile through the sunbeams,
but I can tell your facade
is about to come crashing down.
What would I do if you cried?
I miss you. I love you.
It hurts to be apart.
A sunshower...
Don't say another word.
Stand up!
Bow!
It's so cute!
Ai! Hurry up or we're
leaving your butt behind!
Wait up!
Ignition.
Vroom! Vroom, vrrroom!
Vroom, vroom!
I can't believe you, Ai!
Eating lunch out in the schoolyard has
been more fun lately, or so it seems.
Let's sit here.
I've been dying to eat...
Huh?
Ai, what are you doing?
C'mon, let's eat.
Boo!
A monster!
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Mind if I eat my lunch here?
Do whatever you want.
I'm just trying to sleep.
It's okay,
I won't bother you.
I've never been good
at this kind of thing...
Damn it!
Where do you think
you're going, bitch?!
No!
Someone help!
Hands off the girl.
What's it got to
do with you, huh?!
Doesn't matter what. Worry about
how I'm easy to piss off first.
H-Hey...
You'll regret this!
Excuse me...
I don't suppose you're...
One of those delinquent types?
I've always had a thing for them.
Delinquents, I mean.
Hopefully I'm not
asking for too much,
but if you know someone
who's good in a fight,
good at riding bikes,
is really tall,
and has a gentle smile
with perfect white teeth...
My!
Oh, but he can't be ugly.
And if this special someone drives a bike with
400cc or more, you just have to introduce me!
I'm Ito Ai, I'm in class 1-6.
How stupid can you be?!
You really think there's
someone like that, huh?!
Um...
This is a 750cc, isn't it?
Talk about impressive!
It's much bigger
than the Road Pal!
I've always wanted to ride
something like this, even just once.
Y'know, I saw one in a movie
called High Teen Boogie.
The lead character in it
was a bike gang leader.
He was so cool I could die!
I decided I'd find my own gang leader,
and fall in love with him, like in the movies!
My lunch got squashed.
Look, I'm tryin' to sleep here.
Oh, sorry.
I won't say another word.
So don't worry.
Oh no!
Hey, you mind if my
friends eat with u—
Oh, Ichikawa!
Welcome back.
Sorry to drop in like this.
It must be important
for you to be here this late.
It's almost time for the
club's regular circuit, you see.
I need to get every machine
checked over by then.
Oh, by the way, we don't have a whole lotta participants this time round.
If you know anyone,
feel free to bring 'em along.
Where is it this time?
It's Tsukuba Circuit,
your favorite.
Oh, and by the way,
I don't mind you riding
around at this time of night,
but don't go doing
anything stupid out there.
That's all I ask.
I know, I know.
If I get myself in no fit state to get married,
I'm all yours, Ichikawa.
Hey, come and
get a look at this.
Huh?
Isn't that Mi?
So whenever I couldn't find you,
you'd be hiding around here, huh?
That's not how it is...
Yeah, right. Like I'd
believe that, you horndog.
Still, I can hardly believe it.
She has some real nice legs...
But then you see her flying around on
a motorbike, hanging on for dear life...
Which reminds me, Gun,
your bike fixed yet?
Yeah.
Mi asked if we wanted to go
to Tsukuba Circuit on Sunday.
We're going, right?
You can't! Anything but the bike!
Shut it! He's had this
comin' for a long time!
And breakin' his bike's the only
way we're gonna feel any better!
You can't!
C'mon, get out of the way!
You bitch!
No!
Ouch!
Why, you little...
- Damn it!
- No, get off me!
Help, he's gonna kill me!
Now's your chance!
Go do it!
Alright!
Hold it right there!
If you so much as touch my CB,
I'll make sure you regret it!
Move it!
Damn it.
You got away with
a mild concussion.
Not counting those scratches on
your knees, elbows, and forehead.
You really are a strange one...
I can't believe you'd get
yourself hurt protecting my CB.
I don't really know why I did it.
But I just didn't want them
to get their hands on it.
That bike was
shiny and beautiful.
Thank you.
My bike would've been a
lot worse for wear without you.
You said you wanted to ride a bike, or something like that, right?
Fine.
If it's only for a while,
I can give you a ride.
You really mean it?
"Auto racing auxiliary facilities"
I wish we could've rode
together a little longer.
So this is the circuit, huh? It's so
much bigger than I thought it'd be.
Best feeling ever. My spine's already tingling just from being here.
Gun!
Sure took your sweet time, huh?
Hey.
Hello.
There's a good reason for this.
But it's a long story,
so I'm not gonna go into it.
Well, that's just how it is, okay?
Yeah, right.
Now who's the horndog?
Nice of you to show.
I've been in need of a good race.
Am I okay to ride?
I know I'm about to race,
but don't go wandering off.
Do your best, okay?
Sure thing.
That's him. He's the one
the Princess brought along.
That kid pisses me off.
I don't know who that rich kid is...
but how about we...
'show him the ropes?'
Listen up, Gun! It's your first time here,
so go easy on the throttle!
Just get a feel for the course!
Go!
What the hell is wrong
with those guys?!
It's like they were waiting
for him to take off.
Those two are some of
the best drivers in our club,
but their manners
need a lot of work.
What are those jerks up to?
Those jerks...
You won't get away with that!
I can't believe that guy...
I was sure he was
gonna go flying there.
Blocking a newcomer from the inside line... talk about cheap.
But you've gotta give him credit,
it barely even fazed him.
This might get interesting.
This greenhorn is trying
to make a move on me.
I'll drive hard and
open up the gap.
He's lookin' good! Damn good!
Gun blew past two of them on one lap!
W-What the hell is going on?
My bike's at its limit,
but I can't pull away.
What do you think, Ichikawa?
He doesn't even have the basics down,
but he's damn fast.
Doesn't exactly
seem like a beginner.
It's like he's walking a tightrope
on a windy day without a harness.
You gonna take a chance on him?
Haven't decided yet.
As he is now, he's more
like a highway racer.
This is insane! It took me ages to
even get anywhere near that lap time!
And yet, this little punk...
I'm faster... I can take him.
Damn it all! It wasn't
supposed to go like this!
No way am I gonna
lose to some greenho—
Dumbass. You're going in too fast.
Godammit! I ended up screwing
up my own throttle work.
Hey, speed racer!
You're comin' next time, right?
It'll be Suzuka or Fuji next time!
Maybe this is just me thinkin', but I don't
think you've got those hairpins down yet!
Don't go dyin' on us, okay?!
Sure.
Later!
Is this what people
call bike buddies?
You're welcome too, little lady!
S-Sure thing!
Wow! I can't believe it!
Before I knew it,
I threw up a peace sign.
Whenever I'm with Gun,
I get to see tons of new stuff!
It's a brave new world!
Today, we have a new
student starting in our class.
This is Hijiri.
Please, introduce yourself.
I'm from Osaka.
Hijiri Hideyoshi's the name.
I'm all about guts
and nothin' else!
My bad habits are...
I get into fights all the time.
While I don't always start 'em,
I always make sure to finish 'em.
You're that dipshit
from the other day!
Who're you calling a
dipshit, you little runt?!
Don't gimme that shit!
The hell are you doing here?!
Ain't it obvious?!
I transferred to this school!
Hey, Teach, I'm done! No way am I
staying in the same class as this dipshit!
W-What's wrong with you?!
What's the big deal? I'll see
the principal myself if I have to!
You're so full of yourself!
Go on, get yourself
expelled for all I care!
W-What's that?! You tryin'
to pick a fight with me, huh?!
Who's pickin' a fight
with who, dumbass?!
You're the stupidest
guy I've ever met!
Even a gorilla wouldn't
pick a fight with me!
No shit! How'd one of them turn
up to school, you caveman?!
Who are you calling a caveman?
You little monkey man!
What'd ya say?!
Sure was heating up in there, huh?
I thought you were gonna
start swinging for each other.
The reason I can't stand that little runt
is because I lost to him on a bike before.
So he's really that fast, huh?!
Yeah.
So we're not settling this with our fists,
we're settling it on our bikes.
So, what's your plan?
Ain't it obvious?
I'm racing that little runt again.
Gun!
I need help!
Miyuki has... Miyuki has—
Something happened to Mi?
Some strange guys showed up and
forced Miyuki in the car with them!
Satoru, what's the
meaning of this?
It's about that beanpole
from the other day.
And we just need you out
of the picture for a while.
Your skull must be
thicker than your helmet.
What was that?
I don't know why you're
so bent out of shape,
but it takes real scum to
try something like this.
Bottom of the barrel.
The rumors were right. You really are just
some rich kid without a care in the world.
I don't think you quite
realize the situation you're in.
Do you, m'lady?
You bitch...
You sure they
said the riverbank?
Yeah.
Hiro, get movin'!
Don't have to ask me twice!
Why're you looking
at me like that?
You always have that look. You think you can see right into my head, don't you?!
When I... joined the Ichinose Racing Team,
you were still in middle-school,
but I couldn't help being drawn to you.
Hands so delicate,
yet so steady with the machine,
and your form through the corners...
I'd always been watching you.
But...
since you've got money, you think
you can look down on other people.
Am I wrong?
This is the first I've heard of it.
Besides, money, status...
aren't you the one
who's hung up on them?
Shut the hell up!
I hadn't planned
on doing this today,
but... but now I wanna
teach you a lesson.
Hang in there, Ichinose Miyuki.
If someone so much as touches you, I'll make them regret being born!
Shit...
A CB750F!
Gun!
I can't believe that
punk would show up.
We'll get our own back
for the other day.
What's with you, punk?!
Eat this!
Hey, asshole!
What'd you do to the girl?! Tell me!
Talk!
Dumbass, we didn't do shit!
Correct answer!
Get outta the way!
Move it, assholes!
Damn you... how could
you do that to Mi?!
You'll pay for this!
What? You done already?
Come back in ten years, kid.
Damn it... I'd rather die than
let you get away with this!
You kids can say just
about anything, huh?
Damn it... that guy a
monster or somethin'?
He's a dead man!
See you in hell!
Damn it!
Damn it...
You're not going anywhere!
Damn it... I thought he
was just some rich kid...
How wrong could I be?
I-I was...
I was actually kinda relieved
when I heard your bike...
Any longer, and I might've done
something I could never take back.
On your feet...
Now listen up, I'll never show myself in front of her as long as I live.
But I'm not giving up on riding.
If we happen to meet on the circuit...
how about we settle things for good?
Sure, but you won't stand a chance.
Mi?
You're not hurt, are you?
No need to cry anymore.
Is there?
The worst is already
behind us, see?
Hiro...
As a boy, do you
think I'm ugly?
N-Not a chance...
You're real cute,
and smart too.
And I... I...
I... like you.
What do you want, dipshit?
You trying to pick a fight again?
Tomorrow morning, 4:30. I'll be waiting for you at the same mountain pass as before.
Fine by me.
'Bout time I dealt with you.
Shit... At the next hairpin,
I'm staying on him, no matter what.
What an idiot.
This is no different from last time.
That guy's got a
screw loose for sure!
He jumped his bike to
get it back under control.
Nipping at my heels.
What's with this guy?
How's he still on my tail
with a driving style like that?
Someone's chasing us?
What the heck?!
What's that machine?
Challenging us both, huh?
I'm ready when you are!
What?!
Wanna occupy the inner line from the get-go?
Like hell I'm letting you!
They overtook me!
Who the hell is that guy?!
Damn... that was smooth.
I didn't even get to breathe.
You fired up, Beanpole?
If you're gonna go, then go.
Now's your chance, dipshit.
Don't blame me
if you crash out!
You really thought I'd back down?!
I'm not goin' down without a fight!
Dumbass, you think you
can corner at that speed?!
Y-You gotta be kiddin' me?!
That's gonna hurt in the morning.
You don't hold back, huh?
Didn't think anybody was
stupid enough to do that.
Neither did I, but it
kinda killed the mood.
Mornin'!
I-It's a chick...
Well, if it isn't Mi...
Wait, so you didn't
know it was me?
Are you sure
you're okay to ride?
You didn't show at school
yesterday, so I was worried sick.
I skipped yesterday.
That's one hell of a machine.
What's it called?
Doesn't even know Formula 1 models.
I'd be ashamed to be that stupid.
Keep it to yourself!
You've always gotta
say something, dontcha?
There's not much of you to look at,
but you're still an eyesore.
What's that, dipshit?!
Got something to say, ankle-biter?
Sorry to interrupt,
but I've got places to be.
The mountains will have eroded by the time you're done arguing.
I'm glad I listened to Hiro
and came all the way out here.
I never thought people with skills
like that would end up at my school.
Supposing...
Supposing I get those two together,
they'd make the ultimate combination.
Next summer, things are gonna get
interesting at Suzuka, and that's for sure.
It sure is snowing hard, huh?
Guess I won't be riding any time soon.
That bike's the only thing on
your mind, isn't it, Hideyoshi?
Y'know, I heard there was a really
bad crash on that pass you drive on.
Some things never change.
There are a lot of idiots
on the road, after all.
If it's that dangerous there,
then maybe you should stop going.
I'll be fine.
Hideyoshi!
I... get kinda scared sometimes...
Especially when I'm waiting for you to come back from your morning ride... I just think...
I just think,
if something ever hap—
Tomoyo!
Let's go already.
Don't get so worked
up over nothin'.
Tomoyo, please understand,
I'm doing this for you.
What do you want?
What's with you?
Whatcha starin' for?!
Lookin' at you makes
me wanna hurl!
Who lit your fuse today?!
C'mon, you wanna piece of me?!
What? So that's
why you're all sulky?
You two belong in
kindergarten, that's for sure.
Gun! Hiro!
Come here, there's
something I wanna talk about.
You know about the 4-hour endurance race
held at Suzuka over the summer, don't you?
Yeah, and I know about the
8-hour race the day after.
What about it?
I was thinking of entering it under the Ichinose Racing Team.
You serious?
That's amazing!
D-Do you really mean that?!
Yeah, and I need
three more riders.
You serious about this?
We'll race as two pairs,
and I'll be driver number four.
Count me in! Even if I've gotta
work with that stupid beanpole!
What was that?!
Ya heard me! I don't jus' race
for fun like you rich kids!
Like hell I'm working with him!
Gun!
Please enter the race,
just this once.
Get up already.
Gun!
When did I say I wouldn't?
Ta-da~!
It only took six hours to get here from Tokyo, but we're finally at Suzuka!
It's wonderful!
Suzuka Circuit is even
bigger than I thought!
I want each of you to practice
with your own goal in mind.
One more thing, we won't be measuring your times until this afternoon.
So, for the time being, none of
you will know how long you take.
But why not?!
That's just boring!
Trust you to object.
This rule was made
specifically for you.
By trying too hard to lower your time,
your corner entries will suffer,
your bike will become unstable, your corner exit
will go to shit, and your times would just get worse.
I know it's your first time
at this kind of event,
and I know it'll
go to your head,
so, instead, I want you
to focus on your pace.
Okay...
Dumbass. You really thought
you'd post a time that easily?
Suzuka ain't that easy.
I can take him!
Ah... he's already gone...
What am I going to do with them?
I told them to take it easy on the first lap.
His time on the West course has improved by two seconds since this morning.
Come to think of it, Gun's been sticking
like glue to the guy in the white helmet.
He's trying to learn the lines
from a more experienced rider.
Ah, it's finally over!
We'll settle this later!
What's with that guy?!
Oh, yeah, he said he
had somewhere to be.
I'll go change,
be back in a sec.
S-Sorry!
Dad, Mom, it's
been a while, huh?
Tomoyo is doing great.
We're still getting along fine,
so don't worry about us.
I was at Suzuka, and since
I was in the neighborhood...
I thought I'd best come
see you before I went back.
I didn't have time to buy you
any flowers, so sorry 'bout that.
What?! I got a flat?!
That's strange, how'd I get
one all the way out here?
Yes, this is the
Hijiri household.
Yes?
- Dad! Mom!
Dad!
Mom!
Well then, I gotta go.
Don't worry about
me on the way back.
I'm not the type of rider who'd have a
crash on the Tomei Expressway, after all.
I've been saying it's too cold out to be wearing
a short-sleeved sailor uniform for a few days now,
but now that the Sun's out,
you get reminded of how hot it really is.
Though, when the boys disappear,
we do something a little unladylike.
While summer was hiding behind the rain clouds,
we could tell it was just around the corner.
Gun!
You didn't bring an umbrella?
Nah, It wasn't
raining this morning.
Still, everyone knows to bring
an umbrella at this time of year.
The rain never
bothered me anyway.
If you're out on your bike in the rain,
yeah, it's no fun at first, but the drive home
feels much better when you're soaked through.
It's almost the big day, Hideyoshi.
That race has been the only thing
on my mind for the last six months.
I don't really know much about races,
but all that matters to me is that you're safe.
If your bike is maintained and you stick to the rules, safety won't be an issue.
If I perform well there,
it'll be my shortcut to going pro.
Hideyoshi!
Don't worry about it,
just let me do my thing.
Oh, the rain stopped.
Whoa, it's so red!
It's beautiful...
Summer's here already.
The center line continues
all the way to the horizon.
As you rest your chin on your hand,
I can't take my eyes off you.
So before you fall asleep,
please let me know one thing...
"Racers to starting positions"
Would you kiss me for
longer than your other girl?
Get a move on, #2 rider.
What was that?
Cause I'm #1, obviously.
They only brought you here to prop up the machine for me, dumbass!
Oh, is that so? Then
I'd better get going!
What are you doing, Gun?!
Oh shut up, will ya?
That little shit...
Only 40 more seconds under the scorching Sun
before the race is underway.
The light will turn yellow
ten seconds before start.
And then the signal will change to green and a go sign will be raised.
The eyes of the
world are on Suzuka.
And now, second by second,
the start time is approaching.
Now, at last, only ten seconds left!
The signal turned yellow!
Drivers on their marks!
We have 60 vehicles participating today!
The light turns green and the
drivers make a run for their bikes!
Whoa, an accident just off the start line!
Down goes bike number 37!
The lead group heads into
the corner side-by-side.
In the lead, holding onto his
pole position, #1, Okamoto!
Now they're entering the s-bends!
Whoa! #3 makes a break for it!
Bike #3, who had been neck-and-neck with #1, makes an overtake and seizes the lead!
Our opening lap is as
intense as any sprint race!
As soon as they leave the cambered corner,
the top group will approach the uphill section!
And the competition for
the top is really heating up!
Having just passed through the Dunlop gate,
the top group is disappearing into the West course!
We're entering lap number seven.
No change to the top with bike #3, Matsui of
the Hamamatsu Racing Team, leading the pack.
Onto the second group:
Ooya on bike #2 and Onozuka on bike #5 are really fighting for their position.
Maehara on bike #34 seems to
have come off around Degner.
More info on that to come!
So, how's our team doing?
Right, Hideyoshi is in 17th, with a lap time of 2 minutes 38.16 seconds.
What about the princess?
Being measured as we speak.
29th place. Time is 2 minutes 41.25 seconds.
Do you think they're
a bit overpace?
Gun, how do you manage
to remain so calm?
Who said I was?
I'm dying to get out there.
If I don't get on that bike,
I think I'm gonna explode.
I don't care how fast these other guys are,
I'm not losing to any of 'em.
No changes to the lead with Matsui on bike #3 leading the pack into lap 12.
He just clocked in
another smooth lap!
My watch has a time split of
three seconds for second place.
As you can see,
he's gained a huge lead!
But #2, Ooya, is hot on his heels!
And Onozuka isn't far
behind on bike #5!
It's too hot... my throat's so dry.
I'd hoped the wind would
cool me down a little,
but with the heat reflecting off the asphalt, it's like I'm driving into an inferno.
It's a little better if
I stay beneath the cowl,
but it's still like I've been thrown into a frying pan where someone's turning up the heat.
It's hot... so hot...
Alright, get ready to swap drivers.
Ai, can you get the pit
sign out for Hideyoshi?
Sure.
Haga, get the charger ready.
Okay!
Hagino, the board!
On it right now!
And remember, once we're done
with Hideyoshi, it's the princess' turn.
Gun, are you ready?
I was born ready!
Leave it to me!
It's lap 18 and the leader, Matsui,
on bike #3 is coming in hot to the pit lane.
Their bike will be refueled
and their riders swapped.
And Onozuka,
#5, isn't far behind!
As a result, the race leader becomes Ooya on bike #2, as he flies past the stands.
Followed by Yamada on bike #6.
Hamamatsu Racing Team's
pit work is as fast as ever!
And they're back on
track within five seconds.
Ibe, the rider
replacing Matsui, is off!
And here comes
Hijiri on bike #16!
Gun, keep it together.
I know, but I've been
waiting a long time for this.
Here, Hideyoshi!
That's payback from the start line!
That asshole...
Gun, what the hell was that?!
Oh, shut up!
This is a great pace.
How can you not love it?
Charging is done!
Good. Hiro, get going!
Are you okay, Miyuki?
Thanks, I'll be fine.
The race has been
going for almost an hour.
And it's maintained its
sprint-race-like pace!
Bike #3, Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing is
in the lead and is entering his 23rd lap.
But Murakami, #5, from Suzuka Riding is about six seconds behind.
The lineup was just as we predicted.
But something's happening
in the second group!
A rider just clocked in a blistering
time of 2 minutes 35 seconds!
Ichinose Racing's #16 is really putting the pressure on the other riders!
You're so cool, #16!
The crowd's more excited to see
me than that reckless little runt!
Koma, on bike #16, just did a lap
faster than Ibe who's leading the race.
Whoa there! Bikes #11 and #50
collide on the entry to the chicane!
Will Koma get caught up in it?!
And he avoids them!
What's Koma's lap time
going to be now?!
Koma's time just reported to us is... 2 minutes, 34.91 seconds!
He's amazing! He broke
the 34 second barrier!
That dude's crazy!
Who is that guy?!
Check the entry list.
It says Koma on #16.
That'd be the Ichinose Racing Team: Koma Gun and Hijiri Hideyoshi?
They're both only 17!
They're so young!
Wait, they're still
in high school?!
Now Koma's making a move
on Yamada in 4th place!
If you give him a target to
chase, he's unbelievably fast.
In other words, if there's nobody in sight, you can't light a flame under him.
Maybe that's why he can't
drive like this all the time.
Has he always had this level of insight?
Or has instinct brought him this far?
Whether it's on the pass or on the circuit,
chasing and then blowing past them is his style.
And when that happens,
he's insanely fast.
The guy's a natural sprinter.
Alright, Hideyoshi, we're
changing riders again. Get ready.
Alright!
Gun!
What's the deal with
you and Hideyoshi?!
It's not like it's saving us any
time in the pits, you moron.
That's just how I say hello.
Same goes for him too, I guess.
Matsui from the Hamamatsu
Racing Team is still in first.
And Okamoto from Green
Grass is just behind.
Onozuka on bike #5 is in third, but Hijiri
on bike #16 is making use of his slipstream.
Oh? That one seems interesting.
That #16.
He's my sort of rider.
Bike #16?
Oh, you mean the other rider?
That stupidly fast kamikaze novice?
No, I mean the shorter
one who's riding right now.
Can't you see why?
Among the 40,000 spectators here,
how many do you think know what he's doing?
Five? Maybe two or
three would be generous.
While they're polar opposites,
if those two geniuses are a team,
I think we could see #16 winning today.
That little shit
thinks he's so smart.
That beanpole's riding it too hard on
the engine, it can't take much more.
All I've gotta do is maintain our current position and not put too much strain on the engine.
I'm able to keep up with the bike in front at only 80% power.
I'm gonna preserve as much
of the engine's power as I can,
then it's all down to that beanpole and his explosive driving!
That's strange. The princess
hasn't come around yet.
And there's no way
she'd miss the pit-in sign.
Do you think something
happened to her?
Are you okay?
Who's that guy?
What just happened to me?
O-Ouch...
Corner 130R.
That's right, I came off.
I've gotta keep riding!
At least your
bones are still intact.
Can you keep racing?
I don't know... it hurts like
hell whenever I move it.
And I've lost all strength in it.
I see.
Courage is needed to race, but a different kind of courage is needed to retire.
I'll respect whatever
decision you make.
You two just have to work
it out amongst yourselves.
Hiro...
Let's do it, Mi.
We'll adjust our time splits to
keep your driving to a minimum.
I'll give it everything I've got.
We're finishing this together.
Fuckin' dipshit!
Go die in a ditch!
What?! The tires are
worn down already?!
That beanpole's riding has
turned these tires to shit!
You can't be serious?! I bet everything I had on winning here today!
To hell with relying
on others after this!
I'll go pro my own way,
and I'll do it for Tomoyo!
But I've gotta win first!
These tires are done for! They're stopping me from going on the throttle out of the corners.
All because of his shitty driving!
What?!
Are you serious?!
It's over...
For both my summer...
And my dream...
It's the end...
of everything.
He crashed?!
Don't gimme that shit!
He's the last person who'd ever
do that! There's no way he would!
Ah, but still...
Gun, take it easy!
Hey, you!
Are you okay?
Don't touch me...
Don't touch me!
Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing Team is
the race leader going into the 69th lap.
Murakami, #5, is back in second, and Yamada is back in third.
Thank you.
And here comes Hijiri, walking
his bike around the final corner.
It's so heavy...
And here was me thinking racing bikes were
designed to be light, but it's so damn heavy...
That said, why...
Why are my legs
movin' on their own?
Even if I bring it back to the pits,
there ain't a thing they can do about it.
I can tell that much.
It's so far...
How come the pit
lane's so damn long...?
I can hardly even see straight...
Feels like my heart's about
to jump outta my chest...
I know I can quit now,
but like hell I'm gonna...
I'm sure that beanpole's
waiting for me...
And until he gets it,
there's no way in hell I'm stopping...
You can do it, Hideyoshi!
Hijiri, you're almost there!
Don't give up!
It's all yours...
Beanpole!
Yeah, it's mine alright...
You'll never believe it!
Ibe from Hamamatsu Racing has come off on the s-bends and lost his lead!
With this, Murakami on bike
#5 takes the top position!
Ai, when this race is over,
let's go to the beach.
Yeah, let's go!
Whoa! Koma's back in the
race after swapping in for Hijiri!
But with all the repairs,
he's a whole lap behind!
Ibe of Hamamatsu Racing also managed to drag his bike back to the pits!
Here come the mechanics!
What will they make of it?!
Don't push yourself
too hard, Princess.
Murakami leads into the 72nd lap and we've still got 44 bikes on the track.
The lineup of the top group
is really getting shaken up!
With injuries like these, I'll try to stay on course for at least 15 minutes.
Matsui on bike #3 is
coming out of the pits.
But he's more than a
lap behind first place.
And Koma of the Ichinose Racing Team is
charging down the main straight and after Matsui.
Though, since they've both had accidents,
they're both lagging behind the battle for first place.
Let's hope they give it
their all until the very end!
Not a chance. No way
they're gaining a whole lap.
But that #16 is crazy fast!
He's really closing
the gap on #3.
It's Mi!
Gun!
For their final rider change, Suzuka Riding is
replacing Murakami with Onozuka, their ace rider.
Onozuka on bike #5 is now in the top position, and I don't think he's going anywhere.
Oh, wait! What's this?!
Matsui on bike #3 is in 7th and has just
clocked in a lap time of 2 minutes 33.84!
And Koma on bike
#16 isn't far behind!
His time is 2 minutes...
and 32.74 seconds!
He broke the 32 second barrier!
Wow!
Matsui and Koma are
exiting the final corner!
With 40 minutes to go,
Onozuka on #5 enters his 83rd lap.
Matsui and Koma on lap 83 have finally caught up
to Hanakawa in 5th place around the s-bends.
Matsui cuts in on
the cambered corner.
Damn it!
After overtaking Hanakawa on bike #7, Matsui
and Koma have once again climbed the rankings.
No blocks seem to
stop their combination!
That's Matsui for you! He cuts
past Gouda on bike #21!
Whoa! Matsui's gone wide
and Koma takes his chance!
And #16 overtakes #3!
That kid's got drive.
Things are really starting to heat up.
What?!
Ichikawa, if Gun keeps
the pace of his last lap—
He'll make his way
to the front again.
And #3 makes a break for it!
Damn it... I'll overtake you
as many times as I have to!
Even if he is a runt,
he still got the bike back to me.
He was battered, broken,
and could hardly breathe.
And you thought I'd run out of steam here?! No fuckin' way!
At last, Yamada in 3rd starts feeling
bikes #3 and #16 nip at his heels!
Both are trying to break into the lead with bike 6 between them!
Finally, they entered their 90th lap! With just
under 13 minutes until the checkered flag is waved!
Bikes #3 and #16 are closing
in on Shigeno in second place.
They're closing the gap
through the Casio triangle!
Now the three bikes are exiting the
final corner! It's anybody's game!
I'm scared... but
I'm not sure why...
This is amazing!
Nobody can keep up with
Hamamatsu on the back straight!
But #65 is still fast!
Last year, Shigeno on bike #65
had to retire after a crash.
But this year, he's aiming
for the championship!
The leader, Onozuka,
is 20 seconds ahead!
Oh, but here comes Koma!
He's giving it his all,
but he can't break out!
I'm not that easy.
Goddammit!
Next time, you're mine!
Whoa, Koma's
going in too hot!
What?!
It's a crash!
Wait, he regained control!
Now Koma's driving like a true GP racer!
In five minutes, the checkered flag will
fly for this four-hour life-or-death race!
The race enters its final stretch!
There he is!
No doubt about it!
That's #5 in first place!
Bikes #3 and #16 are really
piling on the pressure!
Bike #5 can already feel
them breathing down his neck!
No way!
Those guys are something else.
I can hardly believe it...
I can hardly take my eyes off them...
I can't believe how cool they are...
It's all or nothin'! How
much cooler could they get?!
The final lap!
Onozuka is making a break for it,
but Matsui and Koma are close behind!
I've come too far to
be overtaken now!
Their only chance
will be on 130R!
Whoever takes
the inside line wins!
Damn it!
You can't get much
more inside than this!
We're moments away from
seeing the checkered flag.
Who'll be in the lead on
the exit of the final corner?!
Will it be Koma, or Matsui?!
And #16's in the lead!
The sea! I can see the sea
just beyond the first corner!
My throat's so dry... it's killing me.
Matsui is attempting a breakout!
Will he manage?! Will he?!
Will it be Koma or Matsui?!
And across the line!
And that's all she wrote!
The winners are the
Hijiri-Koma pair on bike #16!
We did it!
He really did it!
The Ichinose Racing Team!
Hiro...
Me, a specialist rider?
That's right.
They're called the
Hagiwara Racing Company.
The races they arrange make us
look like amateurs in comparison.
And those Hagiwara guys saw your performance at
the four-hour race and want you all to themselves.
They want me?
What do you say?
If you really do want to get into the racing scene, I don't think this is a bad offer.
Does this mean my
dream will come true?
But on one condition.
Condition?
The thing is, you'll need to get
promoted to B-class before year's end.
But if you pull out all the
stops in the remaining races,
they can recommend you
get promoted to B-class.
And what's more,
Hideo "Pops" Yoshimura...
After all this time...
my dream's finally coming true...
Tomoyo! You seen
my Katana keys?
Aren't they in
the usual place?
Why else would I be askin'?
Now that's strange,
I always leave them around here...
Hideyoshi, can't you
just skip this morning?
I mean, I could...
They say, if you can't find something before
going out, it's God's way of telling you something.
Are you listening
to me, Hideyoshi?
Dumbass, that's
jus' a superstition.
Oh? Found 'em!
There they are. Must've
dropped them 'round back.
Right, I'll see you later.
Ain't nothin' to worry about.
Hideyoshi...
I don't like the color
of that sky one bit...
The mountain pass
sure is great, huh?
It's somethin' else, alright.
That said, this is it for me.
This is the last time you'll
ever race me on the pass.
Startin' today,
this highway racer's finished.
I'm joining the big leagues.
He looks out of it.
What's gotten into him?
Thanks for everything,
and see you 'round, winding
roads of the mountain pass.
Wh-What's with you?
It's called a handshake, Beanpole.
But what for?!
Don't you worry.
You're one weird dude.
Thank you.
What's gotten into him today?
Wanna go? We can
take it nice and easy.
Yeah, nice and easy.
You're awfully lively for
some rich, little upstart!
I'm gonna beat you
on the pass this time!
In your dreams!
Didn't we just pass those guys?!
They're so fast!
You tryin' ta get
yourself killed, dipshit?!
That got the blood flowing!
It's too narrow!
Stop, Hideyoshi!
Wh—
Someone wiped out!
I can make it!
This can't be real...
You're really somethin',
you know that?
A man among men.
Look who's talkin'. If you weren't
my partner, then we wouldn't...
be standing here right now.
Hideyoshi...
Gun, you gonna enter
the final race at Tsukuba?
You'll have to for a B-class license.
I've already missed
the entry deadline.
Don't worry, it's been dealt with.
Hideyoshi said you'd probably
come around, so I signed you up.
He said that?
By the way, Gun, how about you ride
around on Hideyoshi's bike from now on?
It should be an easy fix.
No.
I could never do that.
Gun, what are you doing?
His blood, sweat, and
tears went into this Katana.
You think I could ride that?!
Gun, don't do it!
Nobody's riding it anymore.
This was the only thing
Hideyoshi left behind.
What will we say
to Tomoyo now?
I couldn't bear to let
someone else ride it,
but I also couldn't bear to see it gather dust in the corner of some garage...
It's better this way...
They can be together now.
It's all yours, Hideyoshi...
Not once did I manage
to overtake your Katana...
But you quit while you
were ahead, you dumbass...
With this, my memories
of you are gone.
I'll forget you in no time.
See you around, Hideyoshi.
And don't forget to give 'em hell!
You always bragged that
you never needed friends.
You just had to play
the outlaw, didn't you?
Your youth ended and all you got was
seven lines in the corner of a newspaper.
From a curve on the coastline,
your bike disappeared
into the summer.
Hey, what were you trying to hide when you
turned your back on that street corner?
Ah, there are some things
that love just can't save.
It's sad, but it's the truth.
I shed a tear whenever I
drive down that road.
It's like a thorn going
straight into my heart.
Whenever you'd leave, you'd raise
a peace sign to the night sky.
And it wouldn't go down
until you were out of sight.
Must've been sad to
be alone all that time.
Ah... I'm so sorry...
If only I could come to
understand your loneliness,
could we have been friends?
Ah, there's just one seat
I can't bear to take.
This is part of youth.
Hey, who did you want to talk to,
when you closed your
eyes for the last time?
Ah, there's just one seat
I can't bear to take.
This is part of youth.
The End