He's fast...
That runt's not fooling around.
This isn't working. Forget
overtaking him, I can barely keep up.
He always pulls
away on the corners.
Damn it! What
the hell's going on?!
I'm already riding on the limit.
So why can't I catch up?!
Crap!
That was one hell
of a crash, huh?
At least you're still in
one piece, Beanpole.
I see how it is.
Then lemme give you some advice:
your riding sucks.
What?!
I know riders can be clumsy, but if they end
up wrecking their bike, then they ain't shit.
I'm nothing like you
young rich kids!
I'd rather break my
neck than my bike.
With driving like that, the only time you'll overtake me is in your wildest dreams!
It takes everything you've
got just to not die in a crash.
That asshole...
The Legend of Revving Engines
PART 1 - TSUKUBA CHAPTER
The center line continues
all the way to the horizon.
As you rest your chin on your hand,
I can't take my eyes off you.
So before you fall asleep,
please let me know one thing...
Would you kiss me for longer
than your other girl?
Whenever you speed up,
you become like the wind.
And I can only ride behind
you when you're lonely.
You still keep your
heart closed to me,
but one of these days,
I'll make it mine.
I can see your innocent
smile through the sunbeams,
but I can tell your facade is
about to come crashing down.
What would I do if you cried?
I miss you. I love you.
It hurts to be apart.
A sunshower...
Don't say another word.
What?! You've been lugging
your 750 around town all day?!
It's nothing to laugh
about. I swear...
If you'd called me,
I'd have brought the truck over.
Sure didn't go
easy on it, did you?!
Besides, I'm sure there are a ton
of other mechanics on the way here.
Well, maybe you're right,
but I managed.
You managed? I don't think
any normal human would've.
You the Hulk or somethin'?
Pops...
How's she lookin'?
She'll be fine once
I'm done with her.
Gimme a week and she'll
be back up and running.
Thanks.
Now listen...
Bike parts can be replaced easily enough,
but I can't say the same for you.
So, take care of yourself,
will ya, Gun?
Doesn't look like you'll be making
it to class this morning.
So, how's about
some coffee?
Stand up!
Bow!
It's so cute!
Ai! Hurry up or we're
leaving your butt behind!
Wait up!
Ignition.
Vroom! Vroom, vrrroom!
Vroom, vroom!
I can't believe you, Ai!
Eating lunch out in the schoolyard has been more fun lately, or so it seems.
Let's sit here.
I've been dying to eat...
Huh?
Ai, what are you doing?
C'mon, let's eat.
Boo!
A monster!
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Mind if I eat my lunch here?
Do whatever you want.
I'm just trying to sleep.
It's okay,
I won't bother you.
I've never been good
at this kind of thing...
Damn it!
Where do you think
you're going, bitch?!
No!
S-S-Someone help!
Hands off the girl.
What's it got to
do with you, huh?!
Doesn't matter what. Worry about
how I'm easy to piss off first.
H-Hey...
You'll regret this!
Excuse me...
I don't suppose you're...
One of those delinquent types?
I've always had a thing for them.
Delinquents, I mean.
Hopefully I'm not
asking for too much,
but if you know someone
who's good in a fight,
good at riding bikes,
is really tall,
and has a gentle smile
with perfect white teeth...
My!
Oh, but he can't be ugly.
And if this special someone drives a bike with
400cc or more, you just have to introduce me!
I'm Ito Ai, I'm in class 1-6.
How stupid can you be?!
You really think there's
someone like that, huh?!
Um...
This is a 750cc, isn't it?
Talk about impressive!
It's much bigger
than the Road Pal!
I've always wanted to ride
something like this, even just once.
Y'know, I saw one in a movie
called High Teen Boogie.
The lead character in it
was a bike gang leader.
He was so cool I could die!
I decided I'd find my own gang leader,
and fall in love with him, like in the movies!
My lunch got squashed.
Look, I'm tryin' to sleep here.
Oh, sorry.
I won't say another word.
So don't worry.
Oh no!
Hey, you mind if my
friends eat with u—
Oh, Ichikawa!
Welcome back.
Sorry to drop in like this.
It must be important
for you to be here this late.
It's almost time for the
club's regular circuit, you see.
I need to get every machine
checked over by then.
Oh, by the way, we don't have a whole lotta participants this time round.
If you know anyone,
feel free to bring 'em along.
Where is it this time?
It's Tsukuba Circuit,
your favorite.
Oh, and by the way,
I don't mind you riding
around at this time of night,
but don't go doing
anything stupid out there.
That's all I ask.
I know, I know.
If I get myself in no fit state to get married,
I'm all yours, Ichikawa.
Don't talk like that!
I-I've already been married
twice and have my own kid.
Well, it's getting late.
I'll catch you later.
What's with her...
Side chick would suit me fine.
L-Like I could ever
afford two of you!
Talk about innocent.
Hey, come and
get a look at this.
Huh?
Isn't that Mi?
So whenever I couldn't find you,
you'd be hiding around here, huh?
That's not how it is...
Yeah, right. Like I'd
believe that, you horndog.
Still, I can hardly believe it.
She has some real nice legs...
But then you see her flying around on
a motorbike, hanging on for dear life...
Which reminds me, Gun,
your bike fixed yet?
Yeah.
Mi asked if we wanted to go
to Tsukuba Circuit on Sunday.
We're going, right?
You can't! Anything but the bike!
Shut it! He's had this
comin' for a long time!
And breakin' his bike's the only
way we're gonna feel any better!
You can't!
C'mon, get out of the way!
You bitch!
No!
Ouch!
Why, you little...
- Damn it!
- No, get off me!
Help, he's gonna kill me!
Now's your chance!
Go do it!
Alright!
Hold it right there!
If you so much as touch my CB,
I'll make sure you regret it!
Move it!
Damn it.
You got away with
a mild concussion.
Not counting those scratches on
your knees, elbows, and forehead.
You really are a strange one...
I can't believe you'd get
yourself hurt protecting my CB.
I don't really know why I did it.
But I just didn't want them
to get their hands on it.
That bike was
shiny and beautiful.
Thank you.
My bike would've been a
lot worse for wear without you.
You said you wanted to ride a bike, or something like that, right?
Fine.
If it's only for a while,
I can give you a ride.
You really mean it?
You must be hungry, huh?
I'll get you something in a second.
"My dear Gun..."
"It's been almost two years
since you moved to Japan."
"It'd be nice if you could come see us in California over your summer vacation."
"My memory isn't what it used to be, and it'd be a shame to forget my only son's face, after all."
"I wish you could be here to see the blue
skies and blue seas of Santa Monica."
"Sending my love from L.A.
and across the Pacific - Dad."
That brings me back.
He's always been
quite the poet.
Those in search of speed only ever arrive at one place, and that place is the circuit.
I've been searching for it my whole
life, and it's led me to one place.
The circuit.
"Auto racing auxiliary facilities"
I wish we could've rode
together a little longer.
So this is the circuit, huh? It's so
much bigger than I thought it'd be.
Best feeling ever. My spine's already tingling just from being here.
Gun!
Sure took your sweet time, huh?
Hey.
Hello.
There's a good reason for this.
But it's a long story,
so I'm not gonna go into it.
Well, that's just how it is, okay?
Yeah, right.
Now who's the horndog?
Nice of you to show.
I've been in need of a good race.
Am I okay to ride?
I know I'm about to race,
but don't go wandering off.
Do your best, okay?
Sure thing.
That's him. He's the one
the Princess brought along.
That kid pisses me off.
I don't know who that rich kid is...
but how about we...
'show him the ropes?'
Listen up, Gun! It's your first time here,
so go easy on the throttle!
Just get a feel for the course!
Go!
What the hell is wrong
with those guys?!
It's like they were waiting
for him to take off.
Those two are some of
the best drivers in our club,
but their manners
need a lot of work.
What are those jerks up to?
Those jerks...
You won't get away with that!
I can't believe that guy...
I was sure he was
gonna go flying there.
Blocking a newcomer from the inside line... talk about cheap.
But you've gotta give him credit,
it barely even fazed him.
This might get interesting.
This greenhorn is trying
to make a move on me.
I'll drive hard and
open up the gap.
He's lookin' good! Damn good!
Gun blew past two of them on one lap!
Isn't he great?
I never knew he could
ride a bike like that...
I wonder why people want
to drive as fast as lightning.
On an unrelated note...
What's this girl to Gun?
W-What is she? Pretty sure
I'd like to know that too.
O-Our eyes met.
When that happens,
you're supposed to smile.
W-What the hell is going on?
My bike's at its limit,
but I can't pull away.
What do you think, Ichikawa?
He doesn't even have the basics down,
but he's damn fast.
Doesn't exactly
seem like a beginner.
It's like he's walking a tightrope
on a windy day without a harness.
You gonna take a chance on him?
Haven't decided yet.
As he is now, he's more
like a highway racer.
This is insane! It took me ages to
even get anywhere near that lap time!
And yet, this little punk...
I'm faster... I can take him.
Damn it all! It wasn't
supposed to go like this!
No way am I gonna
lose to some greenho—
Dumbass. You're going in too fast.
Godammit! I ended up screwing
up my own throttle work.
Do you wanna go faster?
Until now, I've seen more riders than I've been able to count.
But I've never seen
anyone ride like you do.
You're different.
You drive too fast to be
relying on instinct alone.
Driving like that'll kill you.
If you keep racing at this level, I'm not
worried about you causing yourself harm.
But if you're wanting to go faster,
I'd quit while you still can.
Because if you don't, that bike's
gonna be the death of you.
Wait a sec.
I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
I just ride because I wanna
be faster than everyone else.
It's all I can do.
Then you'll have to
change the way you ride.
Instincts alone won't
get you anywhere.
You have to think.
Think when you're riding.
Gun!
What did he wanna talk about?
By the way, what do you
think about when you're driving?
Let's see...
I don't think of anything.
What brought that up?
Nah, just forget about it.
C'mon, let's get you home.
Okay!
Hey, speed racer!
You're comin' next time, right?
It'll be Suzuka or Fuji next time!
Maybe this is just me thinkin', but I don't
think you've got those hairpins down yet!
Don't go dyin' on us, okay?!
Sure.
Later!
Is this what people
call bike buddies?
You're welcome too, little lady!
S-Sure thing!
Wow! I can't believe it!
Before I knew it,
I threw up a peace sign.
Whenever I'm with Gun,
I get to see tons of new stuff!
It's a brave new world!
I'm currently studying like
mad to get my scooter license.
Once I pass my exams, I'll give Gun and Hiro a run for their money!
Today, we have a new
student starting in our class.
This is Hijiri.
Please, introduce yourself.
I'm from Osaka.
Hijiri Hideyoshi's the name.
I'm all about guts
and nothin' else!
My bad habits are...
I get into fights all the time.
While I don't always start 'em,
I always make sure to finish 'em.
You're that dipshit
from the other day!
Who're you calling a
dipshit, you little runt?!
Don't gimme that shit!
The hell are you doing here?!
Ain't it obvious?!
I transferred to this school!
Hey, Teach, I'm done! No way am I
staying in the same class as this dipshit!
W-What's wrong with you?!
What's the big deal? I'll see
the principal myself if I have to!
You're so full of yourself!
Go on, get yourself
expelled for all I care!
W-What's that?! You tryin'
to pick a fight with me, huh?!
Who's pickin' a fight
with who, dumbass?!
You're the stupidest
guy I've ever met!
Even a gorilla wouldn't
pick a fight with me!
No shit! How'd one of them turn
up to school, you caveman?!
Who are you calling a caveman?
You little monkey man!
What'd ya say?!
Damn it...
What a buzzkill. Can't believe
he's in the same class as me.
Sure was heating up in there, huh?
I thought you were gonna
start swinging for each other.
The reason I can't stand that little runt
is because I lost to him on a bike before.
So he's really that fast, huh?!
Yeah.
So we're not settling this with our fists,
we're settling it on our bikes.
So, what's your plan?
Ain't it obvious?
I'm racing that little runt again.
Gun!
I need help!
Miyuki has... Miyuki has—
Something happened to Mi?
Some strange guys showed up and
forced Miyuki in the car with them!
Satoru, what's the
meaning of this?
It's about that beanpole
from the other day.
And we just need you out
of the picture for a while.
Your skull must be
thicker than your helmet.
What was that?
I don't know why you're
so bent out of shape,
but it takes real scum to
try something like this.
Bottom of the barrel.
The rumors were right. You really are just some rich kid without a care in the world.
I don't think you quite
realize the situation you're in.
Do you, m'lady?
You bitch...
You sure they
said the riverbank?
Yeah.
Hiro, get movin'!
Don't have to ask me twice!
Why're you looking
at me like that?
You always have that look. You think you can see right into my head, don't you?!
When I... joined the Ichinose Racing Team,
you were still in middle-school,
but I couldn't help being drawn to you.
Hands so delicate,
yet so steady with the machine,
and your form through the corners...
I'd always been watching you.
But...
since you've got money, you think
you can look down on other people.
Am I wrong?
This is the first I've heard of it.
Besides, money, status...
aren't you the one
who's hung up on them?
Shut the hell up!
I hadn't planned
on doing this today,
but... but now I wanna
teach you a lesson.
Hang in there, Ichinose Miyuki.
If someone so much as touches you, I'll make them regret being born!
Shit...
What's the holdup, Satoru?
Go on, get it over with.
Shut it! I'll do it
on my own terms!
Damn it...
You don't cry and you don't beg.
Still too scared to show
your own weakness?!
Jeez...
You're not lookin' so cute now.
You're just some woman!
Miyuki, a girl should try to be cute.
One day, you'll meet someone,
fall in love, and start your own family.
Those things are very
important for a woman.
Doesn't interest
me in the slightest.
I don't get what the big deal is.
If that's how you think now,
that's fine with me.
Once Miyuki finds someone she likes more
than her motorbike, she'll come around.
Mama...
I wish I could've been a cute girl.
Papa, I'm sorry things
turned out like this.
What's wrong, Satoru?
A motorbike!
A CB750F!
Gun!
I can't believe that
punk would show up.
We'll get our own back
for the other day.
What's with you, punk?!
Eat this!
Hey, asshole!
What'd you do to the girl?! Tell me!
Talk!
Dumbass, we didn't do shit!
Correct answer!
Get outta the way!
Move it, assholes!
Hiro...
Damn you... how could
you do that to Mi?!
You'll pay for this!
Hiro...
What? You done already?
Come back in ten years, kid.
Damn it... I'd rather die than
let you get away with this!
You kids can say just
about anything, huh?
Damn it... that guy a
monster or somethin'?
He's a dead man!
See you in hell!
Damn it!
Damn it...
You're not going anywhere!
Damn it... I thought he
was just some rich kid...
How wrong could I be?
I-I was...
I was actually kinda relieved
when I heard your bike...
Any longer, and I might've done
something I could never take back.
On your feet...
Now listen up, I'll never show myself in front of her as long as I live.
But I'm not giving up on riding.
If we happen to meet on the circuit...
how about we settle things for good?
Sure, but you won't stand a chance.
Mi?
You're not hurt, are you?
No need to cry anymore.
Is there?
The worst is already
behind us, see?
Hiro...
As a boy, do you
think I'm ugly?
N-Not a chance...
You're real cute,
and smart too.
And I... I...
I... like you.
And then?
After that, Mi suddenly collapsed.
Then we took her
straight to the hospital.
The doctor told us she's got a bit of
anemia from the psychological shock.
It's nothing serious.
And then?
There wasn't anything else
we could do, so we went home.
And then?
Then I got something to eat,
took a dump and went to sleep.
That's not what I meant.
Oh, my bad.
Then why do you want
to know every little detail?
I mean...
I was kinda worried about stuff.
Huh?
Not like her to be a downer.
Your bra strap is about to break!
Really?!
Just kidding.
What do you want, dipshit?
You trying to pick a fight again?
Tomorrow morning, 4:30. I'll be waiting for you at the same mountain pass as before.
Fine by me.
'Bout time I dealt with you.
Damn, that runt...
He's way better in
the slower corners...
He's already starting
to break away.
Alright, at the next hairpin,
I'm staying on him, no matter what.
What an idiot.
This is no different from last time.
That guy's got a
screw loose for sure!
He jumped his bike to
get it back under control.
Nipping at my heels.
What's with this guy?
How's he still on my tail
with a driving style like that?
Someone's chasing us?
What the heck?!
What's that machine?
Challenging us both, huh?
I'm ready when you are!
Wanna occupy the inner line from the get-go?
Like hell I'm letting you!
They overtook me!
Who the hell is that guy?!
Damn... that was smooth.
I didn't even get to breathe.
You fired up, Beanpole?
If you're gonna go, then go.
Now's your chance, dipshit.
Don't blame me
if you crash out!
You really thought I'd back down?! I'm not goin' down without a fight!
Dumbass, you think you
can corner at that speed?!
Y-You gotta be kiddin' me?!
That's gonna hurt in the morning.
You don't hold back, huh?
Didn't think anybody was
stupid enough to do that.
Neither did I, but it
kinda killed the mood.
Mornin'!
I-It's a chick...
Well, if it isn't Mi...
Wait, so you didn't
know it was me?
Are you sure
you're okay to ride?
You didn't show at school
yesterday, so I was worried sick.
I skipped yesterday.
That's one hell of a machine.
What's it called?
Doesn't even know Formula 1 models.
I'd be ashamed to be that stupid.
Keep it to yourself!
You've always gotta
say something, dontcha?
There's not much of you to look at, but you're still an eyesore.
What's that, dipshit?!
Got something to say, ankle-biter?
Sorry to interrupt,
but I've got places to be.
The mountains will have eroded by the time you're done arguing.
I'm glad I listened to Hiro
and came all the way out here.
I never thought people with skills
like that would end up at my school.
Supposing...
Supposing I get those two together,
they'd make the ultimate combination.
Next summer, things are gonna get
interesting at Suzuka, and that's for sure.
I'll keep a smile on my face,
even when we say our goodbyes.
Nervous yesterday.
From the moment I wake up,
I wanna ride on the special street.
You can pretend all you want, but you can't hold on if your heart's not in the right place!
I'm never letting go of my dream!
As we ride away, my tears
are swept away in the wind.
Don't cry more. It's alright.
Don't let the bustling
street corner get you down.
Wink and kiss. It's alright.
You're not alone!
I'm sure everyone's made
mistakes at some point.
So even if I lose my way,
I'll keep on living!
Never stop!
Everything will change someday
when the world is born anew.
I can change. It's alright.
I wave at you from the
bustling street corner.
Hello. Yes, it's alright.
I just want to hold
you in my arms.