The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let other see your tears
December of 1941.
In order to capture
Southern Asia's resources by force,
Japan had deployed its Combined fleet
in the vast Southern Pacific waters.
According to the Southern strategy, the unit,
tasked with protecting the operation's flanks and rear,
is the 1st Mobile Fleet -
a large unit of 30 ships,
with 6 aircraft carriers as the core.
Episode 1
Surprise attack on Pearl Harbor
On the fateful day, December 8th, at dawn,
the 1st Mobile Fleet carried out
a secret 5800km expedition,
creeping in the waters
360 km north of the bay of Pearl Harbor.
Chief, the task force is ready for sortie.
I have...
been in charge of getting us all up to here, but now...
The rest is up to you.
The latest intel arrived.
Enemy forces anchored at Pearl Harbor are as follows:
Battleships - 9, second-class cruisers - 3,
seaplane tenders - 3, destroyers - 17.
Aircraft carriers and heavy cruisers are dispatched.
No countermeasure is afoot.
The aircraft carriers are not there?
But since it's Sunday,
it should be back until tomorrow.
Any chance to cross path with it?
If so, we have the upper hand.
But Pearl Harbor gets alerted.
Does it matter?
A sunken carrier is just as good.
It's time.
Got it! Sir, if you excuse me.
Counting on you!
If the enemy's carrier spots us,
without the attack party to guard us, we're screwed.
The 2nd wave wings will hold its own!
The price of such defense is still a few ships!
What did I tell you before?
Chop the Gordian Knot!
Precisely! Go there and do what you do best!
The first ones to take off
are carrier-based fighters of the Zero type.
Also known as Zero Fighters.
Equipped with two 20mm cannons,
they're a maneuverability-focused aircraft.
It particularly excels in dog-fighting.
This is the main fighter of the Japanese Navy.
Victory by all means
I'm off!
Next goes Nakajima B5N.
It is capable of carrying
800kg of bombs or a torpedo,
while making incursions far behind enemy lines.
This aircraft's object of prestige
is its horizontal bombing accuracy rate of over 50%.
If only I were younger...
You'd fly, too?
Of course. With the vanguards!
6:05, 1st wave wings take off,
while at 7:15, the 2nd wave would follow.
A total of 350 aircraft,
with 765 people in them
folding into one huge formation
in the midst of Pacific Ocean.
Right now, they are about
to change the course of history.
Among those, the Aichi D3A carrier-based bomber.
During a nose dive, it has an accuracy rate of 80%.
Pilots put infinite trust in this model.
Awfully cloudy up here.
Captain, if our inroad agrees
with Honolulu program, we'll be ok.
They're unaware so far.
Carefree jazz's playing.
And now, a weather forecast.
Hold on!
Over Oahu, the sky is partly cloudy.
The wind blows at about 7.5 knots per hour.
Hey, our foes are nice enough to share the forecast!
Beware, you're forgetting
there are still plenty of Japanese living on Hawaii.
Nothing exploitable on the radio.
Only distraction from the hell captain is taking us to.
We're at Oahu.
Oh, it's beautiful...
A heaven on earth.
Such a pity to carpet bomb it.
Alright, we're closing in!
Assault formation!
The squadron commander just reported back.
It is action time, isn't it?
Admiral, the captain's plane
just transmitted the assault signal.
Admiral...
They've done it. They made it there!
Successful surprise attack!
Alright, stick to the battle plans!
Thus, the hell of war had broken loose
across the Pacific.
The enemy is still unaware?
Two carriers are missing.
Are they? Whatever. They'll get ambushed
on their way back by the 2nd wave wings.
Engage!
Damn you!
Would you just look at this mess?
Our fleet is blown to smithereens!
I saw it. I saw it all.
I was still in my nightwear when it started.
Admirals, it is portentous
for you to both stay here.
If you died on-duty
who would take the reins?
Fine, I'll hide away
in the office on the opposite side.
Still, look at the havoc the Japs wrecked on!
I will notify the aircraft carriers
so that they push the enemy out.
Alright, anti-aircraft is annihilated.
Now, it's naval bombers' turn to act!
Alright, 1st wave wings are done dropping thunder.
30 minutes before 2nd wave shows up.
Take a good picture of the damage.
Okay.
The alleged Japanese parachute unit landing
was but a hoax.
Great strategy, even though it's from the enemy.
A sweeping blow.
What's that talk? Our tax dollars
go to patch up these surprises!
Now that they've done their worst, there's no doubt
our people will repay this treachery.
Admiral!
Just a spent Japanese bullet?
It would have been merciful if it had killed me.
Alright, done checking the aftermath.
No more latecomers left behind. Time to withdraw.
Jettison that pile of scrap!
Move it, you idiot!
Second wave cannot take off!
Jettison into the sea anything that clutters the deck!
No worry, the sea is warm around here!
Okay, emergency landing!
Attaway.
You returned safely!
Had us all worried here!
Reporting! Our attacking forces...
Yes, the results. What are results?
Yessir! According to my observations,
4 battleships are sunk, 4 more badly damaged.
So all of them?
Aside from the absent Enterprise and Lexington.
All except carriers?
Aircraft carriers are intact?
We may strike back,
if we hold position for 2 or 3 more days!
Don't say nonsense!
We don't have any tankers in the vicinity.
Can they come at short notice,
after we summon them with Morse?
Their carriers are out of shape!
If we hit their aircraft carriers
even betraying our location becomes a least worry!
So the carriers?
Admiral! Each carrier is ready
to maneuver for another attack!
Do we launch this attack wave?
The foe will definitely strike again.
Counter measures are in place.
Any civilian unrest?
People are in disarray.
The foe killed the radio broadcast.
How about their carriers?
Allegedly stationed upper south of Wake Island.
Dispatch the patrol again.
Admiral, let's sweep the north.
Coming from the south would make a lot more sense.
Listen, we have to find the Japanese carriers...
And then, obliterate them.
How about operation's objectives?
All are met.
The American Pacific Fleet won't be able
to operate from Pearl Harbor within the next 6 months.
We favorably protected the flanks and the rear
of Southern operation.
We have orders to launch multiple attacks!
We are also ordered to be as wary as possible,
making sure casualties are minimal.
How is the enemy's condition?
Reports say, they've significantly bolstered their counterattack response.
2nd wave attack losses are of 24 planes for us.
A next wave would come with more losses.
Besides, the enemy aircraft carrier...
Let's go for the night attack!
For this purpose, we have a special
night-time torpedo bombing team!
Are you suggesting a gamble?
A better gambit
than just returning!
Aviation officers!
It's risky to get too involved
into strategy planning.
We aim to sensibly balance attacks efficiency
with our limited force.
Japan's industrial capabilities
cannot vouch for repeated mistakes.
But the grand-admiral of the Navy wants us
to kill as many birds with one stone as we can.
Westward, the weather is against us.
While taking off is possible,
landing is something else entirely.
What can this mean?
As you can see, we've taken the course
to the north-northwest.
There won't be any more waves?
I told them not to call it off.
Damn it, this is frustrating.
They say admirals are prone to panic attacks.
They see airplanes
as a mere auxiliary force.
All they value are the big gunned ships,
misunderstanding this new era of warfare.
Always so timorous, damn it.
Seniority fries their brain.
If only it was up to Yamaguchi...
Prepare an airplane!
I'm going to the Headquarters on Akagi.
Captain!
Forget it, I'll do it myself!
I'll talk to the Chief!
Let me go!
This is a mutiny! Let me go!
The Japanese army's landing at Barbers Point
proved to be false.
All we hear is falses.
The actual Japanese army isn't as much of a bogeyman.
Infantry reports
countless cases of friendly fire.
Out of 17 liaison aircraft from Enterprise,
7 were shot down as this.
Excuse me, radar station reports,
the enemy is to the north.
However, why is there no new wave of attack?
Our gasoline tanks are still untouched.
Now that they've done it,
we're probably due to retreat to San Francisco.
Pearl Harbor waters are shallow.
The vessels will be easily fished up.
This once again
proved battleships obsolescence.
Hardline lawmakers, whether they like it or not,
will finally see aircraft carriers as the future.
The old man will be thrilled.
Old man?
President Roosevelt.
As a proponent of carriers theory,
he wants them mass produced.
They went for this strategy,
without rounding it off...
Did their commanders wussy out?
Or was it...
Or was it?
A trap?
Our submarine located an enemy fleet
heading for Pearl Harbor.
Enterprise, too?
Must be. The likelihood of that is very high.
Just a likelihood?
Isn't our survival hanging on likelihoods!?
Idiot! One strikes the iron while it's still hot!
There is a time to scatter stones
and a time to gather them.
Admiral, I have a suggestion.
Operation's objectives were met.
We now lack intel on the enemy.
And due to the bad weather coming our way,
our fuel supply is at risk.
I think, we better return the whole fleet
back to Japan safely, while we can.
The true battlefield for our Imperial Navy
lies in the southern waters.
Shouldn't we crush the enemy
in a determinant battle of fleets, fair and square?
That's right, the Indian Ocean awaits!
Course to north!
At that moment, there was no one
in Akagi high command,
able to predict, with full confidence,
what would be the effect of further waves of attack.
And so, it remains arguable to this day,
whether or not extra waves of attack
would have changed the outcome of Pacific War.
Some accuse them of cowardice,
others observe a more cautionary attitude.
However, it is said that a truly talented commander
would never lose sight of his objectives,
aptly taking a critical decision
without batting an eyelash.
Conversely, if you let the situation at hand
influence your decision at a moment like this,
no satisfactory result comes out
of your objective's oversight.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
June 1942.
Two major task forces -
Japanese and American
spot one another at a measly distance of just 240km,
in the Battle of Midway.
How do you approach the foe,
how do you assess his condition?
And how do you fight him?
The commanders put
all of their reckoning and intuition at use.
Deeming situation favorable,
America stepped in.
Just as it was about to dispatch its 2nd wave wings,
Japan's mobile fleet
had been engulfed
in a swarm of American dive bombers.
Time is capital!
Had the American bomber attack come 5 minutes later,
the Battle of Midway
would become a can of worms.
However, was this 5 minutes frame
another stroke of fate?
The Pacific War is told to have its own Battle of Sekigahara,
which is this one, Battle for Midway.
Please witness more fateful decisions
being taken next week.
Episode 2
Battle of Midway (Part 1)
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation by Perevodildo
Quality Checking by Ziusudra
Supplementary materials by History Asian
Editing by Paul Geromini
RAW by Moozzi2