The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
December 2nd, 1941.
Six days before the surprise attack at Pearl Harbor.
The great fortress of Singapore,
the Britain's pride, is in exceedingly high spirits.
That day, brand new ships arrive to the port
to bolster the British East Indies fleet - Z-Force.
Comprised by a battleship Prince of Wales
and a battlecruiser Repulse,
it stands prepared to protect the colony.
This transfer has been announced worldwide,
creating an unquestionable appearance
of Singapore's defenses being impregnable.
Episode 7
High Seas Naval Battle for Malaya
Prince of Wales -
formerly deployed in the Atlantic,
she stood her ground
against the German battleship Bismark.
With the cutting-edge technology on-board, her fame of an unsinkable battleship was was roaring across the globe.
35,000 tons. Cruising speed of 28.5 knots.
Armed with ten 35 cm cannons,
as well as sixteen 13 cm high-angle guns.
Also on-board, mounted co-axially 8 pieces per turret
and dubbed "pom-pom,"
anti-aircraft guns with firing rate of 6000 per minute,
Aside from that, numerous dual machine guns
are mounted all over her.
Battlecruiser Repulse.
32,000 tons, max speed 30 knots.
Though formally outdated, recently refitted
with newest equipment like that on Prince of Wales.
Meanwhile, at the Japanese military base
on the Hainan Island.
Admiral,
Prince of Wales and Repulse are at anchor in Singapore.
If we sortie now, they will definitely come out.
Surprise is our goal.
Making the landing a surprise is our priority.
However, with those still around, attempting a landing under the enemy's radar involves much more risks.
Yes. With the British East Indies Fleet still in the area,
the Army supply through the sea is jeopardized.
The British fleet needs to be eliminated
as soon as possible.
Commander,
please let our air squadron
show Prince of Wales and Repulse their place!
Good. Please do.
If need be, I'm prepared to even sacrifice
the entirety of our escort fleet,
in order to get our landing party
safely to the destination.
Let's do it.
We won't let them lay a finger on our convoys!
A certain death from the sky awaits them if they come out.
"The sun rises at Yamagata" -
such a coded telegram meant that the onset of the war
was scheduled on December 8th.
On receiving that cue, the Japanese troops set out
on their furtive advance through the Malay Peninsula
with Singapore as their ultimate goal.
Dead ahead and above!
British plane, one vehicle!
So they finally decided to stick their head out!
No two ways about it:
the enemy must be radioing Singapore with "Found
a large Japanese formation" like mad right about now.
If the British East Indies Fleet sorties now, we'll be in deep.
What are you talking about?
Should even the Prince of Wales come out now,
the seas west of the Anambas Archipelago
are already bristling with our mines.
And even if they try to trick us, coming from the East,
they'll just end up in the tight snare of our submarine fleet.
However,
if the British realize
the intent behind our surprise landing,
it will spell trouble for the entire Malayan campaign.
It'll be alright.
As per our plan, we'll make a false report on our course,
misrepresenting it as bound for Thailand.
A big Japanese formation is advancing towards Bangkok.
The composition: 25 transport ships, one battleship,
5 cruisers, 7 destroyers.
However,
in Singapore, the overall commander of the British
East Indies forces, Air Chief Marshal Brooke-Popham
still in doubts about the true intentions of the Japanese convoys, failed to enact any countermeasures.
As a result, the Japanese transports
suddenly changed course to the west at 00:45 on the 8th
and began landing on parts
of the Malay Peninsula, completely unopposed.
Upon receiving reports of this, Phillips,
the Commander-in-Chief of the British East Indies Fleet
gathered his closest staff.
The Japanese troops that finished landing last night
can only have this one thing in their sights - Singapore.
The Japanese realize that a frontal attack from the sea
would not suffice to bring down a fortress like Singapore.
It falls on us, the pride of the British fleet, the Z-Force,
to launch a surprise attack, under the Air Force coverage,
blowing the Japanese out of the water.
The Japanese battleships are traveling
with the escort of 20 warships.
And we made it known to the whole world
that Prince of Wales and Repulse are now in Singapore.
Now is not the time for us to hesitate.
When we meet the enemy,
we face him decisively, hitting hard.
Such has been the lifelong tradition of our Royal Navy,
and our article of pride!
At 5:35 pm of the 8th,
with Prince of Wales as its flagship,
Z-Force of the British East Indies Fleet
had set sail from Singapore's naval base
so as to deal a surprise blow to Japanese convoys.
Sir, a telegraph from the Air Force Command.
Fighters on bases heavily damaged by Japanese bombardment. Cannot provide cover for Z-Force.
What?
Alright, the surprise attack is possible without air coverage.
Pass the Anambas from the east and proceed to the north!
The Japanese also know that passing them
from the west would be the shortest route.
So they made it impassable with mines.
Knowing that waters west of Anambas Archipelago
are swarming with mines, the Z-Force
manages to bypass them safely and head north.
However, next afternoon, on the 9th,
the Z-force was still entirely oblivious to the fact
a fleet of Japanese submarines was patrolling this route.
The report of the Z-Force being spotted
was promptly radioed
to the base of the 22nd Japanese Air Flotilla.
5th Submarine Fleet, 30th Submersible Squadron,
an emergency radiogram from I-65.
Read it.
Spotted: 2 enemy's Repulse-class battlecruisers.
What?
Read.
Observed from the east.
Course at 340 degrees. Speed at 14 knots. 1515.
That's nonsense!
What do you mean by that?
Prince of Wales and Repulse were seen still in Singapore
by our reconnaissance plane just this morning.
So who should we believe here?
Order the reconnaissance photos printed. It's urgent.
This is just a large merchant ship.
It's neither Prince of Wales nor Repulse.
Which means, the ones spotted by I-65...
Are the real ones!
The enemy is heading our way.
Alright. Sortie!
At 5:34 pm,
from the air base in Saigon, Indochina
a wing of torpedo bombers took off,
tasked with attempting a raid on the Z-Force.
The Japanese convoys east of the Malay Peninsula
immediately retreated to safety of Thai coastal waters.
With heavy cruiser Chokai as its core, the escort fleet
sets out, determined to destroy Britain's Z-Force,
in cooperation with the Air Force fleet.
We'll join the pantheon of heroes
by sinking Prince of Wales.
We must, by all means, stop them from getting close,
until all our troops are disembarked!
By all means!
Ain't nothing we can do in this storm.
Should we retreat?
8:10 pm.
the torpedo bombers that took off from the Indochina bases
discovered a fleet that looked like what might be Z-Force.
Found enemy ships. Course at 150 degrees, 140 km.
Those halfwits!
They mistook us for the enemy fleet.
If we don't respond promptly,
we'll be under attack.
Radio this out immediately:
Flare dropped over our allied fleet.
Weather over the ocean is deteriorating.
Scouting is impossible.
We've already had one case
of friendly ships being mistaken for the enemy.
All right.
Withdraw the attack wings.
We'll face them tomorrow!
In turn, the British fleet
convinced that the Japanese scout aircraft
had discovered them, was rapidly turning back.
However,
the Japanese side never really discovered Z-Force.
Thus,
however miraculous,
both the enemy and the friendly forces
turned their backs at one another
and parted ways at the same moment.
Having abandoned the prospect of a surprise attack, Z-Force
was on its way back to Singapore.
Until, at 00:52 on the 10th...
Sir, we've got an emergency call
from the headquarters in Singapore.
The report says, the Japanese troops
are attempting a landing in Kuantan.
What?
Sir, a surprise attack is possible!
We're 640 km away from the Japanese air base in Saigon.
The threat from the Japanese planes is negligible.
Both the enemy convoys and the escort vessels
are currently ours for the taking!
Alright. This time, we don't sidestep.
Send one destroyer ahead for scouting.
Z-Force sent out the destroyer Express
to Kuantan as a liaison.
With hopes of dealing a surprise blow to the Japanese fleet
glowing in them, the Z-Force set out on its way.
However,
once again, Z-Force was entirely oblivious
to the presence of a Japanese submarine I-58,
shadowing their every move.
We're not letting them get away this time.
Keep tracking the enemy until the very end.
Once we find them,
unleash a full-scale attack with all forces.
"Unsinkable battleship" is but a legend. We can do it!
Sink Prince of Wales and Repulse with planes.
This should definitely be doable!
Dispatch the recon aircraft at once.
4:55 am, December 10th.
Nine Mitsubishi G3M land-based aircraft
took off for a reconnaissance mission from Saigon air base.
However, the Japanese efforts at locating
British Z-Force were proving more and more futile.
We've been here for five hours already.
Damn it.
Where did the Royal Navy go?
Captain, the planned 600 nautical miles mark was passed.
Idiot!
You expect us to return empty-handed?
We'll keep searching until we find them.
Captain!
I can see the Malay Peninsula.
It's Kuantan.
At that moment, a dim shadow flashed through spotter's eyes.
Hey, look!
Enemy ships!
Good, let's make sure.
Approach under the cover of clouds.
Roger!
No room for mistake! It's Prince of Wales and Repulse!
We did it!
Nice! Congratulations!
Operator, a telegram!
Sir!
"Found Prince of Wales.
North latitude: 4 degrees. East longitude:
3 degrees 55 minutes. Course: 60 degrees.
They're giving us a warm welcome.
Damn! If only we had a torpedo with us!
Reconnaissance missions are a bore!
Idiot!
You can't wage war all by yourself!
Reconnaissance and sinking missions
are equally important!
Sir!
Alright. Keep an eye on them
until our attack planes arrive.
Ain't letting them get away!
Third recon aircraft spotted the enemy
off the coast of Kuantan.
Don't let them escape.
We must make sure to sink them with planes!
Every attack wing is rushing to the coast of Kuantan.
I wish you a good fight!
We should definitely expect the Japanese air attack.
Prince of Wales fears not
any possible attack from above.
The enemy is unrelenting.
Our defensive plan must be impeccable.
We would be fine, no matter when the attack comes.
It's time to make a display
of the Royal Navy's stoicism.
Every single one enemy plane
must be shot down into the sea.
Enemy main forces are maneuvering.
Course: 60 degrees. Speed: 20 knots.
What's taking the attacking wings so long?
They'd better be here soon!
Captain.
There is no more fuel.
Alright. Everyone, jettison your things!
It'll help save fuel.
Your weapons. Throw your clothes out, too.
Hurry!
That was when eight planes of the Japanese air squadron
took position 3,000 meters above Repulse.
For the first time in the history of naval warfare,
the airplane-on-warship battle had begun.
Confirming a bomb hitting Repulse!
But it won't sink from just one.
Torpedo bombers are here!
Two torpedoes! Confirming hits on Prince of Wales!
The propulsion system stopped working!
Fire!
Pound away at them!
Fight until the very last man!
Telegram to Singapore:
"Under heavy bombardment by the Japanese planes.
The British are also hitting back pretty hard.
They're not giving up
on their "unsinkable battleship!"
8 planes of the 8th squadron,
counting on you!
Torpedo squadron!
This time, counting on you for sure!
The British fleet was fighting back
with tremendous tenacity.
However...
It was Repulse, who met her end first.
Life jackets on!
All crew gather on the upper deck.
Prepare to abandon the ship.
Lord help us all.
Repulse is sinking!
Glorious sight. She fought well.
As the battle progressed, Prince of Wales as well...
Fire!
Pound them away!
Captain!
All crew, abandon ship!
All crew have abandoned the ship.
You put up a good fight,
a brave knight, and a champion of the British Empire.
Captain! Let's hurry to get on the boats!
No, I'm good enough here.
Chief!
Captain!
Sir!
Sir!!
Captain!
Prince of Wales is sinking!
Captain,
we've no fuel for the way back!
Report the results of the battle.
Watch out!
Think they're out of bullets?
No, it was Bushido!
We did it?
An airplane sunk an unsinkable battleship.
The fall of Singapore is now but a matter of time.
The next day, a Japanese plane flew over to the sinking site
of Prince of Wales and Repulse.
There, it dropped two wreathes.
In the High Seas Naval Battle for Malaya,
both the Japanese and British forces fought splendidly,
impressing the enemy with their majestic performance.
One of the wreathes was intended
for the British soldiers.
And the other one was dedicated
to the fallen Japanese soldiers.
The wreathes symbolized the respect for those who keep on
fighting despite all odds, determined to fulfill their duty.
However, albeit not yet fully realizing it,
inadvertently, with those wreathes,
the Japanese Navy ushered in the age of aircraft.
And before long, that short-sightedness
would spell a major disaster for themselves.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
Next time, in the Southern Pacific,
the Coral Sea would serve as a backdrop.
The Japanese plan to capture Port Moresby
will soon bring about the first ever in the world's
naval warfare history carrier-on-carrier battle.
Zeros and Grummans would come together
in a spectacular dogfight.
Then, amidst a terrible squall,
looking for a prime chance of scoring a victory,
both the Japanese and American task forces
would apply all of their wisdom in the fight.
Episode 8
Battle of the Coral Sea
Next week's decision:
Battle of the Coral Sea. Don't miss it.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2