The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Having unleashed the war on the Pacific with the successful surprise attack on Hawaii, the Japanese army
capitalized on that momentum to advance on Hong Kong, the Malay Peninsula, the Philippines, Celebes, Borneo, and so on.
The stage was set for the capture of Java operation.
The ultimate goal of Operation Java
was the acquisition of its abundant oil resources.
As well as connecting the islands of Sumatra and Java
into one big defensive ridge.
At that time, the island of Java
was part of the Dutch East Indies.
These days, we know it as Indonesia.
First, the desired oil fields and air bases
of Sumatra and Palembang were captured
by forces of three Japanese
forward paratrooper battalions.
Episode 9
The Fall of Java
From General Staff' point of view,
among all Southern Strategy operations,
the capture of Java would be likely to pose the biggest challenge.
The matter of raised concerns was the possible destruction of oil installations before the Japanese army takes control.
Through the efforts of 3 paratrooper regiments,
both the oil field and the air base were captured intact.
In the same manner, the Japanese army had previously conquered Sumatra, completing the isolation of Java.
Lieutenant General Imamura arrived in the area
with his 40,000 strong 16th Army.
On February 27th, they began their march
through the island of Java.
The combined allied forces in Java were under the supreme command of Dutch Lieutenant General ter Poorten.
Defending Java were the combined ABDACOM forces:
Dutch, British, Americans, and Australians,
as well as local conscripts.
A joint total of 80,000.
Meaning they outnumbered the Japanese 2 to 1.
However, the combined Dutch command
was facing the risk of 50 million people of local populace
also suddenly taking up arms against them.
By that time, in Indonesia,
under the joint leadership of Sukarno and Hatta,
the National Independence Movement,
resisting the Dutch rule, was thriving.
In anticipation of the approaching Japanese army,
Rear Admiral Doorman of the Dutch Navy
ordered the combined allied fleet to set sail.
But it got wiped out in an instant by the Japanese fleet
in the Battle for Surabaya, off the coast of Batavia.
However, among the ships then anchored at Bantam Bay,
only watching this battle unfold with bated breath,
four Japanese transport vessels
were hit with the torpedoes.
However ironic, those friendly torpedoes passed right under
an American cruiser that was already doomed.
Among the transports hit, was Sakuramaru, carrying Lieutenant General Imamura, the 16th army commander.
To his sheer surprise, Lieutenant General Imamura,
found himself swimming through the warm southern waters.
However, Lieutenant General Imamura
casually changed ships, and on March 1st,
the Japanese army launched a full-scale landing
on the island of Java with all available forces.
The main body of the 16th Army was split
into three formations, each one making steady progress.
With Bandung as their goal, all three were advancing.
All forces have successfully made it ashore!
How's the battle situation?
Looks exceedingly favorable for us.
No, you could even say too favorable.
I see.
Both we and the enemy alike wish to take as little damage
as possible before this battle is concluded.
Roger.
We don't fight to kill as many as we can, but to enforce
a surrender with minimal casualties on our side.
Relax, it's still a long way off.
Unaware of the Japanese army movements, the combined forces commander ter Poorten was sick worried.
We're currently analyzing the combat reports
from each one of the districts.
The Japanese forces number 30,000 to 40,000 troops.
Can't we get reliable information sooner?
In our combined army of four nations, it always takes one army some minutes to communicate with another.
Exactness! The more exact information is what we need!
What about the local populace?
Why not employ them
for obtaining reliable information?
Yes. Well, as a matter of fact...
What is it ?
Landed in the Kragan Cape area -
around 50,000 Japanese.
50,000?
And apparently, 80,000 more Japanese
are landing in Bantam Bay.
80,000?
What? 200,000?
Putting together various reports from locals,
we have concluded that the Japanese
have at least 200,000 troops in the region.
The estimates concerning the Japanese troops
were vastly exaggerated by the natives
and in this fashion passed on to the Dutch.
It was believed until the very end
that the 16th Army numbered up to 200,000 troops.
The combined Dutch efforts at gathering the intelligence
were not only sabotaged by the natives,
but also by their own lackluster methods.
The Natives from the National
Independence Movement made every effort
to expedite the Japanese army's advance
and ensure a success for the operation.
What's your latest info on the Japanese activity?
We need reliable information.
What's that?
You want to know about the Japanese activity?
Good luck with that.
They haven't brought us today's newspaper yet.
All over the front, the enemy is not putting up
much of a fight. It's a bit anticlimactic, even.
The less resistance we meet,
the less casualties we are taking.
A new tank model?
So, as of March 3rd, we have received a report
that no Japanese troops have yet landed on Java proper.
Eh? What a load of bull!
It's a Japanese tank!
In order to damage the Dutch combined forces' morale,
Lieutenant General Imamura
launched a massive deception campaign.
The Japanese army in Burma
seems to have entered Rangoon unopposed.
No way!
Did he just say Rangoon?
In Britain, Churchill's Cabinet
has assumed the responsibility for the fall of Singapore.
It appears that it's going to resign in full.
The natives found the broadcast
extremely to their liking.
The Japanese troops have furthermore solidified the natives' support for their campaign.
However, as they were actually approaching Bandung,
the resistance of Dutch combined forces
understandably intensified.
It was at this point in time, when the Japanese army's steady advance seemingly started to grind to a stalemate.
On March 7th,
a suicide corps was formed
from more than 700 Japanese soldiers.
They were to infiltrate the suburbs of Bandung.
If the Indonesians' animosity had become so intense,
ever waging a guerrilla warfare is no longer viable.
Even if I order my Dutch troops to surrender,
the troops of other nations are free to disregard
a ceasefire order from me, if they so desire.
Commander.
As long as there's even a single one
of your Dutch soldiers still in the fight,
our British and Australian troops
won't lay down their arms.
Although the words of Major General Sitwell,
Commander-in-Chief of British-Australian forces
were filled with determination,
they now had nothing in common with the reality.
Major General Pesman, responsible for the defense
of Northern-Central district of Bandung
surrendered willingly in just under few hours
after the Japanese suicide corps' attack had started.
Have you confirmed it's a herald from Pesman,
Northern-Central district of Bandung defender?
Yes. Without a doubt, he is a truce bearer.
All that, despite the determined resistance
they've been mounting...
I believe, the enemy is setting a trap for us.
In these circumstances,
only razing the city to the ground is acceptable.
We have no choice but to set it on fire.
Sir.
I understand what you're getting at.
The casualties on our side are mounting.
The enemy will continue to resist
and won't come out of the city,
probably preparing a fortified position
for a decisive showdown.
However, that would entail
enormous collateral damage to the locals.
No, we will evacuate as many as we can.
Sir, please make a decision.
Time is running out.
Even if it means increased strain on our own forces,
the local populace must be protected.
Burning the city is unacceptable.
By inflicting such a suffering on them here,
we'll lose their favor for the rest of the occupation.
We didn't come here to hurt the locals.
Roger!
Okay, let's ask the secret service agency to do their thing.
With an interpreter to accompany him, a Japanese military officer disguised himself as a local civilian.
As a part of one big stratagem, he had already infiltrated Bandung and was awaiting for an opportunity.
On March 7th, before the Japanese troops
overwhelmed Lembang,
immediately upon receiving an order
from his military commander, he enacted the plan.
First Lieutenant of the Japanese Army Yanagawa.
I'd like an audience with the Supreme Commander
of the Allied Forces on Java, Lieutenant General ter Poorten.
What?!
The Japanese army had taken the Island of Java
completely under control.
The isolation of Bandung is also finished.
I suggest that you surrender yourself immediately.
Prolonging the resistance any further would be futile.
On March 8th, the Dutch combined forces
finally laid down their arms.
The Bandung District Defense Commander
Major General Pesman,
Governor-General Tjarda,
and Lieutenant General ter Poorten,
as well as the Army Chief of Staff
Major General Bakkers - 4 men in total
came to Kalijati
to meet with the Commander-in-Chief Imamura.
The scene of destruction in the Bandung area
presents a sorry sight.
We shouldn't subject the locals
to any more misery than that.
I wish to surrender Bandung on good terms.
We didn't come here for the surrender of Bandung!
What the Japanese military demands
is a complete, unconditional surrender.
The Bandung Radio Station
finally broadcast a ceasefire order to all forces.
Thus, the capture of Java, which was expected to pose
the biggest challenge of the entire Southern Strategy,
thanks to discretion in planning
and the cooperation of the natives
unexpectedly ended in a complete success,
achieved with limited casualties.
On March 10th, commanded by Lieutenant General Imamura,
the 16th Army triumphantly entered Bandung.
In the entirety of the Pacific War, no other operation was so warmly welcomed by the natives as the Operation Java.
This and the fact it met all the objectives according to plan,
made it truly a one-of-a-kind operation.
Some say, those commander's decisions
of Lieutenant General Imamura
to be considerate to the natives' interests all along,
not resorting to the tactics of complete annihilation
were the products of true humanity.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
One of the Southern Strategy operations
was the capture of the Celebes.
This time as well, the paratroopers were to raise the curtain.
Although a better cooperation
with the ground troops was strongly encouraged,
those basking in praise for being Divine Soldiers,
sent by the sky itself, paratroopers
were still struggling to acknowledge the existence
of land troops, giving rise to strong feeling of animosity.
But at a later point, this animosity would cause a decision
to be made in a wrong time, giving birth to a major blunder.
The next decision:
The Navy Paratrooper Corps. Please look forward to it.
Episode 10
The Navy Paratrooper Corps
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2