I'm finally entering the heart of the organization.
You'll pay for stealing my virginity!
Here we are.
The slave training room is beyond this door.
N-No way...
No!
Okizari Fansubs presents
Desert Planet
Sex Pet Kate
When I was dancing, a mirage in the desert
Oh, I see an oasis
Bathed in moonlight
I was dreaming of embracing you
Suddenly I realize
Just how I'm really feeling
Come over to me, I wanna be close to you
Baby, touch me now
Thinking 'bout you every night
You know me, baby, don't you fall in love
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you...
All aircraft have completed deployment.
Good. What's the status
on Second Lieutenant Kate Curtis?
Recon officer, call Smith.
Roger!
Smith here.
Smith, how are things going on your end?
We'll be in the area where we lost
her signal in about 30 minutes.
I can sing five more songs in that time.
I'll leave it to you until you find them.
Act on your own discretion.
Yes, sir!
It's showtime!
Yay!
Listen. The success of this operation
depends on how quick we are.
If the worst happens, we can accept
the loss of Second Lieutenant Curtis,
but we must find their hideout.
Although I know there's little hope
to avoid casualties completely against Ulfan.
Kate, what do you think
about our training room?
This is Ulfan's true sustenance.
And this is just the Doune branch.
We have a lot more hideouts, even bigger than this one, throughout the galaxy.
The slaves you see here were taken from
Doune's tourist spots, hotels, and stations.
Some were even abducted from spaceships
flying through this star system.
A-Am I also going to be trained like that?
No, I'm not going to make you into a slave.
Then, what'll happen to me?
For now, I'll keep you as my pet.
Pet? Are you going to teach me those techniques
just to make me your pet?
Dick is giving it his best.
You're doing pretty well now.
Oh, hey, bro.
Really, all your slaves are so well trained.
Even a greenhorn like me
can get them to obey.
Come on, Amy.
Say hi to Brick and Kate.
Yes, Master Dick.
Why is she glaring at me?
What did I ever do to her?
I am Master Brick's pet, Amy.
I just turned 19.
Wh-What's with this girl?
So unreserved.
Is she an exhibitionist or something?
Yes, very good.
This is how to greet someone as their pet.
What the hell?
How about that? Isn't it beautiful?
Look at her carefully and remember it well.
No way...
Bitch... Making fun of me.
Who do you think I am?!
Bro!
What?!
Please stop it!
If you keep this up, you'll kill the girl!
Shut up!
Don't you dare tell me what to do.
Never... tell me... what to do.
Shit!
This situation is far more humiliating than it looks...
I'm...
Hold on.
...that person. Got it?
What? No way!
You can start now. Hurry up!
I'm Kate the pet.
I'm going to be trained from today on.
I just lost my virginity today,
but I can't stop wanting more!
I must be a sex maniac.
But I'll do my best to be a good pet.
Thanks for having me!
Why the hell do I have to say that?
Good, Kate.
Always respect Amy as your senior
in masochism and learn from her example.
My senior? What does that make me,
a junior masochist?
Answer!
Yes, understood!
As far as tastes go,
I like both your faces about the same.
For hair, I like Amy's better.
Dark and wet to the touch.
It's really sexy.
I didn't choose to be a redhead, you know.
But for her proportions, I like Kate better.
I've always had confidence in my breasts!
But Amy is taking growth stimulants,
so she'll also have great breasts soon.
What the hell...
So... how do your privates feel?
I see your hard training is bearing fruit.
This squeezing force is no joke.
Master Brick...
Please...
Master Brick... Please...
You can't!
What can't I do, Kate?
No... U-Um, I mean...
Amy is my pet.
I can do whatever the hell I want with her!
But... That is... But...
But I'm your pet too.
You just said that.
And yet you've been favoring her all the time. It's not fair!
If you train me well,
I can do a lot better than her in no time.
I also...
I see. Now you're asking
to be trained yourself?
Huh?
Dick, I'm leaving Amy to you.
Gotcha, bro.
Master Brick!
Don't worry. I'm not abandoning you.
Only until Dick gets the hang of it.
She really likes Brick. That's why...
What's so special about him?
Nothing at point MW9.
Nothing at point N3.
Nothing at point NE5.
Are you sure we're in the right area?
Yes. We lost the transmission
within a kilometer of here.
Find the entrance to the hideout
or the Lieutenant's signal, anything!
We'll find them even if we have
to comb the entire desert!
So what does the training involve?
A whip? A candle?
First, you'll be put into a box
of sandworms in my room.
What? You mean those sandworms?
Yeah.
What? But I'll be eaten alive.
Don't worry. They're only maggots.
About the size of your finger.
It's just that there are thousands of them.
What?
What? What do you want?
How dare you disgrace me
like that in front of the boss.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
It's no big deal to fail
at picking up a woman.
Picking up, you say?
My promotion was postponed
because of that.
Hey, now. Don't act like a kid.
Kate is good game, all right.
But a single girl can't affect your promotion.
Are you saying I lack something
besides the points?!
You really don't get it?
You bastard!
As expected of Mr. Exec Candidate Jenkins.
Being violent and short-fused
during training is all you've got.
It's not all violence and pain.
It turns into pleasure in no time!
Watch out!
Kate!
Bitch!
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
How are you, Brick?
He won't escape his fate
of getting sliced up by me!
Brick!
Listen here.
Don't you dare touch my Kate again.
"My"?
Shit...
Really, Cathy? I couldn't find you
in the training room, and you were here?
You're late.
Yeah, that jerk Jenkins
required my attention.
I see.
Who's this woman?
And where is he now?
Taking a nap.
So that's her?
The Galaxy Police public safety officer?
Yeah, I'll introduce her to you.
Name's Kate. I think she's a Second Lieutenant.
Oh?
She's pretty.
Not that pretty.
You're much more gorgeous today.
Thank you. Such a compliment
from you is delightful.
But I've never seen you
treating your pet yourself before.
I just understand her real value.
I'll sell her for a good price.
Okay, should be good now.
The cut will heal soon.
Come on, Kate. Greet Cathy.
Bro, where are you going like that?!
He'll pay.
Don't be silly!
You need to treat your wounds!
Shut up!
He's going to pay.
Lieutenant, we can detect
the transmitter again!
What?
Where? Bring it up on the screen.
In the NNW2 zone.
Good. Order all aircraft to scramble.
I'm getting trained starting today. I'm Kate.
Please teach me to be a good pet,
as my senior in masochism.
Hey!
It's all right.
She didn't know, after all.
I'm not your senior in masochism.
Actually...
I'm Brick's wife.
Huh? It can't be...
Hey, Cathy.
Don't say anything yet. I have an idea.
Leave this to me. I promise you'll like it.
I'm Brick's wife, but that's not all.
I train girls, just like he does.
Whatever belongs to Brick, belongs to me.
Which means I'm also your master.
You'll come to accept it very soon.
For now, I will be your trainer.
What?!
Brick...
You're back sooner than I expected.
Yes. We caught the man
who had the Second Lieutenant's transmitter.
When we realized he was with Ulfan,
we thought we'd have a hard time with him.
But unexpectedly, in return for drawing a map
to their hideout, he asked to be let go.
This was almost too easy.
We're already gearing up for battle.
Oh, nothing to complain about there.
I'm putting you in charge
of the assault on their base.
Really, sir?
Yeah. I'll back you up on the public front.
We'll start the attack
at 3:10 Doune standard time!
It seems Brick was treating you as a pet,
but I'll train you as a slave.
Wh-What?
I don't want some middle-aged
deviant woman to be my trainer.
Brick won't stand for that.
Say something, Brick.
That face and pose are great.
I've never seen a girl as fit for it as you.
That costume also fits
like it was made for you.
What are you talking about?
I feel like a sausage in this!
Ow!
I want you to thank me.
Now!
Thank you very much.
It didn't sound sincere.
You were supposed to say,
"Thank you for a present
that fits a lewd girl like me so well, Master."
Th-Thank you for a present...
that fits a lewd girl like me so well.
You forgot "Master."
Didn't you hear me?!
Say "Master"!
You don't understand
your position yet, do you?
But it's only a matter of time.
You'll see how you'll want to say it soon.
How much of this can you endure?
Put on a good show for me.
No... No, please stop!
Well, well.
It went in without any resistance.
You must really like being tortured.
N-No...
Now I know why Brick liked you.
Well then, how about I give you some more?
Brick...
Don't...
Don't look...
at me like that!
Brick...
Brick!
Now, call me "Master"!
My...
My only master...
is Brick.
So?
Excellent.
Kate. Kate!
You did well enduring it all the way.
It's important that you don't call anybody else "Master."
I can safely leave you to Brick now.
We used to be married,
but not anymore.
We're both sadists,
so it's no wonder we broke up.
We're just coworkers now,
nothing more than that.
I'm sorry for lying.
So... take good care of him for me.
What a relief...
She's all yours.
Thanks. You saved me some trouble.
No problem.
But you also have to treat Kate well.
Maybe she'll be a good wife for you later.
Good wife, huh?
Chief, could you take a look at this?
There's been a hovercraft parked
outside the hideout for a while now.
Probably some lovebirds.
Every night around now, someone always comes to have hover sex around here.
Women like that are totally useless to Ulfan
and can't be used as goods.
See? What'd I tell you?
This is why night shifts are so boring.
If anything, I'd prefer a full-scale attack
by the Galaxy Police to this.
We've taken over the radar room.
Yes, Jenkins's information was correct.
Yes, confirmed.
Yes.
At 3:10? Understood, Major Smith.
Where am I?
Brick!
Are you awake?
Is this the sandworm room?
No way.
This is my bedroom.
I see. I thought it was too clean to be-
What did you say?
What's the matter, Kate?
I mean... Should a pet be in its master's bed?
It's okay. Calm down.
Sorry I didn't tell you about that before.
But you see, being a masochist
is more than just a physical thing.
If you can't mentally turn pain into pleasure,
you can't become a true masochist.
I'll do it!
I'll be a real masochist, I promise!
So, please let me stay with you.
Brick...
Don't be such a crybaby, Kate.
But...
I'm a pet.
I was a virgin just this morning.
I haven't even had a shower yet.
And now I'm in your bed.
I'm so...
Please, Brick.
I can't believe I'm feeling so horny.
I can feel my body shaking.
It's an attack!
Attack?
It's a rather loud knock on the door
from your friends.
All right!
Go!
Come on!
Are you okay?
The strings are cutting
into my skin from moving.
Ready?!
All done! It can go right now.
Good job.
Cathy, take care of her.
Okay. Leave it to me.
Brick!
Aren't you coming with us?
I still have things to do here.
Then, I'll stay too.
No! You go with Cathy.
No! I don't want to!
I want to be with you!
I won't ever let go of you!
Listen. You're my woman!
I won't let anyone have you.
Not the Galaxy Police, not Ulfan.
I'll come for you, no matter what.
You're the one I'll always come back to.
Wait for me.
Cathy! Go.
Be careful.
Don't worry. I can't die.
After all, I've only made love to you twice.
Idiot.
Let's go! Move it!
Bro's such a sentimental guy.
Don't raise your head!
How the hell did they get
into our secret passageway?
What's going on?!
Burn! Burn!
Everybody who gets in my way will burn!
No, I have to finish Brick off myself.
Go! Go!
Don't let them get away!
Boss!
All the slaves are packed into the shuttle!
What's this?
The self-destruct system.
Huh? Are we going to destroy the hideout?
Never leaving any evidence
has kept our organization afloat.
All or nothing. That's the Ulfan way.
Remember that.
Captain, what could this siren be?
Captain, they're backing off.
Should we go after them?
Tch, they're running for it?
I didn't expect it to happen so soon.
We're withdrawing. Contact HQ
and tell everybody to retreat.
Let's hurry. We've only got ten minutes.
Jenkins?
Hurry. We have no time.
Boss, did you like my present?
So... you led them here?
But I was worried they wouldn't finish the job,
so I came here myself.
Jenkins!
Jenkins, do you understand the situation?
Of course, I know that time is running out...
for you!
Tch. He's gone mad.
Boss!
It's just a scratch.
Dick!
Hey, how long are you going to hide?!
Listen. When I jump out to distract him,
run for the other door.
Brick, take my gun.
Come out already!
Thanks.
Shit, he's always getting in my way!
You fucking eyesore!
I'm going to kill you!
Is that all?
Didn't you say you'd kill me?
S-Stay away!
P-Please forgive me! I was wrong.
You can have that woman.
I'll give up on the promotion too.
I'll do anything you want.
So, please let me go!
No... Don't shoot me, please!
Th-The hideout!
It self-destructed.
No way...
I won't...
last much longer, either.
Ouch...
Cathy, are you okay?
Cathy!
Hang on. Hang on, Cathy!
Listen to me, Kate.
I can't go on.
And this hover can't, either.
So from now on,
you have to walk on your own.
No! I can't leave you here-
Kate!
Cathy!
I promised Brick. So did you.
But the hideout is gone.
Don't you trust him?
I do. I trust him.
Then you should keep your promise.
Go straight east from here,
and you'll find the mining site.
Right. The place where you were kidnapped.
That's the designated meeting place.
There's an emergency kit in the trunk,
so take it with you.
It has mineral water
and some nutritional drinks.
Less than two hours until sunrise.
You need to cover some distance before it gets hot.
Now go, and hurry, Kate.
And... when you see Brick,
tell him I kept my promise.
Brick! You came!
I never doubted it!
I knew you would come and get me.
You're finally awake, Lieutenant?
Lieutenant!
Anyway, we're glad that you're all right.
But what happened?
Honestly, we almost gave up on rescuing you
after their hideout self-destructed.
The only possible way for you to survive
was if Ulfan had taken you away.
Bastard... You were going to sacrifice me
all along, weren't you?
So, with heavy hearts, we retreated
and began reassembling the search party.
That's when, by pure coincidence,
we found you on our way back, unconscious.
We danced in gladness and gave thanks to the divine hand of fate.
That's how we rescued you.
By the way, why were you there?
I...
I'm sorry. I'd rather not discuss it now.
This mission must've been
an absolute nightmare for you.
But thanks to your excellent work,
our operation was successful.
Don't worry about the rest
and get some sleep.
Um, is the enemy...
Were the enemy commanders all arrested?
Or were they all killed in the explosion?
Unfortunately, an escape shuttle was seen
flying off just before the hideout exploded.
Based on how well the self-destruct worked,
the boss and the executives must've escaped on it.
But don't worry. No matter where they flee,
we'll hunt them down and finish them off.
No, better yet, we'll arrest them.
Yes, sir.
Thank God. They've all escaped.
Brick must be alive.
He'll come back to me. He promised.
Brick, we'll meet again one day.
I know we will!
The universe is a small place, after all.
The moon's tears feel as heavy as my own
I sense a fleetingness in your profile
This love is frustrating, turning its back on me
Yet I still want to see you
I whispered, "I love you"
"I'll be with you forever"
If you, even through countless long nights...
If you were by my side, holding me close
I wouldn't need anything else
Showered in the spilled and melted moonlight
I felt like I could finally be honest
So I whispered, "I love you"
Some months later
Wow, it's so cold!
Here, it's actually tolerable.
Brick!
Miss!
We have a nice hotel just for you!
Everybody!
Are you here for sightseeing?
I envy you. I'm here for a job.
Original Subtitles
Translation Check
Timing &
Typesetting
Editing &
QC
Raw Provider
Tokyo Rose
Perevodildo
Collectr
Paul Geromini
Muzussawa
ProxyMan
Attention, please!
Now on the path for another dimension.
When I was dancing, a mirage in the desert
Oh, I see an oasis
Bathed in moonlight
I was dreaming of embracing you
Suddenly I realize
Just how I'm really feeling
Come over to me, I wanna be close to you
Baby, touch me now
Thinking 'bout you every night
You know me, baby, don't you fall in love
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever
Oh, baby feel for you
You know it, baby, don't you fall in love!
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you
Desert Planet 2
Sex Pet Kate
The erotic sci-fi original video animation that became a huge hit among fans,
the sequel to Desert Planet: Female Public Security Officer Kate is finally complete.
The long-awaited sequel is finally here  !
And the erotic elements in it
far exceed the first part.
A woman writhing in the pleasure of being abused
When I was dancing, a mirage in the desert
A girl who becomes submissive
despite her true feelings when tortured.
Oh, I see an oasis
Harsh training, sadism...
Bathed in moonlight
I was dreaming of embracing you
and even more training await you here.
Resignation  -
Suddenly I realize
The two become separated
in the heat of battle.
Just how I'm really feeling
Come over to me, I wanna be close to you
Baby, touch me now
Thinking 'bout you every night
You know me, baby, don't you fall in love
Kate, who willingly becomes a pet
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Her hands and feet bound
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you
A further power-up on Part 1,
with even more tears and action.
You know it, baby, don't you fall in love!
At the mercy of the whip and the electric prod
Take it easy
Take me far away!
Teased, intoxicated,
and falling into depravity...
You're too close, too much to handle
Teased, intoxicated,
and falling into depravity...
Don't let me down
Teased, intoxicated,
and falling into depravity...
What awaits these two?
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you
Desert Planet 2: Sex Pet Kate.
Desert Planet 2
Sex Pet Kate
Released simultaneously on VHS and LD
on February 25, 1995
Simultaneous VHS and LD release
on February 25, 1995.