Original
Subtitles
Tokyo Rose
Translation Check,
Timing & Typesetting
Perevodildo
Editing &
Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Paul Geromini
Muzussawa
Raw Provider
ProxyMan
Okizari Fansubs presents
Desert Planet
Female Public Security Officer Kate
When I was dancing, a mirage in the desert
Oh, I see an oasis
Bathed in moonlight
I was dreaming of embracing you
Suddenly I realize
Just how I'm really feeling
Come over to me, I wanna be close to you
Baby, touch me now
Thinking 'bout you every night
You know me, baby, don't you fall in love...
I'm Second Lieutenant Kate Curtis of the Galactic Union Military Security Department.
Currently undergoing training
for undercover duty.
You know what, forget the formal introduction.
I'm 19 years old. My three sizes are
88-58-90, from top to bottom.
My weight is... a secret!
I have natural curly red hair, and I was one of the sexiest girls at the military academy.
But that was actually
just the beginning of my misfortunes.
Would you hear me out?
Lieutenant Kate Curtis, coming in.
What's with this sly-looking old fox?
I am Major Jones,
the commander of this mission.
I will brief you on the operation.
This is Doune, the planet
where you'll be stationed.
On the surface, it's just a run-of-the-mill frontier planet,
but the number of young women
disappearing on it has grown each year.
What's more, there's a pattern to these cases.
Do you think it's an organized crime case?
That's what I want you to find out.
Oh? Does this mean...
Ah, no... I mean, am I to serve
as live bait, sir?
Yeah. The truth is, all the victims
had some things in common,
so the bait needs all those qualities as well.
First, she has to be very pretty.
Secondly, she has to be buxom.
Yup, that's me all right.
Lastly...
Lastly?
She has to be an airheaded, willing girl.
Say what?
That's why I chose you for this mission.
And yet somehow I wish you hadn't.
Let me introduce you to Lieutenant Smith.
He'll be your backup during this mission.
Second Lieutenant Kate Curtis.
Lieutenant Smith.
Lieutenant, show her the equipment.
Doune is mostly desert.
You'll need the equipment
in this suitcase to deal with it.
Is it a heatproof suit of sorts?
Something like that.
But in this case, a clothing cooling device
alone won't be enough protection.
So don't forget to cover yourself fully
with this heatproof cream.
Fully, sir?
That's right. All over your whole body.
My whole body?
Down there too, without exception.
Down there too, without exception, right?
We don't want you to get burned.
Don't get... huh?
This piece of equipment
contains a transmitter.
Isn't that a vibrator?
Keep it on you at all times during the operation,
so you can send us a signal.
I-It goes down there too?
That's right.
...I would've said if I were joking.
Then stop saying things like that deadpan.
The real transmitter is built
into these earrings.
This is just something to maintain
your "willing girl" facade.
Naturally, you may use it
however you see fit.
No, I'm sure that won't be necessary...
That's all for now.
You change clothes at the station,
go down to the planet,
and follow the instructions
from the communications unit.
Good luck.
Understood, sir.
So here I am, trying my best
to play an airheaded girl.
But what am I supposed to do
if they can't rescue me before I get raped?
I'm still a virgin, you know!
Ladies and gentlemen, this flight
will arrive at relay station Bronve shortly.
ETA is 10 AM Doune Standard Time.
Passengers transferring to Doune,
please proceed to gate three.
Flight 341 from Doune has just arrived.
The next departure will be at 10:30.
Shower room...
Well then...
Crap! I only have twenty minutes left.
I have to hurry and get changed.
What are these?! There's nothing but sex toys and skimpy dresses in here!
This swimsuit is the only
remotely decent thing here.
That lecherous old fox!
No!
This is Doune, girl.
You knew where you were going.
Now bring that ass here,
and I'll have a go at it.
Stop!
Freeze! I'm a Galaxy Police Officer!
Leave her alone!
Shit!
I won't forget this!
Damn it, that was so close!
Why did you get in my way,
you useless bimbo?
You don't look familiar.
Are you really an officer?
H-Hey, move your foot!
You're talking to an officer!
I'm from the Galaxy Police Force!
I'd watch your mouth if I were you.
I'm a captain.
So, you want to say that again,
Ms. Fresh-out-of-the-academy?
It hurts...
Captain, I beg your pardon.
Would you please move your foot?
Call me "Captain, ma'am."
It hurts...
Please, Captain, ma'am, forgive me.
I've been on that rapist's tail
for a long time.
I was so close to catching him
with his pants down and getting my revenge.
You useless bitch!
Pay attention now, girl.
I'm Doctor Eva.
I'm with the Space Military Hospital at Tajim.
If you ever get sent there,
I'll take good care of you.
That hurt...
I can't believe she's a doctor.
She must be just some whore
who's really into getting raped!
That really hurt...
H-Hey!
Why do I have to dress like this?
I can be the bait just fine without wearing
such embarrassing clothes.
Miss...
You're shaking. Are you okay?
Do you need help?
No, I'm fine.
Good, I just wanted to make sure.
By the way, are you going
to Doune on vacation?
Yes. It's my first time here.
What a coincidence!
It's the same for me.
I feel the hand of fate is at work here.
How about it? Wouldn't you like to enjoy
your vacation with me under the scorching sun?
No! Don't touch me!
That prudish bitch.
Next time I see her,
I won't ask so nicely!
The remaining time to Tajim airport
is about one hour.
Please enjoy our video service until then.
My first assignment, and it sucks...
An informational tourist video?
What's that?!
This untamed planet will ravish you.
Once you get raped by a desert nomad,
you'll be burning with his passion.
If they run this video every day,
no wonder the number of cases keeps climbing!
Between the major, Doctor Eva, and the tourism video...
What the hell is going on with this planet?!
I wanna go home!
Wow, it's hot!
It's still tolerable here.
In the desert of Doune, it's much worse.
Oh, is that so?
H-Hey, what is he looking at?
I can't take it anymore.
But, if I hide it, I can't play an airheaded girl.
Oh, well.
Are you here for sightseeing?
I envy you. I'm here for a job.
I have to stay on this hell of a planet
just to make my sales goal.
Really? That sounds awful.
If you have the time,
we should go on a date.
No, Kate, be patient. This is your job.
Still, it's awfully embarrassing!
Can you hear me? It's Jones.
Yes. I read you well.
Good. Here are your orders.
Can you see the row of doors
at the far end of the corridor on your left?
A handsome boy in a red shirt
is standing over there.
He's a bellboy at a love hotel and a low-tier thug,
tasked with inviting women traveling alone
for a "guided tour" of the erotic kind.
Get his attention and wait
for the organization to take the bait.
Understand? Then let the operation begin.
Now, hold on a minute. From what he said,
they must already have a suspect in mind.
They never told me that!
Did you make sure?
Yeah, I went an extra mile to...
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a hotel.
Is Pixy a nice hotel?
Well, yeah. It's C-level.
Huh? Um... But I think the single rooms are all booked.
That's fine. I don't mind the price.
A double room is nice too,
so spacious. Right?
Yes... Thank you. I'll take your luggage.
Oh, thank you!
Miss, I was asking him for a sightseeing tour.
Wouldn't you like to go with me?
You still have some time before check-in.
Oh, I don't know.
Aren't you busy with your work now?
I work at night. Please don't be shy.
Let's go now.
Ugh. Why are they all so handsy?
Oh, aren't you assertive?
This way, please.
It's going well so far.
Yes, my eyes never fail me.
I picked the size of her dress perfectly.
All right, then. Take care of the rest.
I'll be in the usual place.
Understood.
Here you go.
Are we driving in a love hotel hover?
That's not good...
Come on.
Why do you have to sit so close to me?
There's plenty of room here.
Calling Captain Pixy. It's me, Dick.
So that's his name.
The clients requested a sightseeing tour first. Please tell the boss.
Boss?
Yes. That's right. A lady's solo trip.
Ready for the usual special treatment.
We will take the route from B7, turning at A4.
We'll stop by S6.
We'll go from A2 to B3 on our way back.
Hold on... What are you touching?!
Miss, you should drink this.
This is the hottest time
to be in the desert.
This must be an aphrodisiac.
Too bad. I already know
this type doesn't last long.
What's this? The blue one looks tastier.
It controls your perspiration
and prevents dehydration.
Red for women, blue for men.
But they work and taste basically the same.
Yeah, it's good stuff.
You'd better take it before you get heatstroke.
If I don't drink, they may get suspicious.
Just a little...
Oh no! I accidentally drank it all.
Okay, we can go now.
It'll be a little shaky, but don't worry.
This hover is in perfect order.
Got it? Don't do anything
until you find their hideout.
Roger.
Okay, go.
Sorry I'm late!
Hey, hurry and follow those two cars.
Y-Yes, sir...
Miss, what's your name?
I'm Brick, a freelance salesman.
I'm Kate. My job is... a secret!
Do you mind, Kate?
Oh, come on...
Huh? What's that?
Oh, that's a sandworm hunter.
And the ones on the left are hunting moles.
I wonder if the major is keeping up.
Hey, get us beside them.
Okay.
Nothing but desert here, so they're not going to stop soon. Over.
It's a cop!
It's fun to hunt for moles,
but sandworms are valuable because you can extract perfume from their waste.
Oh, really?
A rocket launcher?
What was that just now?
Crap, it's a worm!
A sandworm showed up!
Are they going to be okay?
They should be.
Seems like there's more of them.
I hope so.
That was a sandworm.
They emerge from the sand very suddenly.
What sandworm? It was a missile shot
from a launcher, clear as a day.
But what if they killed
the major and his squad?
I'm scared! Let's go back.
Oh, Kate. You're shaking. It's okay.
Don't worry. We'll be in a safe zone soon.
Until I can make contact with them,
I have to follow the plan.
Oh crud, that drink is starting to work!
It wasn't an aphrodisiac. It was a diuretic!
This isn't good...
There's no way I can defend myself
from him now.
Thank God...
Please, let me get out.
Oh? What are you going to do outside?
Pee! Please, let me go!
Did you hear that? She said "pee"!
She said it so loud.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Monsters... A lady is in trouble, and they're laughing!
This thing is hard to clean up.
Please take your mess outside.
Hey, if you don't do it quick,
you're going to explode.
Please, don't come any closer.
If you want to pee, go down
those stairs and do it on the sand.
It won't make any sound there.
Kate... Kate?
Lieutenant?
We've been attacked... by that organization.
Position unknown.
Somewhere in the middle of the desert.
We're atop a stone platform approximately six meters high and ten meters square.
There are some abandoned crane trucks
and boring machines.
Roger. Continue... your mission...
When the time... the rest to us.
So anyway, all I have to do is arrest those guys
and take them away, right? Yippee!
Quicksand!
This is bad. I can't move.
Brick, help!
Please, Brick! Brick!
Don't just hold the loop! Pass your hands through it and hold the rope tight.
Brick...
Okay!
Here we go!
Ouch!
Brick? Hey, what happened?
H-Hey! Cut it out with the distasteful pranks!
Let me introduce you.
That's the famous sand mole of Doune.
You can't eat its meat,
but its skin is perfect for a heat-resistant coat.
What are you talking about? Help me!
I don't want to hear about those monsters!
Oh? I'm surprised you didn't faint.
Please, raise me out of here already!
It's going to eat me soon! H-Hey!
Stop!
No! That's the wrong way!
No! Help me!
If you don't want to die,
do what I tell you.
I will! Just bring me up already!
All right!
Put me on the ground already, Brick.
Hey, I'm still hanging.
My hands are going numb.
I see.
Dick, call the boss. We have the prey.
All right, bro!
Wh-What? Those two were accomplices?
Well, then. For starters, I expect a "thank you" for saving you.
Why should I...
Thank you.
Looking closer, I'd rate you pretty high
in both face and body.
At least 50 points each.
Oh, rates me high, huh?
But this isn't the time to be excited!
What's going to happen to me now?
What was your first experience,
and how many men have you had?
Come on, speak up!
I... I haven't had any.
What? You must be kidding.
Come on. Tell me the truth!
No... Please, believe me! It's true!
It's true!
Well now, seems you're not lying!
I believe you, miss.
I give you 100 points!
I won't have to work for at least six months.
By the way, is that even your real name?
And what do you do?
I'm Kate Curtis. I'm... a stewardess!
Excellent. 150 points.
You'll get me promoted to an exec.
You look like a goddess to me, Kate.
Bro...
Sorry to interrupt the fun,
but the boss says to return
with the woman right now.
Idiot! We were just getting to the good part.
Tell him we'll be back by nightfall.
We'd better go now, bro.
After all, it's about Jenkins.
Jenkins?
It must be about your promotion.
No, if that was the case,
he would've notified me in advance.
They wouldn't do it in such a rush.
But if it involves Jenkins...
Okay.
Oh... Bro, what are you doing?
If you use that...
I'll have my fun with her in the hover.
No time to do it here.
But...
It's fine! You prepare the hover for sex.
Sorry.
A drug?
I was going to give you proper treatment without hurrying,
but we have to rush back to the hideout.
So, I'll have to use this. An extremely effective aphrodisiac from Planet Alreune.
No! Please, anything but that!
Don't be shy.
It works best for hover sex.
You see? Right here, you're this excited already.
It's awful!
In a few minutes, it'll kick in.
Along with the intense vibrations of hover sex, it'll set you on fire.
He'll pay for this. I'll arrest all of them,
if I have to do it all by myself.
Dick, did you punch the auto-drive data
into the computer?
Sure, bro. We'll get to the hideout
even if we're all asleep.
Good.
I feel so miserable.
They tied me up with my own underwear.
But I'm sure there'll be an opening for me.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, is this how you always kidnap women?
It depends on the woman.
Usually, we let them relieve
themselves there, then rape them.
Well, thanks for saying
I'm not a usual woman.
Then we train them thoroughly at the hideout
and turn them into sex slaves.
Will I be trained too?
I don't know. It's up to the boss.
But I would rather train you
as a prostitute myself.
A prostitute?
Of course.
It'd be a waste to reserve
a body this marvelous for a single man.
You must share good things
with everyone else.
For now, Dick and I will have
our fun with you.
Who do you think you are?
What should I do? At this rate,
I can forget about arresting them.
I wonder what our Kate has in her bag.
Ah! No, don't open it!
To think Kate, a virgin, is into this stuff.
No, you're wrong! I can explain!
How am I wrong?
It sure doesn't look like a swab to me.
This isn't fit for a virgin.
Maybe this is?
Bear with it, Kate.
No...
The drug is working. I can't take this.
Time to move on.
No! Please, no!
No!
Which vibrator do you normally use?
I don't use anything like that.
Tell me the truth, or else...
You get this.
I'm telling you the truth!
I've never used such toys!
Oh? So you prefer fingers to vibrators?
Stop it.
Your first climax today. How many more times will you come before we arrive at the hideout?
When it's a woman such as her...
Major, our agents were attacked.
What the hell?
Our agents tailing Kate just called.
It appears someone attacked them.
What about the Second Lieutenant?
For now, we've radioed her
to cancel her mission.
Lieutenant, get 365A-08 on the line.
It looks like she's safe for now.
We need to have an emergency meeting.
All right, time for the main part.
I'm finally about to lose my virginity...
by getting raped here,
in the middle of some desert!
It can't be!
Now, get on top of me.
It wasn't supposed to be this way.
No...
It hurts!
No, please stop!
I finally...
It's only starting now.
It hurts...
It hurts!
Strange... It's strange.
I've never felt like this before.
What's happening to me?
You keep wailing that it hurts, but your face looks like you're melting from pleasure.
No, that's not true!
Oh? Then why do you keep moving
your hips without any help from me?
It's... because of the drug!
Ready for the next round?
Hey, Dick, your balls must be blue already.
You can have her now.
It's me, Brick. Open up.
Dick! Show some restraint!
If you work her that much,
she'll be worn out!
Dick! Put something on!
Kate, are you planning to sleep forever?
We'll be meeting the boss soon.
At least put your underwear on!
Oh, right.
Your hands are still tied.
Hold on a sec.
Okay, let's use this.
N-No way, I can't wear that!
You think so?
No, I like this one.
The boss'll like it too.
What's there to be embarrassed about?
It was in your own bag.
Yep. You look good in black.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
Brick?
You just had your first experience.
It must be hard to walk.
It's Brick! I'm back!
Wh-What is this?
Aren't we in the middle of the desert?
Okay, just be a good girl now.
You're late.
Come on, Boss. You know how it is.
I was in S6. I couldn't come any faster.
Well, have a seat now.
Oh? So he's the boss?
The guy who hit on me at the spaceport.
So he's one of them?
So, what's up, Boss? Why did you want me
to bring the woman so soon?
I have some questions for her.
For this woman?
Lately, the police have been getting closer and closer.
If she's a public safety officer,
she'd certainly know something about it.
Officer? Aren't you a stewardess?
Y-Yes, that's what I actually am.
Tch. Was I the only one in the dark?
That's why we need to train her quickly
and get more information.
Okay, I get the picture now.
And what about him?
Bastard! How dare you take this woman before me?!
She was supposed to be mine
in the first place!
Hey, now. Did you forget our rules?
Finders keepers.
I can do whatever I want with her.
My team dealt with her cop friends!
I have a claim on her too!
I see. So you were the one
who attacked our guys? Bastard!
Besides, the Boss assigned me
the job of abducting women for us!
So? She dumped you back at the station.
You screwed up. I saw it.
That's right. Screw you.
That's enough, both of you.
Jenkins, it's not your day, plain and simple.
The woman belongs to Brick now.
This conversation is over.
Brick, I'll definitely pay you back for this!
You get nothing! Good day, sir!
With that narrow mind, he can never
make a good Ulfan executive.
Ulfan? Really?
That face tells me you do know something.
N-No! Don't make me go
through plastic surgery!
Calm down.
Please! Help me, somebody!
Calm down, dammit!
We're not going to do anything to your body!
Just teach you some sex techniques, that's all.
Can I really trust you?
Of course. Only low-level women
need to go through plastic surgery.
We wouldn't harm a high
quality woman like you.
That is... unless you slack off
in your training or practice.
Brick, why don't you show her the dungeon?
If she sees those slaves,
she'll be happy to accept the training.
Good idea. Before putting her in the worm box,
I'll take her to the dungeon.
I'm finally entering the heart of the organization.
You'll pay for stealing my virginity!
Here we are.
The slave training room is beyond this door.
No way...
No!
The moon's tears feel as heavy as my own
I sense a fleetingness in your profile
This love is frustrating, turning its back on me
Yet I still want to see you
I whispered, "I love you"
"I'll be with you forever"
If you, even through countless long nights...
If you were by my side, holding me close
I wouldn't need anything else
Showered in the spilled and melted moonlight
I felt like I could finally be honest
So I whispered, "I love you"
Attention, please!
Now on the path for another dimension.
When I was dancing, a mirage in the desert
Oh, I see an oasis
Bathed in moonlight
I was dreaming of embracing you
Suddenly I realize
Just how I'm really feeling
Come over to me, I wanna be close to you
Baby, touch me now
Thinking 'bout you every night
You know me, baby, don't you fall in love
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you
You know it, baby, don't you fall in love!
Take it easy
Take me far away
You're too close, too much to handle
Don't let me down
I'll never fall in love without you
With me forever!
Oh, baby feel for you