Look, I'll take it easy, okay? Easy...
Wh-Who's there?
What's with those looks?
Totally gross.
Karin
I-It's you, Karin!
So this is the best
the Dark Magician Donpapa can offer?
Can't even conquer
that micro-nation for us?
C'mon, Führer Taiman is waiting.
There's no time to be tumbling down the ramp, hurry up!
It was you who threw that blade!
Fuhrer Taiman
Führer Taiman! I will now update you on the progress of your plan for world domination.
First, the US is 40% conquered,
Canada at 50%,
Japan at 56%,
China at 58%,
the leader in Europe is Italy at 53%,
the Middle East is at 74% average.
The former Soviet block
boasts an impressive rate of 85%!
It seems to proceed
even faster than planned.
Yes! At the current rate,
in five more years,
the world will be united
under your rule, milord!
All of these achievements
are the fruit of hard work of Karin Fox.
Karin.
Milord?
You need to make space
for another medal again?
Congratulations!
I’m simply doing my duty to the Führer.
Just being of use to him is enough for me.
Speaking of which...
What became of the mission to conquer
the Champon Kingdom that I assigned to the Dark Magician Donpapa?
Oh, a-about that...
My sin is beyond forgiveness, my Führer!
Please don't take it as a sign of my weakness,
but if only you could help me
in some way with the Champon...
It went south over there, I take it?
Well, that's fine. Karin!
Sir?
Your next mission
is to take Donpapa’s place
and make sure the Champon Kingdom falls.
Yes, sir.
Please wait, sir!
Give me another chance to redeem myself!
No, you have served me well
for a long time.
You should get some rest now.
Not at all! I’m still fired up and ready to work—I don’t need any rest!
Donpapa.
Y-Yes?
We can't have you go outside
while completely plucked like that, can we?
We'll give you a medal of pity too.
Only half of it, though.
Right, congratulations are in order!
By the way, Führer, the Champon Kingdom
is a tiny micro-nation—
about as important
on the world stage as a speck of dust.
Why are you so particular about it?
Certainly, it's but a small country, for now...
For now?
I can't help but feel
that in the near future that country
will become a major obstacle
to my plans for world domination.
I understand, Your Excellency.
Champon Kingdom, huh?
In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state
that remains closed to the outside world.
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Another round, Champon
(Another round, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
I find a love letter in my shoe box,
so it's a dream after all
My strengths are innocence, passion, and tenacity
Hey baby, please ignore my uncool sides
Hey lady, with all my heart...
In the end
(In the end)
I will be
(I will be)
The greatest ninja or shogun,
but I'm not sure the world will be able to handle that!
We're free, aloha
Our hearts are wild, ho-ho-ho
Don't care about clubs, cram schools, or scores—
all that stuff can go up in the wind!
Water, gold, earth, fire, wood, aloha
Earth, heaven, underworld, ha-ha-ha
It'd be really hard for me to survive
without the TV, games, and videos—
won't someone bring them to me?
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Chapter 1: Mysterious Lady Came Around
by Means of Falling From the Sky
Hey, Takamaru!
Why are you in such a hurry?
I can't wait to see that thing
they found this morning!
Thing they found this morning?
What? Qué?
You'll know if you go there!
If I go? Where?
Just before the southern mountain pass!
H-Hey!
Crap...
You'd think this thing is convenient,
but when you have to go uphill,
it just rolls back—it's a burden, if anything!
What’s so curious about it?
Haven’t you ever seen a rock this big before?
Please look under the rock.
What about that tree?
That shoot can't grow up straight
because of this big rock above.
Don't you feel sorry for it?
Well, maybe a little.
So I figured, why not just move this huge rock somewhere else?
And...?
That's all.
You scatterbrain!
And I was an idiot for coming
just because you piqued my interest!
There's no way you can move
a rock this big.
And that pose too...
Lame like hell!
And I can’t just leave a friend in need...
Okay, I'll help you!
Ow-ow-ow...
Hey, you. Are you okay?
Worry not!
So it doesn’t want to be moved, after all?
Well, then...
That log broke, so it’s a dead end now.
Wanna blow it away with these?
Hey, you?
Plucking technique!
Oh my god!
End of tape.
What is that sound?
Great, great!
Very strong, my guy!
I thank you for instructive sparring!
Who are you telling it to?
Anyway, you gotta teach me
that badass move!
I would love to,
but it’s a difficult one.
I see. Difficult, huh?
I’m happy for you, Mr. Tree!
Hey, Kibo Takamaru, Yumega Al Zaemon,
what are you doing up here?
Ba-dump?
Hey, Mirai!
I'm not Al Zaemon, just Al!
It was for this shoot.
Because of the rock, it couldn’t grow straight, so I rescued it.
You rescued the tree?
It was growing under a huge rock!
So you smashed that rock to pieces?
Yes! We did.
“We?”
Come on, my guy.
Don’t let me down.
Mirai is always too demanding towards me.
O-Okay...
Yes! “We!”
I’m telling you—doing something nice
always makes me feel happy!
See? I can be useful too.
Is that so?
Then go clean up the rock chunks—
it’s blocking the road.
Rock chunks? You mean these?
All these?!
Mirai, you see, thing is...
You’re good kids. And good kids don’t forget
to clean up after they’re done playing.
Blast.
Ugh, I'm tired!
Mirai made us clean up the rocks, and then also watched us do it all the way to the end!
She doesn’t trust us at all!
Didn’t I tell you?
We can just replant trees
without smashing all the rocks around!
I considered that too.
Still, if that tree sprouted there, it probably has a mind to grow in that exact spot.
More of that sentient trees nonsense!
Huh? Well, if that rock ended up there,
maybe it had a mind to stay there forever too?
Maybe what I did was just arbitrarily destroy the relationship between the rock and the tree?
Hey! It's an airplane! A fighter!
Which country’s plane is it?
Why is it flying so low?
Not clear, sir.
Now that’s cool!
Yeah, it’s coming this way. Hey!
Huh?
What the hell was that?!
A lady flew it!
What?
Ouch!
Hey, that hurts!
We can’t stay here!
That plane has been
getting shot at for a while now.
Seems like that rocket is with the bad guys.
What was it you said
about some woman earlier?
The one piloting that plane under attack—it was a lady!
All right, let's help, then!
How? We don’t have any means to fly!
Don't worry!
Leave it to me!
Come on, Takamaru!
Out of my way!
Here, Takamaru!
It’s this guy’s time to shine!
You have a plane!
Did you make it?
Just right! Bull’s eye!
With this, even we can help!
It’ll have one hell of a virgin flight!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Something’s not right with that plane.
You stay here while I get closer
to observe the situation.
Ah, Mirai-sama, ba-dump!
Takamaru, get in the back!
Is this the back?
Huh? Are we going to row with our feet?
It's a human-powered plane.
Couldn’t you tell by the looks?
When you pedal that, the propeller spins,
the plane moves, gains speed, and then flies!
Then that makes me...
Engine! The engine!
Go ahead and pedal—as hard as you can!
Understood! As hard as I can!
As hard as I can!
All right, then.
Why don’t you give it a spin?
Incredible, Takamaru!
It’s a super power,
ultra power, miracle power!
We’ll get there in a flash!
Okay, take off!
We did it!
We’re really flying, Takamaru!
Engine condition is good! Let’s go!
Hey, baby! Al-sama has come to help,
so you can relax now.
Human-powered planes are quite fun!
Shut up! Engines aren’t supposed to talk!
You just keep pedaling without complaining!
And now, begin shooting down
the baddies! Let’s go!
Huh?
Whew... It’s pretty sturdy for a plane!
Shit!
Then how about this?
Bastard!
Got ‘em!
Oh shoot...
Now... Where was it...
What’s going on?
I, Tarobo, won’t forgive anyone who disrupts the peace in the Champon Kingdom—
even if it’s during my lunch break!
Who is that? I, the Baby Goblin Jiro,
won’t forgive them either!
No, Jiro! You wait here.
Father!
Father...
Crap!
They’re shot down!
Goddamn!
There’s a missile tailing us!
Not like I’ll let it catch up!
Easy now! You’re pedaling too hard!
You’re gonna tear away our wing! Hey, hello!
It’s caught up!
Oh, no!
Are you okay, boys?
Great Goblin Tarobo!
I don’t care which country that plane’s from—
I won’t let it wreak havoc here!
Yikes! No good!
Wait!
Let Tarobo take care of the rocket,
let’s save that lady now!
Yeah!
We’re here!
Gimme your hand!
Forget about that hunk of scrap!
She’s landed all the way up there!
You think she’s alive?
Are you okay, you two?
Mirai-dono!
We'll manage—
why don’t you check on that girl first?
Girl?
She’s unconscious now,
may be injured too.
You two do something on your own,
I can’t help right now!
Ah! Hey! Mirai!
Stop! Do you think you can escape
from Tarobo-sama?!
This is no longer my responsibility.
It’s tear gas...
Smart trick!
Like hell I’ll let you...
Oh dear me.
Did I tear it off?
Mirai-sama.
Mirai-sama?
A lady was riding it?
She may be injured!
They still haven’t brought the rope?
I’ve sent for it,
but it might take a little longer.
We’ve got to get up that cliff soon—
she could be hurt and in serious danger!
Father, I’m going to use this Ninja Kite.
There’s no time to climb
that cliff the usual way!
She’s a kite! A kite!
She was the turtle last time,
but it’s a kite now!
Takamaru, you’ll help me, won’t you?
Certainly!
Wait, Mirai.
We can’t leave such a dangerous mission to you children.
That's our duty to...
But father, this kite
can’t lift a grownup into the air!
Yes, but still...
Let’s leave this to children,
as part of their training.
Takamaru, Mirai, don’t let us down!
Takamaru, how does it look?
Too low?
The height is just right.
Now please start bringing me closer.
Okay, so far so good.
Please hang on!
What’s that?
No good! This is when the wind direction around here changes drastically!
You’re right! We’re in trouble!
Mirai-dono, we’re ready to take off!
Understood!
All right, pull back as soon as we can!
Oh no!
This is bad!
Takamaru’s pinned against the rocks!
If this keeps up, he’s gonna suffocate!
But with this violent wind,
it’s impossible to pull Mirai back!
Takamaru, are you okay?
I-I'm fine. I'm fine, but I won’t be able
to take it for much longer...
Takamaru!
Shit...
Goddammit!
Takamaru!
Damn it!
Isn’t there anyone who can help?!
Jiro!
Nice follow up, pipsqueak!
You saved us!
Oh! She came to her senses!
Where am I?
At the Champon Kingdom.
Champon?
How are you feeling?
You got away with just a scratch,
you’re lucky.
Still, you can’t downplay
what Takamaru pulled off either.
It wasn’t that hard, really.
Jiro-dono, you saved me.
I thank you once more.
What kind of Jiro—
son of the great goblin Tarobo—
would I be if I abandoned Mirai-san when she needs me?
Ugh! That kid sure is adorable!
Jiro-dono must really like Mirai-dono, huh?
Why is Karin here?
Huh? Is that your name—Karin-dono?
There was that rocket that shot you down.
Don’t you remember?
Rocket?
Huh? I can't remember!
Where did I come from?
Why did I have to be
shot down by a rocket?
I can't remember a thing!
You can't remember?
Then maybe you remember this?
Ah! This is mine.
At least you remember your pouch.
I picked it up for you.
Ah! Thank you!
This pouch is very important to me.
It wasn’t that hard to get, though.
The one who really helped you out
was the beaming boy right there.
Thank you!
Karin-dono, isn’t that right?
There are other ways to transmit your feelings to others without hugging them like that.
Like the clouds and the water flowing by,
I merely happened to be then and there.
Besides, it was also
just part of the training for me.
There he goes again
with his samurai jabber!
Our Takamaru is a really weird boy, y’know!
I-Is that so?
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer
I'm really glad that Karin-dono
was well after she fell from the sky.
But the machine man
that Al built is going wild.
He also asked me to attend with my macho techniques.
After all, the geothermal power plant is in big trouble!
Next time: The Machine Man Alfred
Blows his Whistle and Goes on a Rampage!