Hey, boy, whatcha lookin' at?
Hey, Takamaru!
What are you staring at?
At the sea...
and plenty of other things!
"Plenty of other things?"
Like what?
That I don't quite understand myself.
You're always talking in riddles like that.
DAIKATSUMARU
You sure have strange tastes.
Why do you want to go
to the Champon Kingdom of all places?
My friends are waiting for me.
In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state
that remains closed to the outside world.
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Another round, Champon
(Another round, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
I find a love letter in my shoe box,
so it's a dream after all
My strengths are innocence, passion, and tenacity
Hey baby, please ignore my uncool side
Hey lady, with all my heart...
In the end
(In the end)
I will be
(I will be)
The greatest ninja or shogun,
but I'm not sure the world will be able to handle that!
We're free, aloha
Our hearts are wild, ho-ho-ho
Don't care about clubs, cram schools, or scores—
all that stuff can go up in the wind!
Water, gold, earth, fire, wood, aloha
Earth, Heaven, Underworld, ha-ha-ha
It'd be really hard for me to survive
without the TV, games, and videos—
won't someone bring them to me?
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Chapter 4: Mirai-dono Dons Western Clothes
and Goes Wild
Okay, okay! Is there anyone still in the classroom?
We'll have Claude-kun coming today!
Oh, Karin-san?
Good morning, teacher.
You're not going to the dock with everyone?
It's because Yukari-chan asked me
to arrange flowers for her.
Yukari-chan
Yukari-chan?
Ah, you mean the vase?
Yes. There's also Ichiro-kun,
Nijiro-kun, and this here is Yumi-chan.
I've given names to them all.
Yes, I like the names you gave them!
Oh no, I forgot! We have to hurry.
Come on, Karin-san, you come too.
Okay.
I'm here!
Hey, kid! You're gonna have to unload your stuff yourself!
Okay!
Claude!
Claude-dono! Welcome back!
Toys! Toys! Toys!
Takamaru!
Al!
It really is you, Claude-dono!
It hurts, Al!
Coming like that without warning—
simply wonderful!
Dad allowed me to come.
So I've decided to spend
my summer vacation here.
So, does it mean you'll be staying for longer than last time?
Yeah.
Toys! You brought them, right?
Of course! All brand-new games,
fresh off the shelves. Look—they’re right there!
Wow! Great!
Al Zaemon.
As always, you're just after stuff
to waste time with, huh?
Mirai-san!
Long time no see.
I may need your help in some way while I'm here. Thank you in advance.
Claude, you've grown quite manly,
you know that?
Huh? You think so?
I wouldn't necessarily say so...
Welcome, Claude-kun!
Hey, everyone!
I missed you too!
My oh my, we're late after all.
What kind of person is Claude-san?
Ah, let's see...
His father’s a prominent Japanese diplomat,
and he really hit it off with Takamaru-kun and the others.
Hey, everyone! Let's all gather together
and return to the school now!
Okay!
Hey, Takamaru.
What is it?
I was practicing the Bity-Scratchy Style
on my own back in Tokyo.
Are you serious?
I wanted to show you the results of my training sometime later, would that be good?
Sure thing!
Splendid execution, Claude-dono!
Really?
Since you've advanced so far already,
you should train with this next.
Yes, keep it up.
And now...
1, 2...
1...
That's enough for today.
It's not a good idea to push yourself
right from the start.
You'll need to come to school starting tomorrow, right?
Thanks. But it was nothing, really.
But you people sure have a strange country.
You don't even have summer vacations.
Maybe you're right.
Speaking of which, you're no longer exempted from school, Claude-dono?
Yeah.
I'm glad to hear that.
But what was stopping you before?
Before?
I wonder what it was...
To tell you the truth, I don't know.
It turns out the school
was not all bad guys.
There are also games and comics...
I'd like to meet them.
Huh?
Your school friends,
and then the people of Japan too.
I'd like to see the world
and meet all sorts of people.
You should come someday.
Huh?
I'm inviting you to Japan!
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Can Al, Mirai-dono, and everyone else
come along too?
Of course!
You promise?
I promise!
Wow! That's it! I cleared the stage!
Good morning.
Claude-san!
Please wait!
And you are...
Karin!
I see. So you're living with Mirai-san?
Yeah.
Having lost your memory must be tough.
I've gotten used to it now.
More importantly, haven't you heard
anything from your father
about the end of Champon's isolation?
Huh?
I mean, your father
is a government diplomat, right?
He is, but I don't know anything.
I see.
But he said that one day, when Japan and Champon can stand as equals on the world stage,
Takamaru, his friends, and we Japanese kids
will be the ones to lead the way.
Does that include me too?
Of course! We'd be happy to have you.
Really? I'm so happy!
C-Come on, we're almost at school.
Wait, Claude-san!
Think of it, Al Zaemon—
your life is going to lapse into chaos.
Even this morning, if I hadn't come to wake you up, you'd have been late again!
Yeah, right!
Like I asked you!
Spare me your concern, all right?
No one asked you to wipe my ass
every single time, you nosy woman!
Yeah, that's right—why can't you be a little cuter, like Karin?
I-If that sounds hurtful,
you should really try...
Al-san!
You have no heart
to say that to poor Mirai-san!
She’s like that ’cause her family
makes a living as ninjas!
Good Morning, Karin.
Good morning, Al-san.
Hey, Claude, why are you walking to school with Karin?
It's a coincidence.
I ran into him on my way to school.
Really, that's all?
Ah, my goodness! I must hurry
and bring these flowers to Yukari-chan!
I'll help too!
Claude.
What do you think of that girl Karin?
She seems like a bit of a goody two-shoes.
I'm really not good at judging people.
We all have our good
and bad sides, don't we?
Still, it seems all the boys
prefer girls like her.
Maybe someone like Al does...
Okay, this should be all.
I'm back, Taka-chan!
And look what I brought you.
Is that the real thing?
Oh? Some fake pro wrestlers
were raising hell while I was away?
It seems the bald bird you kicked out the other day also had a hand in it.
Their minions that we captured back then
also seem to be an odd bunch.
Odd bunch?
Without delving too much into it,
this, plus the series of strange incidents lately...
I think we ought to be
more careful from now on.
Hm...
By the way, did you find your wife?
About that...
I see.
You nosy woman!
Yeah, that's right—why can't you be
a little cuter, like Karin?
Like Karin!
Even if I'm not concerned with such banalities
as acting manly or womanly,
I know I can become more feminine if I try!
I'll settle it once and for all tonight
with Great Goblin Tarobo.
And then...
with Kibo Takamaru!
Bite
Pinch
Scratch
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Pinching technique: Part II.
Focus your mind on your fingertips and twist your wrist. Pinch with explosive power...
Pinch the flesh between your fingers
as if intending to tear it away.
Bity-
Scratchy
School
Techniques
Bity-
Scratchy
School
Techniques
It's... Like this, right?
Wh-What was that?
Who?
Who's there?
M-Mirai-san!
Wh-What happened?
Why are you dressed up like that?
Th-That's a secret for now.
Here.
Put it away.
Um...
Claude!
Y-Yes?
What do you think?
Does this make me look like a city gal too?
Huh?
Don't take me wrong, I'm confident.
I just wanted to hear the opinion of the actual city dweller—you.
What do you think?
Aren't they an odd bunch?
Hm... I see.
Odd bunch indeed.
Until you give them another order,
these men keep repeating the same action
without any alterations.
They're like robots.
If you fill the world with men like that that you can control...
Yes. That's probably
what Taiman is trying to do.
I thought I had a pretty good shot at leaving the right impression...
But if Claude reacted that way...
I guess it really doesn't suit me all that well.
What's that?
Great Goblin Tarobo and Kibo Takamaru—
if we manage to do something about these two,
we'll have nothing to fear from Champon.
Tarobo—I can get why, but this Takamaru is just a kid. Is he really that formidable?
I don't know, but I feel like he draws his strength from a bottomless well.
If we don't crush him now, he may become a major obstacle for us in the future.
Near that rock, right?
Okay, just land there quietly.
That rocket from before...
I'm sure that was it.
Ugh! I'm really not cut out
to wear such dresses!
Hurry, Drill Knight!
We need to be done here by morning.
Just don't let me down, won't you?
What is that?
A tail?
How very peculiar.
Karin-sama, I was able
to drill deeper than expected.
Good.
The rest is up to this goblin sealing stone.
I can already see
Tarobo's stupid baffled face.
What are you doing?!
You're not really Karin, are you?
Mirai?
What are you doing here?
What is it? Answer!
What's so funny?!
What's with that outfit?
You look weird! Weird!
Totally lame!
Hey, look who's talking!
What's the deal with your tail?
Now that you've seen it...
I-I guess we've got no choice.
You're not human, are you?
S-So what of it?
Are you another one of Taiman's minions?
Karin-chan doesn't know!
You fool!
Did you stage that elaborate act
just to drive a wedge between us?
I hated you the moment I saw you.
Such a goody-goody all around!
Just like Takamaru, you nauseate me!
What's that dress, even?
Oh, I get it!
You love Al, so you dressed up like that
to be a match for me, didn't you?
Aren't you a dumbass?!
That stupid brat is already
head over heels for Karin!
Shut up!
Why don't you die?
I stepped on it!
Enough with the games!
That was too easy.
Time to finish her off.
Shit!
Leave it to me!
Idiot, don't waste ammo like that!
Blow that rock up.
Bye-bye, Mirai-san.
All right, let's hurry and finish the job now.
Yes!
Wearing this stupid dress
blunted my skills as a ninja!
Is this how it's all gonna end...?
Thank you for this instructive sparring.
I've been away for quite a while.
What’s more, I feel like evil was allowed to rear its head during that time.
You're a human, yet you can fly?
Great Goblin Tarobo, I've been waiting.
So I guess that evil I felt
was your handiwork?
And you still stick your nose up
when dealing with others?
I'd be careful not to break it if I were you.
You dare to insult me?!
I've been looking forward
to fighting you with all my heart!
Are you Karin Fox?!
I'll pay you back for what you did to me 3,000 years ago!
Do you hope to defeat me
with just your strength?
We'll see about that.
Useless.
Fool!
Not so fast!
Stupid goblin flying to the fire,
you'd better not underestimate me!
Petrification!
What?
Freeze!
I-I can't move!
What a shame, right?
Isn't it your sole weakness—
the goblin sealing stone?
Defeated...
Why don't you try moving,
if you even can?!
What?
That guy was no joke.
But I paid him back now.
Takamaru!
Takamaru! It's Mirai-san...
Mirai's been hurt!
Huh?
Well, in any case,
the best she can do now is rest.
The rest depends on her inner energy.
Al! Give her some of that medicine.
Now... Call me at once
if there are any developments.
Sorry for the trouble.
Don't mention it.
I'm just doing my job.
Mirai-dono!
Mirai-san!
How is it looking for her?
She needs complete rest.
Is that so?
Does this make me look like a city gal too?
Mirai-san...
This is bad!
This is bad, people! Very bad!
Shut up!
Stupid pipsqueak,
now's not the time to run around yelling!
Dad... My dad...
Tarobo-dono...
How did you allow this to happen?
Dad!
Mirai returned home half-dead,
and Great Goblin's been petrified...
What on earth happened here?!
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
JmePenseBon
Mirai-dono is seriously injured,
and Tarobo-sama has been turned into stone.
I have a bad feeling about what's gonna happen next!
Next time I'm going wild
with my macho technique.
It seems I'm gonna cause a huge inconvenience to Al and the others,
but it's not like I get a say in this.
Next time: Great Regrets!
My Macho Form is Too Dangerous.