Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Another round, Champon
(Another round, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
I find a love letter in my shoe box,
so it's a dream after all
My strengths are innocence, passion, and tenacity
Hey baby, please ignore my uncool side
Hey lady, with all my heart...
In the end
(In the end)
I will be
(I will be)
The greatest ninja or shogun,
but I'm not sure the world will be able to handle that!
We're free, aloha
Our hearts are wild, ho-ho-ho
Don't care about clubs, cram schools, or scores—
all that stuff can go up in the wind!
Water, gold, earth, fire, wood, aloha
Earth, Heaven, Underworld, ha-ha-ha
It'd be really hard for me to survive
without the TV, games, and videos—
won't someone bring them to me?
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Chapter 2: The Machine Man Alfred
Blows his Whistle and Goes on a Rampage
So, federalism collapsed mainly due to economic problems,
Social Sciences Department
because the so-called socialism
should be an extension
Social Sciences Department
of sufficiently developed democracy and conscientious individualism...
You could say the collapse happened because the people's mindset—their mentality—
just wasn’t there yet—
especially among the leaders.
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
The
Collapse
of
Federal-
ism
So, at this point in time,
the level of the people of Earth
is such that their actions are always built upon the principle of every individual's greed.
So I’d like us to take a moment to look inward and reflect on our lives in light of these events.
That's all for today!
Hey, boy, Takamaru! Wait a second!
Do you know we'll have
a transfer student coming today?
Transfer students are new friends
joining our class, right?
Do you know who it is?
Ah, I guess it's Karin-dono,
who we rescued the other day.
Bull's eye! Amazing, Takamaru...
is what you'd expect me to say.
But we hardly ever get transfer students here,
so it’s no surprise even you figured it out.
More importantly, Al, what was that contraption you were fiddling with earlier,
instead of listening to the lecture?
I'll show it to you later.
And I've got the lecture recorded on this.
Ah! Amazing!
A Japanese-made recording machine!
Recording machine?
It's a radio cassette player, dammit!
Yes, yes!
Allow me to introduce you to
your new friend!
I trust you all know about
the plane incident from the other day, right?
The one who suffered a regrettable accident
on that plane was Karin-san!
Yes, yes, Karin-san,
please introduce yourself now.
Huh? Um... I'm Karin,
but I don't know anything else about myself,
so please take good care of me.
Yes! Let's all get along with Karin!
Kibo Takamaru...
What's up with that guy?
Even when the irresistible Karin hugged him,
he didn’t so much as flinch!
I wonder what's on his mind...
So all you remember is your name—
nothing else at all?
Huh?
Yes, but the doctor said I'll start remembering things over time.
Oh, where's Takamaru-san?
He needed to train, so he went home.
Anyway, Karin, why don't me and you...
Yumega Al Zaemon,
why are you still loitering here?
What's you problem, Mirai?
You keep saying that all the time!
Karin-dono, I've come to pick you up
Yes, Mirai-san.
Pick up?
Mirai-san and her family
allow me to live at their place.
Ugh?! At that ninja mansion?
Somebody was after Karin-dono
when we first met her.
She'll be safer with my father,
the royal spy.
Now, Karin-dono, let's get going.
You should go home early
and help with the chores too.
Stop lecturing me!
Who'd ever be interested
in helping with chores?
I see. That girl Karin says
she's lost her memory
due to the shock of the crash?
Correct.
I've also let the rocket escape...
I apologize.
Just as we're about to establish diplomatic relations with Japan,
any regrettable incident
is the last thing we want.
I wonder if it has something to do
with the Dark Magician Donpapa we drove away the other day?
I doubt someone named Führer Taiman
will give up so soon.
So who exactly is that Führer Taiman?
Who knows... His true nature
is a mystery, even to me.
By the way, Taka-chan...
I'm going to the Nebuta Festival
in Japan starting tomorrow.
Going to look for your wife again?
Y-Yes...
I feel sorry for Jiro,
growing up motherless like a weed.
Apparently, my wife’s been spotted selling cotton candy at various festivals.
Zugai-dono, it pains me to trouble you again,
but could you look after Jiro?
Please leave it to me, Tarobo-sama.
It appears that Jiro-dono
went to school with Mirai again today.
Those two already are
like a parent and child!
Even at just 14, Mirai’s already a very reliable mother.
Taro-chan, when you see your wife, you gotta make sure to apologize properly this time.
Yes, yes.
I know, Taka-chan.
Kirameku Ninja Mansion
Mi...
Karin-dono, where are you headed?
M-Mirai-san, I don't know much about your country,
so I thought I'd take a look around...
It'll be dark soon, I'm coming with you.
Ah, no. I wanted to take a stroll on my own.
And then...
Then I might remember
something about myself...
That might be a good idea.
Be careful, though.
Okay.
Come to think of it, Mirai-san...
Hm?
You're pretty close
with Al-san, aren't you?
What do you mean?
Well, as soon as Al-san got just the slightest bit curious about me,
you reproached him so harshly!
W-W-Wh-What are you talking about?!
I was just...
I'm off!
Oh no, you're going into my bag!
Karin-dono! What are you doing here,
in the rugged rocks?
When I asked at your house,
they said you went to the mountain.
Oh, I come here to train my legs sometimes.
But I couldn't wait to see you again!
Oh, is that so?
You're such a powerful person.
I admire you a lot.
During training,
I ended up breaking a stone wall,
so I'm bringing these stones to repair it.
And what's this?
Various fossils and Jomon figurines
that I found around here.
You're a man of so many talents!
You've also saved the kingdom
from a birdlike monster before, haven't you?
It was me and my friends—we did it together!
And it was also part of my training.
You just keep talking about training.
Why should you train so much?
That's simply because
I want to become strong.
And what do you need
to become strong for?
Huh?
That, I don't know.
I completely forgot!
Sorry, I gotta run!
T-Takamaru-san!
The sun's gonna set!
I didn't make it in time, no sir...
Takamaru-san!
What's going on?
Al-san!
Al-san?
Oh, hey, if it isn't Karin?
What's up? What happened?
It's Takamaru-san...
Oh, no! What are you doing, Takamaru?
What happened to Takamaru-san?
Ah, don't worry about that.
It's in his nature to fall asleep
as soon as the sun sets.
What, really?
Once he falls asleep,
even the great goblin can't wake him up.
But it's fine. He'll be
wide awake at dawn tomorrow.
Is that so?
He says he’s meeting people
from all over the planet while sleeping.
He’s a bit of a hothead.
Huh? Surely, that’s not possible.
Is this baby your younger brother?
You really did what Mirai said
and went to help your family—that’s great!
You think so?
This here is Taku.
Yumega Takusan, or just Taku.
Yumega Takusan
Quite the joke— one is Yumega Al Zaemon,
and the other is Yumega Takusan!
With names like that, you can’t expect
the brothers to get along well.
That's not true!
They’re absolutely wonderful names!
You don’t need to pretend.
Anyway, Karin, did you know
I built this car all on my own?
Amazing! You’re a mechanical genius!
If even this surprises you,
you’re in for a shock.
The thing I’m building right now
is an even more super deluxe mecha!
Even more super deluxe?
Wanna see it?
Yes, absolutely!
All right, I'll arrange
a special showing just for you!
What? Seriously?
I’m delighted!
Then how about tomorrow—
Sunday, at 11am, near the Backbreaker Statue?
Backbreaker Statue?
Oh crap!
Sorry! I’m sorry!
What?
You’re late, Yumega Al Zaemon.
I didn’t know where it was,
so I asked them to walk me here.
And I’m Mirai’s guardian!
And I just wanted to see
that mecha you’re building!
OK, I get it, everybody.
But make sure you don’t faint
from seeing my new mecha!
Bite
Pinch
Scratch
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
That's a geothermal power plant.
Geothermal power?
You’ll now meet a teacher named Genman, who built it.
Genman-san?
Yubikiri Genman.
Well, he's a man of great talent,
who invented all sorts of stuff.
At this time he should
definitely be at the Factory.
So, that place, “Factory,”
is where your keep your mechas?
Of course!
My mecha makes a bit of use
of this power plant.
Wow! I can’t wait to see it!
Hey, teacher!
Is that you, Al?
You’re early today.
Because it’s Sunday!
What's with the car?
Yubikiri Genman-sensei,
I hope you don’t mind us visiting.
Long time no see!
Oh? You brought friends today?
Yubikiri Genman
Hm? And who is that young lady?
My name is Karin.
Oh, are you the girl who crashed in a plane the other day?
Well then, since you brought everyone with you,
it’s to show them your latest contraption, yes?
I guess.
It's not completed yet,
but you could try starting it.
Hooray!
What is that thing
that looks like a cooking pot?
Just watch.
Okay, stand up!
Good Morning, Al-san.
I-It was your voice!
This is my very own handmade
Super Alfred!
It runs on combustion energy by mixing
magnesium with water,
and it’s got an onboard computer.
I also put in the tape,
so it can even speak a little.
You built it all yourself?
“Of course...” Or so I would’ve liked to say.
Al! I would also like to play
with this mechanical man!
All right, then.
Just remember to handle it with care.
To tell you the truth, teacher Genman helped me out a bit... No, helped me a great deal with it.
Hey, Takamaru!
What the hell are you making Alfred do?!
Look, this button...
The geothermal power plant produces clean energy,
but its construction involves serious risks.
Al build this robot to alleviate that issue.
You impress me every now and then.
You’ve seen nothing, Mirai!
I can set it up to go to the plant
and back all on its own!
Come on, pipsqueak!
Don’t make it do more weird poses!
Ugh! I’m not giving it to you guys anymore!
May I...
Oh? Karin, wanna try it too?
But I’m scared.
It’ll be fine.
Just try fiddling with it a bit.
Okay.
All right, toggle that switch
on the bottom left to turn it on.
Okay.
Then slowly turn
the dial on the right.
Okay.
Such a simple scheme. In this case,
I can set this robot loose
and have it wreck the power plant.
Here.
Yes, I'll try it.
When that happens, those guys are bound to turn on each other.
S-Switching it on!
Alfred will smash the rocks!
Al, that's weird!
Karin-dono!
Karin!
Al, cut the power!
It won’t turn off!
Watch out!
Teacher!
Genma-sensei!
Alfred going to work on the power plant.
This is bad!
We gotta stop it no matter what!
Got it!
A-Alfred...
Please wait!
That Machine Man sure is fast!
Alfred!
Al Zaemon, how do I stop it?
T-Turn the valve
on his back to the left!
Got it!
H-Hey!
Mirai-dono!
I need to move freely!
Kibo Takamaru, you’ve gotta help me!
B-Be there in a moment!
Faster!
Mirai-san!
Jiro!
Takamaru, get on now! Quick!
Ready when you are!
Okay!
Mirai-dono!
Alfred!
M-Mirai?
Mirai-san!
The Machine Man
is running even faster now!
Ah, Dr. Genman?
What's the matter?
Huh? Robot Alfred has gone rogue?
Mister Machine Man, you’ll have to forgive me
for dispensing with the mannerisms!
Champon Geothermal Power Plant
Get away!
The power plant...
Was destroyed by Alfred!
It’s still moving!
Alfred will smash the rocks.
Commence smashing!
This is bad!
It’s heading for the lava furnace!
Close the valve!
In this state, it’s gonna explode!
Alfred!
Alfred! Stop!
Stop! Stop, please!
Al, watch out!
Damn you!
Al, forget it!
Let me go!
Alfred must obey me!
Macho Takamaru?
Takamaru!
Alfred...
He’s after Takamaru now...
He wants to harm a human...
Alfred has gone completely nuts!
Damn you!
Stupid thing!
Come on, you junk!
Junk!
Stupid junk!
Takamaru!
He can’t hold out for much longer...
Takamaru’s Macho Technique wears off in five minutes!
Teacher, Karin!
What’s that?
Magnesium.
I’ll throw this inside
to trigger an internal explosion.
Huh?! But that’ll waste
all of Al’s precious work!
Teacher! Wait for me!
I built this robot.
Let me do it!
Al!
Takamaru!
Help is coming!
There you go!
Takamaru!
It's going to explode!
Takamaru! Al Zaemon!
Genman-sensei!
Mirai-san!
Takamaru! Al Zaemon!
Genman-sensei!
Hey, Mirai!
Takamaru and Al are safe.
Takamaru! Al Zaemon!
Al’s car?
Al-san!
It’s you, Karin?
Are Takamaru-san
and Genman-sensei all right?
Yeah. They’re fine.
Takamaru’s built tough
from all that martial arts training.
I’m sorry.
I must’ve broken the controller.
It's not your fault.
Alfred was my own faulty design.
What matters is that Takamaru
and everyone else is safe.
Well, that goes without saying.
Still, I’ve caused a huge deal of nuisance
to the power plant with this incident.
Al-san! If you don’t cheer up...
Even I... Even I will grow dejected!
Karin?
Al-san, please cheer up!
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
JmePenseBon
The professional wrestler I am enthusiastically supporting Great Owada will be coming
from Japan with his entourage!
I was planning to fight against various martial artists,
but instead I got Kitsutsu King,
who had some deadly techniques
to counter the Bity-Scratchy School.
Next time:
“Dangerous National Foundation Day!
The Pro Wrestler Has Arrived!”
Episode 3: Dangerous National Foundation Day!
The Pro Wrestler Has Arrived