In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state
that remains closed to the outside world.
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Another round, Champon
(Another round, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
I find a love letter in my shoe box,
so it's a dream after all
My strengths are innocence, passion, and tenacity
Hey baby, please ignore my uncool side
Hey lady, with all my heart...
In the end
(In the end)
I will be
(I will be)
The greatest ninja or shogun,
but I'm not sure the world will be able to handle that!
We're free, aloha
Our hearts are wild, ho-ho-ho
Don't care about clubs, cram schools, or scores—
all that stuff can go up in the wind!
Water, gold, earth, fire, wood, aloha
Earth, Heaven, Underworld, ha-ha-ha
It'd be really hard for me to survive
without the TV, games, and videos—
won't someone bring them to me?
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Chapter 5: Great Regrets!
My Macho Form is Too Dangerous
What's that?
Isn't that Karin's pouch?
What? Why do you have it, Takamaru?
Well, when I woke up this morning,
it was by my bedside for some reason.
When you woke up?
Actually, where's Karin-san?
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen her today.
Karin-san ended up in Champon
because someone chased her, right?
Yeah.
Well, maybe they finally got her
during this uproar?
Shit!
I'm gonna go look for Karin!
I also have to report to the castle now.
Please look after Mirai for me.
Okay.
Understood!
Wh-What did you say?!
Taro-chan has been turned into stone?!
Zugai, Koen, we've gotta help Taro-chan!
This could only be the work
of that Taiman and his army!
Please calm down.
To disturb Your Majesty
is exactly what the enemy wants.
I think it's in our best interest
to be more on guard now than ever before.
Zugai, Koen! Gather everyone
for a strategy meeting!
Yes, sir!
I was so distracted by what happened to Mirai,
I completely forgot! I'm sorry, Karin.
Karin?
Al-san!
What, Karin?
What happened?
It's Takamaru-san...
He stole Karin's pouch!
Huh? What did you say?
H-Hey, hold up, are you sure?
Yes.
But why'd Takamaru ever need to do that?
Ah, actually.
Mirai was attacked
and seriously injured last night.
Do you know anything about it?
Mirai is seriously injured?
So then, she didn't die after all?
If so...
Ah, that's right!
Takamaru-san did that too!
It happened last night...
What could that be?
Takamaru-san!
In the flesh!
Give me your pouch! Right now!
Huh?!
I've been wondering
what's in there for a while.
I've been so curious I lost my sleep!
So give it to me at once!
No!
Give it!
Takamaru! Breaking into a woman's room
late at night—what's the big idea?!
It falls on me to punish this pervert boy!
Takamaru...
Punch!
No way...
Do you see now how strong I truly am?
So give me your pouch now
and don't make a fuss!
No...
S-Surely, that can't be true, right?
You don't believe what Karin says?
No-no, no... I believe it!
I believe you, so stop crying, okay?
Don't cry!
I'll do something about it.
Really?
O-Of course!
I'm so happy!
You'll fight for me, won't you?
No, I mean...
If I have to...
I-It's the Drill...
I couldn't fight to the fullest...
Dad has turned into stone,
and Mirai-san is badly injured!
What should I do?
Jiro-dono, I understand how you feel,
but boys shouldn't burst into tears that easily.
Mirai-dono is gonna laugh at you
if she finds out later.
Al!
Were you able to find Karin-dono?
Takamaru, there's something we need to talk about. Won't you come with me for a moment?
What did you want to talk about?
Takamaru, you're a precious friend to me.
I don't want to live my life distrusting you.
So talk honestly.
I don't quite understand,
but all right.
What were you doing last night?
Last night?
So that's the Takamaru brat?
Shh. I'll show you something
far more amusing in a moment.
Amusing?
Huh?
Is that what Karin-dono said?
Well, I have no recollection of it.
Think harder, Takamaru.
This is a heavy problem!
What happened last night?
Try to remember!
So, what do you say? Surely, nothing
of the sort could have happened, right?
I say I don't remember a thing, after all.
Takamaru!
H-Hey!
T-Takamaru?
What's wrong?
It's not time for sleep yet!
It can even do this.
Hey, Takamaru, wake up!
"Middle of conversation"
is not the time for sleeping!
Why'd you break out your
Macho Technique all of a sudden?
Go, Takamaru!
Takamaru!
Also, we need to keep a close eye
on the area around The Smoking One...
What the... They're not supposed to operate without an order!
Gather up, people! Gather up!
Takamaru is not the kind of guy
who'd go around felling trees for no reason.
What's gotten into him?!
Well then, only one more to take care of.
What do you mean?
We made a bit of a blunder last night.
Who'd think that Mirai
would prove that tough!
Stop! Stop! Takamaru, you need to stop!
Can you hear me?
I said, stop!
You stupid...
Seriously, Takamaru!
Something's terribly wrong with you!
Karin-san? Where have you been?
Good grief...
You'd save me a whole lot of trouble
if you just died then and there.
"Trouble?"
I'm talking about putting her
out of her misery, of course!
Wh-What?
Surprised, aren't you?
What are you going to do?!
Jiro!
How could you—
Don't make this any more difficult, will you?
Who are you, really?
Takamaru, stop!
Maybe Takamaru's caught
a bad case of some brain disease?
He's just like Alfred was the other day!
Oh, no! He's heading straight for the Ninja Mansion!
I will... protect Mirai-san!
Why don't you just quietly
watch from there, Claude-san?
Now, as for you...
This is the end, Mirai!
You lowlife!
H-Hey, what the...
What are you clutching at?!
Let go of it, you hear?
Let go!
You little pervert!
Let go, you creep!
I've just about had enough of you!
Takamaru!
Ah, my flute...
Where's my flute?
Karin, there you are!
You're not hurt, are you?
Takamaru went completely off the rails.
Ah! It was so sudden Karin got scared!
Bullshit!
She's been leading everyone by the nose!
Karin tried to kill Mirai-san!
What? What are you talking about?
Why would Karin want to kill Mirai?!
I don't know all the details,
but it was Karin who injured Mirai-san!
Claude doesn't know what he's talking about.
That's right.
Some people can be that annoying.
I hate it!
Mirai ended up catching me red-handed.
I had to get rid of her.
Bite
Pinch
Scratch
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
You guys were too easy to fool.
Karin...
Especially Al—
all I had to do was act a little helpless,
and you fell for it at once.
Thanks for the laughs, though.
You're joking, right?
Now that the Great Goblin Tarobo is sealed away,
Macho Man Takamaru will raze
this Champon Kingdom to the ground!
Come on, Takamaru,
deal with your best friend first!
Was Karin... Was Karin
manipulating Takamaru all along?
Takamaru...
How about it? How does it feel
to be strangled by your best friend?
Karin, who are you really...
I'm the top executive
of the Taiman army, Karin Fox.
Karin...
Now die!
Who did it?!
Mirai?!
You obstinate pig!
Takamaru!
Hey, Takamaru?
What's wrong with them?
Oh? What's this?
Zugai-dono, did you find anything?
No, just some strange device
behind their ears.
Ugh... That jerk Takamaru!
Karin! I can't believe you've been
fooling us all this time!
Karin, both Al Zaemon and Takamaru
thought of you as a friend.
Don't make me laugh!
No matter where you turn in this world,
all people do is scheme, lie, and backstab!
How can you even
call yourself human?!
Humans? Pft.
Don't lump me in with them.
I'm not a human.
So I can act any way I want, unbound
by stupid concepts such as emotions or morals.
How about it?
Don't you think it's great?
You understand?
Dammit...
What's great about it?!
I'll make you pay, you monster!
Oh?
Takamaru?
Whatever. I can get a new flute anytime.
Al! I'm looking forward
to seeing you "make me pay!"
Ah! Wait, you! Karin!
Are you running away?!
Al!
Zugai-san?
What happened?
What's all the fuss?
Mirai?
Father, what happened is...
As expected—it's here.
It was highly unworthy of me.
I was completely unprepared.
I’ve let myself be misled
by this device.
Takamaru, it’s not something
you had a choice in.
No, I’m sure they only succeeded
because my spirit wasn’t strong enough.
I should’ve trained more.
Takamaru, let's go.
We'll find Karin and kick her ass.
Wait, Al Zaemon.
There's something I want you to do first.
Damn this rogue Karin...
Are you for real?
If Mirai's map is to believed,
there should be a stone on that island similar to one for sealing goblins.
So, is this the place?
Has to be it...
Gee...
But which one?
How would we ever know
which hole to search?
What should we do?
Just search all of them, obviously!
It’s here! Ah, no.
Here! Here. Not, not here.
This is the one! No? No...
What’s here?
There's something in there.
What? Did you find it?
I'll try to reach it.
How is it?
Did you find the stone?
Huh?
What is it?
What?
What could that be?
It has a sharp, hard tip...
Sharp tip?
And it’s turning!
Turning?
You...!
I am Drill Knight, the right hand of Karin Fox,
the top executive of the Taiman Army!
It seems you came to look for the goblin sealing stone, but I won’t let you have it!
With my beautiful drill,
I’ll send all of you six feet under!
What?
Al, leave him to me.
I need to make it up to you for going rogue
with my macho technique.
Drill Knight-dono, it is essential for us that the Great Goblin is restored to how he was.
If you insist on stopping us no matter what,
I’m going to be your opponent here.
That brat should still be under Karin’s control.
Well, why not?
It’ll look good on my service record.
Very well!
I’ll give you a taste of my beautiful drill!
Champon Kingdom’s martial arts instructor,
son of Kibo Koen, Kibo Takamaru charges!
Anything but that technique!
So that’s how it is?
You can't hurt my full-metal body!
If so...
Biting technique!
H-H-He dented it!
My beautiful mechanical body...
My beautiful mechanical body!
And you dented it!
Die!
What?!
You think you can control my beautiful drill?
Then how about this?!
Takamaru!
You prick!
Isn’t it fun?
Damn brat!
Takamaru!
For you, I have this!
Oh my god!
My nice hair!
Now you’re getting it! Go!
I’ll rid my boss of all three of you at once!
Jiro, your fan!
Die!
Your stupid tricks won’t help you!
What?
Metals are quite difficult to grapple with.
Thank you for this instructive sparring!
You showed him, Takamaru!
Impressive as ever!
I’m still learning.
Okay, let's find the stone now.
Karin!
Impressive for a bunch of snotty brats—
to beat Drill Knight himself.
Well, I always knew this was the extent
of Drill Knight’s abilities.
Now, Takamaru!
Turn Macho already!
Interesting dancing style you have...
Are you stupid?
That's strange... Why?!
We’ve long removed
all the chips you planted!
Tsk. So you figured it out?
But you can’t defeat me
with that kind of toy!
Oh, really? Why don’t you dance for us
once more, one final time, Karin?!
No!
Yeah! We got her!
That was the last straw!
Now you’ll definitely pay for this!
She’s running with her tail
between her legs.
I see now.
Karin's weakness is frogs?
You need to approach
every opponent individually!
O-Ouch, geez...
Watch where you’re going, you!
It hurts!
What's wrong with you, Karin?
Karin! Has something happened?
Aren’t you supposed to be
in the Champon Kingdom?
Th-That's the Undersea Fortress Jugon!
What’s on your mind,
bringing something like this out?
I'll sink Champon
to the bottom of the sea.
What did you say?
No way, Karin! You have to stop!
Taiman-sama clearly ordered us to conquer
Champon Kingdom—not destroy it!
The people of that kingdom are too dangerous—
we must destroy them before it’s too late!
How can that micro-nation
be so dangerous?
I think you should know it better than anyone,
what their children are capable of.
Even as enemies, I can’t help but admire
Takamaru, Al, and Mirai.
In ten years’ time, those kids will be completely immune to these cheap tricks.
You nip the danger in the bud—
while it’s still defenseless!
Course Z built.
Undersea Fortress Jugon surfaces.
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
JmePenseBon
They want to send our homeland
of Champon to the bottom of the sea!
Karin-dono attacks again with her dreadful Undersea Fortress Jugon.
What’s more, Karin’s true form
is even more incredible!
In the next, final episode:
“Stand Up, Champon Kingdom!
The Boys Who’ll Bring About the Future.”