Takamaru, Al, Mirai,
and all of Champon Kingdom...
We'll send all of you
together to the bottom of the ocean!
Karin is seriously going to do it.
I can't just stand by and do nothing.
In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state
that remains closed to the outside world.
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Another round, Champon
(Another round, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
I find a love letter in my shoe box,
so it's a dream after all
My strengths are innocence, passion, and tenacity
Hey baby, please ignore my uncool sides
Hey lady, with all my heart...
In the end
(In the end)
I will be
(I will be)
The greatest ninja or shogun,
but I'm not sure the world will be able to handle that!
We're free, aloha
Our hearts are wild, ho-ho-ho
Don't care about clubs, cram schools, or scores—
all that stuff can go up in the wind!
Water, gold, earth, fire, wood, aloha
Earth, heaven, underworld, ha-ha-ha
It'd be really hard for me to survive
without the TV, games, and videos—
won't someone bring them to me?
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
Chapter 6: Stand Up, Champon Kingdom!
The Boys Who’ll Bring About the Future
It's not this hole either.
Takamaru, please do this one next.
Donpapa-dono!
B-Back for more, you bald bird?!
Is that Drill Knight?
Did you guys send him under?
Poor guy.
He's so spent even Karin abandoned him?
D’ya come to be a pain in the dick again?
Takamaru, go get him!
Wait, you boys.
I didn't come to fight today,
look at that first!
What’s that?
Undersea Fortress Jugon,
stop the engine!
Where’d that island come from?
It's not just an island.
That is the ultimate weapon of the Taiman Army,
Undersea Fortress Jugon.
Jugon?
Karin brought Jugon here
to start a monster tsunami
and sink the Champon Kingdom
to the bottom of the sea.
What?!
Takamaru, you have to stop Karin.
You must come with me now.
Karin-dono will start a monster tsunami?
D-Don’t try to trick us, stupid bird!
You're a bad guy, aren't you?
This is a trap, you hear?
It’s a trap!
It’s as clear as a day!
I'm going to that island.
Hey, you trust him?!
But what about the Great Goblin
who was turned into stone?!
Wait, Al. We’ll do something
about the sealing stone on our own.
Takamaru, you go to face Karin!
H-Hey...
Donpapa-dono, please show me the way!
And off they went...
Jiro, you go to the island and tell Mirai-san and everyone what’s happening!
But my dad...
Hey, pipsqueak!
Takamaru said we do that, so it’s decided!
See? I’ve got these instead of Takamaru.
Look! We’ll blow the rocks away with these
and bring your father back better than before!
Don't you cry, pipsqueak! Boys don’t cry that easily, that’s also what Takamaru said!
Come on, go to the island now!
Dad! Wait just a bit more!
I need to get going now!
Donpapa-dono, is this all artificial?
That's right.
That's incredible.
You’ve seen nothing yet, kid.
The main body of this fortress is submerged,
but before you can start using it...
No way! Karin got to work right away!
Let's go, Takamaru.
Got it!
Who’s there?!
Drill Knight?!
Drill Knight-dono?
Drill Knight!
Drill Knight-dono,
I am sincerely impressed by your determination to keep on fighting even when tattered like that!
Takamaru!
What are you thinking at a time like—
Takamaru! You’re probably
the only one who can stop Karin!
Is that so? Understood.
Go already!
So that’s Undersea Fortress Jugon?
That's right!
And they want to use it to ravage our island?
If she’s not stopped,
we’ll all drown here!
I hear that our country’s been
through a similar disaster in ancient times.
Your Highness,
we, the masters of Kibo Style,
will board that island as a suicide squad
and will neutralize the crew.
I, the royal spy, will do the same!
Wait, both of you.
We must prioritize the protection of lives and assets of our people over fighting.
Isn't it something you said once?
We must come together!
Yes, sir!
Sugiura, get the Champon Kingdom
and the people on high alert.
Yes, sir!
Like that!
Champon Castle Basement
And done... All right,
begin the dog paddle style tsunami!
In only thirty more minutes, Champon will submerge to the bottom of the sea.
Isn’t it lovely?
It reminds me of that time I sunk Atlantis just like that a long time ago.
It’s Takamaru!
Takamaru is in the fortress!
He couldn’t wait too!
Hi, Takamaru-chan!
I’m so happy you’ve come to play with me!
Karin-dono, you must stop
the tsunami machine at once.
If you don’t,
I won’t show you any mercy.
My oh my, did you seriously hope
to stop me with threats?
Then you leave me no choice.
It goes against my principles
to fight women.
Karin-dono,
I hope you’ve prepared yourself.
Backbreaker Statue
Ralliart Statue
Ready!
You’re a strong fighter.
Now you’re not getting away!
Pinching technique
of the Bity-Scratchy School!
It really rubs me the wrong way—
doing it to a woman.
Karin-dono, please surrender quickly
and stop the tsunami.
Surrender?
So which one of us should surrender now?
K-Karin-dono, you were actually a dog?!
Not a dog—a fox!
Can’t you tell them apart?
Huh? Oh, that was awfully rude on my part...
Exactly, and you’ll pay for it!
In my 4,000 years on this Earth,
I’ve never met a weirder brat than you!
4,000 years? Are you really
such an elderly person, Karin-dono?
E-Elderly person?
Look closer!
I’m an immortal nine-tailed fox!
I’ve been reborn hundreds of times—
more than you can ever imagine!
But I only see four tails there.
Attentive kid.
I’ve lost the rest 3,000 years ago
when someone I was fighting pulled them out.
Fortunately, that someone
was turned into stone recently.
So then, the one
who petrified Tarobo-sama...
Yes, it was me!
There it is!
The goblin-sealing stone!
Al, you won’t free it that way.
Let me!
Damn it!
C-Claude...?
Champon Castle Basement
Backbreaker Statue Basement
Ralliart Statue Basement
No way, boy?
Out of breath already?
You must be wondering
about your island and friends, right?
Take a look.
Seems like it’ll switch to butterfly soon!
How about it?
Isn’t it a great view?
Oh?
It’d be boring if I let you die that easily.
You’re gonna have to stick around
a little longer until the job is done, boy.
Goodness me,
is this really what’s in Takamaru’s mind?
Unbelievable!
How childish can one really be?
Always blowing the hot air,
but in the end he’s just a kid!
Maybe I don’t really have
to finish him off, even?
I wish Lord Taiman, Donpapa, and the grownups of the island could take a peek at this too.
H-Hell no!
I still can’t let my guard down with him!
Do you copy?
We’ll begin in five minutes from now!
Roger that!
We’re standing by!
Hey, it’s about to become
real dangerous here!
Bite
Pinch
Scratch
NEW Bakumatsu Era Super Boy
Takamaru
What awaits your friends now is death
in desperation at the bottom of the ocean.
I too have a long, long history of jealousy
and betrayal with you humans.
It's unfair that you alone get to die happily
in such a carefree and bright world.
I will now show you plenty
of the ugly sides of humans!
Let's go!
Here we go, boy!
First—the betrayal!
Now jealousy!
Lust!
Hatred!
How about it?
This is the true essence of human spirit,
developed over thousands of years!
Takamaru, your body and soul should be on the verge of explosion with that energy!
Now, let me savor your suffering!
It's here! The Smoking One farted!
Put your back into it!
No good!
It won’t spin further!
Betrayal, jealousy, lust, hatred...
And then, as the final accord,
I’ll let you taste plenty
of the humans’ ultimate emotion—
the pillar of despair!
Don't give up! Keep trying!
It won’t turn!
Al, Claude!
Oh! It gave in!
Spin it right round!
The Champon Kingdom...
Rose from the water!
It worked! We did it!
Th-The despair shattered...
Impossible!
Wh-What’s going on?!
He’s absorbing them!
This guy is absorbing the four pillars!
He’s mere human... Just an 11-year-old kid!
This shouldn’t be possible!
He’s swallowed all of them up!
It’s pulling me in!
At this rate, he’ll swallow me as well!
I won’t get another chance.
I have to finish him off here and now!
Die!
Wh-What are you...
Takamaru’s Macho Form!
He wishes to have another instructive sparring!
D-Doesn’t matter—at the end of the day,
you’re just a creepy kid!
It seems you’re weak
against attacks from above!
Macho Flight
Wh-What?!
What’s that?
Is that Champon Kingdom?
The island was just a bridge?
You weird people.
Champon Kingdom...
What a messed-up place!
It’s over.
I lost.
Takamaru, kill me!
Karin-dono.
What?
You were a truly formidable enemy.
Thank you for an instructive sparring!
I’ve heard that already!
Just kill me already!
No, the sparring is over now.
Besides, you’re one
of my school mates now.
How can I be your school mate?!
That’s exactly what I hate
the most about you!
To think I lost to a brat like you...
And now you're trying to further humiliate me!
Karin!
Donpapa?
This boy Takamaru is a figure of great importance, more than you can imagine.
Karin, his human capacities
far surpass your calculations.
Human capacities?
Karin-dono, do you think Drill-dono
will get better if we repair him?
That's right, Karin.
Take your Drill Knight with you
and retreat to the Taiman Army base.
You lost this one.
Be it his capacities or great importance—
I don’t acknowledge such qualities!
He is weird—that’s all I know!
Takamaru!
What is it?
I'll come to face you again.
Ah, then I’ll be training as hard as I can and waiting for that day!
Donpapa-dono.
What is it?
I appreciate your assistance today.
I did it purely out of curiosity—
about the future that awaits you.
And about the new era that you’ll usher in.
I don't understand exactly what you mean,
but I’ll be doing my best.
I see. Well, I'm looking forward to it!
Oh? Even Karin-kun couldn’t handle it?
That’s rather surprising.
Don't give in to panic. The world
is still moving in my desired direction.
Good morning!
Wait for me!
Al!
Good morning.
Al, what’s with your hair...
None of your business, that’s what!
If I went to school with a “Help Me” hairdo I had, I’d be everyone’s laughing stock.
Besides, in cities like Tokyo or New York,
almost everyone wears this hairstyle to school.
Oh? Is that so, Claude-dono?
Yeah... Sort of.
So I thought!
Hey, Yumega Al Zaemon!
What is that hairstyle?
Why are you picking on me again?!
No matter if it’s popular in the city or whatever,
that hairdo is inappropriate.
But I think it looks kinda cool!
Listen up, Takamaru.
It's not a question of whether it's cool.
Yumega Al Zaemon,
as a proper school student, you must...
All right! I got it, dammit!
You’re so finicky!
The End
For now
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer