Baby Goblin Jiro
I'm not joking! The handstand is the best
Fukuda Claude
Homework, calligraphy, and genius—I don't need any of that
Hey baby, let's spend another cheerful day together
Hey lady, this is my heart speaking—I love you!
Every day is a fun school! Look, the teacher is smiling too
Kibo Takamaru
Seating order, uniforms, grades—I couldn't care less!
Yumega Al Zaemon
Hey mammy, we'll eat plenty today
Kirameku Mirai (14 y.o.)
Hey! daddy, with all my might, in the end...
(In the end)
I will be...
(I will be)
The world's best PhD, minister—wouldn't that be nice?
We are samurai, nice to meet you!
Topknots in our hearts, Ho, Ho, Ho
If you take a good look at the Smoking One,
you'll see a rainbow in the blue sky
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday—feeling great
Thursday, Friday, Saturday too—Ha, Ha, Ha
Waiting for that girl on our usual hill
on our way home from school...
I'm so excited and thrilled!
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday—feeling great
Thursday, Friday, Saturday too—Ha, Ha, Ha
Waiting for that girl on our usual hill
on our way home from school...
I'm so excited and thrilled!
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
Oi, bowy!
Whau down'd wou bway wid be?
Oh, no!
Oh my god!
In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state that remains closed to the outside world, just as it was during the Tokugawa period.
Bakumatsu
Era
Super
Boy
Takamaru
O-O-Oh, no!
H-Hey! Wh-Who are you?!
I'm one of Donpapa's
three minions, Begabo.
Begabo? The hell does it mean, you prick?!
What, a matchlock?
You're so old-fashioned for a boy!
That thing won't shoot
until you light the fuse!
Y-Yeah, I know that, all right.
Goddamn, give me a minute.
OK...
Die!
Oh, shit!
Eugh...
Wh-Why are there mushrooms?!
Y-You're giving me the creeps, you freak!
With the next one, I’ll bury you in mushrooms
till you can’t even breathe!
Me...
Even that honesty is creepy!
Leave me alone!
Oh, shit! I'll just have to cut that tongue out!
Douchebag! Die!
I got you!
Huh?
Shit...
Oh my god!
Goddamn! My very nice-looking punk hair!
Why, that's just a fresh look!
Besides, it suits a student better!
Shit! I'm not taking advice from a dirtbag like yourself on how a student should look!
Oh, no!
With just one more lick on your head,
I'll make you into a model monk!
Model monk?!
I'd be much happier
if you just killed me instead!
I-I surrender! I give up!
See? Just like that!
Don't cry!
Donpapa-sama might want to meet you personally.
Well, he won't be able to see you down here.
I'll overlook it just this once,
so take your time.
Yes, cry.
Cry...
Yeah, you can do it now.
While you still have the time...
You first!
Hot! It's hot!
It's hot!
I'll let you taste my handmade bomb...
I-I understand now! I was wrong!
I'm sorry! Help me...! Huh?
What a cowardly boy—apologizing
to make the opponent lower his guard!
You are you kidding me, you moron?!
Get back here, you turkey! How could you do that to my precious hair?! Stop, you!
Much obliged.
So it's you? The lively boy
who came to rescue our hostage?
It pains me, but I can't
let you go through here.
Why don't you go home?
Sir, are you with the baddies?
If so, I'm going to ask you
to give my friend back at once!
I see. Then there's only one way out.
I'm one of Donpapa's three minions, Kinisky.
Let's do it!
Wait a moment!
Where is your blade?
I don't need it.
My body is my weapon.
In that case, I can't use this either.
The Martial Arts Instructors of Champon Kingdom,
the son of Kibo Koen, Kibo Takamaru,
is going to face you!
Let's fight!
You know a thing or two about fighting.
Hey! If you don't surrender now,
I'll break your spine! Yield!
H-Hey! I won't let such cowardly moves pass!
Chicken Wing Face Lock!
You can't scratch or pinch from this position!
Surrender now!
I'll break your neck!
Biting?!
It hurt!
Look! Your teeth left a mark!
You dishonest brat!
Scratching, pinching, biting—
all the cowardly moves!
Don't you have a shred
of a martial artist's pride in you?
Cowardly? This is part of the Kibo Style,
passed down in our family,
the Biting Technique
of the Bity-Scratchy School!
B-Bity-Scratchy School?
Could it be that there is still a school
that has inherited such ancient techniques?
Kibo Style, Bity-Scratchy School.
Bity-Scratchy
School Dojo
In ancient times, it was a fundamental and effective weapon in human combat.
Bity-Scratchy
School Dojo
Biting
Biting,
Pinching
pinching,
Scratching
scratching...
were all commonly used.
But just as quickly,
these techniques disappeared
from the world's modern martial arts.
There were a lot of reasons, but mainly because it came off as some childish, petty,
cowardly catfight between women—
basically, people thought it was just lame.
But can you really dismiss this most effective weapon simply because it looks somewhat lame?!
And that's why these techniques have been passed down from generation to generation—
they are Kibo Style,
Bity-Scratchy School techniques!
Bity-Scratchy
School
Th-This boy is the
Bity-Scratchy School follower?
Kibo Style, Biting Technique's ultimate form!
Ah... H-Hey, wait!
S-Screw you!
I thought we agreed not to use any weapons!
How about this?!
I thank you for this instructive sparring!
Th-The pleasure is mine, boy...
Well, I'll be!
What unreliable minions I have!
So then, should I go
stop them all on my own?
Yes, welcome!
Candies
T-Takamaru!
Claude-dono, stay put,
I'll rescue you now!
You boys really have admirable courage for someone who's that clueless. Yes, impressive!
But this one’s the son of Japan’s Vice-Minister of Foreign Affairs—
a valuable hostage we’ll use
to blackmail the Champon Kingdom
and hand this island over
to my lord, Führer Taiman!
So it's not that simple!
My hair!
Pinching technique
of the Bity-Scratchy School!
Give my friend back, or you can say goodbye
to all the hair on your head!
What atrocity—doing that to the few hairs I have left!
I'll make you pay!
Takamaru!
Now you're at my mercy.
Well, kid, here comes the payback for what you did to my hair! Get ready to receive it!
Hey, Claude! If I want to keep playing with your toys, I guess I’ve gotta rescue you first, huh?
Al!
Al! But what's on your head?
You even had time to get a haircut?
Wh...
What are you talking about, you nutjob?
Let's do it, you damn bird!
Here's another naughty boy!
Why are you only aiming for my head?!
Oh, now you're getting it!
Pff. Less talk, more action!
Scratching technique...
Takamaru!
If you make eye contact with me,
you will lose control of your body.
Stupid bird...
Al!
Al, throw it away!
I wish I could, but I just can't let go! Whoa!
M-My body can't move!
A-Al!
C-Claude-dono!
A-Al, what should I do?
Claude! Th-Throw the bomb away from me!
Well, Claude, you time is running out fast.
What are you going to do?
Claude-dono!
Please help!
Useless! That kid is not like you two.
Still, though—to die from your own toy!
You guys are having the worst luck today!
H-Hey, you bird! No, I mean, Mister Bird,
we were wrong! Please help me!
I-I mean it, I repent from the bottom of my heart!
Do you see these tears in my eyes?
I’ve had more than enough time to watch your cowardly little-boy tactics on my monitor!
Oh! Goddamn, that can't be true!
Please, Claude!
Claude, hurry up and help!
Mirai-dono!
N-Nice follow, Mirai!
M-Mirai-san!
I...
What are you—a man or a worm?
Listen up, Claude.
Your two friends are risking their lives to save you.
And I might die here too...
all to save your pathetic life!
You'll have to live with that guilt!
Doesn’t it haunt you already?!
Claude, if you're a man,
don't run away! Fight!
Hey, Donpapa!
I'll be your opponent!
D-Damn you!
You just keep aiming for my head!
Let's go!
Mirai-dono, don't look him in the eyes!
Daddy...
Telephone
Yes, hewwo?
I-Is that you, Jiro?
It's me, Kirameku Mirai!
Oh-wow! What is it, Mirai-san?
Tarobo-sama is urgently...
What?
needed at the Smoking One...
My dad? My dad...
Remember this, Jiro.
Never call out to me while I'm meditating.
Disrupting the balance of one's connection
to nirvana is very dangerous.
Mirai-san, I'm coming to help you!
By combining those,
I can reach great speeds!
I'll be the one who helps Mirai-san!
What's wrong, brave boys and girls?
Is this all you've got?
How about it?!
Takamaru!
Al!
Mirai-san, I'll be there soon!
C-Claude!
Not again...
Mirai-san!
Goddamn punks!
Good idea! Don't let him open his eyes!
Claude, hold on to him for dear life!
Hey, pipsqueak!
Out of the way!
We did it!
Didn't we?
Is that all?
That was the final straw!
Crap...
He's still kicking?
But what else can we do?
T-Takamaru!
Wow! Those muscles!
He's like a super miracle boy!
B-Brutal...
I-Incredible...
Thank you... for this... sparring!
Hey, T-Takamaru?
H-Hey? Hey, Takamaru!
What was that macho body just now?
Oh, that? If I hold my breath, I can become a muscleman, but only for five minutes.
Kibo Takamaru...
He can't be underestimated.
Anyway, where's Claude?
It was so scary!
You did great, Claude.
You fought alongside us.
Yeah. Your biting was
just as good as Takamaru's.
Maybe it really was!
Daddy!
Oh, Jiro! Are you safe?
Tarobo-sama!
Mirai!
Sorry I wasn't home.
Is that the Great Goblin Tarobo,
the guardian of the Smoking One?
And what about those two boys?
They are Kibo Takamaru
and Yumega Al Zaemon.
No! I'm just Al! Al, you hear!
Al and Takamaru?
I've heard a lot about you
from the King Zako Takanokami.
From the king?
Takanokami and I are friends!
Friends with the King?!
Hey, Mirai! Mirai!
What is it?
Since when are you friends
with that rump?
I'm not a rump,
I'm Jiro!
J-Jiro? Anyway, when did you make acquaintance of the Great Goblin?
That's a secret.
Tsk! You're so stingy.
Come on! Look me in the eyes!
So? What is it about your eyes?!
Answer me!
Oh dear me,
now he's completely plucked!
B-Brutal...
Yumega Al Zaemon, didn’t you go through quite the drastic haircut yourself today?
Sh-Shut up! Shut up!
Blast! No way I can go to school
with this kind of haircut!
I find that hairdo more appropriate.
Shut it already!
When did I ask for your opinion?!
You! Donpapa, isn't it?
Ah? Y-Yes, sir...
Go home and tell this
to your Führer Taiman...
Y-Yes, certainly.
It's no use trying to invade our country,
as long as our kingdom
has these brave children,
and me—the Great Goblin Tarobo!
Yes, certainly...
You also can't come close to it ever again.
Next time, I won't be this lenient.
You look mighty tasty to me—
so if I catch you again,
I’m sticking you on a skewer
and tossing your bones
into the ramen broth!
Hey, Claude. Claude!
What?
Your toys—are your toys all right?
They're all in my backpack.
Good! Don't forget you've promised
to leave them to us!
Yeah, sure!
Yumega Al Zaemon, have you...
It's Al! Al!
And why not, anyway?
He already promised to leave them to us!
What about my share?
Y-Your share...
Are you talking about the toys?
You play with toys too, Mirai-dono?
She's just joking, Takamaru!
I-I'd like to own one of such rare toys too!
Are you saying it's weird
that I play with toys?
Th-That's not what I meant...
What are we gonna do?
You, who call yourselves grownups—
what's wrong with you?
Especially—you, Taka-cha—
No, I mean King Takanokami.
S-Sorry, Taro-chan.
I got plastered before I even realized it.
Well, no use crying over spilt milk.
I'm glad it didn't cause any major incident.
But imagine what would have been
if it wasn't for the heroism of those children...
Mirai, Al Zaemon, Takamaru, Jiro—
they've done more for us
than we could ever ask for!
And you, Fukuda-dono.
Y-Yes?
Your son Claude also
proved himself to be very brave.
M-My Claude?
By the way, I hear the politicians
in your country are all at sixes and sevens.
Y-Yes...
Fukuda-dono, I've been discussing it
with my subjects since long ago.
I'm going to abdicate.
We want to end our isolationist policy and open up the Champon Kingdom to the world.
Oh? Is that so?
Hold it, let's not breed misunderstandings!
We’re not here to be your
pocket-sized satellite—
we want a relationship
built on equal footing.
But that's only after today's children
have grown up a bit.
Is it acceptable? Please convey this
to your superiors when you return to Japan.
When Takamaru, Al, Mirai,
and boys like Claude will grow up,
it'll be a new century, one filled with hope,
dreams, and a shining future.
"What is true democracy,
true independence?"—
you can trust them
to give the answer to that.
Wait, you!
Wait, Claude!
Hey, Claude!
I thought I told you that you can't come to school no more!
So you don't fear us, huh?!
Say, why don't I...
smack you like usual?
Oh! He's about to cry!
Crybaby! Crybaby! Crybaby!
Crybaby!
Claude, if you're a man,
don't run away! Fight!
H-He's defiant!
You've got some nerve, you punk!
Hurry up and cry!
Ouch!
I'm bleeding!
Asshole!
Now you've done it!
You jerk!
Takamaru!
Ow...
Right? Know what I mean?
No way!
If I go to cram school
looking like this, they'll scold me!
My mom's gonna go ballistic!
C-Claude! Next time, we'll mess you up so bad
you'll be too scared to go outside again!
I'm scared!
Hey, wait for me! Don't run!
I showed them!
Takamaru, Al, Mirai-san, I did it! I won!
Hey, boy, Takamaru!
What's up with the toy?
Who knows, looks like it's broken somehow.
No, it didn’t—it just ran out of battery.
Battery?
Al! Your hair's mostly back to how it was!
Gotta stay fashionable somehow.
See, we don't have these
flat batteries on our island yet.
And this one won't fit...
Man, we're totally screwed.
What about Mirai-dono?
Ah, Mirai's one is cooked too.
Connect these...
Then the circuit is completed...
It's shorted on me!
Good morning!
Oh? That haircut is quite something.
Nothing special!
Hey, Yumega Al Zaemon,
what kind of haircut is that?
It's Al! Al!
Listen up, you.
It is among the student's duties to...
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
But I think it's kinda cool
Enough, enough!
The End
for now
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer