Japan's Foreign Affairs Vice-Minister Fukuda Fukutaro
How much longer?
About four minutes, sir.
This is tricky, Fukuda-kun.
Japan is a developed country and one of the world's leaders,
yet within its territory there is an island that remains closed to the outside world.
Yes, sir, Champon Kingdom, I know.
What's more, there's that boy—
carrying a sword, wearing a topknot,
and still thinking it's the age of samurai!
Indeed, it wouldn't make a good look
if other countries find out.
That's right, not a good look at all.
We'll be the laughingstock of the world!
So what I need you to do,
Vice-Minister Fukuda...
You go there!
Huh?! Me?
B-But Foreign Minister,
that island seems to be inhabited
by all sorts of weird creatures.
Not that I know of.
No such report has ever been filed.
Rather, I heard that it's untouched nature is a sight to see.
I'm sure you were worried about your son, weren't you?
Then you should bring him along.
Yes, do just that.
Too bad it doesn't have any golf courses, it seems.
I hope you're not too bored!
Blast! Why do I have to go to that island?
Inspector, it's observable now.
The Champon Kingdom.
Where?
Really? It's but a tiny island!
Why did they call that Champon Kingdom?
And what's that childish shape anyway?
Oh? I can see some weird statue.
Where? Lemme see.
Oh!
The Smoking One
What on earth is that? Such a weird structure!
Some moyai-like guy standing on one foot
with a tanuki pouring liquor on top of it?
And further up, something incomprehensible with a silly face puffing out clouds of smoke?
Could it be the guardian
of the island or something?
Those islanders are an idiosyncratic bunch.
Whoa! There's something's approaching!
What's this?
Baby Goblin Jiro
Funny machine!
I-It's a child...
N-No, it has wings...
Hey!
Hey! Jiro!
What?
Don't pester that thing!
Hurry up and come down!
Oh, no... It's my dad!
Coming up now!
Great Goblin Tarobo
Jiro, if you don't hurry,
you'll be late for your Shichigosan Ceremony.
Aye-aye, dad!
Wh-What, what are these guys?
Bye-bye!
I'm going to my Shichigosan Ceremony!
What? What? What's with this island?!
Fukuda Claude
In modern-day Japan, there is an independent state that remains closed to the outside world, just as it was during the Tokugawa period.
Bakumatsu
Era
Super
Boy
Takamaru
I'm not joking! The handstand is the best
Homework, calligraphy, and genius—I don't need any of that
Hey baby, let's spend another cheerful day together
Hey lady, this is my heart speaking—I love you!
Every day is a fun school! Look, the teacher is smiling too
Seating order, uniforms, grades—I couldn't care less!
Hey mammy, we'll eat plenty today
Hey! daddy, with all my might, in the end...
(In the end)
I will be...
(I will be)
The world's best PhD, minister—wouldn't that be nice?
We are samurai, nice to meet you!
Topknots in our hearts, Ho, Ho, Ho
If you take a good look at the Smoking One,
you'll see a rainbow in the blue sky
Kibo Style Kendo
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday—feeling great
and
Thursday, Friday, Saturday too—Ha, Ha, Ha
Bity-Scratchy School Dojo
Waiting for that girl on our usual hill
on our way home from school...
Kibo Takamaru
Sensei! I am grateful for the training!
I'm so excited and thrilled!
Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday—feeling great
Takamaru's Father Kibo Koen
Thursday, Friday, Saturday too—Ha, Ha, Ha
Waiting for that girl on our usual hill
on our way home from school...
I'm so excited and thrilled!
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Everybody, come, come
(Everybody, come, come)
King of Champon Kingdom—Zako Takanokami Kaodeka
Come, come, Champon
(Come, come, Champon)
Now, don't be shy, come to see it at least once!
Kibo Takamaru, 11 years old—
heading to school!
Good morning!
Good morning, everyone!
Acorns?
Hey, boy!
Too slow, Takamaru!
Don't mind if I ride that too!
Kirameku Mirai (14 y.o.)
Saved...
Much obliged, Mirai-dono!
You again?
Mirai! You've gotta punish this jerk!
He jumped me for no reason!
What are you talking about?
It was you who brought a gun!
You beget chaos wherever you go.
Kibo Takamaru, Yumega Al Zaemon,
why don't I just leave you hanging there?
H-Hey!
Ah! Please wait for me, Mirai-dono!
I don't wanna be late to school!
Ugh! I'm Al!
Don't call me Al Zaemon!
What are you talking about?
You must cherish the name you received from your parents, Yumega Al Zaemon!
Yumega Al Zaemon
G-Goddamn! I'm Al! I don't want a lame name like Al Zaemon!
Al, don't you think it's not the time to talk about that?
Dark Magician Donpapa
Oh, hello there!
I'm sorry I kept you waiting,
Fukuda-dono!
All right, then...
Did you get a good sleep last night?
This here is the king of our beloved country,
Omoshirogao Zaemon Sugiura
Zako Takanokami Kaodeka.
I-I'm Fukuda Fukutaro,
sent to inspect your small island
on behalf of Japan's Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
"Small island?!"
How rude!
Small as it may be, our Champon Kingdom
is a splendid independent country!
You have no grounds
to consider us Japan's territory!
L-Legal status discussions always take time, so let's take it slowly.
By the way, my son Claude
is nowhere to be seen...
I took your son to our school.
S-School?
B-But my son hasn't been to school
in six months now...
Oh? Is he one of those famous
Japanese school truants?
Kirameku Zugai
The best way for boys and girls
to learn and play is together.
I'm sure Claude is enjoying his gym class
with everyone right now!
Good! The white team is behind,
but it's catching up fast!
Keep it up, both of you!
All, right, it's my turn!
You, the City Boy! Take care of the rest here!
Gold medal for me!
All right, then, Claude, it's your turn!
Yes, yes! Claude, do your best!
Come quickly, white team!
Don't let him win!
It's hopeless now!
Oh? What's wrong?
Takamaru-san will overtake him now!
How are you, Claude-dono?
Oh? What's wrong?
Anyone can do that jump!
There's no way I can do
something this incredible!
Incredible? You mean this obstacle course?
Yes! There's something wrong with you all
if you can do that so easily!
It's there! It's hiding there!
Yep!
Whoa! Got a big one!
Here you go!
Thank you!
Found another one!
In the shadow of this stone!
Whole three of them here!
Hey, boy, Takamaru!
What are you doing?
Hey, Takamaru!
Wait a second, Takamaru!
Here, it's yours.
Hey, wait!
Why, if it isn't Takamaru?
You lot are wasting your time
with toddlers again?
Why not come home sooner
and help with housework?
Looks who's talking!
You guys aren't exactly making the best use of your time either!
Huh? Hey, City Boy, what's that?
We're not loitering around, Al.
We're here on a duty to escort the son
of an important inspector from Japan.
Really? Such a simple mission
for the king's spy?
Must be important.
No, let me...
You do this, this, and then this.
And then...
Goshdarn...
It exploded!
It's a miracle!
How did you do it!
No, anyone can do that if the sensor
of the robot matches the laser of the pistol.
Hell knows what you just said,
but it sounds wonderful.
Here, and there...
And now... Finish!
I'll be damned!
You are genius!
Yeah, it felt like you were
that guy yourself!
Hey! What... What's that thing?
Ah, hell knows what it is,
but it's always been there.
When it does that,
it means the children should go home.
Father, it's time.
Let's stay a little longer.
You two, why don't you be friends with Claude while he's in our country?
You don't have to ask
for something like that!
Claude, won't you rent this toy to me again if we're friends?
Sure, anytime.
But I don't think I'll be staying here for long.
Huh? So then you'll be taking
the toys with you?!
I'll leave them to you
when it's time to leave.
Yahoo! That's OK with me!
Then, I'll be your friend from now on!
Don't forget to leave your toys to me.
S-Sure...
Al Zaemon, can he really call you a "friend?"
What's it to you?!
We're already friends, you hear? Right?
Listen here, when people hang out together...
Yeah, yeah, OK, OK, OK, I heard you!
Father, what are you laughing at?
Ah... No, nothing. Sorry.
Hey, Dark Magician Donpapa!
Yes! Führer Taiman, sir!
There is information that the Great Goblin Tarobo
of Champon Kingdom
is going to open up the country!
We're going to use this opportunity
to usurp the Champon Kingdom for ourselves!
Yes, sir! I have just a secret plan for this.
Please take a look!
Here I have a huge variety of alcoholic beverages, including beer, wine, whiskey, and more!
This is my own reserve for the night—
I mean, my secret plan!
Home
economics
room
Rain clouds?
The rain is set to only come every Wednesday!
Tsk! This is a pain!
It's the Smoking One
that's spewing out rain clouds!
I figured out the mechanism here!
Leader!
The rain keeps picking up!
It's raining!
How very strange!
Gotta hurry!
Run, boy, run!
This is a natural disaster.
Our weather schedule got twisted.
Weather schedule?
What could that be?
Don't you know?
For over a thousand years,
it's been up to the Smoking One
to decide whether it's going
to rain or shine in our kingdom today.
Rain or shine?
Now that's silly.
Pops, what happened to Tarobo,
the Great Goblin of the Smoking One?
Well, last I heard he was heading
to his son's Shichigosan Ceremony.
Dispatch an emergency party
to inspect the Smoking One.
At once!
My word...
Leaving the weather to a goblin!
What a weird island!
If we incorporated it into Japan...
There'd be nothing to gain from it!
The real fun starts now! Do it!
That's right!
Keep the booze flowing!
Embrace this special
drunken medicine from Donpapa!
I can't wait to go back to Tokyo!
At this rate, not only will Claude not get better—
he’s gonna end up one of those crazies!
Upsy-daisy...
What's this? Booze?
What's going on?
Now this stuff is good!
Huh?
What are you doing, teachers?
Oh, Takamaru?
School’s out for the day!
That's right!
What's gotten into you?
Takamaru, you drink too!
Drink, drink!
Ugh! Terrible!
Isn't it alcohol?
Alcohol running from the tap—
where else would you find that?
Let's all go to the castle and get drunk!
Next, I'll take his son hostage and use him to blackmail the King of Champon!
With all the grownups on the island drunk off their heads, this kingdom’s as good as ours!
I'm home, Papa.
Not here, huh?
Dat thing you's gnawing
lookin' mighty tasty to me!
Mind lendin' dat toy to we's?
W-We're in trouble, everyone!
Claude's been kidnapped!
Our toys's been kidnapped!
What's the rush, Takamaru?
You've gotta see this!
Toys!
Wh-Wh-Wh...
You don't need a special cause to drink...
Al's father Yumega Tsubushinosuke
Hey, father! What are you doing?!
Oh! Al, drink with us!
Is that your son?
Well, I'm a secretary to Japan's Foreign—
Father! Father!
Father!
Hey, head coach! Zugai-sama!
Ugh...
Your highness! King!
There's the farmer's daughter,
at the mountain pass near the village...
We can't count on them...
Doesn't matter if the grownups can't help us.
We'll just have to do it on our own.
Goddamn! They'll pay
for taking away my toys!
Whoa... It looks way bigger up close!
It's 400 meters high.
We've no choice but to climb it!
Hey, you two!
If you keep climbing it like that, you won't make it to the top even in three days!
M-Mirai-dono?
What's with that outfit?
What’s the big idea,
making us laugh now of all times?
So the Smoking One is full of secret tunnels?
What's your deal, Mirai?
Why do we have to bring along a turtle shell?
It's about to begin.
This sound...
It's just like right before
the Smoking One starts farting and peeing.
Takamaru, place that shell on the hole.
On top of it?
Hurry! We don't have much time!
All right!
Okay, now get inside!
Here it comes!
What's this, a hot spring?
It's a geyser.
Geyser, is that...
Like a hot spring that erupts over time?
That's right!
And it'll carry us to the top!
This sound...
So this is what the Smoking One's
fart and pee really are?
Kibo Takamaru!
Yumega Al Zaemon!
Kibo Takamaru! Yumega Al Zaemon!
Are you safe?
It separated us?
Ah! Mirai-san,
help me!
Oh! Did your friends come to save you?
Let's see...
It hurt, goddammit!
Al! Al! Takamaru!
Takamaru, help me! Takamaru!
That's great!
What courageous children!
You're pathetic in comparison!
Are all the city kids like that?
Don't ask me!
Shut up already!
Fine, let's reward those kids appropriately for their courage.
I am one of Donpapa's three minions, Ninja Gorgeous.
As much as it pains me,
I'll have to take your life, little girl!
"Ninja" means someone who is discreet.
Only a fool introduces himself before a fight.
And I'm not a little girl!
You talk too much!
You can block my sword
with your arm—I'm impressed!
A ninja needs not flashy decorations.
Don't they hinder your movements?
Spare me your concern!
Unnecessary showing-off!
Unsteady stance!
And stupid useless hat!
It hurt!
That's it—you've done it!
Look, I won't show you any mercy now!
Cloning technique!
What's wrong?
Why won't you attack?
Such a showy technique
is just a waste of effort.
What? Showy technique?
You broad!
You see, the cloning technique is only effective if the enemy is actively trying to attack you.
If I just wait it out,
you can't do anything to me.
Silence!
What's wrong? Tired already?
See? You can't support that many of them
It hurts!
It hurts! Don't you know
it hurts, you little girl?
I hate those who call me a little girl
or a child the most! You'll pay for it!
Wait! No, please wait!
It hurts!
Foreigners can't become ninjas!
You're eating too much meat!
It hurts!
You'd need to eat more small fish!
Y-You'll regret this!
And you won't be able
to save your friends anyway!
Ah! Wait!
Not bad for a cretin.
Got it? Take this as a lesson
and never use your powers for evil again!
Shut your mouth! I'm not taking orders from a stupid little girl!
Got it! I was in the wrong!
Forgive me!
The fool...
Takamaru! Mirai!
Geez, these two...
Where in the world did they go?
Even I can feel lonely when left for so...
What the hell!
A pile of trash?
Oi, bowy! Whau down'd wou bway wid be?
Oh no!
Oh my god!
To be
continued
RAW
Translation
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
True Noobow Gamer