Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
Episode 206
Pootan! Pootan, let's play!
No, poo. Pootan is busy working
on his tax return, poo.
Damn you! I hate you, Pootan!
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
See you again around
next week
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
Noboru Yamaguchi (16) (Comedy nut)
Radio name: ''Ajishio Taro''
How stupid.
It's a crime that someone gets paid
to make such a stupid show.
Moreover, to make the matter worse, the ratings
tend to be high when the show is so worthless.
But let me say one thing.
Even if the numbers are good,
it's trash unless I approve!
Pootan is always great!
The current TV shows are already belly-up.
Ishikawa got knocked out again.
He took a tremendous kick to his jaw.
As I thought, the only option is for me to
become a comedian and correct this situation.
I wonder if Yamaguchi doesn't like him?
I don't mind doing it on my own,
but I worry if the public
can follow my high-level comedy.
lf only I had a powerful partner who
could handle my sense of humor...
In that case, there's only one man
who could become that partner.
Open
Southern
Wind
Hasn't Takenouchi lost some weight lately?
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Radio name: "Honey Boy"
Yeah, he might have thrown up.
Shinjiro Hayashida (16)
By the way, there's one thing
that has been bothering me.
I feel like someone's been
following us around lately.
Really? Aren't you imagining things?
Now, the question is what to do from here.
How do I approach him?
If a stranger abruptly says...
Do you want to form a comedy duo with me?
Huh?
It would naturally cause
Honey Boy to shy away!
I could just tell him that I am
"postcard artisan, Ajishio Taro."
But he's ranked higher than
I am in late-night radio shows,
so there's a chance that he'll take
the lead when we form a duo later.
It's not a good idea to let him
know who I am right now.
A while back, agencies would assign
the partner without asking when a duo was formed.
But these days there are many cases
where the partners are classmates
from middle school or high school, or they
were in the same theatrical company.
But we aren't classmates,
nor do we even go to the same school.
Moreover, our schools have
an extremely hostile relationship.
Hold on a second.
It's dramatic when two people
with no connection meet.
It may become a legend
after we become popular.
Having a head trip
All People Have a Past!
Comedian Noboru Yamaguchi
Then Mr. Yamaguchi and Mr. Honey
met at a coffeehouse by accident?
All People Have a Past!
Comedian Noboru Yamaguchi
Yeah, sort of.
All People Have a Past!
Comedian Noboru Yamaguchi
What a coincidence!
All People Have a Past!
Comedian Noboru Yamaguchi
Oh, no! What the hell am I thinking?!
How embarrassing!
Daydreaming about my own
popularity before I've even debuted!
What do you wanna do, make people laugh
or become a snobby intellectual?!
Anyway, I want to form a duo
with this Honey Boy!
All I have to do is express
that feeling to him honestly!
There's no need to try and act cool!
All right! Here I come!
Well, really, Pootan is the best!
Yeah! I even bought the plush figure.
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
Episode 782
Pootan, Pootan! Listen to this.
Pootan working hard on pottery.
What is it, poo?
When I was walking in town earlier,
an older man who I've never seen before talked to me.
He said "Hey, long time no see!" or something like that.
I see. And?
And he said "Let's go out for a drink
once in a while" and walked off.
And what did you do, poo?
I didn't know what to do, so I said
"Yes, of course!" or something,
because it'd be rude if he were
an acquaintance, wouldn't it?
But no matter how much I think about it,
I think he was confusing me with someone else.
What do you think, Pootan?
Well, that has nothing to do with Pootan, poo.
Geez, you're always cold!
Pootan
To be
continued
The show will continue on and on, poo.
I watched the show again
and I think that it really isn't funny at all!
But just saying "it's stupid"
is something that an amateur would do.
In any case, as someone who aims
to be a professional comedian,
I have to analyze why it's so popular.
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
I've purchased a book like this,
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
It's not too late
a               for you to follow it!!
How to enjoy
a         Pootan
and Pootan goods like these...
At any rate, it's such a monstrous show that
makes that genius, Honey Boy, go ooh and aah.
There's got to be something to it!
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
Episode 783
I won't miss any secrets to its popularity,
even by a millimeter!
Heartwarming Hilarious Comedy
Pootan
Episode 783
Hey, Pootan, Pootan! Someone
called out to me in town again.
Pootan grinding sesame with a wooden pestle.
Another older man who you don't know?
No, this time, it was someone I knew.
So it's okay, right, poo?
But this time I didn't remember his name.
I see. Something like that
happens often, doesn't it?
It gets very uncomfortable, poo.
I was very nervous.
But I managed to cut the conversation short and escaped from there.
If it was a buddy of mine or a childhood friend,
I can get through by calling them "you,"
but since it was someone from work,
I couldn't speak that way...
Oh, it was someone from work.
By the way, what do you do, poo?
Well... I can't tell you that.
But thinking about it, you are a rude person,
forgetting your acquaintance's name, no?
No, that's not really the case, Pootan.
Why not, poo? Tell me, poo.
Because he didn't remember
my name correctly either.
He called me "Taro" or something.
That's so funny.
In any case, what's your name again?
It's not just stupid,
this show is really confusing!
But if I say "it's stupid" carelessly,
they may say that it's because I'm old-fashioned.
What an unpleasant era this is, that we can't
say "it's stupid" honestly when it's stupid.
In a way, it's similar to violence.
This isn't good! What am I whining about?
I sound like some dumb comedian
who's envying a popular show.
Calm down. Think about it.
There must be some secret
to the show's popularity.
We've hit rock bottom, Pootan.
I see! I got it! The secret
of this show's popularity is...
This plush costume!
Especially in the realm of comedy, things like
costumes and wigs are universally popular.
Strange things tend to captivate
the childlike hearts of people in all eras.
Innocent children probably
don't even think there are people in them.
It's a little makeshift,
but I'll acknowledge it.
In short, it's only these costumes
that are popular, not these two.
Okay! I'll now pull myself together
and watch the rest of the show!
Well, then, next is the most popular corner
of this show, "It's Time for Free Talk."
Is there anything to talk about?
No, not really.
They took them off.
Dear Mother,
I feel that I'm completely used to
the life at Cromartie these days.
Oh? Is that you, Kamiyama?
You're...
Well, if it isn't Tabata!
I knew it was you, Kamiyama.
Long time no see, Tabata.
Since we're going to different high schools,
we haven't seen each other at all.
If I remember right, you're going to
Cromartie High School, right?
How is Cro-High?
I'm doing okay somehow.
Just as I expected from you, Kamiyama.
I heard that it's tough in Cro-High
since there are many bad kids there,
but I was thinking that you'd be just fine.
But I also kinda thought that you
could possibly become like this.
Yeah, but while people at Cro-High
look scary, they're actually nice.
How about you, Tabata?
Classes at our Kokaku High are pretty tough,
and I'm barely keeping up with them.
Yoshio is studying hard too.
I see. Yoshio has been always
a hard worker since middle school.
Say hello to Yoshio for me.
Okay, I'll tell Yoshio you said hello. See you later.
Later.
Tabata is also working hard
in a different school.
All right, I'll do my best too.
I'll go home and watch Pootan or something for now.
I'll watch Pootan again and
figure out the reason for its popularity!
Gerotan
GE
Pootan will not be shown today.
Hello! Gerotan came to the beach today.
GE
Hey, don't say it's unseasonable.
This isn't a beach in Japan.
GE
Pootan will not be shown today.
The coasts in foreign countries
are different from ones in Japan,
and you see special beaches and
private beaches suddenly, so be careful.
Pootan will not be shown today.
It's dangerous to just wander around.
I stepped on a sea cucumber!
That's all right. It's not poop.
It's a sea cucumber.
That was close!
Pootan will not be shown today.
I heard that sea cucumbers run away
after throwing up their own internal organs
Pootan will not be shown today.
when they come across their enemies.
That's scary, isn't it?
Gerotan, the picture and
your lines don't seem to match.
Pootan will not be shown today.
Hey, don't worry about it. No nagging, okay?
It feels good just floating like this.
Pootan will not be shown today.
Drifting in the waves... drifting...
Gebebebo!
Yay! I easily get seasick.
But it's fun because a lot of fish came to feed, isn't it?
Gerotan
The End
Gerotan doesn't like parties on
a houseboat either, right?
Oh, yeah, there's that story too.
Gerotan
The End
This isn't Pootan...
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
I'm the main character, Takashi Kamiyama.
It's possible that people have forgotten me.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Looking forward
to the next episode
What's Gerotan?
It's a long story,
so don't ask.