Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
The Conflict Intensifies!
Cromartie High School vs. Bass High School
Jackson Setouchi (16)
Jackson Setouchi. He's like a boss of Year 1 at Bass High.
Due to his great physical strength,
he's also known as "Bass' King of Destruction."
Akio Takejo (16)
Akio Takejo.
Setouchi's right-hand man, the one he trusts the most.
Bass High's Year 1 #2 man.
It's even said that Bass doesn't
make a move without him.
Year 1 Students Regular Meeting at Bass High School
Unless we do something,
Cromartie will keep looking down on us.
Our Year 2 doesn't stand up to Cromartie.
That's why they look down on us too.
Yeah, that's right!
Should we also beat up
our Year 2 at the same time?
But we have a tradition
of respecting seniority.
Even if Year 2 is pathetic,
we, as Year 1, shouldn't complain.
Cromartie's tough.
Particularly, I heard that you can't stop
that Takenouchi guy when he snaps.
But don't you think it's about time for Bass
to end its history of being below
Cromartie with our, Year 1's, hands?
His nose hair's sticking out.
Are you saying we should do it by ourselves?
Are you serious?
That's not something that
we can decide just like that.
But upon the honor
of Bass' name, we have to decide
if we are to fight against Cromartie
or if we should back down!
It's definitely sticking out.
Cromartie... It sure is scary there.
It's bugging me so much
I can't focus on the meeting.
All right! He noticed it!
My prayer may have worked.
Now I can relax and...
What the... It moved?
But think about it calmly.
Our fighting power is
definitely as good as theirs!
Calm down. Thinking scientifically,
there's no way it can move.
But he's touching his nose again,
which could mean...
There are more now.
Akio Takejo's nose hair was sticking out too.
And there were going to be more and more.
The Idle Student
Cromartie Municipal High School
I'm bored.
The Idle Student
Yeah...
Kamiyama, was school
always this boring and dull?
Yeah, that's how school is, Hayashida.
When we're at this sensitive stage in our lives,
being really bored is, in a way,
similar to being tortured!
I say it as a delinquent...
But developing such patience is also
important in preparing for the real world.
Basically, school is a place to study,
so it can't possibly be fun.
Our school is a school for badasses, but in
that sense, it's the same as other schools.
In any case, I'm fed up
with this familiar scenery.
Well, being bored means
that we're peaceful and happy, so....
I wish something really
surprising would happen.
Lero!
I didn't know Freddie had a horse.
Hayashida, didn't you see it
in front of the restroom before?
Now getting back to the earlier topic...
Delinquents are often mistaken,
but school is a place where you study,
not a place where you expect
something fun or surprising.
But I think other schools
could be more interesting and fun.
That's an illusion.
You sound like a child
who envies what others have.
A friend of someone I know goes to a school
that seems to be very interesting.
But you see, that friend is just exaggerating.
His school is normal, just like ours.
In short, everyone's bored,
but they try to convince themselves that
the environment they're in is interesting
because they don't want to think that they're
the only one who's spending a boring life.
In any case, every school's the same.
They are normal, just like ours.
I don't know why,
but I just want some excitement!
I'll tell you bluntly. There isn't even one such
excitement here. I can say that with certainty.
Lero Liro Lero Leo!
Isn't that a wild horse?
Geez... It's extremely imprudent
to come to school by horse.
Well, I don't care about that.
But I still think other schools are
more exciting and interesting.
You still don't get it? Any school is boring.
People who say school's fun are so bored
that they feel even stupid stuff is interesting,
or they convince themselves that theirs is interesting.
In other words, you're saying that
we shouldn't bother complaining how boring it is
when it's supposed to be boring.
In any case, our school's too normal.
Good morning.
Normal is fine. What's wrong with normal?
I'm not really expecting anything that incredible.
All I want is a little something
that'll give me a bit of a laugh.
An incident that'll give us a bit of a laugh?
Yeah.
Ouch! Ouch!
There's trouble!
Maeda's being bitten by a horse!
Well, that happens all the time.
Yeah, it does.
NOT!
Bass High School Gym Storage Room
At Least It's a Battle
Without Honor or Humanity
If you're gonna fudgin' kill me, do it now!
That's not gonna happen,
since you're an important hostage.
What? A hostage?
Jackson Setouchi
Oh, yeah!
We're gonna lure Cromartie's Takenouchi
to our Bass High by using you as a hostage.
Today's the end for him.
You bastard! That's a dirty trick.
Who cares about dirty tricks
when fighting, you idiot?!
Our guys are heading to Cromartie right now.
We got a call from Aki.
Seems like he got to Cro-High.
Okay, give the phone to me.
Here you go.
Jackson Setouchi
It's me, Setouchi.
There's a guy named Takenouchi.
Call him out and tell him this:
"We have Maeda, so come to Bass High alone."
Damn!
Bass High No. 2        Akio Takejo
We're at Cromartie's front gate,
Cromartie
High School
and we just ran into something disturbing.
What? What did you say you found?
Footprints! And they aren't
just normal footprints!
They're horse hooves!
And they're as big as elephant's feet.
Make up your mind
if it's a horse or an elephant.
I said it was a horse, didn't I?!
It's not an elephant!
In any case, it's a huge horse.
It's so huge, as if it may not be a horse!
Calm down. This isn't like you.
Anyway, I can't explain well over the phone.
What should I do?
I certainly can't understand
it at all over the phone.
Hey! Does your school have a horse?
No, we don't have a horse.
Akira Maeda
But there's a guy who comes to school by horse.
Talk
Takejo
Oh, hell! I found another disturbing thing!
What is it this time?
It's a vending machine!
There's a vending machine
in front of the school gate!
What are you talking about?
We have a vending machine in
our cafeteria too, you know.
No, that's not it. This isn't
a regular vending machine!
What the hell's that vending machine like?
All right, listen carefully!
This vending machine...
Guts
Doesn't have a slot for 100 yen coins!
Hello.
Jackson
Setouchi
Akira
Maeda
That's probably not a vending machine.
Talk
Takejo
Oh, hell! I found something
even more disturbing!
Talk
Takejo
Again?
There's a gorilla...
A gorilla...
Now look here...
If it's someone with a face like gorilla's,
any school has at least one such guy.
I've never seen someone
with a face like a gorilla's.
Neither have I.
No! Not someone like a gorilla, but a real gorilla!
All right, all right.
You're saying there's a gorilla.
But just the same, that gorilla's
wearing a school uniform, right?
You moron! There's no way a gorilla'd
be wearing a uniform, is there?!
ls there a gorilla?
There is, but I don't know if
he's one of our students.
Oh, hell! An even more
disturbing thing has shown up.
Come on, there's no way that something
more disturbing than a gorilla appeared.
What could be more
disturbing than a gorilla?
Surely you're not gonna tell me that
there's an alien or something?
Bingo.
And did you find Takenouchi?
No, he isn't here.
So that's what it was!
Or rather, I've started feeling like
I don't care about Takenouchi any more.
Why are there aliens,
but no Takenouchi?!
Can I go home now?
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
There's also a next episode.
Well, the night's wearing on,
but please bear with us a little longer.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Let's watch out for horses
I wonder if Maeda and Freddie's horse don't get along?
Ouch!