Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
Takeshi Hokuto, 16 years old.
Heir to the Hokuto Foundation.
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
His father is the chairman of the Hokuto Group
and also chairs the board of directors
of several high schools.
His son, Takeshi, has controlled
eighteen high schools
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
using his own force and his father's power as his weapons.
And at last, he transferred to Cromartie
High School, known as the worst of them,
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
to bring them into his clutches.
Mr. Hokuto! Please wait for me!
Empire of Ambition
So this is Cromartie?
Such a filthy place.
Lackey
If there's someone who defies you,
let's have him expelled right away,
with your father's power.
People are pigs!
I'll hammer my ideals into the heads
of these incompetent pigs to control them!
First, we'll start here, right?
I can handle this myself.
You wait for me there.
Okay.
What happened?
There was a guy who looked
like a pro wrestler just now.
I wonder if it was an illusion?
Well, this school is famous for its badasses.
No, this guy's on a different level
than badasses and delinquents!
How can I describe it?
There's nothing to be afraid of!
You've seen many badasses
up until now, right, Mr. Hokuto?!
No, I've never seen anyone like that!
Please calm down, Mr. Hokuto!
If you stumble in a place like this,
you won't be able to go forward!
That's true.
But you see it with me as well this time! Promise!
Okay.
Freddie, that's my seat!
You aren't even in our class!
Our class is next door, Kamiyama, Hayashida.
Hey, Freddie. We were also mistaken
as to where our classroom was.
He was being slapped on the head for some reason.
Yeah. I'm really surprised right now as well.
He just looks tough, probably.
No, that can't be it.
It's camouflage to deceive us!
There's nothing to worry about.
If you don't like him, all you
have to do is have him expelled.
What if he resents me for it?
You're more of a worrier
than I thought, aren't you?
But what worries me even more is that
I have a feeling he'd still come to school even
after being expelled, like nothing happened.
If that's the case, we can't do anything to him!
Please calm down.
No matter how monstrous he may look,
he's still just a human being like us!
Now that you mention it, you're exactly right.
Regardless of how he looks,
he's just a human being like us, right?
Now, let's open the door.
Have some confidence!
Okay! Here goes!
That's not a human being!
Hello, Mommy? I can't go into the classroom.
Get Daddy on the phone for me!
The Strike Back Empire
Takenouchi, Freddie, that gorilla.
These two guys and this animal
seem to command Year 1.
In short, all I need to do is
get control of them, right?
No, believe it or not,
that's not really the case.
What?!
Actually, according to the information I have,
it seems that the moves of these three
are centered around one man.
I see. Then that means that
I just need to defeat that man, right?
No matter who he is,
he'll be a piece of cake for me.
Just what kind of guy is he?
That man is...
...this guy.
Main character Takashi Kamiyama
What? What is it?
I wondered what you were like.
You're just a worthless man.
You'd better kneel down
in front of me immediately!
Please hold on a second.
What are you talking about?
Listen carefully! My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
I'll control this school too.
For the sake of my ideals!
Here comes another weirdo.
As a first step, I've decided to bury you.
What are you saying?
Do you think that such violence is allowed?
Freddie wants a banana.
I guess the foolish masses can't understand it.
My father is the chair of this high school.
He can expel you all.
Can I say something?
What is it?
This is a municipal school, so there's no chair.
What? Municipal?
In the first place, your uniform is different.
That's a white uniform, isn't it?
He's right.
I came to the wrong school. What'll I do now?
I've already completed the transfer process,
and it'd be very embarrassing
to say I made a mistake this far into it.
I can't use Dad's power in this school.
But I've said this much, so I can't take it back.
I wonder if he's all right?
Okay, I've decided!
I'll just use lies to cover it up.
Well, listen carefully, you bastards!
My dad isn't the chair of this school!
Then what is he?
You're not making sense.
You're the one who said he was the chair.
Well, hold on, my dad is...
The evil mastermind who controls
the Japanese government from the shadows,
the Shadow Premier!
Mastermind?
For my dad, it's easy to control a municipal
high school from the shadows.
You bastards are also
nothing but his subordinates.
Ouch, he did it. He's talking really crazy!
Even elementary students
wouldn't believe such nonsense!
What? ls that true?
Yeah.
That's incredible!
They bought it! These guys are total morons!
Even I'm getting confused as to what I'm saying.
So, what is the son of the evil one
doing in a school like this?
Young master!
Son of the evil one?
Oh, he's talking about me.
Let's see...
To defeat that evil mastermind, of course!
But the mastermind is your dad, right?
That's right... Let me see...
For a man, there is a time when he has to fight
for justice, even if it's against his own father!
Can I say one thing?
Oh, no! Did he figure it out after all?
Please let me help you! For justice!
Really?
Hey, hey, hey.
I'd be upset if you forgot about me.
About this Hayashida!
You dumbass! Of course
you're our comrade too!
Okay, now we have all the players.
From today, we are comrades for justice!
All right! Starting tomorrow, let's give it our best!
Yeah!
We're in deep trouble.
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum on a guitar in the mountains.
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Let's strum
on a guitar
in the mountains
Eiji "New" Nonaka
This has nothing to do with the story!
Sixteen year old Takeshi Hokuto,
who made an unheard of mistake
by transferring to the wrong school.
He was driven into a difficult position due to
lies that he kept telling to hide that mistake.
To say the least, your father
being the evil mastermind is...
Stop it! When I think that was
what I said, I'm so embarrassed.
But from how that story went,
we now have to form a team with them
and fight against the evil mastermind.
Think about it calmly.
They're idiots who fell for a story like that.
They're sure to have completely
forgotten about it after one day!
Truly, they were incredibly stupid, but...
They're probably frolicking around somewhere.
Captain!
Captain?!
They've got a good memory
in spite of their stupidity.
Well, we've looked all over for you, Captain!
Salute to our Captain!
Where the hell did they buy those clothes?
They're certainly mistaken somehow,
Captain, I mean, Mr. Hokuto.
Captain?
What the hell's that about?
I'm so embarrassed.
Would you stop saying "Captain"
in front of everybody?
Why's that, Captain?!
This isn't good! They're serious.
I'd better do something.
It wouldn't be good if we hang out
with them any longer, Mr. Hokuto!
Besides, you're going to control
this school, aren't you?
I forgot about that.
I see! Is this what they want?
Perhaps this is a trap meant to ensnare me.
No, it can't be. They're definitely stupid.
Because their eyes are serious...
If that's the case, I have no choice but to
evade the issue by feeding them more lies!
This looks pretty bad.
Listen, everyone. The truth is,
my dad found out about our troops.
What?! The boss of our enemy did?
It seems that my dad, who's the
mastermind of the Japanese government,
was so afraid of my existence
that he sent in an ex-Green Beret
from the US as an assassin to kill me.
Oh, boy... He started his ridiculous talk again!
An assassin from the US?
Man, it looks like your dad is serious!
Yeah.
They bought it again!
If I were with you any longer,
you'd be involved too.
So I've decided to leave our troops.
Nice! Good work, Takeshi!
But if you quit, who the hell
is going to be our Captain?
That's obvious.
Kamiyama, I leave the rest to you!
But I don't know if I can play
such an important role.
You can do it!
Hayashida...
You too, Freddie...
I understand. Follow me, everyone!
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
I can finally go home. I'm so exhausted.
I can't even imagine what will happen
if I keep telling lies to those idiots from Cromartie.
I can't stand it! Okay, I'll tell them
the whole truth tomorrow!
And I'll transfer schools again!
Welcome home.
I'm home.
We're going to spend our nights here
to protect you from now on.
As Captain, I can't let you die alone in vain.
Thank you very much, Captain.
Things are getting crazier.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
I thought about many things, but you
can't predict what happens in the world.
You can't predict what happens
in the next episode either.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Next Episode, Pootan
Could it be there's an idiot among us?
Who are you talking about?