Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Jakajan!
Cromartie.
Tabigebe
Kelp
Bonito
Plum
Oh, I'm Gerotan!
I'm making onigiri right now!
But don't worry! I'm not planning on making that your DVD bonus!
Gerotan is going to eat it himself!
He's going on a journey!
Don't worry about it everyone,
just keep an eye on Cromartie High School for me!
Gerotan travels around the world
Model Gerotan
and punishes restaurants that are full of themselves despite serving bad food!
Boo! Boo! What?
Gerotan, can you drive a car?
Oh, no, I'm rolling back!
I'm on a slope, after all.
I feel sick when I'm moving backwards!
Wow, I puked so much!
It's a bit of a waste, isn't it?
Well, I have plenty more to say about Cromartie High School after this!
Right now, we’re airing
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
We’ll also have an announcement about a giveaway from the show.
Also, there will be a gift
announcement from the program!
You'll get a gift from Gerotan too.
From Gerotan?
Dear Mother,
Cromartie High School is said to be
among the worst in Tokyo.
In this case, the worst offender is that fortune slip that brought me misfortune.
Indeed, it is evil incarnate.
At Cromartie High School,
I'm doing my best as always.