Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
I wanna go to Koshien.
That's impossible with your attention span.
I see... I wonder if it's really
impossible for me to go to Koshien?
You'll be fine.
All you need is the passion
to want to play baseball.
K-Kamiyama...
Thanks! Courage is springing up
in my heart now!
If my words help,
I'll help you as much as you want.
Yeah!
I don't want to throw cold water on things,
but do you know the rules of baseball?
First, get a buzz cut.
That's not a rule.
First of all, you can't play baseball
unless you have nine people.
Don't worry. I'll be all right by myself.
Like I said, that doesn't work. It's a rule!
I can't quite agree with your opinion, Maeda.
You don't know much about
baseball either, do you?!
Well, I will concede the point to you
and admit that you have to have nine people.
But isn't being restricted
by rules a sad way of living?
It's true that we need rules.
But sometimes breaking them
creates something new.
People who are restricted by rules
don't make any progress in the end.
That's why you can't make friends, Maeda!
Yeah, what Kamiyama says is right.
Why don't you stop acting tough and
listen to what your heart's saying?
Before gathering nine people for baseball,
shouldn't you find your friends?
Thanks, everyone.
I don't have any friends and...
Hey, that's not what we're talking about!
Anyway, baseball needs nine people!
If I hold the other team down myself
and hit home runs, there won't be a problem.
Leave it to me.
No matter how incredible you pitch
to strike out the batters,
if there's no catcher, it's a wild pitch,
so they'll steal first base.
Don't worry, because I'm the
get-'em-out-by-letting-'em-hit type.
You only know the details about
weird stuff, don't you?
Anyway, you can't play unless
there's nine players in your team!
Okay, I got it. All I have to do is gather
nine people, right? Don't get so worked up.
We have many friends,
so we'll find enough people soon.
Sorry, we have only eight people.
And moreover, two of them aren't human.
More like, these are the guys we
usually hang out with, aren't they?
Can I ask you something?
I've counted several times, but
aren't there only seven people?
You aren't counting yourself, are you?
Five, six, seven... eight...
I never said that I wanted to play baseball.
Just accept it, Maeda!
This is how you start making friends.
While we were talking,
we got the ninth member.
Maeda's old lady.
Hokuto's lackey would be enough!
So, we have founded the
Cromartie High School baseball team,
but first we need to get equipment.
But we don't have that kind of money.
So why don't we do
something about it with our brains?!
Let's use wooden swords!
They can substitute for bats.
I see. I didn't think of that.
What about a chest protector?
It'd be enough if we wrap bleached cotton cloth around our waists.
If we think about it this way, I guess there are many substitutes for baseball equipment.
We can do it! We can play baseball!
Stricter Enforcement
for Motorcycle Gang Month in Effect
Metropolitan
Police Department
They won't believe that we're
gonna play baseball like this.
Oh? Where's Hayashida?
Dear Mother,
this is the thick woods of Fuji.
I heard that once you set foot in here,
you can't get out.
How terrible.
We only came to Mt. Fuji two days ago
for baseball training camp.
It was a mistake that we didn't
find some lodging first.
We got lost in the woods, since some
idiot said camping would be cheaper.
Fine then. It would make you happy
if I apologize by dying, right?
Hey, Maeda, aren't you going too far?
It doesn't matter, because he's
always all talk and no action.
What did you say, moron?!
Are you making fun of me?!
Shut up!
Stop it, both of you! You're only
wasting your energy by fighting!
Sorry. This isn't the time for that, is it?
We're all irritated because we're hungry.
We should eat something.
There should still be a can of mackerel.
And do we have a can opener?
Don't worry, I have one here.
Generally in this kind of situation,
it often ends up that there's canned food,
but no can opener.
Well done, Maeda.
If I do say so myself,
I never lose my cool under any circumstances.
It's all over if you panic in this kind of situation.
Everyone needs to settle down and act calmly.
But that's not the canned mackerel.
Mecha-ratta!
The canned mackerel is this one!
The sun went down and it's getting
colder and quieter around here.
Are we gonna die here like this?!
I still had a lot of things that I wanted to do!
For example?
For example... well...
No, you don't have to force yourself to find it.
We're just sixteen years old.
Is this how it's gonna end for us?
What the hell should we do?
Open 24 hours
Ramen
Hello, welcome!
Welcome!
Well, a large ramen again?
This customer's been coming here for breakfast,
lunch and dinner for the last three days.
Where on Earth does he live?
Thanks for coming!
Open 24 hours
Ramen
He doesn't have any problems paying
and is well-mannered,
but I wonder which country he's from?
What should we do?
We're in trouble.
How can we get out of here?!
It's already been four days since
we wandered into the thick woods.
Everyone has now gotten completely worn out.
Even Hayashida, who's always energetic,
is in this condition.
There's no life in Hokuto's face either.
And Freddie...
A naruto?
Okay, calm down. Think carefully.
Why is a naruto stuck to Freddie's face?
That's right! It means that
there's some food in this forest!
And we all split up to search for food.
What did we find?
In the end, this is all we could find.
Then where did Freddie get the naruto?
It's a mystery.
Well, there are many mysteries in thick woods.
Come to think of it, where did Hayashida go?
It's been almost five hours.
Hey!
That's...
Hey! It's me!
Hayashida! You're all right?
Well, I bought these at a convenience store.
I guess convenience stores
really are everywhere, aren't they?
But I walked an animal trail
for at least three hours!
Wow, that must've been a lot of work.
Hey, Hayashida...
If you got to a convenience store,
shouldn't you have just asked for help?
We're all close friends, aren't we?
I can't go alone, leaving you guys behind.
So I rushed back.
Hayashida...
I love you, man.
Well, that's a little...
By the way, Hayashida,
I'm sure you didn't, but...
What? What is it?
Where's the hot water?
Oh! I forgot it!
Geez! How could you forget
something so important?!
Are you really trying to help?
We're gonna starve to death, aren't we?!
That's not the issue here!
Joshua Tree
The fifth day since we entered the thick woods...
Day 5
I've already lost my hopes and dreams.
What are you saying, Hayashida?
Wasn't our dream that we were
to go to Koshien to play baseball?
You're right! We came here to play baseball!
That's right! Even if we're in the thick woods,
if we give up our dream, that means we lose!
We should play baseball!
Yeah...
Really?
Ready?
Yeah!
Oh, no...
Don't hit the ball hard in the thick woods!
We've only got one ball.
I'll go and get it.
Open 24 hours
Ramen
A man!
Pops!
Get that ball over there for me.
Okay.
Five hours later, Hayashida came back.
So I was able to meet a very kind pops
who owns a ramen restaurant.
I guess things aren't really that bad in the world.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Why didn't you ask that pops for help?
Oh! That's right!
Sorry, I just panicked.
Looking for a ball calmly
is more abnormal than that.
Look at the sky.
Birds are flying freely,
as if they're laughing at us.
Wild animals have nothing to fear, no matter if
they're in thick woods like this or anywhere else.
Hey, hold on a second.
Speaking of animals,
we had a gorilla on our team, didn't we?
Oh, yeah!
Hey, look at that!
The gorilla's beckoning.
But can we trust him?
It'll be all right.
Let's go follow him.
But he walks fast.
Don't lose him.
Look at that!
He's climbing the tree and
looking around the area!
Just as you'd expect from a gorilla.
He does things differently!
He's starting to look dependable!
And after three hours
of wandering around in the thick woods...
Oh, I'm tired.
Is this path really the correct one?
Lights!
There's no mistake!
Those are lights from a city!
We did it!
We're saved!
Thanks, gorilla. It's all thanks to you.
This is a different gorilla!
Then where's our gorilla?
Previous gorilla that got lost
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
The next episode is... The next episode is...
Just as I thought, you don't intend
to do the preview, right?
What are you saying, Hayashida?
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Dejiko (Di Gi Charat)
[Voice: Asami Sanada]
Dejiko has come to
Cromartie High School, nyo.
Dejiko...