Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Maeda's house
Happy birthday scumbag
Happy birthday to you, man
Happy birthday dear Maeda
Happy Birthday
Happy birthday to you
All right! I'm gonna go crazy today!
Hold on a second, Hayashida.
It's nice to be casual,
but this is Maeda's house,
so we'd better restrain ourselves.
No, that's okay, Kamiyama.
What?
Because you all got together for me today, right?
You're really a nice guy.
I'm glad that we're close friends.
That's my line.
I'm really feeling happy today.
These guys always gather at my house
for a "decide the strongest man meeting"
or unimportant events
I don't understand, without asking me.
It's really been a bother.
But they gathered today
to celebrate my birthday.
There's no reason for me to get upset.
Even if they go crazy today, I'll let it slide.
But there's just one thing
that I wanna say to you...
My birthday was last month.
Happy birthday!
But if I said something like that,
it would only ruin the atmosphere.
They just made a mistake.
I know for sure that
they didn't do it on purpose.
I'm totally changing the subject,
but I heard there's an idol's autograph session
at the bookstore near the station.
Why don't we finish up
Maeda's birthday early and head there?
Yeah, that's fine too.
So that's okay, right, Maeda?
Let me tell you something...
That's Maeda's old lady.
What are you guys saying?
Didn't you gather today
to celebrate my birthday?
Well, that's what I wanna say,
but technically it's not my birthday today.
I don't know what to say anymore.
Hayashida...
What are you doing, jerk?
This is the second time
I've hit someone in my entire life.
That shows how upset I am.
Even if it is among close friends,
there's things you can say and things you can't.
If you really cared about Maeda,
you wouldn't have said that.
Isn't that right, Hayashida?
That's enough, Kamiyama. I don't mind at all.
No, Kamiyama's right.
I got carried away and said a stupid thing.
Sometimes careless words hurt
other people's feelings, don't they?
Sorry, Maeda. Forgive me!
Stop it! This isn't like the Hayashida I know.
Okay, all settled then.
Now let's start again from the beginning.
Actually we have a present for you.
This is a specially made cake, Maeda.
You're the star today. Now blow out the candles.
Thanks, everyone.
Okay, I'll blow them out in one breath.
Happy Birthday
Maeda, happy birthday!
Well done!
Happy birthday, Maeda!
That's my old lady!
A few days later
There's someone that
I want to introduce to you.
What? Who is it?
This is my little brother, Beta Mechazawa.
Guts
Mecha-ratta.
Mechazawa's little brother, he said?
It's not good to bring your
little brother to school, is it?
No, I don't think that's
the surprising part, Hayashida.
I heard that he's really good at fighting,
despite his appearance.
I guess you could say he's resilient.
Just what you'd expect
from someone related to me by blood.
I see, I think I understand what you mean.
Shall we try having him fight
one-on-one with someone? Just kidding!
What?!
A few days later
Mechazawa's little brother finally got fixed.
Wow! They fixed him up real good!
The people at Sato Electronics
really are pretty skilled.
But isn't he smaller than before?
I think it's okay, don't you?
The newer the cell phones are,
the smaller they get too.
Speaking of which, what happened
to his older brother, Mechazawa?
Well, I heard that the incident
came as a huge shock to him,
so he ended up confining himself to his bed.
If anything, I'm kinda more worried about him.
Hey, I just thought of something.
If he's with us, we won't lose a fight
no matter how strong our enemy is.
How in the heck can we win fights using him?
Let me see him for a sec.
We can win fights like this, right?
If we're throwing something,
we can throw just rocks or balls!
And he's dented again.
Of course I'm against
using him as a fighting tool.
But if you're going to use him,
you have to fully use his abilities.
Exactly! Use your head more.
He's more or less intelligent.
And he can also walk
and his body is small.
That means there's only one way
we can use him, right?
What's that?
Spying.
Spying...
But far from picking up information as a spy,
there's a risk that he'll be picked up
by someone and taken home.
Don't worry about it.
I'll teach him about those kinds of things.
Education is important for anything.
If I teach him from the ground up,
within a month he'll...
Hokuto, eyes down.
What is it?
This isn't working at all!
Next day
Mechazawa's saying that since
he got better without a hitch,
he wants to come and get his little brother.
What're we gonna do?
The Sato Electronics person told me that fixing
his little brother would take until tomorrow.
Mechazawa loves his little brother.
I think he'll certainly get angry when he finds out
that his little brother got broken again.
I can just see his angry face.
Not that his expression changes much.
Hey, why do you always gather at my house?
I have a good idea.
Give me that tea caddy.
Here, done.
Well, to say the least, this isn't...
If we put it far away like this, he wouldn't know.
If we can weasel our way
through today, it'll be fine.
I wonder if this'll work.
Listen, don't ever talk about his little brother.
Even if he starts talking about his little brother,
do everything you can to avoid it!
Isn't that Mechazawa?
Sorry for being late.
We've been waiting for you. Have a seat.
Well, it's great to see you got better.
I'm really sorry that I worried you all.
By the way, where's my little brother Beta?
He's all right. He's sitting here just fine.
Well, forget about that and
make yourself at home.
You're a nice guy, Hayashida.
You seem rough, but you're
actually very considerate.
You're embarrassing me.
If you say that, well, I guess
I'll have to be considerate then.
I'll make some tea now, so...
Fury
What happened to my little brother?!
He's in the hospital right now.
At Sato Electronics Store...
How dare you mess with me,
switching him with a tea caddy?!
He isn't much different from a tea caddy, is he?
Hayashida, you're going too far.
You'd better stop making
a fool out of me, moron!
Your yapping is really annoying!
The data has just been formatted.
This'll do.
That's going too far, Hayashida!
Put him in the closet for the time being.
If my old lady finds out, I'll be scolded.
Next day
His little brother, Beta, was repaired safely.
I like him better, because
it's easy to deal with him.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Everyone's acting normal,
but to start with, what the hell
is this Mechazawa family?
Well, there's no use discussing this right now.
No, isn't now the time to discuss it?
His little brother's also in the picture now!
If we don't, it's gonna drag on like this.
Where's their house? Do they have parents?
Or more importantly, who created them?
There are lots of questions, aren't there?
Who created them? Hey, man...
Why doesn't anyone say it straight?
Because no matter how you look at them,
they're definitely robo...
Don't say any more!
What you are about to say is bashing Mechazawa.
Listen. We're badasses,
but we don't bash others.
Bear that in mind!
Okay. I won't talk about it any more.
Then let me say my name...
No, I don't wanna hear that either.
But the Mechazawa family's true identity
is something that weighs on my mind.
It's possible that he came
to our school with some sort of goal.
There's no way that such a small,
toy-like thing has a goal.
You're thinking too much.
But even for cell phones, the more
advanced they are, the smaller they get.
It's possible that even this thing
may have amazing capabilities.
What're you talking about?
Don't compare everything with cell phones.
It's a ring tone.
Is it really a cell phone?
More like, who's calling?
Anyhow, someone answer it.
You gotta be kidding.
That's creepy, I can't answer it!
Yes, hello?
K-Kamiyama...
Oh, yes... I see... Got it... Goodbye.
Who was it from?
Oh, it was a wrong number.
Hang up on those right away.
Hey, it's ringing again.
All right, then, I'll answer this time.
We're counting on you, Hayashida.
Yes, hello?
What?! Got it! We'll be right there!
Hey, who was that?
That was from Maeda!
It seems something's happened.
He asked us to come to his house.
It must be big if Maeda himself
asked us to come to his house.
What I wanna know is,
where was he calling from?
Maeda
I was just cleaning the closet, and...
It's gone.
He isn't here!
This is a mystery.
In addition, he disappeared
after such a short time.
Did he start walking by himself?
Could it be that he got
thrown out as oversized trash?
Anyway, calm down, everyone.
If we act rashly,
we'll make matters worse.
He's right. Let's calm down a bit.
Let's have some tea and think about it
calmly for the time being.
Oh, there's some iced tea in the fridge there.
Okay, the fridge there, right?
Hello. Please excuse us.
Excuse me. Can I have a glass of iced tea?
Hey, that's the one! That's it!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
This was supposed to be the time
to announce the next episode.
But I couldn't do such a thing.
Do it!
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Next episode, Jackson
It could've been my old lady's birthday.
If so, that's the right answer!