Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Physical
Exam
Site
Okay, everybody lined up here,
please take all your clothes off.
Geez, what a pain.
Fine, you want us to take
our clothes off, all right then!
Take them all off, huh?
Got them off!
Okay, then, those who took
their clothes off, please sit here.
First I'm going to use a stethoscope.
It'll be a little cold, but bear with it.
Hold on a second.
Why am I calmly using the stethoscope?
I heard rumors about Cromartie High School,
but this is even worse than what I've heard.
No matter what appears,
it shouldn't be surprising,
but why does it have to be
like this right from the start?
But I'm a veteran doctor.
No matter what shows up,
I should just perform my job.
But from an outside perspective,
this looks really stupid.
No, this isn't good.
Stop thinking such foolish things.
Focus on the medical exam.
Could you turn around
so I can see your back?
That IS my back.
I can't tell the difference
between his front and back.
Forget it. I'll pull myself together
and go to the next one.
What is this guy?
I wonder if speaking Japanese would work?
Could you look this way?
It seems that he understands the language.
Okay, there's nothing wrong.
You're in good health.
I'm almost there.
But I can't lower my guard yet.
I don't know what else might show up next.
What if a demon or a bear appears?
I could at least deal with it
if it were a gorilla or something.
Thank goodness that it's a gorilla!
Thank goodness...
Thank goodness it's a gorilla.
As I thought, a gorilla's good.
Well, thank goodness.
Right! A gorilla's the best.
Right, right...
Well, thank goodness it was a gorilla!
Of course NOT!
Doctor, please calm down!
A few days later
Oh? What's the matter, Mechazawa?
You look pale.
Well, I got the results from
the physical exam from the other day.
The doctor says, "Have a thorough
checkup at a different hospital."
I'm known as a calm man, but even I'm worried.
I'm so concerned.
I wonder if I tested positive for something?
Tested positive?
For what?
Well, I don't think you've got
a terrible disease or anything,
but, how do I put it...
Well, I don't think you should
worry about it too much.
Guts
That doctor gave me a reference
to a different hospital,
Guts
but would you come with me?
Well, if that's what you want.
Guts
We wouldn't be of much help, though.
Personal Computers
Audio
Camera
Personal Computers
Audio
Camera
Cheap
Dirt
Hiromoto
Home
Appliances
Going
out of
business
sale
Let's see... Let's see...
This is definitely the address, but...
Satou Electronics Store
Did I write down the wrong lot number?
No, I think this is probably the place.
Well, there are lots of doctors
who also own electronics stores.
What? Are there such doctors?
Well, in any case, why don't we go in?
We can talk after that.
Hello, welcome!
Excuse me... We brought him here
with his doctor's reference.
Oh, that. Yeah, I've heard all about it.
It looks like this is an older model,
but if we fix it good, you can still use it fine.
Well... that's...
Youngsters these days carelessly toss
things away once they get a little beat up.
Isn't it sad when the owners
don't care about their machines?
Machines have hearts too.
I understand that very well.
Then, do you have a warranty certificate?
A warranty certificate?
Don't you mean health insurance?
No, I don't think so.
Oh, you don't?
Then it might be better to
contact the manufacturer directly.
Hey, is this guy really a doctor?
He's starting to tick me off!
This doctor just talks rough, that's all.
People often say that the rougher a man talks,
the more skilled he is, right?
Well, just leave it to me!
I'll at least do the maintenance work for you.
Well, we'll wait for you outside, then.
Satou Electronics Store
Well, I'm glad that you feel
better now, Mechazawa.
We're relieved too.
Please input your name following
the voice instructions.
A password will be set up.
Please try to avoid using
personal information such as your birth date.
The data's gone!
Maeda's house
There was a birthday party
going on at Maeda's house.
Happy birthday, man.
Happy birthday,
man.
Happy birthday, dear Freddie...
So why are you doing it at my house?
You're such a cold person.
I worked hard getting ready for this, Maeda.
Do you really know when Freddie's birthday is?
Did you ask him?
No, since we don't know when it is,
we decided it's today on our own.
Happy birthday, you bastard.
Happy birthday,
scumbag.
Happy birthday, dear Takenouchi.
It's happy birthday, you!
My name is Yutaka Takenouchi.
Yutaka Takenouchi (16)
I may be repeating this too much,
but I'm the boss of Year 1
at Cromartie, and its strongest man.
I'm strong in fighting,
but I get motion sickness easily.
They told me that they'd
hold a birthday party for me,
so I made the mistake of coming without
thinking too much because I just felt happy.
But the one problem is...
Birthday Party Site
Here
It's being held on a houseboat!
There's trouble! Takenouchi fainted!
Here, tempura's done!
Tempura again?!
Now he's being violent!
Stop it, Freddie!
Takenouchi, he's not the boatman.
You can't hit him!
Killer Queen
The reason I asked you to gather here today
is solely because I would like it to be clear
about who among us is the strongest man.
The Mohawk occasionally has a good idea.
That's just what I wanted.
I'll accept a challenge from anyone, anytime!
I'm opposed to such violence.
We should discuss it peacefully.
Hold on a second.
What is it?
I totally understand the idea
of deciding who's the strongest man.
I understand that feeling very well.
But there's one thing that I wanna say.
Maeda's
house
You don't really have to do it
at my house, do you?!
Why do you always gotta be a party pooper?
We just replaced the tatami mat!
Don't gather at my house without permission!
Don't open the fridge without permission!
Don't eat a banana!
Don't meow!
It's your cat.
All right! To decide who's the strongest,
a one-on-one fight is the best, of course.
Sounds interesting!
I'll make them regret rushing
towards their death.
Then, the first fight will be Maeda vs Gorilla...
Forget that! Why do you just
decide without asking?
You're standing out big time today, aren't you?
Of course I am! This is my house!
Anyway, it's a bother, so there's no way
you're going on a rampage in here!
If you really want to do it,
go outside and do it there! I'm serious!
It's cold outside.
If you don't stop complaining, I'll call the police!
We have no choice.
Then let's decide who's
the strongest man through discussion.
What? Why?
Anyways, I want to go on a rampage here.
I'll really fudging kill you.
All right! I'll make it clear who's the
strongest man in the Hokuto Corps.
What?
Hokuto Corps?
What are you saying among all the confusion?
What? It's not?
Aren't you guys in the Hokuto Corps?
Well, in a way, Mr. Hokuto
is suitable as our leader.
In this world I think it's okay that the first one
to say it wins, regardless of actual ability.
No, that's not why I said Hokuto Corps...
Well, I don't know who's the strongest,
but it doesn't matter!
In any case, with all of these members
gathered here, we need fear nothing!
When you really think about it,
these are incredible members.
That's right! There's no doubt that we can defeat
any vicious enemy with these members!
That's true.
That means that we have
nothing in this world to fear!
That's my old lady.
She's really scary!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
There are many more people who
have not appeared yet,
but it doesn't mean anyone
will appear in the next episode.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Next episode,
rebooting
The initial setup
has been saved.
All right, this'll do.