Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Shore
Fish
This is Tokyo's kitchen,
Tsukiji Fish Market.
A place that provides food for 10 million people.
Gorilla's Sushi
-A Record of Success through Excellence-
Good Morning!
Hey!
Good morning!
I'm counting on your help again today!
You're working hard as usual.
Yeah. I'm what's called
"a poor man with no free time."
Hey, you're early again today.
Morning, Mr. Gori!
Look, Mr. Gori, I've got good fish in stock today.
Take a look at these.
These are shore fish, red snappers!
So how about it? Wanna buy some?
These are top quality goods.
What's the matter, Mr. Gori?
Darn! You've got a well-trained eye,
so you'll take the good ones again.
So be it.
Go ahead and take that with you.
How about this much?
What?!
Man! Got it. You can buy it for that price!
Hey, Mr. Gori.
Got a bargain again, huh?
Who's that?
Huh? Oh...
Currently showing "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
He's the young man who joined Sakura Sushi.
He's a reliable guy.
Although he has a careless side, he's honest by nature,
so I look forward to seeing how it turns out.
Gorilla Sushi
Hey, Gori, you're working hard.
That reminds me, the chief was saying
"I guess I'll try letting Gori make food for the employees for now."
Huh?
Oh?
What, you've already made a dish secretly?
It's stewed food? Then I'll try it
and see how it tastes.
Yes, this is good.
You did a good job bringing out
the taste of the leftovers.
The basics are the same for any kind of cooking.
A good chef can cook anything well.
In that sense, you may have a
natural sense of flavors.
Shut up!
Welcome
You got a problem, dumbass?!
No, like I said, the restaurant owner
isn't in right now, so...
So what?
All you gotta do is stamp
this paper with his seal!
Him again? He's an ill-natured landshark...
Hey! The restaurant owner is out.
Come back later!
What? I can't ask whether it's
convenient for you each time!
All things considered, you guys are strange,
clinging to a dying restaurant like this.
Well, either way, you guys aren't in
any position to give me orders.
After all, I'm the restaurant owner's...
Hold on, Gori!
Gori!
Chief!
That landshark is my son...
Gorilla's Sushi
-A Record of Success through Excellence-
Currently showing "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
I believe I told you not to come here anymore.
Hey, Dad...
You have no right to call me "Dad".
You just have to stamp this document.
Contract
It's that simple.
You'll be able to say good-bye to this red sushi
restaurant and you'll make some money too.
There's not gonna be any
better deal than this, right?
Are you still attached to the sushi restaurant?
Or is it humiliating to sign a contract
with me, your own son?
Chief!
This is the second time you hit me.
Only twice? I should have hit you more...
I still remember...
The first time you hit me was the
first time you sent me into the kitchen.
You lashed out at me, saying that my way of washing the cutting board was crude or something.
You hit me over a little thing like that...
I think it was around that time
that I started going astray...
Do you remember that?
You went astray on your own.
Don't blame it on others.
I put forth so much effort
to make you a successful sushi chef.
I hoped you would
take over this restaurant...
It is a child's duty to carry on
his parents' wishes...
What's wrong with that?!
Such a fool. Keep saying that
for the rest of your life.
I'll come again. See ya later.
Don't ever come back!
If you do, I'll throw some salt!
Chief!
Currently showing "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
Ouch...
Mecha-ratta, mecha-ratta.
That stupid old man!
You're the one... from earlier...
Are you new?
I guess I showed you an
embarrassing sight, huh?
Well, Dad and I have been
like that for a long time.
We haven't had a decent conversation in years.
When I was a child, I wanted to be a sailor,
but I was denied without
having a chance to explain.
He kept saying "you'll be a sushi chef."
He's such a stubborn father.
He doesn't listen to what I say at all.
Well, there's no way we can face
each other with open minds now.
Well, see you later.
Gorilla Sushi
Geez, that idiot...
Oh, it's you, Gori. What is it?
Huh?
What the hell are these?
Banana sushi!
Hey, Gori. Hold on a second.
It's true that different ingredients
are popular these days,
but come on, bananas are just going
too far. Don't you see that?
All right, if I eat them,
it'll make you happy, right?
Sushi like this will probably taste so bad
that I won't wanna eat it anyway.
I told you so. What kind of taste is this?
This tastes so bad that people can't eat it.
Listen carefully, okay?
I know you like bananas, but it doesn't mean
that bananas are good with any dish.
If a chef forces something on others just because he likes it, he's not a first-class chef!
That's a selfish ego...
Forcing what you like onto others...
That's the same as me forcing
my son to be a sushi chef.
Simply insisting on my opinions
without thinking about others' feelings.
In other words, this awful
banana sushi represents me?
Gori... You made these banana sushi
in order to teach me that?
Gorilla's Sushi
-A Record of Success through Excellence-
Currently showing "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
Dad... I really think I got my
stubbornness from you.
I used to rebel against your
stubbornness too, didn't I?
When I think about it,
I've become a stubborn dad like you were.
Oh? It's already this late.
Gorilla Sushi
Gorilla
I'd better get ready to open the restaurant...
Huh? Is someone there?
Wh-What are you doing?
I had a little time to spare.
Don't worry, I'm just kinda fooling around.
I just tried cutting and trimming a fish,
but it's pretty hard, it turns out.
I was impressed that you do
this kind of work every day...
I don't get it... What the heck's gotten into you?
To tell you the truth,
I got something like this...
Look.
That's...
banana sushi!
Oh, you've seen this before?
That Gori guy... he gave it to you too...
Oh, you too, Dad?
Humans are selfish beings.
They want to force what
they think is good onto others...
Are you talking about me?
Well, don't be so edgy. I'm like that too.
That's probably why Gori
gave this banana sushi to me too...
Like father, like son.
My stubbornness is just like yours.
What are you saying?
I won't tell you to become
a sushi chef anymore.
Go ahead and do as you like,
but don't keep your current job.
Oh, it's time. I gotta go.
Next time I cross this threshold,
I may have a buzz cut.
If that happens, help a guy out
and hire a kitchen helper.
See you.
Gorilla Sushi
So I owe everything to Gori, huh?
I'm glad that you two could reconcile.
Listen, I told you before that I planned
on opening a new restaurant, didn't I?
I'll leave this restaurant to you eventually,
but I'm thinking about
entrusting that new one to Gori...
What? To Gori?
Yeah. Let me hear what you think.
To tell you the truth...
I was thinking about the same thing.
I thought so.
There isn't any person with that much talent.
I feel that I can safely
entrust everything to him...
Can I say one thing?
What is it?
It's true that he's excellent.
He's got a sense for sushi too.
Although he has a slightly careless side to him,
he's a man with first-class quality.
But he's a gorilla...
Don't say that!
He's not a gorilla!
He's our family, no, more than that!
Do you judge him only by how he looks?!
I'm sorry.
Think how you'd feel in his place,
being called a gorilla!
Listen. I'll tell you one more time.
He's definitely not a gorilla!
Tuna
Yes, I understand.
Well, it's too late today.
I'll talk to him tomorrow.
Gorilla Sushi
Currently showing "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
Good morning!
Gorilla Sushi
Morning! You're early, as usual.
Hey, morning, everyone!
Good morning, Chief!
Today's another fine day.
Let's work hard all day!
Come to think of it, where'd Gori go?
Oh, if you're talking about that gorilla,
he got picked up by the public health center.
Bread
What?
Oh, is that right?
He really IS a gorilla!
Well, if you think like everyone else,
it's obvious this'd happen.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
We think, in this show, we'd like to portray
the dramas of everyday life from now on.
Actually, NOT. This episode
was a one-time thing.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
How many Cro-High students did you spot?
I was watching.
Yes, I was watching the whole time!
I was watching too!