Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
My name is motion sickness...
no, Yutaka Takenouchi.
Today we're taking a school trip to Kyushu.
Since I like looking at old temples and castles,
I've always wanted to
go to Kyushu, where Dazaifu is.
I've been training hard for this day.
I tried getting in a stopped car
and watching moving trains
at the bullet train platform.
Everything was perfect and
there wasn't even one oversight.
But I didn't even imagine
we'd be taking an airplane.
Hey, brother, isn't it too difficult for us
to do something like hijacking after all?
What's with you, all of a sudden?
I wasn't really worried because
it was a high school field trip,
but they all look like yakuza.
Certainly, it's almost making me
feel like we're the hostages.
Let's just quit now. We haven't done
anything yet, so we'll be fine.
What's with these guys?
Were they going to hijack
the plane that we were going to board?
That's a huge crime!
I can't let them do it, no matter what.
But if they actually commit the crime,
our school trip will probably be canceled.
Which means the plane may not take off.
That's actually fortunate for me.
No, that's not good! They may just go ahead
and decide not to hijack the plane.
So I can't act in a way that
may encourage them to hijack the plane.
Even if I'm a badass,
I'm not rotten enough to assist in a crime!
After all, as a citizen,
I should pray that they don't commit a crime.
Okay, then let's hijack the plane
after it takes off.
Hold on a second, morons!
Huh?
What do you mean "huh?", dumbass?!
From how your conversation was going,
you should've mended your ways and
decided not to hijack the plane, right?!
Sorry. To tell you the truth,
this is my first time getting on a plane,
so I panicked a little.
What? Same here. I certainly
understand your feelings.
Well, why don't you
calm down first and talk it over?
Yeah, but I'm no good when lots of people
are around, because I get nervous.
If it's possible, I'd like to have a meeting
where only a few people are around.
Okay! Everyone, go home, now!
What? Then what's gonna happen
to the school trip?
If you don't go home right away,
I'll fudging kill you!
Well, I feel better, since there are only
a few people around now.
You get timid in front of strangers, so...
I should've gone home too.
I feel reassured if I'm with you.
That's right! If we listen to
what he's saying, we're invincible.
Now I don't feel like canceling our plan at all!
Damn! It looks as if I've become their
accomplice somewhere along the way.
I told them to bring us two billion yen and fly the plane to the US.
They said okay.
Let's go, Brother!
No way! Hold on a second!
You skipped too much of the conversation!
I'm getting really sick.
Why in the hell am I on a plane to the US?!
Our boss looks somewhat blue.
I'm not your boss!
My name is Yutaka Takenouchi.
There's no one who's stronger at fighting
or more reliable than me.
I was the boss at a certain school.
But that story's in the past now.
The United States
of America
Nevada
Where the hell does this road go to?
And where am I?
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
The United States
of America
Nevada
Looks like I've come to the US.
Here I shall gain a strong body
that can ride any transportation with ease,
and go back to Japan.
Nevertheless, I imagine
they're all in an uproar in Japan.
Japan
I heard it was really awful,
having trouble with hijackers
instead of taking a school trip,
although I don't know many details,
since I wasn't there due to my cold.
Well, it was good that no one got hurt
and everyone was safe.
But don't you feel like we're
forgetting something?
Yeah, I know it sounds strange
for me to say this since I wasn't there,
but aren't you all forgetting something?
Oh, yeah!
We haven't gotten the money
for the school trip back yet!
That's it!
Nevada (8 pm)
I guess the whole school must be
talking about me now.
Nevada (8 pm)
I guess the whole school must be
talking about me now.
It's unusual for me to feel this lonely.
Come to think of it, I wonder if those hijackers
were able to escape okay?
Somehow, it was hard to dislike those guys.
How beautiful the stars are!
I wonder if my friends in Japan
are also watching the same stars?
Japan (1 pm)
By the way, there's a time difference
between Japan and the US,
so even if it's nighttime in the US,
it's daytime in Japan.
So when Americans are watching stars,
Japanese people are taking naps.
Japan (1 pm)
Why do you say stuff like that out of the blue?
And besides, everyone knows that.
In any case, I wanted to brag that
even I know about astronomy!
Forget that!
What's important right now is whether
we'll get a refund for the trip or not, right?!
But I only got half back for the cancellation,
because it was due to my cold.
You idiot! You canceled
because of your own problem.
Even if it's just half, be thankful!
But in our case, they cancelled it!
It's only right to give us the entire amount back!
Instead of "they," it was
because of hijackers, though...
Hey, can I say something?
I feel like we're forgetting
something more important.
Is there something that we're
forgetting, Takenouchi?
Take
Is there something that we're
forgetting, Takenouchi?
Take
No, it's business as usual.
I see.
Take
There's something that I really want to say,
but I wonder if it's okay to say it.
There's trouble!
Maeda got caught by Bass High again!
Give me a break! How many times
does he have to get caught?!
Shinjiro Hayashida
He hasn't been attracting any attention lately,
so he may be trying to get some
attention in his own way.
Well, in any case, we'd better rescue him soon.
That means a battle with Bass High, right?
But Bass guys are really tough,
so we should be well prepared.
They're picking a fight with Cro-High,
so they must have enough guys for this.
We haven't had a fight this big in a while.
Certainly, it may become
a very dangerous battle,
Main character Takashi Kamiyama
but there's nothing to worry about.
Take
Because we have Takenouchi!
Masked Takenouchi
(actually, it's the hijacker)
Oh, yeah!
We have Takenouchi!
We're counting on you, Takenouchi!
Take
This isn't good. I feel like the situation
has become irreversible.
I've been pretending to be a high school
student to avoid arrest,
but I didn't know, of all those people,
he was the toughest boss.
Anyway, I have to somehow
fast-talk my way out of this,
although I get terrified around strangers.
I'm looking forward to seeing how many
Takenouchi will fudgin' kill today.
Well, hold on a second.
Everyone, listen to me.
Take
Hey, we're already sixteen.
Age-wise we may still be children,
but wouldn't now be a good time
to become independent adults?
What're you talking about, all of a sudden?
You're too old to be fighting, right?
Why don't you become adults now?
Take
And what I'm afraid of the most is the police.
If I get caught by them because of
a stupid fight like this, it wouldn't be funny.
Of course, everyone is afraid of the police.
If you're afraid, you can't fight.
You really don't know anything, do you?
There's a big difference between you
getting caught and me getting caught!
Take
Well, I can't tell you the details,
but if I get caught now, I'll spend
at least twenty years in prison.
T-Twenty years?
Could it be that you have a serious
criminal record at the age of 16?
I knew you were different from us.
You're still young and have a future.
Take
I don't want you to spend
a worthless life like mine.
Takenouchi, you've changed so much.
Your way of thinking is like
someone in his thirties.
It's as if you're a different man.
Or more like, aren't you a different person?
Well, people have to change.
But if you take fighting away from us,
there's nothing left.
Take
When I was in a Mexican prison, long ago...
No way!
Seriously? When was that?
I was locked up in a small cell for days
and there was nothing to do.
Moreover, I was imprisoned
although I was innocent.
After twenty days or so,
I was already mentally distraught.
While in that state, I found a pair of puzzle rings
when I looked at one corner of the room.
I was so upset that I tried to
detach them with all my might.
But the more power I put into it,
the harder it got to detach them.
You don't need power to detach puzzle rings.
What you need is a little trick and a calm mind.
I realized it after struggling with
the puzzle rings for a few days.
And what happened?
I easily detached the puzzle rings that
I couldn't detach with all my might before.
The puzzle rings healed my dissolute mind.
A few days later, the trial was held,
and my innocence was validated.
These are the puzzle rings from back then.
Those are?
How about it? Try to detach them.
They don't move at all.
Let me do it.
I can't do it. They don't come off!
Okay, I'll try next.
Take
Your minds have grown wild like animals,
since all you guys do every day is fight.
And those puzzle rings can't be detached
unless you have a decent and calm human mind.
Take
Wow! They came off!
Oh? I didn't realize that there was someone
Take
who had a decent human mind
among such savage guys.
They came off!
Bass High School
Your friends never come to rescue you.
Is it possible that you don't have any friends?
Yeah, but even if I don't invite them,
they all always come to my house to hang out.
Maybe they're doing it to annoy me after all.
Akira Maeda
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
The cold season has arrived.
Please take good care of yourself and
sleep warm so that you won't get a cold.
Brush your teeth, okay?
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Cro-High hopes
to take off worldwide
Is the US a place that you can't
live without transportation?!