Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Dearest Mother,
I, Takako Kamiyama, was able to get enrolled
in Cromartie Girls High School.
Sudama!! Cromartie Girls High School
I do hope to get used to the school
as quickly as possible and lead a healthy academic life.
Takako Kamiyama (16)
However...
I'm surrounded by young ladies from good families
who are like princesses, and I'm at a loss.
Kamiyama
I've been called a princess
since I was in middle school.
Wow...
I've never dated a gentleman before.
What do you mean?
Gentlemen who are fond of me give up
before they confess their love for me and leave,
thinking "She's out of my league."
And the nickname I got was
"Miss Masako of Default Victories".
Masako of Default Victories (16)
I'll come out and say it,
you all are nothing compared to me.
Oh?
Akiko Maeda (16)
I'd take lessons from dawn to dusk every day.
Of course, I've never lost.
I can talk trash and lay down
a bitch slap at the same time...
I'm what you'd call an honest
to goodness princess.
I've even won five against one.
I don't quite get what you're saying, but what was your nickname?
What? Nickname?
My nickname was...
I never really had a nickname.
Then you're no good.
Like, too bad.
This isn't worth discussing.
What?
There's no point if you don't
have a nickname like
"Fireball Princess of Junior 2"
or "Monster Princess of Junior 3"!
That's right. If you're like
"Suzuki of Junior 4" or "Satoh,"
it doesn't give off the sense of
"Like, that's sooo cool!"
Bye bye.
Please try again next time.
Okay. Please accept my
challenge again next time.
There's no next time.
Aah! There's a gentleman here!
FANCY CLUB
In Takako Kamiyama's class,
they decided that they'd determine
who's the strongest princess.
To start with, I've picked up a couple of people
based on their history of being princesses.
It's these three.
Main character
Takashi Kamiyama
Please wait a minute.
Why have I been nominated?
You silly girl!
Step back now, or I'll, like, fudging kill you!
Shinjirobee Hayashida (16)
I'm the one who nominated Miss Kamiyama.
That is to say...
I want to see the devil that's in you!
I haven't the slightest what you mean.
So, how are we going to decide
who the strongest princess is?
It's got to be through jump-the-elastic!
You got that right!
It's got to be jump-the-elastic!
Setting aside the question of how it happened,
they determined that Takako Kamiyama
was the strongest princess.
Sorry. I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm Tatsuo.
Dearest Mother,
I'm at Year 1 Class 3 right now to see
Cromartie's incredible princess.
So the lady people are talking about is here...
There she is!
Freddie...
Welcome
to the Jungle
Monsters dwell in Cromartie...
Okay, then, let's go.
I'm scared...
One, two...
There, look!
Miss Kamiyama, I heard that there's this
other gorgeous princess in another class.
You've said the same thing each time,
you know that, Miss Hayashida?
Anyway, she's gorgeous!
I've never seen a princess like her!
There's trouble, Lady Mechazawa!
What seems to be the problem?
May I ask what you're rattled about?
Lady Mechazawa?!
What a sober voice...
What?!
You birdbrain!
How many times have I told you that you
should not do things that are bad for your health?!
Shinichihime Mechazawa (16)
Who'll care for your mother if you're not around?
It was my fault...
Lady Mechazawa is worried
about you more than anyone else!
Let us go now, Miss Hayashida.
Yes, let's return to our class now.
Toyoko Takenouchi (16)
My name is Toyoko Takenouchi.
I'm 16 years old.
I currently command the Year 1 at Cromartie
Girls High School as their princess boss.
I'm very susceptible to motion sickness.
Restroom
Ugh, I want to throw up.
I'm in here.
My name is Bushiko Hokuto. I'm 16 years old.
My father is the chairman of the Hokuto Group
Bushiko Hokuto (16)
and also chairs the board of directors
for Cromartie Girls High School.
People are pigs.
I'll hammer my ideals into the
heads of these incompetent pigs
and control them!
Hokuto's Lackey (16)
Listen carefully, everyone.
My father is the chair of this high school.
He can even expel you all!
Oh, this lady's saying strange things...
This is a municipal school, so there's no chair.
What?!
Oh, no, you really did it, didn't you?
Hokuto and her lackey,
who transferred to the wrong school,
remained at Cromartie Girls High School
and set off to the West with their friends
to become a princess who has no equal.
And, time passed...
Everyone, another transfer student has arrived!
Let's welcome her, everyone!
Mother...
"Sudama!! Cromartie Girls High School",
Rosy Cromartie Girls High School
End
we'd like to end it at this point for the day.
Coming up, please enjoy
"Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
This is Cromartie Municipal High School,
a delinquent school everyone fears as the worst,
the most terrible worst school in Tokyo.
In that den of iniquity,
there are Year 2 guys who are senior to
Year 1 Kamiyama and his friends.
And among those Year 2 guys,
there existed men who stood at the top of Year 2.
Tales of the The Four Lords of Cromartie
They are...
The Four Lords of Cromartie.
We're facing a big problem right now.
That is...
Tardy
We're the Four Lords, but there are five of us...
So, that being the case,
I think we'll take on an additional member.
Tales of the The Four Lords of Cromartie
End
Tardy
Hey, why?!
Hey, Maeda.
Have you ever thought about the future?
No, I haven't.
I thought it would be unwise not to
think about the future after all.
But, we're still in the 10th grade.
In any case, how far ahead
are you saying we should think about?
Getting employed, for starters.
I don't wanna be told such a thing
by someone with that hairstyle.
Year 2 Class 2
Yearbook
Soko Elementary School
Take a little look at this.
Huh? A yearbook?
I found it yesterday in the back of a closet.
It has my childhood dream written in it.
Would you read it?
Sure. Let me see...
"I'd like to be a frog when I grow up.
-Shinjiro Hayashida."
I guess you were a strange kid...
Well, I have no clue what that was all about now.
But one thing I can say for sure
is that I've always thought that
I didn't want to live an ordinary life.
I still want to carry out that belief from
here on, even after becoming a delinquent.
What are you talking about?
Oh, Kamiyama.
We were discussing the future...
I wasn't, though.
What about you?
Future...
I'm not thinking about the future.
It is all I can do to live through today.
That's a surprise.
I was thinking that you'd always be planning
your future since you're a down-to-earth person.
I got rid of such thoughts
when I entered this school.
I feel that I somehow was able to put various
things behind me after coming to this school.
To get right to the point,
I've become able to think
"I don't care" in a good way.
Take a little look outside the windows.
What?
I want you to be calm and think about it.
Don't you think you'd be several hundred times
more interested in their future than your own?
Certainly, I wonder where they'll get employed.
No, their employment
or things like that isn't the point.
Of course, I think everyone
has their own concerns.
But when you think about
a gorilla coming to school,
any concern should seem small!
It certainly does. It seems silly to
worry about things, doesn't it?
In short, everyone tends to
think about things selfishly.
However, the world is a big place.
In other words, our concerns are still small.
That's right.
But, Kamiyama...
What is it, Maeda?
It's natural to worry about the future
since we're at a stupid school like this.
Nothing'll come out of it even if we do graduate.
Of course I'd worry.
If that's the case, you should take a look out the window again.
Heave ho, heave ho, heave ho!
Heave ho
Why are they tossing him in the air? Are they celebrating something?
I don't know the reason.
But one thing I can say is that even those kind of
people don't worry even 1 mm about their future.
When we look at those guys acting like that,
our small concerns will be blown away, right?
Yeah. I learned a lesson.
No concerns hold up against them.
But...
You still have more to say?
Even if you say that's the case,
I still worry about the future...
You're a persistent worrier.
Are you really a delinquent?
Delinquents don't have a future in the first place.
You're becoming a cruel guy...
If you don't get it after all that explaining, I have no choice.
Take a look out the window again.
This'll make you feel better...
Fzzrk.
Zap zap.
Pop...
OH, NO!
Dear Mother,
we'll end Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
with this episode.
Thank you for watching for four years.
We've aired only a half-year!
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
We'll do it as many times as necessary!
It's fixed!
Please input your name after the voice instructions.
Man, what a pain!