Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
I'm bored...
Isn't there something interesting to talk about?
No, there isn't.
Hey, got a minute?
Huh? What's up?
To tell you the truth,
I'm thinking of leaving the Hokuto Corps.
What?!
I started getting fed up
with his not being dependable...
I figured nothing good would come
from being his subordinate any longer.
Hold on a second.
What is it, Hayashida?
If you stop being Hokuto's lackey,
what should we call you from now on?
Look, your name is "Hokuto's lackey," okay?
If you quit being Hokuto's lackey,
we won't know what to call you.
Well, like I was trying to say, my name is...
If he quits being "Hokuto's lackey,"
he'll just be "lackey."
Which means we'll start calling
him "lackey" from now on.
Naturally, that makes me feel awkward
because he's not really my own lackey.
Like I said...
This means you need to become
someone's lackey quickly, or...
That's enough!
Listen! My real name is...
You're such an unreasonable guy...
What did you say?!
I'll say it just one more time.
Your name is "Hokuto's lackey"!
Is that a final warning?
That name already stuck.
You have a real name and I know that much.
But a name like the one in the
family register doesn't matter!
Why doesn't it matter?!
Well, I'll simplify and explain it to you.
For example, suppose there's a person
whose name is "Shigeo Matsuzaki."
Shige
He was popular among his friends
and called not by his real name,
Shige
but by his nickname "Shige."
Hey, Shige! You got some time today?
Shige, did you do the homework?
Hey, Shige! Let's go eat.
Shige
Well, Shige's funny as usual.
Let's go hang out at Shige's house.
Shige
But if a transfer student
who doesn't know the situation
Shige
Transfer
student
Shige
Transfer
student
comes and calls Shige "Matsuzaki"...
Transfer
student
Shige
But if a transfer student who
doesn't know the situation
Transfer
student
what do you think will happen?
The whole school will be thrown into chaos.
Makes my hairs stand on end just imagining it.
Well, being thrown into chaos
is an exaggeration,
but it'll certainly spoil the mood.
In short, if you insist on giving us
your real name no matter what,
it'll spoil the mood for the whole school,
and you will be no more.
Then where can I vent this anger and sadness?
Don't be discouraged. I'll tell you a good story.
What?!
It's about an acquaintance
of mine from long ago.
He was called "Mr. Masao" and
he was respected by everyone.
Mr. Masao
Mr. Masao!
Good morning, Mr. Masao!
Hey!
Mr. Masao working
Mr. Masao's occupation was a carpenter.
But it definitely wasn't
something he was good at.
Still, though, everyone in town liked him.
Hey, Mr. Masao!
Hey!
Mr. Masao!
I was still a kid at the time
and used to admire him too.
Oh, I kinda understand what you mean.
It seems a guy who's called by his
first name, rather than his last,
is a popular guy who's respected
by everyone, doesn't it?
I guess it had been about three years
since I had come to know Mr. Masao...
I went to see a dentist with Mr. Masao.
Mr. Masao and I were waiting
to be called in the waiting room.
But the next moment
I heard astonishing words!
Mr. Kenji Masao, please come in
to the consultation room.
Okay.
What?!
Kenji Masao?!
Right... Masao wasn't his first name.
It was his last name!
Mecha-ratta mecha-ratta mecha-ratta mecha-ratta.
Does that mean...
Mr. Masao was someone who just
normally went by his last name?!
Yeah, that's right.
For a second, I felt like I was betrayed...
I hadn't noticed it for three long years, after all.
But when I think it over,
it doesn't matter if Mr. Masao is
his last name or his first name.
To me, Mr. Masao is Mr. Masao.
In short, I wanna tell you...
that's just the way it is.
I see.
I don't have a clue what he's trying to say!
The Ballad of Ishii
aa and Gotou
I'm still not convinced.
What? What are you talking about?
Oh! Could it be about that
names story from the other day?
How dare you all join in and neglect my name!
Who the hell is Mr. Masao?!
Hey, listen carefully! My name is...
Like I said, hold on a second.
Why do I have to hold on?
There's a guy whose name is
Ishii in Class 3, right?
Do you know his real name?
What?! Ishii's real name... isn't Ishii?
Actually, the real name of
Ishii in Class 3 is "Gotou."
That's news to me too.
Is that true?
Yeah, it's true.
But why is Gotou called Ishii?
I don't know the details, either,
but I heard that the real name Gotou at
Class 3 resembles Ishii in Class 5,
and that's why he's called "Ishii."
What? Hold on a second...
Ishii In Class 3
(real name:
aa Gotou)
Ishii In Class 5
Gotou and Ishii...
Those two don't look alike at all!
Well, I heard they act alike...
Even though people say they're alike...
Gotou has to be called Ishii because of that?
Isn't that how nicknames work?
Hey, I have one question.
Is Ishii in Class 5 called "Gotou?"
No, Ishii in Class 5 is "Ishii."
Isn't that unfair?
Why?
So anyway, that's just the way it is.
He up and ended the discussion.
Don't worry about it too much.
Yeah...
I still don't have a clue what he's trying to say!
You're saying you wanna leave my corps?
Yes. I have some thoughts of my own,
so I decided to leave the Hokuto Corps...
I see... That's all right.
"Those who come are welcome, those who leave are not regretted." Do what you wanna do.
You're not stopping him, Hokuto?
Since he says he wants to
leave, there's nothing I can do.
I see. I misjudged you, Hokuto!
What did you say?
I thought you were someone who had
a warm heart though you looked cold.
Stop it, Kamiyama!
Don't blame Mr. Hokuto!
It's me who's at fault!
What an immature thing to say... Nonsense...
I'm going home!
Wait, Hokuto! You shouldn't go home!
Can you go home and leave behind the one with whom you shared joys and sorrows up until now?
Hey, Hokuto, wait for me!
Get a move on! Come quickly!
Hokuto
Here, look, look!
I made a uniform for the Hokuto Corps!
You're a fool!
It's too embarrassing to
wear something like that!
I'm drowning!
Hold on! I'll save you!
Cry! Sob... Sob... Sob...
You fool. I told you not to swim in that river.
Sneeze!
Speaking of which, I remembered
our elementary school days...
There was that time you almost drowned in the
river and I became frantic and saved you...
Mr. Hokuto...
Huh?
We didn't come to know each other
until middle school...
Oh. That was Shimano...
Who's that?
Hey!
I heard that guys from Bass High
abducted one of our students!
What?!
Hold on a second, everyone.
What is it, Yocchan?
Why don't we send THOSE guys
once in a while?
We can't just let powerful guys
like them go to waste.
Yeah, they attract lots of attention,
but they don't actually do anything useful.
They sure don't...
You tell them.
What?!
Like I said, you go and tell them "go fight."
What?! I don't know how to say it,
but they look scary...
It's not because they look strong,
but they just look scary...
Geez, isn't there anyone who knows them?
Oh, yeah! Let's ask Kamiyama.
You called?
We want you to ask them to help us...
Hm. I'll at least ask them.
What are you doing?
Well, it's easier to communicate by drawing...
Hey, Freddie!
He says okay!
Really?
Now I tell you again: fighting
is not your purpose, okay?
Ultimately your purpose is to
rescue our classmate, okay?
Just in case, I'll at least draw a map.
I have a bad feeling about this...
Oh, that's the wrong way!
I still have a bad feeling...
Freddie, you got the wrong people!
Those are Yakuza people, Freddie!
This isn't good. Stop him quickly!
I explained this to you, remember?
Your enemies are wearing school uniforms!
He squatted in defiance...
You think maybe that he's sulking?
I guess we don't have a choice
but to lead him to the place.
Be sure to follow me, okay, Freddie?
Just like a kid...
1 hour later
Bass
High
School
We finally made it.
Oh, the fools from Cromartie are finally here?
We have a strong backer today.
You mean that old guy there is your backer?
Well, he probably looks just like some
regular old guy to small fry like you,
but he's different from ordinary
old guys you can find anywhere.
This guy is...
Hey, he IS an ordinary old guy!
Who is this old guy?
Oh? Where did I make a mistake?
And so... Freddie wasn't useful at all.
We should have asked this guy after all...
That's what I thought,
but let's not ask Gorilla after all.
Right.
How did this man stray in here?!
It seems he switched places
with Mr. Imai somehow.
I don't understand what you mean at all! Where's Imai?
Don't you get it?
The president of Sipin Trading Company says he
won't talk to anyone but the man in charge, Imai.
So if Imai isn't here, we're not
going to get anywhere!
What should I do?
He's already waiting in the other room!
If it's hopeless anyway, let's try staking our company's future on this person.
Entrust our company's future with him?!
As a first step, I'll put a tie on him.
Conference Room
So, we took a great deal of damage this time.
Do you have any explanation for that?
You didn't think up even one
excuse before coming here?
Are you going to just stay silent like that?
Oh, no... Just as I thought, it's not working...
Good! I like you!
Lots of people give stupid excuses
these days when they make mistakes.
To be honest, I was getting fed up with that.
Admitting his own fault
without making excuses...
I haven't seen an honest man
like him in a long time.
I think we can work with someone like him.
Does that mean that
the contract will stay like it has been?
Great
Ambition
But this man isn't Imai, is he?
Oh, so you figured it out?!
Don't stamp it!
Next
Episode
Cherry
Blossom
Dear Mother,
Cherry
Blossom
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
Cherry
Blossom
When you write the kanji "cherry blossom,"
Cherry
Blossom
do not use that slash on top of the right part.
Cherry
Blossom
By the way, in the old style kanji,
it has two "sea shell" characters
up on top of the right part.
Cherrie
Blossom
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
That's just the way it is.
This person isn't Imai, is he?
That's Hokuto's lackey!
Grr...