Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
This is Keough Pass in north Kanto,
a road where sharp curves
appear one after another,
looking as if it threads between the mountains.
Bikers who were fascinated by that pass
were competing with each other every day
because of their need for speed.
The legendary biker, Sadaharu.
The fastest man at Keough Pass.
Because of his genius-like riding technique,
no one has ever overtaken him.
Countless men have challenged him
and been eliminated.
And...
And these men are also about to challenge him.
We'll kick his ass today!
I wonder if Sadaharu will show up?
He'll definitely come!
He can smell competition, just like a wolf!
Can we really defeat him with our skills?
It'll be a piece of cake!
No one can keep up with us!
Yeah! We'll teach him that
he's a big fish in a small pond!
We'll teach him who's the fastest on the Pass.
Is that Sadaharu?
That's reckless!
If he keeps up like that, he'll crash!
I can't believe it!
He turned that sharp corner
at such a high speed!
Is he a monster?!
Dammit!
Our exit recovery is nothing compared to his!
It's no good! I'm pushing it to the limit,
but I still can't catch up with him!
We can't compete against him!
We've completely lost sight of him.
So that's the legendary biker...
My name is Sadaharu.
How long has it been since I met someone
who could keep up with my speed?
Hey, did you hear?
I heard that the legendary biker retired.
What?! Why?!
Let's do our best!
Cromartie High School
Track and Field Competition
Runners, get ready!
The first event - 100m race
I've been a badass since I was a kid,
Akira Maeda (16)
but the one thing I was proud of
was being a fast runner.
I haven't been able to attract
much attention since I entered Cromartie,
but finally my day in the spotlight has come.
I won't be beaten when it comes to running.
Absolutely no one will beat me. No one!
That's how I was thinking
up until a moment ago.
That's foul play!
Ready...
Cromartie High School PTA
The winner is Mechazawa!
A couple of people were taken
to the nurse's office.
Of course!
That's a motorcycle! Someone stop that thing!
That certainly is a motorcycle,
but it used to be our friend,
who wore a school uniform and was
taking classes with us up until recently,
so I'd feel reluctant to bluntly say
"You're a motorcycle, aren't you," you know?
Well, let's say I concede the point
that it's okay if it's a motorcycle,
but even if it becomes a rice cooker next,
can you still say that that thing is our friend?!
Well, don't be so edgy.
The next event should be okay.
The next event is the high jump.
High jump...
If it's just running, he has no equal.
But if it's the high jump, he'll be quite helpless.
Anyone has strengths and weaknesses.
You were too naïve, Mechazawa.
It was your own fault for
getting too carried away.
If you can, just go ahead and jump!
He's flying!
He's gone...
Jaka jan, Cromartie.
I'm saying, show us all the money you have!
Are you listening, moron?!
You have change, right?!
Go ahead and jump! Jump!
If you jump, it'll jingle, right?!
What the hell are you doing, trying to get help?!
Don't mess with me! No one's gonna help you!
It's our turf around here.
If you don't wanna get hurt,
show us your money now!
Hey, hey.
Stop bullying the weak.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
You wanna mess with us, dumbass?!
Fine! Since you're here, you jump too, then!
Okay.
Landed.
This guy's dangerous!
Let's get out of here!
Thank you very much.
I don't know how I can thank you.
No problem. I only did what was right.
Or rather, I didn't do anything.
Oh? You're errand-boy Tanaka?
Looks like the police have finally arrived.
I launched missiles last time,
so they mistook me for a dangerous person and I got arrested.
It took a lot of work to get released,
so I made sure it doesn't happen again.
This vehicle meets safety standards
I'm not carrying any dangerous materials today.
I'm wearing my helmet properly.
The air pressure is perfect too.
I'm properly observing the speed limit!
I'm not doing anything that
violates the law, police officers!
All Season
Road Safety
Campaign
in Effect
Come to think of it,
I didn't have a motorcycle license.
Now, let's do our best
practicing baseball again today!
Somehow, although it's happening little by little,
I feel we're getting close to Koshien.
Really? It's not easy for me to say this,
but I think it's your imagination.
Hey! Don't just hang around
all day, you morons!
Hakkou Group - Rainbakku
Hey, hey, hey, is this really the Cromartie
that's supposed to be so terrible?!
Shoot! So these guys are
the motorcycle gang Rainbakku who's been
invading this neighborhood recently?
So they finally came to our school too?
What's the matter, everyone?
Kamiyama!
There's no way we can
practice baseball like this!
The old me would've depended on the police,
but now I'm not afraid or anything.
What?
Frankly, compared to Mechazawa,
they're nothing,
because, after all, he can even fly.
Oh, yeah!
We do have a special trump card at our school!
He's parked behind the school.
Okay! I'll come with you.
You stay here, Maeda, for the time being.
Hold on a second!
It's been stolen!
Into the sky of hope
You put all your strength and fighting spirit
Can you do it? I can do it!
Your heart is always
geared up for a critical battle
You're world-famous brave men
Even if life's easy here, you call it Cro, Cro
Ah, Cromartie is our alma mater
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
It's time for Takashi Kamiyama's
one point living course.
"Sakigake" can be taken care of with just
one character if written as kanji,
while it requires four letters if written in hiragana.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Mechazawa, protect world peace!
Go, Mechazawa Wing!
Mechazawa Wing?