Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Shooting   Star   Press
"Let me say my name!"
Hokuto's lackey's cry
has not reached anyone as of yet.
Certainly, a meteorite falling on
the school building is a big event.
But I just need five seconds.
I want everyone to memorize my name.
My name is...
There's trouble! Aliens came out of it!
They're coming down this way.
Aliens...
How do you do, everyone.
We're aliens. Nice to meet you.
Now we'll introduce ourselves.
He said they'd introduce themselves!
Wait, wait, wait!
Who are you?
I'm a pitiful man who's lost the timing
to introduce himself for a variety of reasons.
Now I'll even settle for aliens!
Would you hear my name?!
Understood. I shall hear your name.
Thanks. I knew aliens were sensible.
Earthlings are hopeless.
Now, please introduce yourself
to your satisfaction.
Then I'll tell you, alien. My name is...
Captain, a ship has come for us.
Oh, it's already time to return.
Well, then, everyone. Goodbye!
What did they come here for?
I couldn't say my name...
Even to aliens...
Can I talk to you for a moment?
Listening to your conversation with the alien,
I reflected on my actions.
I'm ashamed of myself as an Earthling.
I'm really sorry.
I really want to hear your name.
Really?
Yeah. Isn't that right, everyone?!
There's trouble!
The aliens took Freddie by mistake!
My... My name is...
Moving right along, it's now the day
for the Japan Boss Championship.
Badasses from all over Japan
have gathered at Tokyo Dome.
Hey, look at that.
That's a rep from Hokkaido,
Bear Killer Kashiwabara!
I heard that he won a fight against a bear!
That one's a rep from Niigata,
Exterminator Takashiro!
They said that he can talk with bears!
That guy is a rep from Kochi,
Praise Heaper Okaji!
I heard that he raises a bear at home!
All right! Let's meet in the finals!
What? What did we talk about those guys for?
We will now start the Japan Boss Championship.
Then, here is the first question.
Milk is used to make yogurt. True or false?
That has nothing to do with being a boss!
Please proceed to the true or false marker
that matches your answer.
Now, here is the answer.
Please look at the electric bulletin board.
The answer is true.
The winner is Mr. Kamiyama
from Cromartie High School!
The winner shouldn't
be decided in the first round!
Destrade
High School
Hey, did you hear?
I heard that someone from Cromartie
has won the Japan Boss Championship!
Hold on a second!
We've never heard of such a tournament!
That's bull! We can't allow
them to decide Japan's No. 1 Boss
without our, Des-High's, knowledge!
Well, hold on a second.
Yamaguchi!
Noboru Yamaguchi (16)
Basically, all that's needed is for me to knock down the guy
who won the tournament, right?
Then, shall we go?
Oh! Yamaguchi has finally gotten off his ass!
Hey! We're coming in!
You guys are from Destrade High School!
You got some nerve coming to Cro-High!
I heard that Japan's No. 1 Boss is here.
Our boss, Yamaguchi, wants to fight with him!
I'm Yamaguchi. Where's the one
people call the strongest boss?
That's him.
Takashi Kamiyama (16) No. 1 Boss in Japan
(Pen Name - Honey Boy)
That's me.
Honey!
Hold on a second. Why is such
a puny guy the toughest boss?
That's what I wanna know!
I suppose you have various complaints,
but I'm the champion.
What's the matter, Yamaguchi?
I see, that's what it was!
In short, the Boss Championship was actually
a tournament to select the best comedian.
Japan Comedian Championship
In short, the Boss Championship was actually
a tournament to select the best comedian.
And this genius postcard artisan
became the champion.
If that's the case, I can understand.
Then I definitely can't back out of this fight!
All right! Why don't we start the fight!
Are you insane?
Are you seriously going to fight
with a guy like this?
I understand. I'll accept your challenge!
Then, let's start!
Please press the button quickly
when you know the answer.
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
A quiz?!
I thought we came here to fight,
but by the time we realized it,
we were forced into this quiz game.
Just as you'd expect from Honey Boy.
What a funny turn of events.
Moreover, while saying stuff like that,
I noticed myself wearing a contestant's silk hat
and I'm so funny that
I want to poke fun at myself.
Oh well, I'll give in and say
it's okay to play the quiz match, but...
Why are you the MC
when we came to fight against you?!
Here's the first question!
Ignoring the stupid question
that won't go anywhere...
Just as you'd expect from Honey.
Not only does he know how to make people
laugh, but he also knows how to run the event.
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
After the latest member change of the popular group Morning Musume, which phase are they in now?
Sixth phase!
That's correct!
All right!
Idiot! In the comedy world,
correct answers are worthless!
How much you make people
laugh is the important point.
In short, to us,
"a laugh is the correct answer."
These words might be remembered by
later generations if I become famous.
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Then, here's the second question:
1.41421356 is the square root of 2.
Then what is 1.7320508?
Yes, Mr. Hayashida!
I don't know!
That's it! That's what
the viewers are looking for!
I almost made a snappy comeback saying,
"Don't press the button if you don't know!"
That was close.
If I make a comeback, his joke will stick out.
If that happens, I'm getting
the short end of the stick!
Smart stupidity that almost
made me make a comeback.
This mohawk guy is no ordinary man.
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Then here's the third question.
How many total prefectures are there in Japan?
Yes, Mr. Hayashida!
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Question
Collection
I just got the answer to the earlier question.
Can I answer to that?
No, you can't.
He's prolonging the earlier stupidity well!
Does that mean that the earlier stuff was
a precursor, and well-calculated stupidity?
Then, here's the last question.
By the way, answering the last question correctly earns you three million points!
Then what were those questions up to now?
I see... It's a little ordinary,
but a standard theory
in comedy quiz shows. Good job, Honey.
Crossing America
Boss Quiz
Please listen carefully.
About thirty years ago, in Japan...
It's up to my comical answer now, after all,
in order to liven up the end and finish this.
What should I do? If I have to choose
one out of three, I'll say number four...
But no, that's mediocre.
Then I can answer before the question...
But it won't work if no one
makes a snappy comeback saying
"the question wasn't given yet!"
In short, a dumb answer that doesn't need
a snappy comeback is the only way to go.
Moreover, I'll have to lower my joke level
to match this low-level audience,
which leaves me no choice!
Yes, Mr. Yamaguchi!
Gachoooon!
That's correct!
What?! No way!
Yamaguchi gets three million points!!
What have I done?
Southern
Wind
What do you want,
calling me out to a place like this?
Actually, there's something that
I want to talk to you about.
What? Are you worried about something?
Well, I'm having a hard time saying it.
Just say it. While I may look like this,
I'm actually tight-lipped.
Oh, I see. Well, in your case,
rather than being tight-lipped,
I also figure that you'll forget it by tomorrow.
To tell you the truth, I'm very
susceptible to motion sickness.
What? Motion sickness?
I, Takenouchi, am this big, but I'm not good
with transportation because I get sick.
Well, that's it.
What's motion sickness?
What?! You're asking what it is?
You're kidding, right?
I mean, you don't know
what motion sickness is?
I don't understand the feeling of getting sick
when you're riding in something at all.
Is it a disease?
Well, it's not really a disease, but...
That's why you're so fat.
You really don't understand, do you?
In any case, it wouldn't look good
if Takenouchi, a boss at Cro-High,
gets motion sickness, would it?!
I wanna conquer that problem
before people find out about it, but...
Isn't that a rigid way of thinking
about the problem?
You don't wanna be seen looking so pitiful,
since you're the boss.
Aren't those psychological burdens
giving you pressure
and causing you to feel sick or something?
You suddenly said
something decent, didn't you?
You could get sick due to the load on your mind.
But after talking to me like this,
don't you feel a little better?
Yeah... Come to think of it,
I'm starting to feel much better.
After all, it's not good to have a secret.
It's best to talk about it with someone.
To be honest, I had something
that I was worried about,
but while listening to your story, I started
thinking that it was silly to worry about it.
Really? I didn't think that even you'd have
something that you were worried about.
Say it. I won't tell anyone.
Well, I'm relieved to hear that. Then I'll tell you.
To be honest, I'm wearing a wig.
Well, compared to your concern,
mine may not be that much of a big deal.
No, I don't care about my concern any more!
To tell you the truth, my parents are very strict.
All my brothers are elites.
I guess it's a reaction to that.
When I noticed, I was in the world of badasses.
But I'm afraid of my parents,
so I can't quite be decisive.
So I'm still keeping this hairstyle at home.
No matter how bad you are,
you absolutely must obey your parents.
But if you wore a suit,
you'd look just like a businessman.
Actually, I've seen you in town a couple of times when I was looking like this,
though you probably didn't realize it.
Oh, Kamiyama!
This isn't good! You'd better
put your wig on quickly!
I dropped my wig!
What are you doing? Quick!
Forget it! I'll get it for you!
All right!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
It's time for Takashi Kamiyama's
same old familiar one point living course.
For the Electric Mandolin's year of manufacture,
specs are more important
than the serial number.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Takenouchi is still in the US!
Oh? Freddie! You're back from outer space.