Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
I'm getting old...
Eyeglasses
Eyeglass Shop
There!
Yeah!
Hey, got a minute?
What? What is it?
I know what you're thinking.
But, it's not that funny.
Well, I'm not wearing these
to be funny or anything...
Hey, Kamiyama!
What is it, Hayashida?
Do you wanna go grab a bite on the way home?
No.
See you.
Hey, hold on a second.
Haven't you become cold these days?
Hold on a second.
Why do I have to be called cold
just because I declined a meal?
I'm simply not hungry, that's all.
No, I think you were kinder
and gentler when we first met.
That's right. You've changed recently.
Okay. Listen carefully.
Just because everyone has this
image of me as "gentle" or "quiet,"
just because I seemed a little cold,
people look at me as a "very cold guy."
Things like that happen all the time, right?
I see. I guess that might be true.
On the other hand,
just because someone who's very bad,
like Hayashida, seems a little kind,
people will think
"Oh, Hayashida is actually a very nice guy"
or "He was actually a kind person."
People have illusions like that all the time.
I think that's probably also why I seemed cold.
I see.
For example,
suppose I put my legs up on the desk like this.
And you put your legs up
the same way, Hayashida.
Like this?
How does this look, everyone?
We're doing the same thing,
but for some reason,
only I appear to be a very bad guy.
Oh! That's true!
Only Kamiyama appears to be
a bad guy for some reason!
While Hayashida just looks like
he's relaxing comfortably!
Psychology
This time,
suppose the two of us are reading, like this.
Doesn't it look, for some reason,
like Hayashida's trying very hard to
read a book he doesn't understand?
I see...
Kamiyama looks like
he's just reading it to pass time.
In summary, a person's everyday image
influences the judgment of others quite a bit.
I see.
Moreover, the more a person's actions
differ from the everyday image,
the stronger the impression becomes.
Taking this into account,
let's move on to the next experiment.
What experiment?
I'll fudging kill you, you morons!
Whoa! Scary!
Very scary, Kamiyama!
You looked so scary that I almost
offered you my money!
That's going a bit too far.
How's that?
If a person who is always angry
becomes angry, it's not that scary.
But if someone who usually doesn't get angry
loses it once in a while, it's very scary, isn't it?
Incredible! This is an incredible discovery!
Still, this is just the beginning.
This is the most basic of basics.
What?! Are you saying that
this is just the beginning?
What the hell's gonna happen?!
Psychology
The reason why Hayashida
looked like he was "trying very hard"
was because he's a stranger to books.
Due to that, it was more effective.
Psychology
But, then, what happens if it's someone
who's even more of a stranger to books?
And so...
Enter Gorilla.
This time, we'll have Hayashida and Gorilla
sit next to each other and read.
Now which one looks like he's trying harder?
What?! This time Gorilla's the one
that looks like he's trying harder!
See?
Or rather, hasn't this conversation
taken a strange turn?
I-Incredible...
Hayashida looked like he was trying hard earlier,
but he looks like he's well-read this time!
If it's this effective,
we may be able to apply it to other things.
Good point. Then let's move onto the next step.
There's more?
First, have Gorilla hold a banana as usual.
That's normal.
That's a familiar sight.
That's normal, isn't it?
Then shall I switch the banana with a mike?
Now from your viewpoint, who looks like
he has better singing ability, me or Gorilla?
Gorilla looks like a better singer!
Incredible! It's like he sings with vibrato!
It's just like magic...
This is without doubt a technique that cleverly
takes advantage of the depths of the psyche...
Then, this is the last step.
It's a test to check human judgment.
What? Are you going to do more?
I'll go ahead and wear a sash across my chest.
And l'll put another sash on Gorilla, as well.
And each of us hold a mike.
And?
Now...
Your vote
will change politics
-Takashi Kamiyama
Please give me
your vote!!
-Gorilla
Which one will you vote for?
We'll vote for Gorilla!
No, we won't, we won't.
Ballot
Box
For one thing, you guys don't have voting rights.
So, as you can see,
it's not that I've become cold.
No, you've definitely changed.
That's right. You used to be more polite
or maybe I should say quiet.
Geez, you still don't understand after
I went through all that explanation?
All right, then. That's enough!
Indeed, I might have changed.
But you can't say that "changing"
is a bad thing with absolute certainty.
Rather, without change there is no progress!
Yeah, I know that.
But not changing has its merits too.
How should I say it,
with some things,
it's a relief if they don't change...
There are, right?
Oh, of course, I do also see
the merits of not changing.
The disposition of refusing to change.
Such a policy is also wonderful in a sense.
It' like a "how long do you plan on using that material?" question for once-famous comedians.
Just to be clear, I definitely
don't mean to make fun of them.
In short, I respect both ways.
It doesn't mean either attitude is bad.
Hmm, that's kind of a pain.
For example, a high school girl who used to be very serious can suddenly dye her hair after summer vacation ends.
Yeah, that happens sometimes.
And it makes a big shock
for a lot of the male students.
And they start whispering and gossiping
amongst each other and stuff.
Like "she did something with such and such a person." That's not good, you know!
Well, then should we ignore it?
Then she'd feel lonely, being treated as an outsider.
I'm sure planning such a big change in image means that she has some level of assertiveness and preparedness.
Challenger
In a sense she's a challenger!
I'd like to cheer on such a challenger
from the bottom of my heart!
It certainly takes a lot of guts
to change your image!
All right! Why don't we
support someone like that too?!
YEAH!
It's very hard to go in there now...
The Year 1 Boss at Destrade High School,
Destrade High School Year 1 Boss
Noboru Yamaguchi (Pen Name - Ajishio Taro)
Noboru Yamaguchi, also known
by his pen name Ajishio Taro,
was a little upbeat because the postcard
he sent in was read in a radio show.
I'm hungry, Yamaguchi, aren't you?
Destrade High School Year 1
Jun Ishikawa
Shall we go out for some food? I'll treat you.
What? Are you serious, Yamaguchi?
Yeah, don't be modest.
I'll treat you to sushi or whatever you like.
Yamaguchi also got some prize money
because his postcard was read.
Then let's go for sushi.
You don't pull any punches, do you?
Sushi
I haven't had sushi in a long time.
Well, eat as much as you like.
Sushi
What? Did something happen?
Well... I just wondered if this
is really a sushi restaurant...
Hey, Yamaguchi, this is definitely a sushi restaurant. Look at the sign.
Well, it's 100% true the sign is
for a sushi restaurant, but...
Don't worry about it! Let's go in. I'm hungry.
Okay...
Hey, is this place open?
Isn't it possible that they're
getting ready to open?
Huh? What're you saying?
Oh, I got it. Suddenly you felt like treating me was a waste, right?
You can't back out now!
Hey, chief! Could you make me
whatever sushi you recommend?
Oh, gizzard shad? That's trendy!
Yeah, the fish is fresh and the
marinade is well done too.
There's nothing to complain about.
Hey, it's a gorilla!
Took you long enough to notice!
Wait a second.
That double take he just did...
He's pretty good!
Just what you'd expect from
one of my subordinates.
His sense of humor has improved!
I should recognize Ishikawa a little more...
You've improved!
What are you talking about?!
It's a gorilla! Let's get the hell out!
Listen, Ishikawa. Calm down
and think about it carefully.
"A gorilla at a sushi restaurant"... You don't encounter such an interesting situation very often!
Well, even if you say it's interesting...
Look. There are only about two restaurants
like this even if you look all over the world.
This is an incredible restaurant, right?
Well, that's true.
If the gorilla was just in here, it wouldn't be that big of a deal, but the gorilla is making sushi, so...
Well, if you're with me, you come
across interesting stuff like this.
After all, the god of comedy is with me...
In any case, why is there a gorilla making sushi?
Well, I know why.
What?! You do, Yamaguchi?
One day when there was snow and sleet, this gorilla was probably standing in front of the restaurant.
The restaurant owner,
who couldn't just stand by, let him in...
thinking that even for a gorilla,
it's hard to be out in this cold.
Why was a gorilla in front of the restaurant?
How should I know, idiot?! It doesn't matter.
Anyway, he let the gorilla stay inside
the restaurant, treating him like a pet.
Seeing him beside the chef
would be a peaceful sight.
But all that gorilla chow cost a pretty penny!
The owner had to work extra hard
and was struck down by an illness.
That's pretty dramatic...
"I wanna help the restaurant owner
who took good care of me somehow..."
The gorilla would think in his own way.
He tried watching and imitating
the other chefs, but he was just a gorilla.
There was no way he could make sushi properly.
But without showing
the slightest sign of those thoughts,
I'd imagine the owner would eat the gorilla's
poorly made sushi as if it was really good.
The restaurant owner would surely think...
"Why do they discriminate against gorillas?
What's wrong with a gorilla making sushi?"
I see...
Oh, look. That restaurant owner is finally here.
Oh, no! There's a gorilla in the restaurant!
He was here without permission?!
Of course he was...
Hanshin Koshien Baseball Stadium
Into the sky of hope
You put all your strength and fighting spirit
Can you do it? I can do it!
Your heart is always geared up
for a critical battle
You're world-famous brave men
Even if life's easy here, you call it Cro, Cro
Ah, Cromartie is our alma mater
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
When you have many things you have to do
and you might forget what they are,
you should write each of them down
on paper and put it on your desk.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
You shouldn't do uncalled-for things
Oh!
Please... Say something...