Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Cromartie Municipal High School (Co-Ed)
Shinjiro Hayashida (16)
So it goes something like that,
but do you know what song it is?
Well, not really.
I got it, Hayashida.
What? Really, Kamiyama?
What's the title of this song?
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Well, unfortunately I don't know the title either,
but I know that song.
That's no help then, is it?!
Then I'll hum it this time.
Something may come out.
Are you ready, Maeda? Listen carefully, okay?
What? Me?
Akira Maeda (16)
Okay...
Hold on a second. Sorry, but I feel
that it's different from my song.
What? Different?
The song I'm talking about goes...
...like that.
I see. Sorry about that. My song goes...
Hold on a second, then what's
the song that I just hummed?
Who cares?!
We won't get anywhere if
we're doing several songs!
Let's take care of Hayashida's song first.
Then I'll try humming it again.
Somehow I feel it's different
from the melody earlier.
Why don't you guys go to a CD store
or something and sing there?
The store clerks might know it.
Are you stupid?
It's too embarrassing to sing in a CD store!
That's right. It's true that we can sing here
because we know everyone.
I think you guys would be able to sing anywhere.
I wish I at least knew the lyrics.
Humming the melody isn't really...
You're really stupid, aren't you?!
If I knew the lyrics,
I wouldn't be doing things like this!
It seems that we can't get
any further on our own.
We don't have any other choice
but to ask others to help us too.
That's enough.
A song you unexpectedly heard
never leaves your head,
but you don't know the title of the song.
That kind of thing can happen to anyone.
It's annoying if the song comes
into your head right before you go to bed.
Yeah, that drives me nuts.
Okay, we'll help you too.
Thanks. Then I'll hum it this time.
I've heard of it, but I still
can't remember the title.
As I thought, it's different somehow.
It's just on the tip of my tongue, but...
Damn! I won't feel relieved either,
unless I remember the title.
I'll do whatever it takes to remember it!
All right, then! You guys go and ask others too!
Thanks, everyone.
It sounds like that.
Like that, right? I've heard of it. What was it?
Like that...
Yeah... What was that?
Right?
That's not it! We'll kill you, bastard!
Like that!
Yutaka Takenouchi (16)
By the way...
Was someone able
to remember the title of the song?
No, it's getting more confusing.
We don't know the title, but one thing I can say
is that everyone's singing has improved.
Wouldn't it be better if we sang in parts
of high tone and low tone?
No, that's not the point.
Dear Mother,
We didn't figure out the title of this song after all,
but I still have this mysterious
sense of accomplishment.
That's it! It's that song!
Mechazawa is humming it,
which means he knows this song.
Probably.
Mechazawa!
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Do you often hum that song?
Yeah, I like this song.
Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
Do you like this song too, Kamiyama?
Well, yeah.
Darn! I just carelessly answered
his question without thinking.
Now I can't ask "what's this song?"
anymore, can I?!
Even two hours later, we were still going at it.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
I have to talk about the next episode of
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
But... Let me see... We have another episode.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Later
The title of the humming
song:
"Ningen Nante"
Hayashida, what's the next episode about?
Don't ask me!