Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Finally coming to DVD!
Mechazawa, big news!
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
I heard that Cro-High's anime's going to be released on DVD!
I'm no good with machines.
Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
Well, of all people, I thought you'd know...
No good with machines!?
I said it's impossible!
I'm poor with machines.
DVD Vol. 1 Bonus
Masked Takenouchi's Mask
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
DVD Vol. 1 will be released on February 25th!
That can't be right!
Cro-High's DVD is really on sale!
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
I see...
But why do you all ask me
about fixing machines or DVDs?
That's because you're...
Kamiyama, do you lke Cro-High?
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
DVD Vol. 1 Now on Sale!
DVD Vol. 1 Bonus
Masked Takenouchi's Mask
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
The DVDs keep on coming!
Cromartie Municipial High School
Dear Mother,
Intense characters burst forth in Cromartie High School, a school for notorious badasses! An extremely popular anime with absurd and weak gags!
I have been able to get enrolled
in Cromartie High School.
However I am surrounded by
people of unfamiliar demeanor,
and I am at somewhat of a loss.
Cro-High's DVD is really on sale!
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
I see...
Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
But why do you all ask me
about fixing machines or DVDs?
That's because you're...
Kamiyama, do you like Cro-High?
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
DVD Now on Sale!
(5 Volume Series)
My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
There's something I need to promote
before my inevitable conquest of Japan.
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
Ending Theme "Trust Me" by Bikyoran.
Ending Theme
Trust Me
Performed by: Bikyoran
Now on sale.
My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
has finally been released as a drama CD.
It even includes that episode people said shouldn’t be adapted into an anime…
Drama Album
Special Edition
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
Will you buy it? Now on sale!
Original soundtrack by the legendary progressive rock band "Bikyoran"!!
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
Original soundtrack
Gulp... I want this!
If you buy the Mechazawa pepperbox now,
you'll get a game as a pre-order bonus.
It's the other way around!
"Funny man" and "straight man" game is in the works—Sakigake!! Cromartie Koukou.
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
"Don't Tell me... Are We in a Game?" edition.
By Hudson.
Have you already got that legendary pre-order bonus?
"Don't Tell me... Are We in a Game?" edition.
Now on sale
Yeah, the Mechazawa pepperbox? I was told that if I preorder the game, it will come with it.
I mean, I guess it doesn't make any sense to ask it now!
"Funny man" and "straight man" game is in the works—Sakigake!! Cromartie Koukou.
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School
"Don't Tell me... Are We in a Game?" edition.
Now on sale.
By Hudson.