Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
An autograph session for the popular
comedy show "Pootan" is being held today.
Pootan Autograph Session
Pootan, I'm happy that I'll be able to see you.
Gale Elementary School 5th Grade
Osamu Kido (10)
I've kept my eyes on Pootan since
three years ago, when he wasn't famous.
Since the content of the show
was a little surreal,
I was worried if it was going
to be popular among children,
but it seems like it took off successfully.
Though I believed that they would be a hit,
I'm overwhelmed with emotion by their success.
As a fan from when they were nobodies,
I'm happy to see that they're popular,
but I also feel lonely.
Pootan
Autobiography
And no matter how you look at these guys,
there's no way that they know
how funny Pootan really is.
I especially can't stand
that punk with the afro hairdo.
There's no way that he knows
anything about Pootan.
He makes me sick.
But still, I should feel genuinely happy
now that Pootan has become popular.
I'm happy for you, Pootan.
All I do is watch over you from the shadows.
That's enough for me.
Your face shows more confidence now, Pootan.
I don't see the inexperienced look
that you had when the show started.
I remember you were hesitant about your timing,
as you hadn't gotten the hang
of the character yet.
Okay, please stay in line, boys.
It'll be my turn soon. I'm a little nervous.
This is the first time that I'll see you in person.
How do you do, Pootan!
What? Somehow I feel something is different.
Well, they say that the actual looks
are different from TV images.
And I don't know much
about those things either, so...
Okay! One more time!
No, he looks totally different!
Besides, Pootan doesn't have
a mustache like that!
It's one thing to be a little different,
but being this different is going too far!
Pootan Autograph Session
In any case, why isn't anybody
making a big stink about it?
Oh, yeah, I see. Everyone is being
deceived by that plush costume.
Well, they're transient fans, after all.
As long as the person
is wearing that plush costume,
they believe that it's Pootan,
no matter who's wearing it.
Pootan's also busy, so I'm sure there's times
that he has to have a substitute.
It's a little annoying, but it'd be
childish of me to get upset here right now.
All right, then, I'll pretend that he's Pootan.
But he took off the costume!
Okay, I see! He's Pootan, right?
I'll acknowledge that he's Pootan!
Yeah, that's right. He's Pootan and no mistake!
No matter how you look, he's Pootan!
The person who's signing is Pootan.
The person who's shaking
hands with me is Pootan.
And this is Pootan's autograph,
that I've dreamed of!
And who the hell is he?!
OX Productions
The phones have been ringing
off the hook since this morning
with complaints about the autograph sessions!
What?
Oh, here too?
That's why I said that you shouldn't ask
a guy like that to be your substitute!
There's no point crying over spilled milk, right?
Besides, yesterday we had autograph sessions
at twenty locations nationwide!
But that's how it is when you're popular, isn't it?
And there's a child in front of the office,
and he's making a big stink saying that
he was deceived by a mustached guy
at yesterday's autograph session.
Okay, then, I guess I have no choice.
Fine, then. Bring him right away!
Pardon me.
There was a mustached guy
at yesterday's autograph session.
What was that about?
What are you talking about, poo?
You seem to be making
some complaints about a mustache,
but as you can see, it was me
who was at that site yesterday.
You see? I have the mustache too, poo.
But you don't usually
wear mustache on TV, so why suddenly...
It's a joke, poo.
A joke?
But I feel that joke isn't very funny.
Now, if you understand, then hurry home, poo.
Was that really okay? You were
dealing with an innocent child.
This is how the world of show business works.
Substitutes are everyday things.
I'm somewhat kinder than others.
I know that, but I don't think
it's nice to deceive children.
Guys who are amused
by watching TV are all stupid.
They aren't interested in the content.
They just like the mood.
So they'll think that it's Pootan if we have
someone wear this plush costume.
It doesn't matter who wears it.
Well, I guess that means the case is closed now.
Now it's time for another episode
of the popular show Pootan!
My show got hijacked.
The audience was really cracking up again
at today's stage performance.
Your new performance style
seems to be a hit with them.
Usually a performance style is hard
to change once it takes root,
but you changed it splendidly.
Well, your performance style changed,
or rather everything has changed, right?
You changed so much that it's like
you're a totally different person,
or rather you're a different person...
or what should I say?
You're a different person, aren't you?!
Same time...
This has become a real mess.
Pootan
in street clothes
Pootan - Popularity Rises
Highest Rating 80%
That mustached part-timer took my place.
Weekly TV
yen
Special Article
"Pootan"
New Series?!
Complete Check
My partner should have noticed the difference.
I have to get there quickly.
OX Productions
That mustached guy is a fake!
I'm the real Pootan!
Here, I'll make a snappy comeback,
so you'll have to do this.
They're rehearsing a joke!
Stop it! He's a fake!
What about it?
Good job. You can go home now.
We'll start at two tomorrow, so come here again.
Hey... What the hell is going on?
Enough with your bad jokes!
Since there's a new Pootan, I'll say this now.
I didn't like you that much.
Anyway, I'll be working with him.
Even if you accept such a thing,
the public won't accept it!
The public? The public has already
accepted him as Pootan.
He's got an even better reputation
than the previous one.
Isn't it the case that you think you're
more important than you really are?
Well, in short, it doesn't matter
who does Pootan.
What?!
His pay is cheaper than yours.
If his popularity remains the same,
the TV station will be happy to use him.
But he's quiet, as you can see.
No, he's more than just quiet.
He doesn't speak at all.
A surreal performance style
that tries to be different
will find some brief popularity
with the viewers, sure,
but it won't last long!
In the end, Pootan doesn't work without me!
If you're that confident,
why don't you go it alone?
What are you saying?!
Or are you saying that you can't do anything
without Pootan's name and plush costume?
You bastard! Don't get carried away!
You're an eyesore. Get lost!
Oh? What are you doing in here?
The show's already on!
The show?
But we're both here.
Now it's time for another episode
of the popular show Pootan!
What's with you, Freddie?!
What are you doing in a place like this?
We were both replaced.
Destrade High School Year 1 Boss
Noboru Yamaguchi (16)
That's...
Pootan's plush costume, isn't it?!
Why the hell is he in the middle of town?
Moreover, I've seen that
mustached face somewhere.
I've become a fan lately.
I went to his autograph session too.
Hey, you. Would you let me
feel that plush costume?
You bastard! Are you trying
to pick a fight with me?!
Poo.
It's Pootan!
Hey, if you think I'm just a funny youngster,
you're in for some pain.
Say something, moron!
It's good to feel this
kind of tension once in a while.
It's a big mistake to think
I'm always doing comedy.
Hey, look at that. That guy
is talking to a plush animal.
That's funny. Let's watch!
Oh, no!
Crap... I'm trying to be serious,
but I made people laugh.
It seems that I was born with comic talent.
Oh, there he is!
Freddie!
Geez, what are you doing, bothering everyone?
You should take off that
plush costume right away.
Hey, hold on a second. What's all this?
I'll explain.
Actually, for various reasons,
Various reasons = the story so far
I was hoping that Freddie'd return
at least the plush costume to me.
Now return it to me.
Does he still resist?
I think you're partially
responsible for what's happening.
What?
He's a pure man.
He probably got into Pootan's role
as a result of fulfilling his duty.
Didn't this happen because
you cut corners on your job
by using a substitute at the autograph session?
Indeed, you may be right, but
what more do you want me to do?
The answer is easy.
In the end, he's the fake one
and you're the real one.
If you show the difference clearly, he'll withdraw.
Please show something!
Are you telling me to do
a quick performance here?
You're a pro comedian, right?
There must be something you can do!
No, I don't have any
quick gags that I can do, so...
Don't lie!
Back when you debuted
and weren't yet popular,
you were doing quick gags, weren't you?
But they weren't popular at all.
Since you came up against the wall of comedy,
you switched to the plush animal
performance of Pootan and succeeded.
Do that one!
What? You remember that?
I've already forgotten that stuff.
Wasn't it like this?
Put your hand on your forehead and...
Please stop it. I'm embarrassed
just remembering it!
I see. You want to put that past behind you.
I understand that mentality very well.
If you're embarrassed about such a thing,
it's as if we can see your end as a comedian.
What did you say?
Look. You're at a crucial moment right now,
where the important position of Pootan
may be taken away from you.
I don't feel that you're fighting fiercely for it.
Why don't you try once with the mindset
you had when you started?
Having a mind that doesn't fear shame
should bring you one step up as a comedian.
I see.
I understand. I'll return to the past
and show that performance.
You'll really do it?
Yeah, leave it to me!
You guys, prepare to laugh. Here we go!
It's 37.5 degrees.
Oh, he's already taken it off!
I bet he got bored, since
we kept going on and on.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
There's no need to say this now, but I'm asking
you not to think this is the end of the show
and to watch till the ending title scene after this.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Pootan multiplying to critical acclaim!
Pootan is told that he looks
handsome from behind too, poo.