Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Talking Head
Des-High Year 1 Boss Noboru Yamaguchi
An excellent leader needs an excellent council.
And the fact that I didn't have a capable No. 2 until now
is also the reason our school has been stagnant.
It can also be said that it's because there was
no one who met my standards for the job.
But I finally found the man
who's suitable to be No. 2!
Since Yamaguchi accepted this guy,
that probably means he's no ordinary man.
What the hell is he like?
Well, don't get rattled.
He's actually here right now.
Come in!
Akira Nakao (16)
How do you do? I'm Akira Nakao.
Mick
I'm Mick. Nice to meet you all.
He's No. 2 from now on.
So, nice to meet you.
I'll knock you guys
down with a single blow.
Don't be rude.
Shut up, idiot.
Well, it'd be good if you
work on your timing a little.
Hey, hold on a second!
We didn't call a ventriloquist!
Ishikawa's jaw is dislocated.
Don't say something like "ventriloquist"!
Why you gotta say things
that destroy people's dreams, moron?!
For example, when Americans see magic,
they enjoy it purely as entertainment
even if they know it's a trick.
But when the Japanese see it,
they immediately try to uncover
the tricks and gimmicks.
You can say the same thing about pro wrestling.
Even if it's staged, have a mind that
enjoys it purely as entertainment!
Entertainment?
What do you want from us?
Hey, Yamaguchi, I don't
mean to tease or stir things up,
but can I ask you one question?
Yeah, go ahead.
Which one is No. 2?
I see! Even I hadn't thought of that!
Then I'll ask. Which one is No. 2?
You don't have to ask him, do you?
Mick, we've been together for a long time,
but it looks like only one of us
can become No. 2.
Shut it! Of course I'm No. 2!
You've gotten rude.
Then how about this?
One of you is "No." and the other is "2".
So put together you're No. 2.
Oh, I'll use that one.
The joke's a little old, though.
Then what about me?
You guys are a trio?!
Stay out of this!
This reminds me of Tokyo Comic Show.
Yamaguchi, can I talk to you?
It doesn't really matter,
but I imagine he's
powerful enough to be No. 2, right?
Otherwise, we won't accept it.
Looks like you don't know
his real power yet, do you?
He's not just a variety guy.
Show them what you can do!
Okay!
He took the puppets off.
Is he really no ordinary guy after all?!
Oh? My voice is...
Coming out...
Delayed?
How about that?! Just like
satellite coverage, right?! Well?!
I've seen this somewhere.
To say the least,
this doesn't help in fighting at all.
In any case, he's No. 2 from today.
Take his words as mine.
So which one is it?!
I'm so confused now!
What a pain in the ass!
It doesn't matter which, come and fight me!
This means...
He's No. 2.
Yeah, leave it to me!
Looks like he's serious.
Yutaka Takenouchi (16)
My name is Yutaka Takenouchi.
I'm very strong in fighting and I command Year 1 at Cromartie as their boss.
But my only weak point is that I get
carsickness easily, so I don't like vehicles!
Although I look like this,
I'm actually smart too.
In middle school my deviation value was
easily over 60, even when I didn't study.
The reason why someone like me entered into
a stupid school like Cromartie High School is
My home
Cromartie
High School
because Cromartie High School is
the closest school to my house.
This is very important to someone
who gets motion sickness.
But it takes at least fifteen minutes on foot to get
to school, even though I said it was the closest.
So I feel too lazy to keep doing it every day.
But then, I'd look funny riding wheels.
Wheels - a bicycle
At first, just watching the bus made me nervous,
but I think I can bear it if it's only two stops.
And that annoying guy isn't around here, so...
Oh? Takenouchi?
That annoying guy (16)
No way!
Y-You! Why are you on the bus?
Tell me the reason! What's the reason?!
Well, even if you ask me the reason...
Is your house far from school?!
Spit it out, bastard!
It takes ten minutes on foot
from my house to school,
and about three minutes if I use wheels.
That's closer than my house!
Why are you on the bus?
To tell you the truth, I...
love transportation!
The reason I asked you
to gather today is none other than
Destrade
Emergency
Board
Meeting
to talk about Des-High's course
of action in the future.
Lately at Des-High,
I hear many people saying
that we should be more
aggressive with other schools.
But this is a very important matter
and I can't decide it by myself.
So I'd like to do this democratically
and decide by majority vote.
Then I'll tell you my opinion.
I usually don't say serious things,
but I'll duly tell you my opinion here.
Right now, the situation is unstable
due to the big change
in the balance of power between schools.
I don't think it's a good idea to
be aggressive in that kind of time.
So I cast a vote for "against."
I see. I understand fully.
Well, any other opinions?
I'm for it.
Me too.
Okay, then, we're for it with two to one votes.
Hold on a second!
What? Do you have an objection?
No... Well...
Of course you're not gonna say something like
"this is ventriloquism
and one of them is a puppet," are you?
Then, if Toshiyuki Nishida is playing the role
of Genta Ikenaka when you're watching TV,
are you gonna shout and scream, saying "He's
not Genta Ikenaka, but Toshiyuki Nishida"?
Well, I wouldn't do such a thing,
although that's a confusing example.
I see you've grown. Then
what kind of objection is it?
Well...
Well, his hair style has been bugging me.
What?!
Come to think of it, it bothers me too.
What? You too?!
You should be completely open with each other.
That's what democratic debate is about.
That's just what I want.
I won't lose in a name-calling match.
What did you say?
It's getting exciting!
That's enough!
What's the matter, Ishikawa?
Join the debate too.
Shut up! I'm going home!
Dammit! He always favors that guy.
Whenever something happens,
I'm the only one that gets beaten up,
and I don't even know the reason.
Well, I have sort of noticed that Yamaguchi's
sense of humor and mine don't match, but...
I've been doing fine on my own,
but I guess even a delinquent may need a spirit
of cooperation to work well with others.
I wonder if ventriloquism
is the only way, after all?
What? You wanna do ventriloquism?!
Who're you?!
I'm Paul. I'll introduce my master to you.
Y-Your master?
How do you do? I'm Kamiyama.
I'm Paul. Nice to meet you.
Oh? My voice is...
Coming out delayed.
That technique?!
How are you able to do it?!
So it wasn't a technique that only he could do!
What the heck are you mumbling about?
Please! Please make me your pupil!
All right. Then let's go and
buy you one straightaway.
Buy what?
Next day
How do you do? I'm David.
He's my new partner.
He's looking forward to getting to know you.
Fighting's okay,
and feel the sorrow well... just kidding.
Now I think better of you, Ishikawa!
So you finally understand, Yamaguchi!
It was worth spending 150,000 yen.
Yeah, you win.
What I wanted was that spirit of yours!
This means that I have to rethink
the ranking of our group.
What? Then...
Listen carefully! I have
an announcement to make to you.
He is the new No. 2 from today.
Looking forward to getting to know you!
I have a feeling that we can get along.
How much does he think it cost?
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
I'm beginning to think that
I'd be better off if I say
"I'll tell you about the next episode."
Okay, I'll try my best to do it as I've been doing.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
It's a trio
even if there are four!
I'm Mick!
I'm Paul!
I'm David!
Four of us together
is a puppet trio!