Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
C'mon, Hokuto.
Eat a lot.
S-Stop it!
Stop it!
I-It was a dream.
Yes?
It seems you are awake, Young Master.
Oh, it's you, Jeeves.
I brought coffee for you.
It sounded like you were having a nightmare.
Really?
You were talking deliriously
and saying something like "meat, meat."
Shall we have grilled meat for today's dinner?
No, don't do that.
It looks like you're having various problems.
Various problems ← Please read the manga.
I think you should rest a little.
I guess I can't fool you.
I know everything about you, Young Master.
You've worked for my family
for a long time, so...
By the way, I see you every single day,
but there's something that
I just noticed for the first time.
Yes, what is it?
I've seen your face somewhere, but...
Cromartie High School
Hey, Hokuto, you wanted to ask me something?
Yeah, I have one thing that I wanna ask you.
What is it, all of a sudden?
Do you have a grandfather?
What? A grandfather?
Yeah, I do. But he's a very odd person.
For a long time, he kept starting
various businesses and failed each time.
I heard that, in the end, he started saying
that he wanted to own a coffee farm,
and left his family for Brazil.
We don't know where he's been since then.
I see.
I wonder where he is and what he's doing?
Do you still feel like you
wanna see him, even now?
Yeah, if it were possible.
The Hokuto House
You asked for me, Young Master?
Actually, there's someone I want you to meet.
What? Someone you want me to meet?!
Sorry to ask an abrupt question,
but don't you have a grandchild?
Hey, come on in!
You're...
You are...
Who are you?!
They were unrelated.
Start Me Up
Come to think of it, Mechazawa's
been bummed out these days.
I see. Well, every person's got
different worries, right?
You say every person, but...
Mecha-ratta, mecha-ratta,
mecha-ratta, mecha-ratta.
Hey, that's Mechazawa's little brother, Beta!
He's carrying something.
This is...
for Mechazawa
OS 5.02 for Mechazawa.
OS?
What's OS?
Well, how should I explain...
In short, it's an operating system for computers.
An operating system?
For example, suppose there is a person.
But if you don't educate this person,
he can't speak, nor work.
Similarly, computers
will refuse to run without an OS.
In short, an OS is something that provides
the computer's basic operating abilities.
That's quite a serious matter, isn't it?
Yes. Since it's a very serious matter,
I'd like you to listen carefully.
But it's about computers, right?
Mechazawa is different from computers, right?
Well, I don't know how to answer that,
so why don't we go see
Mechazawa for the time being?
Library
Goethe
It looks like he's agonizing about something.
It's just that, since he's the type whose
expression doesn't change with his emotions,
it's hard to tell.
Maybe it'd be better to upgrade this
OS thing to the latest one after all.
Hold on a second.
With computers, installing a newer OS
onto an old model can cause a malfunction.
Also, it's possible that you won't be able
to use your current printer any more.
That doesn't have anything
to do with Mechazawa, does it?
Even I could tell you that.
In any case, he'll be a new Mechazawa
who's different from before.
That's how upgrading is.
So there are various risks involved.
I see. Well, in any case,
why don't we ask Mechazawa?
Hey, Mechazawa, you look bummed out.
Yeah, I know.
To tell you the truth, I've fallen in love.
Love?! With who?!
But there's no way a lowlife badass
like me can pursue love.
But realizing that doesn't stop this heartache.
If I could, I'd like to have a fresh start
and become a new person.
That's what I've been thinking.
You wanna become a new person?!
I see. If that's the case, there's no problem.
Mechazawa, we'll help you.
Hold still for a bit. It'll only take a moment.
Is it gonna be all right?
It seems like it'll be all right somehow.
Warning
If you continue, all previous
data will be deleted.
Would you like to continue?
Yes
No
If you continue,
all previous data will be deleted?!
Hey, this isn't good!
It'd be better to stop for now and
read the manual one more time.
Continue.
He himself wants to have a fresh start.
So it'd be preferable if we delete
everything without leaving any trace.
That's cruel.
Please enter the serial number.
What's a serial number?
It's a password to prevent
illegal use of the software.
But I can't find the number.
It's not on the CD case.
For name brands, normally a sticker
can be found on the chassis, but...
Kamiyama, could this be it?
That must be it!
Now, all I have to do is to enter
the country name, region name,
department name, date and time.
Installation complete
Mechazawa responded!
Was the installation successful?
Good, it's successful!
Welcome to
Internet Shop
Welcome to Internet Shop
Welcome to
Internet Shop
It's successfully connected to the Internet.
Wow!
But that's not the point.
Sorry.
Oh? Maeda?
How long have you been here?
For a while.
My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
I'm the heir to the Hokuto Foundation
and the next leader of the Hokuto Group.
I'm the man who was born
and chosen to rule the masses.
What?! I've got the body of a seal!
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
Why the heck has something like this happened?
No, calm down! Think calmly.
Let me see, first, last night,
I ate dinner at home and watched TV.
Like it's possible to think calmly
in this kind of situation!
Hey, morning, Hokuto!
What?! That guy is me!
Okay, I get it.
That seal's body has been switched with mine.
How can this be?!
A supernatural phenomenon beyond
scientific explanation must have happened!
As a first step, I need to tell this fact to someone.
Shut up, you stupid seal!
I-It was a dream.
Are you awake, Young Master?
Oh, it's you, Jeeves.
You have a guest.
What? Who is it?
Well, I don't know, since
someone else greeted them.
Hokuto!
Something serious has happened!
What?!
You are...
You're...
It has been a while since I saw you last.
Oh, no, please pardon me for being a nuisance.
I'll ask you again. Are you two really unrelated?
Yes, we are completely unrelated.
We have no connection whatsoever.
By the way, what is this
serious thing you're talking about?
Well, you know...
I was so surprised, I forgot what it was.
What the heck?
Have you had breakfast, Mr. Hayashida?
If you would like, why not
have breakfast together?
Oh, that's good timing!
I'll accept your hospitality,
since I haven't eaten anything
since this morning.
Hey, it's morning right now!
Tasty!
You eat this luxuriously even in the morning?
Be quiet! Shut up and eat!
I'm so full!
Can I lay down on the couch a little bit?
So what's this serious thing?
Let's see... What was it?
What did you come here for, bastard?
Oh! I remember it now!
That's okay. It's not much
of a big deal anyway, right?
There's something attached to Mechazawa!
What?
To Be Continued
What happens next will be revealed
at the end of the show.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
Even though I'm speaking right now,
there seems to be something
floating around in front of my eyes.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
There's nothing more to be
continued in this episode
Free Gift
Let me see. Looks like a free gift
is attached to Mechazawa.
What?