Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Yutaka Takenouchi (16)
My name is Yutaka Takenouchi. I'm 16 years old.
I'm currently commanding
the Year 1 guys at Cromartie High School as their boss.
I'm Yutaka Takenouchi!
Restroom
Isn't it my turn to show up yet?
September
Year 1 students' monthly meeting
at Destrade Technical High School.
Defeat
Cromartie High School
The agenda is, "How can we crush
Cromartie High School?"
Noboru Yamaguchi.
Noboru Yamaguchi (16)
Due to his invincible strength,
he is called the "Silent Unsinkable Battleship"
and leads the Year 1 students at Destrade High.
At the same time, the motorcycle gang
named "Earth, Wind, Fire, and Water"
is also under this man's command.
However, not only is he strong in fighting,
he is also a man who, in fact,
is particular about comedy.
However, no one knows about this fact.
In other words, in fighting, if you
gain control of the head, you win.
Then that means all we need to do is put
the squeeze on Cromartie's Takenouchi?
That's right. That's exactly what I mean.
By the way, who's Takenouchi?
Idiot! Takenouchi is the head of Cro-High!
At least remember his name!
"By the way, who's Takenouchi?"
Sakamoto, you just told a funny joke!
But sadly, he hasn't noticed
his sense of humor himself.
Well, he's what they call a "space case."
But if you learn to do it on purpose,
you could be considered successful.
In comedy, that is.
The point is that since they're acting cocky,
they won't know who's boss
until we put a good squeeze on them once.
After all, whether it's fighting or a woman's
crotch, it's best to put a good squeeze on.
Hey, Ishikawa.
Don't make us laugh at a time like this.
Ishikawa...
What is it?
Ishikawa!
Hey, Ishikawa, are you all right? Snap out of it!
Don't tell stupid jokes!
That's what you get!
Yamaguchi hates comedy and jokes.
Wrong! There's no one
who loves comedy more than I do!
Why did I hit Ishikawa?
It's because he chose to tell
sex jokes without thinking.
This is the typical pattern that someone
with no sense of humor quickly falls into.
And for laughing, the rest of you are also guilty!
The most dangerous thing is
that this kind of guy sometimes debuts
professionally when he isn't good enough.
In a way, it leads to comedians
lowering their standards.
If, by some mistake,
he appears on a TV show,
I'll change the channel without hesitation.
Let's discuss things seriously now.
Yeah. First question is how to get
into Cromartie High School.
You say get in, but it wouldn't be that easy.
Guys at Cromartie are really crazy.
When push comes to shove, they kill without hesitation.
That Takenouchi guy in particular
can't be stopped once he snaps.
How can we get into Cromartie easily?
That's the question.
Geez, idiots!
Isn't there at least one person
who tries to make us laugh?
Read the mood in this room.
It's stupid how you keep saying "Cromartie,
Cromartie," as if that's the only word you know.
"Are you all villagers of
Cromartie Village?", I'd say.
What?
This joke is funny!
Yamaguchi is thinking deeply about something.
I wonder if Cromartie is
too big to deal with, as we feared?
I want to tell this joke to everyone so bad.
But if I did that, I'd plunge
from my current position.
Besides, I'm considered
to be a reserved person.
But this joke can only be used now.
It would be too late after we attack Cro-High.
Okay, I've decided!
I'll quit being the boss as of today.
The only reason I've been acting as the boss
was because I was good at fighting,
but that was a big mistake to begin with.
I can't make people laugh,
even with this hairstyle.
What I really want to do is tell lots of
funny jokes and make everyone bust out laughing!
All right then, I'll announce
this joke to everyone.
The only thing I can do after that is pray
that the God of Comedy blesses me.
Hey, hey!
How long are you going to keep
talking about meaningless stuff?!
I've been listening to what you're saying,
and the meeting hasn't progressed at all!
It's stupid how you keep saying "Cromartie,
Cromartie" as if that's the only word you know!
"Are you all villagers of Cromartie Village?"
Just kidding!
You see?! Yamaguchi really hates comedy!
Open
Southern
Wind
Radio Gaga
I heard that guys from
Cromartie come here often.
Let's catch them quickly
and put the squeeze on them.
Well, hold on a second.
It'd be dangerous, since
this place is in their territory.
Destrade High School has at last turned
their blade against Cromartie High School!
Let's hear Yamaguchi's, our leader's, idea first.
This is the very moment in which
their battle will begin.
Noboru Yamaguchi (16)
And Noboru Yamaguchi, leader
of Des-High Year 1, was thinking...
about how to change this
heavy mood to comedy.
Yamaguchi's coffee
I really don't have time for this stuff.
I have to go home soon and work on the postcards.
His secret hobby is
sending jokes in to radio shows.
At any rate, I'm a "postcard artisan"
who currently contributes
to seven late-night radio shows.
There are many listeners
who look forward to my jokes.
It's no exaggeration to say that those shows
don't start unless I write those postcards.
Last night, they even used five of my postcards.
Since it was five out of seven cards,
my batting average is so-so.
By the way, my pen name is
"Ajishio Taro," and I like it myself too.
But there is only one thing
that this "Ajishio Taro" doesn't like.
Yeah, it really pisses me off!
To hell with Cro-High!
We'll beat up Takenouchi good.
I wanna bust some heads soon.
Yamaguchi's getting furious!
I'm getting fired up too!
That there is another postcard
artisan who surpasses even me...
His name is "Honey Boy."
The next one is by pen name Mr. "Honey Boy."
His postcards always get read
at the most critical times.
Honey Boy, the only postcard artisan
whose sense of humor I acknowledge.
Anyways, unless I exceed him,
I can't sleep peacefully.
Yamaguchi is troubled by something.
He must be worried, since
we're going up against Cro-High.
While I'm sitting here doing nothing,
"Honey Boy" must be cranking out new jokes.
Actually, my hobby is sending
jokes in to late-night radio shows.
You're pretty dull.
You think so?
Are you possibly using
a pen name or something?
It can't be!
Yeah. I thought of it
by accident in the kitchen.
It's "Honey Boy."
Then what kind of jokes are you writing?
Well, in fact, I thought of
a pretty good joke this week.
He's "Honey Boy"!
And he's also gonna
announce a pretty good joke?!
What's the matter, Yamaguchi?
He's really concerned
about the guys behind him.
Those two... They're wearing
Cro-High's uniform...
What?!
Don't get excited. Sit down.
Hey, let me see it.
No way, it's embarrassing.
Don't tell me Yamaguchi is scared of them.
Who the hell are those two?
You screwed up, Honey Boy.
You don't even know Ajishio Taro is right here.
Quit acting so arrogant, tell it to me now!
This is a once in a lifetime chance!
If others hear it, I'll get embarrassed,
so I'll tell you in a whisper, okay?
Yamaguchi is sliding down little by little, I think.
What the hell is he doing?
I can't understand him at all.
So that's the joke.
I see! That kind of joke!
Okay, let's head back.
Even though we haven't fought yet?
More like, what did we come here for?
Honey Boy, you meet your end today.
I sent your joke in by express mail.
Hear it and be dumbfounded.
Next is our popular corner; "Puns by Postcard!"
Today's theme is
"something that happened at school."
We'll start with our regular, Mr. "Ajishio Taro."
He sent another one in.
Make us laugh again tonight!
But there's just one thing that I'm worried about.
Okay, here goes!
"I ate pork cutlet yesterday with a 'cut'
of the money that I extorted."
What a dud.
I knew it!
And he even delivered it by express mail?
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
I wanted to ask Maeda about "Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School's" next episode,
but it seems that he's not around today.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Wait for the
next episode
Is it my turn?!
Please calm down, Takenouchi.