Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Sentimental Bus
Cromartie High School's field trip.
A bus filled with hotheaded
badasses heads straight to Nikko.
In the back of that bus,
a man sits, holding his breath.
Yutaka Takenouchi (16)
Yutaka Takenouchi, 16 years old.
As the boss, I'm currently
commanding Cromartie's Year 1 guys.
I'm an able fighter and considered reliable.
No matter how you look at it,
there is no match for me.
I am respected even by the Year 3 guys.
But even I have one big problem
that I am fighting against.
That problem is...
I get motion sickness very easily!
But I like taking trips. I can't miss them.
Especially since Nikko is my favorite place!
I can get immersed in an elegant feeling
just by looking at the antique temples.
Since elementary school, I've been getting
through this hardship with spirit and guts!
I don't mean to brag,
but I've never once thrown up!
Hey, look. Takenouchi looks furious.
Something must've really pissed him off.
We should really try and keep
our distance from him.
Even if life's easy here, you call it Cro- Cro-
Ah, Cromartie is our alma mater
I wonder if I can find a seat?
What's this? For some reason,
all the seats in the back are empty.
Here we go.
Not good! I've been doing fine
since I started high school,
but I've just made an irreparable mistake.
What should I do? What should I do?
I wanna tell him "Get off, now!",
but I might throw up if I open my mouth!
We are now entering Iroha Hill Road.
Iroha Hill Road!
Just hearing the name makes me wanna hurl.
I've never gotten scared
no matter how strong my opponent was.
I kept winning fights one after another.
But when I face this Iroha Hill Road,
it still sends a chill down my spine!
And how long is this guy going to sit on me?
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I'm in seriously big trouble.
Oh, that's right!
Still, it's disrespectful
if I don't take off the hat, right?
Get off, damn it!
Please be careful, since the bus
will rock violently from side to side.
I'm sorry. It's because the bus is rocking.
Right at that moment, Kamiyama's eyes
looked like those of an assassin.
There's no mistaking it. He's after my life!
I have a lot of enemies.
It's true that I could be targeted at any time.
He's probably working with guys from
other schools, trying to destroy me.
But, Kamiyama, I'm not commanding
Year 1 at Cro-High for nothing!
I have enough power to
turn the tables on the likes of you!
You look pale.
Please pull yourself together.
Sorry! You win! I'm begging you,
please don't touch me any more!
By any chance, Takenouchi, is it that?
That's right, it's motion sickness!
Don't play dumb.
It's obvious that you know it!
My apologies. I hadn't realized
and acted insensitively.
But please don't worry.
I have something carefully
put aside for times like this.
Please have this pudding.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Please have my snack.
It's a little warm now, though...
It's a sleeping cat, meow.
I heard that Takenouchi ate pudding
and then lost consciousness.
Pudding? What the hell?
All right, let's enjoy Nikko, everyone!
Yutaka Takenouchi, 16 years old.
The man who commands Year 1 at Cromartie.
He's an able fighter and considered reliable.
No matter how you look at it,
there is no match for him.
He's respected even by the Year 3 guys.
However, a guy like him still has one weakness.
That weakness is...
He is extremely susceptible to motion sickness.
But it has nothing to do with my strength.
Takenouchi, there's trouble!
Maeda got kidnapped
by guys from Bass High School!
What?!
I'm fundamentally opposed to fighting,
but after all, we must do everything
we can to save our friends!
Maybe we should round up some guys too.
I've fought with Bass High School
several times before.
That school's no big whoop.
No big whoop = One of the delinquent terms.
It means "no big deal"?
I could handle 'em by myself!
Let's hurry, you guys!
Yes! We have everything ready!
Here, please get in.
Hey!
Here.
Can't we just walk over there, since it's close?
Maeda could be getting beaten up
by a bunch of guys right now!
We've got no time to lose!
Not good! I don't like cabs
as much as I don't like tour buses.
Cabs have enough power
to take me out in one blow.
I'm getting sick just by looking at the cab.
Takenouchi, get in quickly.
Things can't start without you.
If people find out that I get carsick,
my reputation will be devastated.
In the worst case, I won't even be able
to walk around in my own neighborhood.
Before we get in the car,
listen to what I have to say.
I know that you wanna hurry up,
but if we act rashly and they turn
the tables on us, it won't be pretty.
We should plan a detailed strategy.
If possible, we should go back
to the classroom and...
It's true that it could be a trap to lure us there.
It may be good to plan a strategy carefully.
You see? This is definitely a trap!
Good thing they
are morons.
Then let's plan a strategy first!
Then let's plan a strategy after we get in the car.
I ended up in the car after all,
and on top of that, I'm sitting in the middle!
Sitting in the middle,
I can't get fresh air, nor can I run away!
And who the hell's the rock singer
looking guy in the passenger seat?!
Oh, no. I'm getting sick thinking
about unnecessary things.
I have to focus my mind.
Stop the car!
Why is that?
Why?
It's because I can't get you guys involved.
I don't understand what you're saying at all.
Bass High is pretty strong.
There'll probably be lots of blood spilled.
You said earlier that they were no big whoop!
In any case, I'll go by myself on foot,
so I'm getting off! No, let me out!
What are you saying? We're all from Cromartie.
When we die, we die together.
We'll never let you get off!
I'll die before that!
Excuse me, sir.
Yes?
I've moved here recently, so I don't know
my way around Tokyo very well.
Oh, it's all right if you take a little longer route.
You were saying earlier that
we don't have any time to lose!
But we can't help it if he doesn't know the way.
Screw that! if you take a longer route
or something, I'll fudgin' kill you!
Calm down, Takenouchi! That's not the driver.
Give me the map! I'll navigate!
Yes!
World Map
1981 Edition
I said I'd navigate, but if I look
at the map for a long time,
there is a risk that I'll get sicker.
I'd better find the shortest route quickly.
Edition
First head south through
the Scandinavian Peninsula,
then go through the Panama Canal,
and cross the international date line...
World Map
1981 Edition
This is a world map!
World Map
1981 Edition
Oh, that's right!
More importantly, Russia's marked
as the Soviet Union!
World Map
1981 Edition
Oh, crap! Takenouchi fell unconscious again!
Two hours have passed since Maeda
was abducted by Bass High students.
Although they got in a cab to save
Maeda without a moment's delay,
because of the fluke of a driver
who did not know his way around,
a tense atmosphere prevailed in the car.
And Takenouchi's car sickness
was at its peak as well!
I can't tell them that
I don't like cars at this point.
If I had known this would happen, I would have
eaten something that's easy to digest for lunch.
In any case, why do I have to deal with all this?
As a matter of fact, I don't know Maeda
that well, and he's just a classmate.
I feel sick. I want to get out already!
It's been more than an hour
since we got in the cab, hasn't it?
Hey, it only takes about twenty minutes
to get to Bass High School, even on foot!
I'm sorry. Our strategy has already failed.
I imagine the cab fare will be high as well.
That's it! That's right!
We don't have any money, so we'll be
in trouble unless we get off soon!
Don't worry. I got a
cab coupon from my parents.
Then no matter how long we ride, we don't
have to worry about the fare, right, Hayashida?
Yeah! We'll be fine
even if we rode all day long.
Do you want to save your friend
or just ride around in a cab?!
Sorry, I just...
Listening to you guys talking gets
on my nerves! Be quiet for a while!
There's trouble!
The scenery outside of the window
is something that looks really unfamiliar.
We can see the mountains!
I'm sorry. It seems that
we're getting close to my parents' home.
Mr. Driver, there should be a limit
to not knowing your way around.
What the heck's gonna happen to us?
Cars rock a lot on rural roads...
Yeah, as things stand, we don't
have time to worry about Maeda.
World Map
1981 Edition
Look! Freddie's looking at the map.
World Map
He's pointing right.
Could it be he knows the way?
I see! He must be looking
for the way with his animal instincts!
Mr. Driver, please go right.
Okay.
World Map
Left, this time.
Okay.
It seems the scenery is becoming familiar.
There's no mistaking it,
we're getting close to the destination!
It was a long way, but we're almost there.
I'll take my anger out on them with all my might!
We're here!
All right! Let's go!
Show them how dangerous Cro-High is!
We'll fudgin' kill them all!
Yeah!
Cromartie High School
Hey, this is our school!
We've come back...
Cromartie High School
Bass High Storage Building
Maeda
Aren't they here yet?
The worst guy here
is the cab driver
I don't know my way around Tokyo very well.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
The next episode of Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School is finally...
Actually, I have no intention whatsoever
of telling you what it'll be about.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
He's coming
What was today's story about again?
Sorry, I don't remember.