Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Um,
I thought we should resume baseball practice,
which we all forgot about,
but since the horse is tearing up the field,
we'll call it off for a while.
This isn't a joke!
First and foremost, people
shouldn't bring horses to school!
Hey, stop it!
Huh? Why?
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Kokuryu's smart, so he can understand human words.
Exactly.
You shouldn't make light of animals.
They're very smart and if
you're friendly to them,
they do things like
soothe your heart.
It's possible that they may soothe
everyone's currently hardened hearts too.
Huh? Really?
Animals really are incredible.
Isn't the horse what
irritated you in the first place?
And then, we hastily
founded an animal lovers club
and decided that everyone
will bring their pets to school.
Wow, people brought a variety of pets, huh?
I brought a typical pet, a dog.
Wow, he's cute. What's his name?
Taro. It's a little too commonplace, though.
Speaking of names, my name is...
Well, then, let's move onto the next one.
I was supposed to bring a lion
as proof of my kingship,
but it got held up due to
the Washington Convention,
so I brought just a picture.
That's just like you, Hokuto.
Oh? You didn't bring anything, Maeda?
Well, I brought a hamster,
but it was eaten by Hayashida's pet.
My condolences...
Well, there are many different things happening,
but I'm glad to know that
everyone has the heart to love animals.
If you have a heart that
loves and adores animals,
you should be able to be kind to others too.
Hold on a second, Kamiyama.
There's one more person.
What? Who's that person?
We can't tell which one is the pet.
Yeah...
That one's the pet?!
Darn!
Maeda, changing straw bedding for horse
Why do I have to take care of the pets?
I'm not the one who suggested
having pets in the first place...
What are you complaining about?
Oh, you were here too?
Even if you're dissatisfied,
deal with it after you complete your work.
If all you do is complain instead of working,
people will think you're useless.
It's not a complaint! I'm just
stating my reasonable opinion!
Then, I'll ask you, have you ever
gone to vote in an election?
Akira Maeda (16) No voting rights!
Voting...
No, I've never gone to vote.
See, I told you.
You must be thinking
"my vote won't change anything," right?
But if there are only people like you,
society won't make progress.
Whoa!
But, there are tons of people in society
who are more irresponsible than I am.
That's why Japan is getting bad.
What are you saying is bad about Japan?
Share prices have fallen
and the yen has dropped.
And the Japanese economy is failing.
There isn't a single good thing.
Oh? Are you saying that if the yen weakens,
it will influence your life somehow?
I don't know about that, but there isn't anything good about the yen getting weaker, right?
You don't know anything, do you?
On the contrary, if the yen is too expensive,
the Japanese companies that
expanded overseas will take a hit.
Don't speak as if you know everything
by seeing only one side of the issue.
Whoa!
In my view, you're only
repeating what's in the papers.
Now that you mention it, you may be right...
In that case, you're only speaking
others' opinions like they're your own.
Why don't you look around and talk about the
things closer to you that you're dissatisfied with.
That's your opinion.
I see... Complaints closer to me, huh?
When I get home,
the first thing I do is take a bath.
I see. And?
You know bath mats, right?
The ones you use to dry your feet after a bath.
This one
My old lady washes this
bath mat every single day.
Oh, I see...
But it shouldn't get very dirty
since you use it to dry your feet
after washing your body clean in the bath, right?
So I don't think it's necessary
to wash it every day.
I think it's okay to wash it about once a month.
It also saves water and power.
What do you think?
I see...
You're saying that since your feet
are clean after a bath,
you don't have to wash the bath mat every day...
Yeah, exactly.
But what about before you take a bath?
I see...
I step on the mat with dirty feet
before taking a bath.
I was only thinking about
when I get out of the bath...
That's what I tried to tell you.
Looking at just one side of the issue isn't enough.
If we clear up the problems
one by one like this,
Japan will be a better place, don't you think?
I don't think so.
The sun shines lightly through
the gap in the clouds,
as if it proclaims the arrival of winter.
Okay, okay. You wanna eat?
I'll prepare it right away.
Strangely enough, when you take care of
animals for a long time,
you start to understand how they feel.
Oh! You're hungry too? Hold on, okay?
I feel relaxed when I'm with these guys...
Somehow I feel that, for the first time,
I've found a place where I feel peaceful...
Oh, it's already time to go home.
Behave yourselves until tomorrow as usual.
Now, I'll clean the stable and...
What in the hell am I doing this for?!
Far from being soothed,
I was almost brainwashed...
I carelessly let my guard down and
came to like the animals before I knew it! Scary!
Moreover, it's already time to go home.
What am I still at school for?
I never said one word about
raising pets in the first place!
Those idiots!
What? What did you say?
Well, I sincerely feel bad about
what we've done to you, Maeda.
I don't know what you mean.
To put it simply,
since we're already bored with our pets
we're thinking about getting rid of them.
Don't screw with me!
I'll fudgin' kill you morons!
You guys are always like that!
You get all excited about things
and then quickly get bored!
Same thing with baseball!
You said you wanted to go to Koshien,
but you don't care at all!
You haven't gotten any better!
Freddie can now pitch at 160 km/h, though.
But he's taking forever to learn the rules.
Come to think of it,
he hit a ball and ran to third base.
Enough!
Don't you feel sorry for the animals?
Have you ever thought
from the animals' perspective?
Even if you tell us to put
ourselves in animals' shoes,
we're not animals, so...
See, I told you!
You guys are just thinking
about yourselves after all!
Maeda, since we're humans,
it's impossible to put
ourselves in animal's shoes.
For example, what should
I do to make a cat happy?
Well, if you stroke its head
like this, it'll be happy, right?
Did you ask the cats about it?
Huh?
No... I certainly haven't
asked them about it, but...
Right?
In other words, the idea that a cat is happy when you stroke it is a baseless assumption made by humans,
and they might actually hate it because it tickles.
Then... the idea that the animals that I took
care of were happy was also my assumption?
If you can't say with confidence
that you understand how cats feel,
can you say you understand how animals feel?
So my interaction with them was
my own baseless assumption?
And why am I being scolded
by people who didn't take care of them?
No, I'm pretty sure the animals
and I understood each other...
Why don't you just
become a cat once and for all?
What? Become a cat?
If you can perfectly understand how cats feel,
I'll admit that humans and animals
can understand each other.
Prove to me that you can
put yourself in animals' shoes.
But... even if you suddenly
tell me to become a cat...
Indeed, even if I suddenly tell you
to become a cat, it's impossible.
For now, I'll give you just one week.
Maeda's house
No... this isn't what it's about, is it?
Rice
Dried Bonito
As a first step, I started adding a dish of
dried bonito to my meals yesterday,
but besides becoming a cat,
it's very good because it helps
make a well-balanced diet.
What else do I have to do?
It'd be good to put on a bell, nyo.
I'll try adding "nya" at the end of sentences.
"Nyo" is a gazillion times
better than "nya," nyo.
Good morning... nya.
I'm an ordinary high school student... nya.
What am I doing?!
Aren't I just passing myself off as a cat?
And thus one week was gone,
without anything to show for it.
Kamiyama...
M-Maeda!
You grew quite skinny...
Yeah... I lost...
I finally got what you're saying.
No matter how hard we humans try,
in the end, there's no way that
we can understand how animals feel.
It was impossible to become a cat.
No...
You're already a fine cat.
Why can't people understand how animals feel?
It's because humans have egos and arrogance.
But you've just noticed that! You'll be fine now!
Thanks... I finally... did it, didn't I?!
Well done, Maeda.
So what should I do now?
What? I think you should
be your usual self, right?
Oh, I see. I felt relieved to hear that.
Of course.
Were you seriously thinking of
becoming a cat by any chance?
And...
I'd like to ask one more thing...
Can I take these off now?
No, it's not!
No!
I thought that was the case!
Yeah, I can't take these off, can I?
Why can't I?
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
If you get too carried away just because
your joke was a little popular,
people won't be faithful to you and stuff,
Heave ho
so get a grip.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Things are finally
getting underway.
Dejiko
Puchiko
I recommend "nyo" at the end of sentences, nyo.
"Nyu" is okay too, nyu.
Nyo...