Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
When riding a motorcycle, please wear a helmet.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Mechazawa!
There's something that
we'd like to talk to you about.
What is it?
We had trouble again with guys
from Bass High the other day
and we heard they were saying that
they'd take us out for good.
It looks like it'll become a big fuss.
So what are you saying you want me to do?
Well, you have a friend at Bass High, right?
Would you talk to him and settle this trouble?
I'm indebted to him already.
Besides, our schools are, in fact, enemies now.
So I don't think it'd work out so easily.
I want to help you,
but there are things that
I can do and things I can't do.
But you're the only one we can depend on!
I've been telling you guys all this time.
These things happen because
you overdo things and show off.
So really it's your own fault.
What did you say?!
You're going too far, Mechazawa!
Are you looking for trouble?!
Stop it, both of you!
I think Mechazawa is right.
We've always been totally dependent on him.
Guys should wipe their own asses,
right, Mechazawa?
Thanks, Ishida. You really
understand me very well.
I consider you my best friend.
But there's one thing I'd like to say to you.
That's not me!
In any case, you guys depend on me too much.
You won't be able to become independent
if you keep acting like that, right?
You talk like you know everything.
I guess, in the end,
we can't even depend on you.
I'm saying this for your own good.
If you don't understand that, I'll leave.
If you wanna say something,
just go right ahead!
Yeah! Then I'll say it now.
I've always wanted to say it!
Like I said, that's not me!
Coffee
Family
Princess
Peach
Geez...
Under 18
Not Allowed
How irritating!
I guess I'll go somewhere
to take my mind off things.
Unlimited
Under 18
Not Allowed
All right! I got them all!
What the hell is that?
Crap! What am I doing in a place like this?!
I gave them a lecture,
and now I'm in this mess,
getting worried if I was right.
I guess that means I'm
actually the weakest one.
I don't care any more.
Since it's come to this,
I'll fall until I hit rock bottom.
ls something the matter?
Seven lined up, but no pachinko balls come out, and they're stuck!
What the hell is going on? Fix it already!
I apologize. I'll try checking it now,
so could you please step aside?
It looks like the wiring isn't connected properly.
Hey, that's not it!
Oh?
The pachinko balls aren't coming out.
Don't stick your pachinko card in me!
Speeding on my motorcycle is
the best thing I can do when I'm irritated.
The freezing wind is piercing my skin,
but it feels good right now.
It gives me an endless high.
Customer pulling in!
Regular
High Octane
Diesel
Welcome!
Would you like us to fill it up?
Yeah, fill it up.
I'm filling it up!
Hey, stop it!
No matter how you look at it,
the gas tank is here, right?
Oh, yeah, no kidding.
How boring.
Hey, Kamiyama, I wonder if
there's anything interesting?
Yeah, if Mechazawa was riding
on a motorcycle or something and speeding,
that'd be very interesting,
but there's no way something like that would...
He's riding it!
Road
Closed
No way!
He's broken again!
He broke into pieces!
I was thinking about saying this earlier,
but this is because he wasn't wearing a helmet!
Well, that's not the point, is it?
Dead
End
If something like this happens in a TV show,
it gets fixed before you know it,
but it's really busted into so many pieces
this time that we can't say such a thing.
You can't even recognize the original shape.
I guess we have to deal with it ourselves.
Unless we do something right away,
they'll be picked up as trash.
But I wonder if we can do it?
If you think you can't,
you won't be able to do anything!
It's important for you
to be willing to take on a challenge!
Is that how it works?
Mechazawa is an important
acquaintance to us, right?
Yeah, he's our acquaintance,
although not quite a friend.
Repair Complete
We don't know anyone like this!
Wait up!
Relax, just come with us.
Please stop!
What's wrong?
If you don't stop it now, I'll call for help!
Go ahead. If you can, why don't you?
Look around.
People see things
but pretend not to see anything.
This area is our turf,
so everyone's too scared to defy us.
No one will help you, so give it up.
You brutes!
What a lively woman.
We'll treat you real nice.
Wh-What the hell...
Wh-Who's that?!
Let her go.
Who the hell are you,
riding a weird motorcycle?!
Who do you think we are, moron?!
Don't think you can get away from this now!
Looks like you won't understand
unless you suffer a little.
I'm firing the second one.
This guy's snapped!
He does crazy stuff!
Let's run away for now!
Damn you! We'll get even with you!
They're gone now.
Thank you very much.
Please at least tell me your name.
Well, I'm not much of anyone.
Oh? Looks like the police have finally arrived.
But they were a little too late,
because I've solved the case.
Guts
All Season
Road Safety
Campaign
in Effect
Why was I arrested?
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
I'm also beginning to think
that this show is doing pretty good.
I think it's okay to say it's
a social phenomenon by now.
Just say so!
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
We wanna hear
your opinions on the show
I heard that celebrities are also
looking forward to this show.
It's fun!