Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
OK Computer
Manuel High School Kiichi Fujimoto
Finished.
Listen, keep beating your
enemy until he can't move.
There are no rules in fighting.
Fujimoto's really scary. He's a devil.
Fujimoto's house
Let's see here....
Well, it's been cold every day.
How's everyone doing?
Come to think of it, I haven't
seen Ayumaro lately.
Busy as usual, I guess. Parentheses, laugh.
Pootan Site
Message Board
Subject: Geez By: Anonymous Posted: Feb. 4 (Wed) 16:48:21
Pootan isn't funny at all.
The people here are all a bunch
of morons.
Must be a newbie who doesn't
know proper etiquette.
How do you do? You're a newcomer, right?
As you can see in the etiquette rules,
malicious slanders are not
allowed on this message board.
Hello?
Also, you should always put your handle,
because otherwise it'll be
considered an irresponsible remark.
Let's get along, following the rules, newcomer.
As you can see in the etiquette rules,
malicious slanders are not allowed on this message board.
Also, you should always put your handle, because
otherwise it'll be considered an irresponsible remark.
Let's get along, following the rules, newcomer.
Mr. Fujimoto...
What is it?
Actually, a new member joined our group,
but he's a little cocky.
So they're saying that
they'd like you to talk to the guy.
All right.
Manuel High School
You're a newcomer, so don't get carried away!
That's Fujimoto for you. He doesn't
show any mercy, even to a newcomer.
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Kiichi
Fujimoto
(He's a nice
person on
the Internet)
Good morning. I'm Kamiyama.
I've been wondering for a while
why this school is so chaotic...
But there's no one here!
Hayashida
Freddie
It's 11 o'clock. It's no longer
just a matter of them being late!
At least Freddie's here.
But he doesn't belong to our class.
Okay! For starters, I have to
teach everyone that being late is bad.
Next Day
Thank you very much for gathering together
today to hear me, even though you're busy.
What the hell's this about, moron?!
If it's something stupid, I'll fudging kill you!
Frankly, I'd like to discuss
"being late" with you all today.
Well, then, we shall end today's meeting now.
Okay, get lost!
No, just let him keep talking.
Look, people have long said that
"a good speaker is also a good listener",
Ken Hirai (17)
He's called "Mr."
a                                because he's repeating the year.
so those who can't listen to others
will come to a bad end.
Thank you very much, Mr. Hirai.
And is there anything bad about being late?
For example, say there are
five hours of classes a day.
If you're two hours late each day,
and if you're paying
500,000 yen a year for tuition and fees,
that's a loss of 200,000 yen for one year and
600,000 yen for three years, believe it or not.
Especially in your case, Mr. Hirai,
it'd be a total loss of 800,000 yen
since you're repeating the year.
I see. It'd be a loss of 800,000 yen for me.
"Time is money," is it?
I guess it means that those who
waste time are worthless.
All right! Don't you guys be late,
starting tomorrow!
Hold on a second, please!
I can't get up early in the morning!
I'm worried about you guys because
I'm repeating the year myself.
Well, but the morning is still a problem.
What time do you usually go to bed?
It was seven in the morning yesterday.
If that's the case, how about coming to school
around six o'clock in the morning?
I see. Then it'd be fine if we come
to school after the meeting.
By the way, the Year 2 guys from Manuel High
picked a fight with me last week.
Okay, that's good timing.
Let's raid Manuel High
before we come to school!
If it's early in the morning,
we can ambush them too.
If you do that, I have a feeling
that you'll be late again.
It's a pain in the ass,
so let's meet up in front of
Manuel's main gate tomorrow.
You're smart!
All right! It's decided.
We'll meet at 10 o'clock tonight
in front of Manuel High!
Yeah!
Make sure you're not late!
What? Me too?
And...
Manuel High School
Everyone's late...
I wonder if they went to bed?
Oh well, I'll wait ten more
minutes and then go home.
But if everyone comes right
after I leave, I'll get ticked.
Oh, I have to go to the bathroom.
But it wouldn't be good if
they came while I'm gone.
Oh, darn! Coming or not, I wish
they'd at least let me know,
otherwise I don't know what to do!
This isn't good. This somehow looks
as if I'm waiting for my girlfriend.
I'm just gonna hurry home.
But it wouldn't be good if they
accuse me of not coming later.
Oh, yeah! I'll leave a note for them.
Dear Gentlemen,
This is Kamiyama.
I've come here
at 10 o'clock.
Since no one came,
I'm going home now.
Well, the letters are a little small.
Since everyone's boorish, they may not notice.
And it's long. They're stupid too,
so they won't read such long writing.
Write simply with big letters.
I'll try rewriting it, paying attention to that.
Kamiyama was here!
Spray
paint
Somehow I think I've seen
this kind of graffiti somewhere.
Kamiyama
was here!
Hey, did you see that?!
The guy's definitely making a fool of us!
This means war!
Manuel High School Year 1 Boss Kiichi Fujimoto
What's the matter?
Oh, Fujimoto! There's a guy who
picked a fight with us directly!
Moreover, he left a note saying,
"Kamiyama was here!"
Who's Kamiyama?
Who cares? Don't get so worked up
because one little fly crept in!
Hey, hold on! Are you serious?
Isn't he being defeatist?
I agree! He isn't the kind of man
who should be a leader!
That's not it.
The person who's the most upset
about this is Fujimoto himself.
But a leader can't get rattled.
He's grinning and bearing it
because it's in front of us.
I see, I didn't know. That's
the kind of man Fujimoto is.
We're nothing compared to him.
Since I'm starting a new homepage today,
I don't have time to deal with
this stupid stuff with them.
Hello, hello! It's been a while.
I tried to set up today's agenda,
more or less.
About Etiquette
Please discuss it frankly with everyone else.
It looks like a chat room has opened.
Hello. It's been a while!
I was hoping to finally get
ADSL service this year,
but it looks like it's not available in our area yet.
I'm a little disappointed. Parenthesis, crying.
Speaking of etiquette, I heard
that there was a Mr. Trouble
who sprayed graffiti on a fence in
my neighborhood just the other day.
He's really such a hopeless guy.
I wonder if he thinks that it's art?
I wish he'd put himself in the shoes of the
person who owns the fence, you know?
Parentheses, anger.
I've already got a response.
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you. It's definitely
an action that can't be forgiven
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
I agree with you    Message by: Honey    Posted: Feb. 7
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
However, don't you think that
this person who sprayed graffiti
had some sort of flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
It's definitely an action that can't be forgiven.
However, don't you think that this person
who sprayed graffiti had some sort of
flaw in his thinking?
I don't particularly mean to support him,
but I feel that I'd like to consider
such things when thinking about it
This guy says some pretty good stuff.
It's not easy to have an attitude
that's not just criticizing,
but also thinking of the culprit's point of view.
Let me see, his name is...
Message by : Honey
Mr. Honey?
I guess it's always worth
getting the thought out there.
Kamiyama
was here!
Hey! Guys from Des-High
are at the coffeehouse on Block 1!
What?!
They've been trolling our
gathering places one after another.
Hey, Fujimoto! I can't stand it any more!
Let's crush those idiots!
Who gives a crap?!
They're just enjoying watching
you guys panicking like this.
But...
You guys should also be more mature!
Fujimoto's house
Geez, the hell with trolls.
Since I have to update my homepage,
I'm too busy for that.
Hey, hey    Message by: Anonymous    Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
Who the hell do you think you are,
talking big on this kind of message board?
This is probably all you can do to
express yourself in your lives. (laugh)
Click here for images
that are well matched to you guys.
Hey, hey, who the hell do you think you are,
talking big on this kind of message board?
This is probably all you can do
to express yourself in your lives.
Parentheses, laugh
A troll!
Dumbass, he's got some nerve,
trolling on my turf.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
but don't you feel pathetic?
It'd be better...    Message by: Satorin    Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
if you don't react to the troll too much.
Trolls are people who enjoy
watching people's reactions.
If it bothers you, you should delete the
message without making any comment.
It'd be better if you don't react
to the troll too much.
Trolls are people who enjoy
watching people's reactions.
If it bothers you, you should delete
the message without making any comment.
I didn't expect to get a comment like this from
the leading figure of this community, Mr. Satorin.
To Mr. Satorin. With all due respect,
deleting without a word is against my policy.
Even if it is a flame,
I think the best way to deal with it
is to reason with him properly.
I don't want to have any trouble with you,
but I'll do it my way.
Hey, hey    Message by: Anonymous    Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
Are you having a quarrel
amongst yourselves? (laugh)
Geez... You guys are
just like kids. (snicker)
To Mr. Satorin    Message by: Eleven PM    Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
With all due respect, deleting
without a word is against my policy.
Hey, hey, are you having a quarrel
amongst yourselves? Parentheses, laugh.
That dumbass! He's mocking me!
The
Troll
Cromartie High School Year 1 Makio Tanaka
You guys have been so annoying.
I won't be satisfied unless
I give him a piece of my mind.
Well, do you know the word "netiquette"?
More like... Message by: Anonymous Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
Don't you feel empty livening up
the message board by performing
in your own play?!
Do you know    Message by: Eleven PM    Posted: Feb. 9 (Mon)
Well, do you know
the word "netiquette"?
More like, don't you feel empty livening up the
message board by performing in your own play?
Bastard! Don't say stupid stuff like that!
I don't know what made you say that.
I am performing in my own play
in this homepage, but...
Boy, it's fun teasing an idiot.
Well, then, I guess I'll go for the final blow.
You're a real
shut-in, aren't you?
Oh, no... I somehow feel
that he's a little bit right.
It's like he's looking inside of my room.
I'm feeling pretty good today.
I feel frustrated. I'm powerless.
I can't find a way to counterattack him.
The number of amateurs
in Akiba has increased lately.
I wish those who can't even build
their own computers wouldn't come here.
Ouch! I'm so...
I can't come up with the words
to counterattack him!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
I'm speaking alone right now.
I haven't seen Hayashida around lately,
and Maeda and Hokuto aren't around either.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Don't lose, shut-in
Let me see... C-5.
Good! Miss.