Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
I'm the heir to the Hokuto Foundation,
one of the major Japanese financial groups,
and my martial arts ability is also top-notch.
Money, power, and strength...
I'm a man with everything.
You can say that I was surely born to be a ruler.
By the way, I transferred to
Cromartie High School by mistake.
Mr. Hokuto! There's trouble!
What's the matter?
Haven't you heard of the Boss Championship?
What's that?
It's a tournament that decides
who the No. 1 boss in Japan is.
What? A tournament that decides
the No. 1 boss in Japan?
The Japan Boss Championship.
It is a prestigious tournament that
determines the highest-ranked boss in Japan.
Leaders from delinquent schools
gather once a year.
It has been held every year,
except for the year of the Oil Shock.
Right then, all of Cro-High was
also talking of nothing but that.
How careless of me, not knowing
about such a tournament.
Be that as it may, why didn't
I hear about it until now?
I hate to say this,
but isn't it because you don't
hang out with your friends much?
Just the other day, everyone said,
"let's go to karaoke,"
but you said that you wanted
to watch TV and went home.
This is a good opportunity,
so let me say that you're losing friends.
What are you saying, you idiot?!
I have many friends.
Then who are your friends?
First of all, you, right?
So your list starts with me?
Well, I'm your junior, rather than a friend.
Now that you mention it,
I really don't have any specific friends.
If only I had gone to karaoke...
Hey, shut up! Don't treat me
like I'm one of the masses!
You don't have friends because you're like that.
Shut up! Are you still saying that?!
In the first place,
making friends is something silly
the powerless, foolish masses do
to seek emotional support!
As the man who will become
the future ruling monarch of Japan,
I need not bother with such worthless things!
I understand.
If you understand, it's settled.
So, are you going to participate
in the tournament?
Of course I am.
But it's kinda tough to join them and tell them
that you want to participate
when you're not even invited.
You aren't invited either?
I was just listening in from the shadows.
I wonder if they're hesitant to invite me now,
since I turned down
the karaoke invitation that time.
Well, I didn't mind going then,
but I just don't like singing that much.
Yeah...
It's fine if it's just listening to others' singing.
In fact, I like listening to good singers.
But in that kind of situation,
it's almost always the case
that there are guys who stick a mike
in your face, saying "Sing!"
If you turn it down, it could ruin the atmosphere.
You know, I'm the type who's very
concerned about others, right?
Yeah...
But I don't want you to misunderstand.
That doesn't mean I'm a bad singer,
though some guys say something
like that right away.
I just don't like singing, that's all.
If anything, I think I'm actually a good singer.
So are you going to participate
in the tournament?
Of course I am!
I'm not talking about a karaoke tournament.
Of course not!
Well, I certainly apologize for
diverging from the subject.
But it's a plain fact that we're at a disadvantage
that we're not invited
even if we want to participate.
If we just go and talk to them,
it'll look as if we're asking them
so that we can participate,
and that's the one thing my pride won't allow!
What should we do? Do you have any ideas?
Then how about this?
We'll make an appeal to them again
about how incredible you are.
Then even those idiots will notice
that they need you and beg you,
saying "please participate."
But it's hard to make those fools see
my brilliance and my high caliber.
I'll assist you in that part. Leave it to me.
Got it. I'm counting on you... er... you.
aaaYou
(Hokuto's lackey)
Around that time,
all the classroom chatter was about
the Japan Boss Championship,
and a heavy, dangerous atmosphere
was filling the room.
I am definitely opposed to
such a violent tournament!
But I'd like to ask, just in case,
what's the prize for the winner?
You're not planning to participate, are you?
But you know, this tournament
is incredibly tough.
To participate representing the Tokyo area,
you have to be someone who is suitably strong.
You small fry...
You're Hokuto!
We're busy right now,
so could you go somewhere else?
Hokuto's lackey
Hold on a second, you guys!
It seems that you don't know how incredible Mr. Hokuto is.
I'll explain it to you now!
What's so incredible about him?
Why don't you tell us?
First of all, he's a person of high caliber.
To Mr. Hokuto, you guys are tiny little things.
I see, high caliber? And how high is it?
Well, you've been talking about Japan's
No. 1 boss or something like that, right?
To Mr. Hokuto, that's already a little thing!
If No. 1 in Japan is a little thing,
does that mean that he's...
That's right! To put it bluntly,
he's at the world level!
So unlike you guys, he doesn't bother
with small stuff in little Japan!
In short, does that mean that
he's aiming to become the world's boss?
I don't really get it, though.
I didn't expect this. Hokuto's really incredible!
I feel that the conversation
is off the point somehow again.
There's something I'd like to ask.
In order to become the world's boss,
what do I have to do first?
I don't know much about it,
but one thing I can say without a doubt is...
That we don't need you here at all!
Just as I thought...
Do your best and become the world's boss!
I can also see you off without worries!
Thanks. Courage is springing up in my heart.
Okay, then! Good luck!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
What kind of boss is the world boss?
After school, behind the school building
at Cromartie High School.
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Then, Hayashida, you look
like your father? I wanna see him.
Takeshi Hokuto (16)
Shinjiro Hayashida (16)
Yeah, but my dad doesn't have a mohawk.
Of course not.
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Come to think of it, Maeda, you definitely
look like your mother, don't you?
Shinjiro Hayashida (16)
Akira Maeda (16)
Yeah, as you all know.
That's incredible, isn't it?
Main character Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Come to think of it... Let me see...
You, which do you look like,
your father or mother?
Just "you"?
Well, I look like my grandpa.
What, like your grandpa?
By the way, did you have a dream
when you were a kid?
How about you, Hokuto?
Mine was conquering the world, I think.
Freddie, what was your dream
when you were a child?
Even if you talk to Freddie,
he won't say anything.
It's even uncertain whether he had a childhood.
And, let me see...
You are...
Hold on a second!
You've been calling me just "you"
instead of my name!
Please call me by name.
Don't tell me that you don't know my name!
Sorry.
No way! You don't know?!
I've been in this school for half a year already!
Mr. Hokuto, we've known
each other for a long time,
so there's no way you don't
know my name, right?
I forgot.
Seriously?! And don't say it
without hesitation like that!
The reason that we didn't know your name is...
Because we didn't think it mattered.
You use that calm tone, but say some
pretty mean things, don't you?
Damn it! I see!
Then you'd be happy if I introduce
myself again, right?! My name is...
By the way, I'm changing the subject, but...
Hey, Hayashida! To say the least,
that's rude, isn't it?!
Hayashida, that's indeed too rude.
Let's just quietly hear his name now.
It certainly was a little childish of me. Sorry.
Thanks, though it sounds strange to say that.
Anyway, I'll introduce myself. My name is...
Freddie spilled juice!
I'll clean it up!
All right? Listen carefully. My name is...
We don't have any juice left.
I'm so thirsty that I could die!
Fine! I'll go and buy it right away!
All right, then! I'll tell you my name!
My name is...
Hey, there's trouble! A fight started
in the class next door!
I got it. You'd be happy if I go there, right?
Thirty Minutes Later
I beat them all up good.
Is he serious?
Were you that strong a fighter?
Are there any other troubles?!
I'll solve them all, so tell me now!
There aren't.
All right, then! All the problems
have been taken care of.
Now I can tell you my name without any worry.
Okay? Listen carefully! My name is...
There's trouble! A meteorite has fallen
on the school building!
That's beyond my power!
Japan Boss
Championship
Will the day come when
Hokuto's lackey's name is made clear?
What will happen to the Boss Championship?
In the next episode of
"Sakigake!! Cromartie High School,"
there will be stuff with all the answers
and also stuff without them.
We hope you'll be looking forward to seeing it.
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
True feelings clash against each other.
Forge ahead as it comes to you.
The first one to say it wins.
It will eventually
work out somehow. Just kidding.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
What's wrong with "Hokuto's lackey"?!
All right? My name is...
We're out of time.