Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Dear Mother,
Cromartie Municipal High School
I have been able to get enrolled
in Cromartie High School.
I hope to get used to the school
as quickly as possible
and lead a healthy academic life.
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
However...
I am surrounded by people
of unfamiliar demeanor,
and I am at somewhat of a loss.
Kamiyama
I dropped my pencil!
Thank you.
Well, it seems some of the people
are surprisingly nice.
He ate the pencil!
Cromartie High's delinquents
certainly aren't famous for nothing.
This is just not normal.
H-He ate them!
Truly, this is not your
ordinary school of delinquents.
Or rather, I feel as though this isn't really
an issue of being bad or delinquent.
Why have I ended up in this place?
Today's Theme
"I Was Once Bad"
Bragging Contest
I ask that you read the manga to find out.
I've been bad since junior high.
Other
Oh, yeah?
They said I was totally uncontrollable
Other
and called me "Fireball of Junior 2".
Fireball of Junior 2
Then, you're the legendary "Fireball"?!
Yeah.
I used to be a well-known badass too.
Other
If I lost it,
I wouldn't stop until I'd beat
the other guy to a bloody pulp.
My street name was "Hospitalizer of Junior 3".
Hospitalizer of Junior 3
"Hospitalizer of Junior 3"...
That doesn't sound very cool.
I was bad, but I've never gotten into a fight.
What's up with that?
I look tough, so they get scared
and don't even try to pick fights with me.
And the nickname I got was
Masa of Default Victories
"Masa of Default Victories".
So, are you actually good in a fight?
Well, like I said, I've never been
in a fight, so I don't know.
It's kinda hard to say if that's impressive or not.
I'll come out and say it,
you guys are nothing compared to me.
I was getting into fights
from dawn to dusk every day.
Of course, I've never lost.
I'd sooner punch someone than talk it over.
I'm what you'd call
an honest to goodness badass.
I've even won five against one.
So, what was your nickname?
What? Nickname?
My nickname was...
I never really had a nickname.
Then you're no good.
It's too bad.
This isn't worth discussing.
Hey, hold on!
Who gives a damn
if I have a nickname or not?!
There's no point if you don't have one like
"Fireball of Junior 2" or "Monster of Junior 3"!
Yeah. If you're like a
"Suzuki of Junior 4" or "Satoh,"
it doesn't give off the sense that you're scary.
That's just normal.
Sorry, try again next time.
Akira Maeda
Nickname coming next time...When is next time?
When's next time?!
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
Dear Mother,
two years ago in the spring of
my second year in junior high,
I did something bad, just once.
Hey, Kamiyama!
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
What is it?
You had a nickname when you were
in junior high too, didn't you?!
Like "Good-for-nothing" or "Moron".
Back in junior high, I was called "Errand Boy"!
"Errand Boy" ...someone who runs errands
That's not a nickname! That's your job!
You've never done anything bad, have you?!
No, because I have been on
the straight and narrow all my life.
But even so, I have done
something bad, just once.
Well, what you call bad is probably no big deal.
Like ringing doorbells and
running away or something?
Well, it really was nothing big,
but I do not really feel like talking
about it right now, so I won't.
Let's
Debut
After all, those who are curious
can just read the manga.
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
Dear Mother,
Main Character Takashi Kamiyama
The other day, I learned of
a revolutionary system
in the world of delinquents called
"Debuting in High School".
In this system, you can set out
anew as a delinquent,
even if you had led a normal life in junior high.
Advice on
Debuting in
High School
Chapter 1
Lesson 1: Looks are a vital part
of being a delinquent.
Amateurs should first try
bleaching their hair blond.
20 Minutes Later
If the chemical is too strong,
your hair will turn white, so be careful.
20 Minutes Later
Shoot...
If you still do not look fierce enough,
try shaving your eyebrows.
All right!
You will look even more fierce
if you furrow your brow.
Like this?!
Skipping the middle part and on to Lesson 5.
Please sever your ties with any upright people
you used to be friends with.
Please ignore them,
even if they try to talk to you.
Lesson 5 will be somewhat tough.
Tabata      Yoshio
Yoshio and Tabata are some of my best friends.
If you absolutely cannot do this,
please meet with them secretly.
Tabata      Yoshio
"Lesson 6, how to walk."
Try to relax as much as possible and walk lazily.
And if anyone stares at you, glare back at them.
All right!
Addendum. When walking around town,
try to walk with tough-looking friends
as much as possible.
First, make lots of tough-looking friends.
I see. This might be something
that would be applicable,
not just in the world of delinquents,
but out in the real world as well.
Once you get to this point, you are just
one step away from debuting in high school.
Now, this is the final lesson.
Please have all of the above
completed before starting school.
Then it's already too late.
Hey, go buy me some sticks!
Lick!
Fight Club
Let's get around to deciding who's
the strongest in our class soon too.
To start with, I've picked up a couple guys
based on their history of fighting.
These three.
Main character
Takashi Kamiyama
Please wait a minute.
Why have I been nominated?
You damn idiot! That's what I want to know!
Step back now, or I'll fudging kill you!
I'm the one who nominated Kamiyama.
What?! Hayashida?!
We've been living in a world of badasses,
Shinjiro Hayashida
so you don't feel scared
even when you see a good fighter
or someone who looks tough.
In fact, you start to feel impressed
by normal guys like Kamiyama.
Aren't you pushing it?
For example,
let's say there's one rabbit
living happily in a pride of lions.
Don't you think that rabbit's one hell of a rabbit?
I get it! That IS one hell of a rabbit!
In other words,
I want to see the devil that's in you!
I haven't the slightest what you mean.
So, how are we going to decide
who the strongest guy is?
It's gotta be through fighting!
You got that right! It's gotta be a fist fight!
And after a heated argument
that went on for several hours,
they decided that the strongest guy would be
"the most fired up guy with the strongest
and most persevering back,"
and that they would settle this with a contest
that would fulfill these conditions.
I hear Year 1 Class 2 is having a contest
to see who's the strongest.
That sounds interesting!
Hey, have you guys determined
who's strongest yet?
Hot...
I can't!
I've won!
Main Character Takashi Kamiyama
Hot!
Somehow, I don't feel satisfied with the results.
I've won!
Rock You
As the days went by, Kamiyama's thoughts about reorganizing this school strengthened.
However, as if to mock Kamiyama,
the school was to follow the way of ruin.
Shinjiro Hayashida
Kamiyama, if you could defeat HIM,
this school might change too.
Oh? Hayashida?
There's a real bastard in Year 1 Class 3.
As long as he's around,
this place will be like the Olympics
for badasses every single day.
Then I'll at least try meeting him.
What's his name?
No, I don't know his name.
What do you mean, you don't know?!
Without knowing his name,
I won't be able to see him even if I go!
When you get there, you'll know.
When I get there, I'll know?
What does that mean?
Year 1 Class 3. This is it. HE's here.
There he is!
No doubt about it! It's this guy!
But is he really a high school student?
Or rather, does he understand Japanese?
Nice to meet you. I am Kamiyama
of Year 1 Class 2.
Excuse me, but what is your name?
In the end, I didn't find out anything
from meeting with him.
I see. What a formidable guy.
Is he really a student here?
So I thought of a name for him.
What do you think of Freddie?
Freddie?
Freddie.
Freddie
Welcome
to the Jungle
Monsters dwell in Cromartie...
Okay, here we go.
One, two...
Look!
Kamiyama, there's this other
incredible guy in another class!
Future Century Cromartie
I've seen enough.
First Freddie, and then Gorilla...
All sorts of things show up at this school,
so nothing can surprise me now.
Anyway, he's incredible!
I've never seen a badass like him!
You've said the same thing each time,
you know that, Hayashida?
Hey, there's trouble, Mechazawa!
What's the matter? What kind of trouble?
Mechazawa?!
What a sober voice!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
it appears there will be another episode of the
anime; "Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
next time, with complete
disregard for public opinion.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
See you again
Oh, Hayashida. You don't need to
show me any more "incredible" guys.
We'll meet again!