Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
Dear Mother,
Cromartie Municipal High School
"Sakigake!! Cromartie High School"
has finally been adapted as anime.
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
However, when the original work is a manga
and is adapted as anime afterwards,
I hear that there are people
who complain about things
such as character design and voice
actor casting. So I was thinking...
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
that I might as well play my role
with this kind of face and voice.
It may surprisingly be accepted
without any problems, pyo. Or,
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
Tabata
it may be fine just like this.
Takashi Kamiyama (16)
No, I think I'll settle with this way after all.
This is getting tiresome.
Those who grumble should watch
this anime 1000 times.
I said anime, but there's hardly
been any movement!
It's moving!
The End
of the introduction...
Cromartie
High School
Dear Mother,
One day, after being talked into it
by my classmate, Hayashida,
I came to Year 1 Class 5.
Hey, there's trouble, Mechazawa!
What's the matter?
What a sober voice!
Listen, Mechazawa.
It seems that Sugawara from our school
got into a fight with guys
from Destrade High School.
It doesn't matter. We just gotta round up
some guys and fight 'em!
Hold on...
He made a "ka-chink" noise!
In short, Sugawara was the one
who started it, right?
I have a friend in Des-High.
This'll be resolved if an apology
is made through him.
Hey! Are you suggesting we punk out, then?
Don't worry. I won't disgrace
Cromartie High school's name.
"Punk Out" One of the terms used by delinquents... maybe...
I'll make it so that I punked out all by myself.
Why do you always take the role of the fall guy?
You're actually pretty tough, Mechazawa,
but if you act like that, everyone
will think you're a wimp.
You're such a good guy!
Stop it! You're embarrassing me.
They depend on him!
What?
Idiot!
How many times have I told you not to
do things that are bad for your health?
Sorry, Mechazawa...
I couldn't control myself any longer.
Even then, you must control yourself!
I don't care what happens to you,
but who'll take care of your mother
if you're not around?!
I was wrong!
Mechazawa is more worried
about you than anyone else!
They're being so dramatic.
No doubts about it, Mechazawa's
the head of our class!
That's right.
We're no match for Mechazawa!
Don't...
He's oiling himself!
Hey, Mechazawa. There's a little
something I wanted to tell you.
What is it?
There's something that's been bugging me
since I saw you for the first time
after entering this school.
Is he finally gonna say it?
Everyone in this class is probably
thinking the same thing.
No, I think everyone in the society
notices it when they see you.
I even think that you possibly know about it too.
Or, I mean to say, don't you realize it yourself?
Just be frank. What do you want to say?
No... Well... It's kinda hard to say...
I think of you as my own family.
I won't mind, no matter what you tell me.
I see.
Then we'll tell it to you straight.
All right! Just go ahead and say it. Please!
Well, then I'll tell you, Mechazawa...
The second button on your
school uniform is missing.
What?
No kidding. I hadn't noticed at all.
That's not it!
It's been bugging me all this time.
Blade Runner's
High
Damn it! Not again!
What's the matter?
This CD player broke again.
If you take it to a repair shop,
it'll cost you big bucks.
I wonder if there's someone who can fix this?
Of course not, you idiot!
Our school is full of dumb-asses.
But there's usually someone in a class
who's good with machines.
Someone who's good with machines?
How about that guy?
Year 1
Class 5            Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
Hey, Mechazawa.
Can you fix this CD player?
I couldn't possibly!
I'm no good with machines.
No good with machines?
Mechazawa, can I talk to you a minute?
I've never been any good with machines.
I can't do this video setting,
no matter how much I try.
I'm asking you, can you just set up
the timer for the recording?
I said that's impossible!
I'm poor with machines.
That can't be right!
But why do you all ask me about
fixing machines or how to operate machines?
You asking why?
Well, you take good care of your friends...
Of course, I'd like to do
whatever you ask me to do.
I'm even ready to risk my life for you guys!
But I can't do machines, no matter what.
That can't be right!
Somehow we felt that you
were good with machines.
That's simply prejudice, isn't it?!
For example, people said stuff like
"women are not good at machines" a while back,
but that's nothing but simple prejudice.
Now cell phones and e-mails are trendy,
and women handle them more
beautifully than men, right?
I see...
At least they're a few dozen
times smarter than we are.
In other words, it wouldn't be good to decide
on things according only to such prejudices.
He's oiling himself again!
But I don't like a digitized world that's a result
of people depending too much on machines.
If there is no heart to heart communication
among people, in the end, I think it feels empty.
The way things are going,
we'll all be controlled by machines!
Is it possible that he's joking?
Hey, Mechazawa.
What is it?
There's one thing that's been bugging me
since I saw you for the first time.
What? Again?
Every time I see you, it bugs me so much lately
that I can't even sleep at night.
ls he finally going to say it?!
I'm pretty sure everyone else
is bothered by it too.
But it wasn't easy to tell you somehow.
Telling you this could possibly hurt your feelings.
Don't worry about it. Say it already.
That's right! Say it already!
Okay. Listen carefully,
since I'll say it only once.
Say it!
You've got a big face, haven't you?
I see!
Very close, but that's not it!
Lost in Cromartie
Shinichi Mechazawa (16)
You bastard! You've been doin'
whatever the hell you like!
Don't make light of Bass High!
This isn't good, Kamiyama!
Mechazawa's been captured!
We'll go save him right away, Kamiyama!
No, hold on, Hayashida.
We shouldn't stop them.
Why?!
I'm certain that they'll say it.
I see! Then it'd be better
to watch from here as usual?
He can take quite a beating.
If you're going to apologize, now is the time!
You can't take me out with those little attacks.
What was that, jerk?!
Hey, Kamiyama, I just had a very scary thought.
What is it, Hayashida?
Could it be that we're the only ones
who wonder about Mechazawa?
What do you mean?
Doesn't everyone, except us, think Mechazawa
is an ordinary delinquent high school student?
But no matter how you see him, he doesn't look
like an ordinary delinquent high school student.
Or rather, he doesn't even
look like a normal human.
We'll fudgin' kill you!
We're gonna pay you back for
what you've done to us, Mechazawa!
Does that possibly mean that there is
something wrong with our senses?
Exactly! Mechazawa is just an ordinary
16 year old high school student!
Are you finished already?
This dumb-ass has got
himself a pretty big mouth!
Come to think of it, I now feel
that there are people like that.
You see? There should be guys like him if we
hang around the Shibuya Center Shopping Area.
Hey, that's not good. Don't do it!
Shut up! I've snapped!
Drum Can
What?
No, he really isn't a human!
What's going on?
My Strawberry Short blade got broken...
What?! You said your
Strawberry Short blade got broken?!
All this time, we all thought that Mechazawa
was an ordinary high school student.
But it could be that he's...
Good, there's a normal guy here! Say it already!
A high school student whose body
is abnormally hard?
I see! His body is unreasonably hard, isn't it?
Are you saying that on purpose?
Are there none among you
brave enough to fight me one-on-one?
What did you say?!
So in the end, you punks
can't even fight without your buddies.
Well, maybe it's too much to ask
from you petty gangsters.
And he's talking cool as usual.
He's right.
Oh, Yokoyama!
It may be true that there aren't
any sort of rules for fighting,
but why don't you at least follow
the basic principles of fighting?
But...
What's that? Don't you think it's disgraceful?!
Five or six people ganging up on one guy,
tying him up, and beating him up...
No, it's just us three.
What about your pride as students of Bass High?
Look at this guy! You did too much.
What?!
All right! This man will say it!
Don't tell me... he's... ro... ro... ro...
Almost there! Robo!
"Roly-poly" Mechazawa,
my classmate from sixth grade!
What? Are you Yocchan, by any chance?
What?! No way!
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
I feel like the "Sakigake!! Cromartie High
School" anime has been airing for a long time.
What? This was only the second episode?
The next one is the third episode.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
To be
continued
It'll be continued!
To be continued.