Warning
When you are watching television
please have the room
brightly lit and be
careful not to get too
close to the screen.
Dear Viewers Sitting in Front of the Television,
the guys that appear in this anime are delinquents.
So, please do not imitate what you see in this anime.
Do not imitate! Or this will happen!
CHARGE!!
CRO
MAR
TIE
Charge!! Cromartie High School
僕が泣いているのは とても悔しいからです
Boku ga naite iru no wa totemo kuyashii kara desu
The reason I am crying is
because I am very frustrated
人の尊さやさしさ 踏みにじられそうで
Hito no toutosa yasashisa fuminijiraresou de
I feel as though the nobility and
kindness of man is being trampled
力を示す者達は
Chikara o shimesu mono tachi
Those who show their strength lose their grace
しなやかさを失って
Shinayakasa o ushinatte
ウソまみれドロまみれ じれったい風景でしょう
Uso-mamire doro-mamire jirettai fuukei desho
Covered in dirt and lies, isn't it a vexing sight?
より強くしたたかに タフな生き方をしましょう
Yori tsuyoku shitataka ni tafu na ikikata o shimashou
Let's live more strongly, fiercely, and tougher
まっすぐ歩きましょう
Massugu arukimasho
Let's walk straight
風は向かい風
Kaze wa mukai kaze
The wind is against us
どけ どけ どけ 後ろめたい奴はどけ
Doke doke doke ushirometai yatsu wa doke
Move, move, move, those with
a guilty conscience, move aside
有象無象の町に 灯りをともせ
Uzoumuzou no machi ni akari o tomose
Light up the town of riffraff
どけ そこ どけ 真実のお通りだ
Doke soko doke shinjitsu no otouri da
Move, make way, truth is coming through
正義の時代がくるさ
Seigi no jidai ga kuru sa
The era of justice will come
希望の歌もあるさ
Kibou no uta mo aru sa
There are songs of hope too
僕の命この世に 捧げてしまっていいさ
Boku no inochi kono yo ni sasagete-shimatte ii sa
I would happily sacrifice my life for this world
First
My name is Yutaka Takenouchi and
I'm the boss of Year 1 at Cro-High.
A lot of things happened
and I finally came back to Japan
after wandering around in the US.
But of all days,
why the hell does it have to be on
the day of another school trip?
↙Here
I feel sick!
Takenouchi's back at last...
Guys, don't look behind you!
He's got that really scary look on his face.
Hey, aren't there two Takenouchis?
Damn! And here I was all relieved
that he got switched with a fake!
What?! You knew it?
What? He was a fake?
Oh, no! It's come up to my throat.
Now that it's come to this,
the only thing I can do is erase
the images of "nauseating" and "throwing up"
from my head with strength of mind!
I need resolve! Concentrate.
Forget it, forget it, forget it, forget it.
Okay! I've forgotten it!
I've just completely erased
the words "throwing up" from my head!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not good with transportation, so...
There's trouble! Takenouchi's
going on a rampage!
Someone, stop him!
My name is Takeshi Hokuto.
I participated in a school trip as a step towards
reigning over the pig-like masses in the future...
But I carelessly got on the wrong train.
Here
Mr. Hokuto, I went and bought some tea for you.
Moreover, I'm with this fool.
Just because I took a wild guess
and got on this train...
Look. If there's something you
don't know, ask people first!
That's a basic thing any person should know!
Well, that's fine.
Since no one is going to bother us here,
I can work in peace on a plan for controlling Cromartie.
That's right!
While those idiots are just excited about the trip, we're discussing the conquest of this nation.
It's an incredibly pleasant feeling, isn't it?
They're talking about pretty pathetic stuff.
Maeda, who also got on the wrong train.
I wish they'd go someplace else.
Cheers!
Congratulations on our school trip!
They're so annoying!
Normally I'd fudgin' kill them all,
but if I move carelessly, I'll throw up.
Oh? I came up with a haiku!
On an aimless trip - Some get wasted by drinking Riding gets me wasted
On an aimless trip
Some get wasted by drinking
Riding gets me wasted.
On an aimless trip - Some get wasted by drinking - Riding gets me wasted
This is bad! I'm getting sicker and sicker, thinking about pointless things.
You gotta have non-alcoholic when taking a trip!
But I can't throw up. I have to bear it now!
To people who get motion sickness,
the act of throwing up means losing!
Okay, I've lost.
Taking care of these fools can wait.
Burp!
Blerp!
Restroom
I gotta throw up soon.
I feel like I'm gonna pass out...
Restroom
I'm in here.
That voice is Kamiyama's!
I thought I hadn't seen him around,
but I didn't realize he was
setting a trap like this...
He's good...
Now you're on my list of people to fudgin' kill!
So you found me...
Who are you, again?
I'm Maeda!
That's right, you're Maeda.
The restroom should be available by now.
I gotta pee!
I knew I drank too many
non-alcoholic beverages.
What the hell are you guys doing?!
Go to the other restroom!
Well, the other restroom is out of order,
so everyone came to this one,
but Kamiyama's still in there.
I'm still in here.
You're still in there?!
Phew, I feel refreshed.
Oh? What are you all doing?
Get out of the way!
I'm going first!
Shut up, small fry!
I'll go first so you all wait there!
What'd you say?! We were
waiting in line before you.
Please hold on a second.
What the hell's with you?
All of you lack calmness right now.
In that sense, since I feel refreshed,
I can judge matters very calmly and neutrally.
Won't you please allow me
to manage the situation here?
It's certainly possible that it would
all come out in one burst if I fight here.
It'd be safer to follow what
Kamiyama says for the time being...
No matter what we say,
Takenouchi is the strongest fighter.
If we have to fight one-on-one, it's possible
that it would all come out in one burst.
I'll follow what Kamiyama says for now.
Okay!
I'll leave it to you.
Right!
Hit
Kogawa | Badass A | Badass B |Takenouchi |
Hokuto's lackey | Hokuto | Kamiyama | Maeda |
Hayashida | Masked Takenouchi | Freddie | Gorilla
To be fair, we'll draw lots.
Hit
Did everyone write their name in?
Restroom
Well, then, I'll check it now.
I also don't know which one will hit,
so it is completely fair.
We got it! Do it already!
It's me.
Why are you going in again?
Hello, I'm Makiko Tanaka.
Correction, I'm Noboru Yamaguchi.
Destrade High School, Year 1 Boss
Noboru Yamaguchi (16)
I'm heading to Kyoto today
because I'm invited to a relative's wedding.
Of course, there's only one goal
that I'd like to achieve,
which is cracking all my relatives up
with my stand-up comedy.
May I have your attention, please.
Is there a doctor among the passengers?
If there is, please come to the
second car immediately.
If this was a comedy skit,
after this, they'd say "is there a
conductor among the passengers?"
and then there'd be the snappy
comeback of "that's dangerous!"
This is a conventional TV comedy pattern.
May I have your attention, please.
Is there a sumo wrestler among the passengers?
If there is, please come to the
second car immediately.
I've never heard of a sumo wrestler's version...
But a first-class comedian like myself
wouldn't be surprised by
something of this level.
Rather, I'd point out its faults
if it was a comedy script.
Is there a green grocer among the passengers?
A doctor, a sumo wrestler, and a green grocer...
What's the connection among those three?
Well, anyway, the second car is
in THAT kind of situation, huh?
Okay, I see, I see...
There's no way THAT kind of situation happens!
Snappy comeback
Geez, just because she's an amateur,
doesn't mean she can say anything she wants!
Heave-ho!
Freddie's horse is on the rampage!
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Aren't there more sumo wrestlers?
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Here, I'll give him some carrots, so calm down!
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Sumo
wrestlers
Green
grocer
Good luck, sumo wrestlers!
I guess I'm still too normal.
Dear Mother,
things finally regained composure on the train,
and it has become like a school trip.
But now a big problem has occurred.
The train will soon arrive in Shin-Osaka.
We passed Kyoto long ago.
Shin-Osaka Station.
I should never have said such a thing...
How long will it be before we get to Kyoto?
You don't know something as
obvious as that? I'm speechless!
Shut up!
We'll take a nap so wake us up
when we get to Kyoto.
Leave it to me!
Oh, no...
It's my fault because I was sleeping carelessly.
Everyone, please wake up!
Huh? What the hell is it?
To tell you the truth, this train has
come all the way to Osaka.
Wh-What?!
It's still Osaka, you said?
Huh?
Are you stupid? The station we're
gonna get off at is Kyoto, right?
Can't you even tell the difference
between Osaka and Kyoto?!
Oh, no.
They don't even understand the basics...
These guys are off the scale.
Everyone, please listen.
I'd like us to study about Japan today.
What?!
Kyoto
Osaka
Tokyo
This is Tokyo where everyone lives.
This is Kyoto.
And there's Osaka ahead of that.
In other words, Kyoto is
between Tokyo and Osaka.
Kamiyama,
using a map made it easy
to understand and we appreciate it.
But we're not that stupid.
Right.
In short, we haven't gotten to Kyoto yet, right?
What? Uh, yes, that's right.
The train will soon arrive in Hakata, the last stop.
To hell with the explanation at this point!
Everyone, please listen carefully!
This train's not going to Kyoto!
What?!
Even if we stay on this train longer,
it is absolutely impossible for us to get to Kyoto!
What did you say? Is that true?
Which means...
Yes...
We have to change trains, huh?
Geez, Kyoto's far away.
Hakata
Are we gonna switch to an express train next?
How can I explain it to them?
Dear Mother,
we are riding on a bullet train again.
More importantly, I don't know where
this bullet train is heading.
Or I should say, I don't even know
if this is a bullet train anymore.
The Hokuto Corps joined
the trip at some point.
I heard that there's this incredible thing
called "The Golden Pavilion" in Kyoto.
The Golden Pavilion?
Is that like the lottery?
Yeah... probably...
What?!
Hey, hey, seriously?!
I think the winner gets gold coins.
That's why it's called "The Golden Pavilion."
S-So are you saying that at "The Silver Pavilion"...
Yes, you can get silver coins!
Wow!
That's incredible!
And do they let delinquents
like us play that lottery too?
I don't know about that.
Society really is cold.
Enough of that conversation.
It makes me dizzy just listening.
Sorry, but we'll be arriving soon.
What?! We're already arriving?
We've got no choice, so we'll get off, huh?
Tokyo
We finally got here!
The school trip was fun!
Tokyo
So, this was a train bringing us back home?
Journey
of the Heart
Well, the trip was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah, it was...
Well, there wasn't anything
especially memorable to me, though.
Is it really okay like that?
What?!
Could it be that we didn't go to Kyoto?
Don't say that!
No, let's make it clear!
We're always like that.
We dodge issues when they inconvenience us.
Isn't that why people laugh at us?
Don't blame yourself any longer, Hayashida.
Kamiyama...
The act of taking a trip
is something that stays only in the
hearts of the people who took the trip.
Even if a person took pictures of the scenery,
if it didn't stay in his heart,
it's the same as if he didn't go.
I see...
Please try remembering, carefully,
the memories that stayed in your heart.
Thanks. We're the ones who were thoughtless.
Now we can tell if we went
on a trip or not with confidence.
So you understand...
As we thought, we didn't go.
Right?
I wonder if we get our deposit back...
Next
Episode
Dear Mother,
Sakigake!! Cromartie High School.
Mr. Masao working
For this anime, I want it to be put
not only in anime section,
but also in artist section.
Sakigake!!
Cromartie High School
Tokyo and Kyoto are about three hours apart
I'm Takenouchi.
I'm Takenouchi too.
I love transportation!