The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
June 5th, 1942.
In the Battle of Midway,
the Japanese side suffered a devastating defeat.
The Japanese losses
were the four aircraft carriers - Kaga, Akagi,
Soryu, and Hiryu, as well as one heavy cruiser.
And consequently, 322 aircraft,
as well as 3,500 personnel.
On the other hand, the US losses
were 150 aircraft and 300 personnel.
But let's not forget -
one essential aircraft carrier, Yorktown
also took a serious beating.
Yorktown absorbed two consecutive Japanese attacks,
which wrecked her engine and caused a serious list to port.
Commanded by Captain Tanabe, submarine I-168
had to put Yorktown out of her misery.
For five hours after receiving the order,
I-168 continued to diligently scout the area
150 nautical miles northeast of Midway.
Midway Atoll
However, stranded in this vast ocean,
will they really cross ways with their enemy?
Ships at the time were not yet equipped with radar.
So the only things they could rely on
were nautical charts, binoculars, and faith.
Episode 12
Submarine I-168
One black dot! Looks like a carrier!
Carrier-like vessel!
Captain, the reconnaissance plane report
also confirms this.
Halt both engines. Prepare to dive!
Halt both engines. Prepare to dive.
Emergency dive.
The sea is perfectly calm.
Captain. The periscope is at risk of getting spotted.
Still, we're lucky that we found the enemy
to the east of us.
The heavens are on our side.
That's not the reason, Chief Navigator.
It's thanks to your calculation being correct.
Time until contact?
Sir. We'll catch up with them in two hours.
Examine the torpedoes once more.
At that time, the torpedoes used in the Japanese Navy
were running on compressed oxygen.
Max speed is 40 knots.
Effective range is 4000 meters.
Payload, or in other words,
the amount of explosive gunpowder it contains, is 500 kg.
Such torpedoes boast an impressive record
of being the most accurate in the world.
Then again, the submarine itself
also features a number of world-class characteristics,
starting with a high surface speed.
Alongside the German U-boats, its excellent performance
inspired horror in all the other countries.
How is it?
Captain, the weather is perfect. It makes the fierce battle
that took place look like a distant dream.
Not the weather, the engine.
Sir, no updates since the previous report.
Busted, after all?
Still, we must make it back to Hawaii, at any cost.
We can't afford dawdling around here.
Sir! Our destroyers are at it right now.
Back at home, our dockyards
are churning out carriers with all their might.
But for the time being, our only remaining two carriers -
Enterprise and Hornet must protect the Pacific at any cost.
To that end, I want Yorktown
to return to the front line as soon as possible.
We're lucky the sea is calm now.
It's our chance to withdraw.
Captain, the wind has picked up.
The wind has picked up.
That's it! The heavens are on our side.
Lower the periscope.
Lower the transmitter.
We're finally doing it.
Better err on the side of caution!
The enemy is on high alert.
Tell everyone to be quiet inside the ship.
Chief Navigator, it doesn't quite fit your plot.
Perhaps, the enemy is being swept by the wind?
No, the enemy is on the move.
We've been shadowing the enemy for a while.
It is my fault.
No, it's nobody's fault.
The scope of your navigational genius doesn't matter
in a place like this, without a single point of reference.
Getting any closer to them
or raising the periscope is dangerous.
Yorktown's propellers don't turn,
so it’s impossible to track her sound.
Aren't the enemy destroyers making enough sound?
You want to track the sound of a destroyer?
We'll pass under the destroyer.
But we can't track it with just one.
Once we pass under a destroyer on the other side,
we'll know for sure the enemy is close enough.
That's way too...
Bold, sir!
We'll be attacking and retreating blindfolded.
let's do it. Depth - 45!
Captain.
Are we good?
A two-hour dive in complete darkness...
Depth - 18. Raise the periscope.
Perfectly on the mark. We surfaced
to the enemy's starboard. Thank you, Chief Navigator.
Still, 500 meters is too short a distance.
Increase the distance to between 800 and 1000.
Captain!
The secret to a blind strike is in the distance.
Huh? What's that...
All the ships stopped?
Yes. Seven destroyers at once.
That's it! We've been discovered!
Let's disengage!
What time is it?
Sir! 12:37.
It's lunch time. They're having a lunch.
All the Americans at once went on a siesta.
The enemy is listening!
Prepare to launch a torpedo!
All tubes ready for launch!
Get ready!
Fire!
Depth - 70! Quick!
37 seconds, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44...
We did it!
30 minutes have passed.
The enemy destroyer started moving,
but not towards us.
Enemy destroyers right next to us. Multiple ships!
Enemy vessel passing directly above.
Enemy fired two depth charges!
Full to starboard!
Enemy depth charges - 54 explosions, 55.
Engage emergency light!
Both the torpedo rooms are flooded!
Stern wheelhouse is flooded!
Flooding in the engine room!
Pump room is fool of seawater!
Steering inoperable!
Both rudders and dive planes are busted!
Batteries are damaged!
Gas is leaking!
20 people in the aft, move forward!
Captain! The depth has passed 100 m.
The ship builder's limit is 75 m.
Trust in Japanese shipbuilding technology!
20 people move from bow to stern!
Pumping station, drain one ton of water!
Put on your gas masks, you hear?
Engage the working batteries!
Roger!
Head Engineer, how long will our batteries last us?
About 2 hours.
Senior Officer, what's our remaining air?
40 kilograms.
Good. If we bear with it for two more hours, the sun will set.
The enemy will also run out of depth charges.
Captain, watch where you step.
It was done in by gas
Oh, we had a mouse with us?
That's a good omen.
You know I-70?
The one sunk during the Hawaiian operation?
When I-70 was departing for the battle, the mice
were fleeing it in droves until none was left on board.
And then, I-70 didn't return home.
I heard that rumor too.
As you can see, our ship
has not been deserted by the mice.
We'll definitely make it.
We'll return safely to Japan.
Ship Surgeon,
don't let this mouse die in the battle!
Sir! It will be my responsibility to nurse it back to good health.
Don't laugh. We're tight on air.
I-168 was out of power.
Not only did the engine stop,
but the stabilizers were also out of service.
When that happens, the air and seawater
in the ballast tanks, surrounding the submarine
begin to move on their own.
As a result of that, the submarine either surfaces sharply,
or sinks, driven by inertia.
However, there are enemies waiting on the surface.
And they won't survive
the 4000 meter journey to the seabed either.
I-168 managed to regain her balance somehow
and tried to bide her time.
The battle between gravity and buoyancy continues.
Eventually, this bitter experience I-186 has been through would spur the Japanese Navy
to remodel their submarine batteries from the ground up for to make them shock-resistant.
The ship is climbing!
All personnel move forward!
Is our crew balancing useless?
Captain. Please order the destruction of the secret codes.
Captain, should we prepare the torpedoes
for a suicide attack?
We're climbing!
Captain, I'm sorry.
We can't stop the ascent.
How long has it been
since the depth charges stopped?
40 minutes, sir.
Good!
Hurry up and prepare to fight back!
Okay...
We'll fight with everything we got.
Let's give it to 'em!
Hurry to your positions!
Enemy warships. Three destroyers!
15,000 meters. Moving away from us.
They haven't noticed us. But that's only because
the sun sets this way. Soon, they'll spot us.
Hurry up to replenish the air and fix the batteries!
Smoke!
Alright, we'll hide in the smoke!
The enemy turned back!
Hey, have you ever seen our captain angry?
Lady Luck favors men like him.
Don't worry!
How much air do we have in store?
About 70 kilograms.
Enemy approaching, 5000 meters.
Make more smoke!
Continue restoring the power!
The motor is operational! We can move!
We rushed to this battle.
Now, it's time to cut and run!
Enemy destroyers are no longer audible.
What is it?
This is for the captain.
All our enlisted men got together, and well...
Captain.
We wanted to thank you in some way at least.
But it turned out nobody could find any words,
so we settled on bringing you this.
Thank you.
Captain, you don't want to drink?
No, I'll drink it downstairs, together with everyone.
You haven't eaten anything
since last night either, Captain.
Really? I haven't had a single meal?
The practices are paying off.
Chief Navigator, isn't it beautiful?
We're taking a night trip.
This submarine captain retained
his mild-mannered personality
and managed to galvanize his subordinates
to work together towards accomplishing their goals.
Even at times of crisis, he remained composed
and cool-headed. And on top of that, daring.
These smart decisions,
and, particularly, his sound judgment in an extreme situation earned him the trust of the crew.
That wouldn't have been possible without his composure.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
In the aftermath of the Battle of Midway,
the U.S. Navy launched a full-scale counterattack.
They conquered the Japanese military bases
at Tulagi and Guadalcanal.
In response, the Japanese army
takes advantage of the darkness
and raids the enemy camp by night.
However, just one decision,
deeply rooted in the traditions of the Japanese Navy
leads to an unexpected mistake.
Look forward to next week's decision:
First Battle of the Solomon Islands.
Episode 13
First Battle of the Solomon Islands
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
History Asian
Moozzi2