The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Solomon Islands
Bismarck Archipelago
Rabaul
New Guinea
Bougainville
New Britain
New Ireland
Solomon Sea
Guadalcanal
Isabel
New Georgia
April 1943.
The Japanese garrisons were mounting a fierce resistance to the US Army that had already recaptured Guadalcanal
and was now steadily advancing along the Solomon Islands.
Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet
Admiral Yamamoto lsoroku
flew over from the Truk Island to the front line base
on Rabaul for an in-person inspection.
Attention!
Salute!
There, what did I tell you?
A Japanese transmission!
The Military Intelligence Service, incorporated
into the United States Pacific Fleet Headquarters in Hawaii,
was holed up in a top secret basement,
only accessible to the cryptanalysis staff.
All the Japanese Navy transmissions, intercepted
in various areas of the Southern Pacific, gather here.
This electric decoding machine was designed and developed by the US' leading cryptanalyst, Major Thomas Dyer.
It has been enhanced to the point where it could effortlessly decipher the Japanese Navy's encrypted transmissions.
monisaa monyo nsachiichii haka moniraha no sude no suhato bunsai da suma rufu gari
Hey, take a look at this.
What's the meaning of this?
It doesn't look like a Japanese sentence.
I wonder if the machine broke.
Look at this, sir.
I can't understand it.
Call Major Dyer here at once. It's urgent!
Episode 18
Operation Vengeance
Major Dyer.
The machine didn't break.
The Japanese Navy changed their cypher.
Did they replace it entirely?
I don't know.
But if they really did,
this machine is no longer of any use to us.
Then we need to manufacture a new decoder, don't we?
How long do you think it will take?
It usually takes about half a year.
However, the cypher isn't necessarily
changed entirely every time.
At any rate, start by cracking this cypher.
Roger!
Listen, we need to decipher this, whatever it takes.
Work around the clock! 24/7 until we crack it!
Roger!
If a war breaks out with the US and the UK, how far can our fleet take us before it's stopped in its tracks?
I'm a soldier.
I'll keep going for as long as you order me.
For the first half a year or a maybe a year,
we'll have a free rein, I believe.
However, I cannot promise anything
beyond that time frame.
Just a dream?
The one year time frame I gave to our fleet
has run out long ago.
Who's there?!
My apologies, sir!
I had a bad dream and so I woke up.
You don't mind me walking to the beach?
For sure! I'll accompany you.
Admiral, use this.
No,
I like it better this way.
You'd never think that a war rages on this ocean.
Have you been stationed somewhere else before Rabaul?
Yes. I was transferred from Bougainville
three months ago.
Oh? So you've been to the front line?
How is it looking over there?
Sir. The Bougainville garrison
is woefully undermanned.
Are you finding Rabaul that much better?
Yes.
Thanks to coming to Rabaul, I got to meet
the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet in person.
At ease.
Sir.
Are you really that happy to see me here in Rabaul?
Yes. You are the guardian deity of our Imperial Fleet.
Like a god.
You're exaggerating. I drink alcohol too. And I'm
fond of gambling. Where have you seen a god like that?
That's exactly why you are a God.
You're one of us. Like a god in human form!
Those fellows in Bougainville don't get to meet the God in person. That's the saddest part of it.
Bougainville, huh?
Bougainville.
Hey, how does it feel to be carrying God?
Sir. I feel like I'm atoning for my sins. I'm so happy.
I got it!
I solved it!
We no longer need to work the midnight oil!
We broke the cypher!
The Japanese Navy didn't change the cypher,
only slightly altered the random numbers table.
Just input that change into the machine
and it'll be good to go!
Then, we can still use that decoding machine?
Certainly!
You're already in Rabaul.
Might as well stop by at Bougainville.
Bougainville is another 500 km from here. It's dangerous.
For the moment, we still retain
air superiority over this area.
I'll be flying with an escort, so it's fine.
Still, our air superiority is contested heavily.
An enemy plane may appear when you least expect.
Pardon me chiming in,
but I also believe that the Supreme Commander
has no business leaving the safe area.
The Imperial Fleet may come under attack
at that exact moment when you're away.
Logically, your arguments are irrefutable.
But thing is, I want to go there.
What's the good of me coming
all the way to Rabaul just to turn back at once?
For our soldiers, defending various small islands all across the Pacific...
"Hey, Yamamoto is here. Get yourself together..." There's nothing much I can do for them, except come there myself.
"If even Yamamoto himself showed up,
I guess this front line of ours ain't so scary, after all."
That's what I want to instill in them.
Admiral, I submit to your decision.
Nice. Come out, come out!
W-We've an emergency!
This is big news!
Put me through to Commander Layton. It's urgent!
Commander Layton here!
Could Yamamoto really be so careless
as to slip up so foolishly?
It's too good to be true.
It has to be a trap of sorts.
Listen here, you bastards!
You blockheads!
Who was smart enough to type this telegram?!
Did someone really think it's a good idea
to radio the admiral's itinerary in detail?!
It's like sending the enemy an invitation to join him!
Inform Admiral Yamamoto
that I flew out of Bougainville to meet him!
Admiral. As long as I oversee the defense of Bougainville,
it's absolutely impregnable!
Please cancel your visit.
I'm not going there
because I don't trust you with the defense of it.
I understand, sir. Still, why did you have to radio out
a precise itinerary of your inspection tour?
What if US Intelligence intercepts this transmission?
They may have broken our cyphers.
Or they may have not.
Usually, it takes them a while to do it.
I can't afford worrying about every little thing,
losing this great joy in the process.
Secretary Knox, do you believe
the contents of this Japanese telegram?
The honor of making this judgment belongs
to the US Pacific Fleet Commander-in-Chief Admiral Nimitz.
Come in.
Top secret telegram from Dutch Harbor in Alaska.
Let's see.
"As arranged previously, on April 18th, the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet Yamamoto
will visit Ballalae, Shortland, and Buin
with a front line inspection.
6 a.m." - This must be in standard Japanese time.
"Riding the Navy Type 1 attack bomber
and with an escort of 6 Zero fighters, take off from Rabaul.
8 a.m. - Arrive at Bougainville."
It mirrors exactly the contents
of the telegram received by Hawaii.
So they caught this encrypted transmission in Alaska as well...
Now, what is their game,
sending it over such a strong frequency?
Could it be a trap?
No, merely the product of their excessive confidence
in our country being unable to crack their cyphers.
We've been given some extremely complicated homework.
You already had your chance to look at the data we have.
Now ask your questions.
Mr. Yamamoto's escorts may be few,
but there are also Zeros stationed on Bougainville.
Our squadron only has the Lockheed P-38s.
How are we to get close to Yamamoto,
while staying clear of Bougainville?
Answer: certainly, Bougainville has some Zeros stationed on it.
Therefore, you'll attack Mr. Yamamoto
before he touches down in Bougainville.
Major Mitchell, it's time to explain your plan
for the remaining part.
If we're to tackle this homework,
here's the solution I came up with.
So we already have the answer we need to arrive at.
The target is Bougainville,
about 600 km from our base.
First problem is "how do we fly there
without the enemy spotting us?"
The answer is, we'll use sea skimming to get there.
Should the key objective Yamamoto change the course of his flight, wouldn't we miss him in this vast Pacific Ocean?
Exactly. That is the most worrisome point.
The distance from here to Bougainville is 600 km.
But it's only 500 km from Rabaul to Bougainville
for Mr. Yamamoto.
A 100 km difference.
There's only one point in the Southern Pacific
where these two lines would most likely collide.
So the next problem is how to find that point.
And what's your answer?
The only one possible.
Take off one hour before Mr. Yamamoto
and ambush him on the way.
Yamamoto is a punctual man
who always adheres to his promises.
I wonder if he really is a man of his word.
The attack on Pearl Harbor was a sucker punch.
No, originally, he planned to launch that attack
after the war had been declared.
But at that same time, the staff at the Japanese embassy in Washington messed up and missed the deadline.
Yamamoto didn't know that
and attacked Pearl Harbor on the scheduled time.
Now, this is the final plan, so take notes.
Course 1 - 133 km.
Cardinal direction - 265 degrees.
Speed - 360 km/h. Flight time - 55 minutes.
Similarly, in the following...
Course 2. 141 km. Cardinal direction -
240 degrees. 27 minutes.
Course 3. 200 km. Cardinal direction -
305 degrees. Fight time 38 minutes.
If things go well, we'll be sure
to run into the enemy before 8 a.m. That's all.
They've done their homework remarkably well.
Still, Commander Layton,
even in World-War I, no enemy Commander-in-Chief had ever been disposed of in this manner.
Mr. President, sir, Yamamoto was the planner
behind the sneak attack on Pearl Harbor.
Don't let it deter you.
We're giving him his own medicine.
Please pass down a decision.
He'll fly in just 2 days.
It's regrettable that we have to do away
with a man like Yamamoto.
Admiral, let me board the first plane.
Don't forget that our navy's custom is to have the superior ranks fly the first plane. That would be me today.
Okay...
The first plane was carrying Admiral Yamamoto, Navy Surgeon General Takada, and Adjutant Fukuzaki.
While Chief of Staff Ugaki and Aviation Adviser Muroi
were both on board the second plane.
Among the Japanese aviators,
this Navy Type 1 attack bomber was known as "Cigar."
While the American pilots
either called it "Betty" or "Lighter."
It was designed to be extremely lightweight,
so as to extend its operational range.
Which in practice produced the serious drawback
of it being highly flammable when attacked.
Lost another one. 16 remain.
Well, whatever. The enemy may have his Yamato soul,
but we here also have our Yankee soul.
Speaking of which, it's almost about time
for our appointed meeting with the gentleman Yamamoto.
Admiral, 10 minutes until touchdown.
Okay. Good.
If so, Admiral, we should start getting ready to get off.
Getting ready, right.
When I meet these soldiers would laughing make a good first impression?
Or perhaps I should bear myself solemnly?
I wonder if we showed up a little too early.
They're here!
Since we found them, might as well use radio now.
Enemy plane spotted!
At 11 o'clock! Altitude 2000.
Thank you! Mitchell speaking. Engage with all aircraft.
Betty spotted. Lose the drop tanks!
Enemy aircraft!
No need to panic. Our base is nearby.
Shit!
Protect the Admiral!
Which one is carrying Yamamoto?
Whatever, I can just shoot down both!
Payback for Pearl Harbor!
Are you okay?
Pull up!
Hello, Betty.
Get this!
Ah! Admiral!
Admiral!
Admiral, it's our fault!
Please try to hang on.
Admiral!
The admiral's plane was shot down! It's falling!
Mitchell speaking.
To all aircraft, both Bettys are downed!
Main objective achieved.
Disengage and retreat, we're due some medals!
If only... If only I boarded the first plane instead...
When, in an ironic twist of fate,
the man who tried his utmost to avoid a war, had to personally take the reins of the fighting,
he stood his own and fought ferociously.
And he probably knew that his end
would come sooner than later.
Yamamoto lsoroku's death
was by no means a thoughtless one.
He believed that by dying
he would pave the way for what is to come next.
This tragic episode served to teach us that the way to win the war is to know your enemy really well.
Even to this day, the first one
to acquire the most accurate information
is most likely to pass down a triumphant decision.
The death of one man, Yamamoto Isoroku, would eventually
lead to the sun setting upon the whole Japanese Empire.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
November 1942.
To relieve the 30,000 soldiers,
left behind during the Battle of Guadalcanal,
the Japanese fleet, loaded with supplies and ammunition,
headed for Guadalcanal under the cover of darkness.
The American side nicknamed this relief transport fleet
"The Tokyo Express."
They started raiding it relentlessly.
Episode 19
Battle of Tassafaronga
Witness the next week's decision:
Battle of Tassafaronga.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, timing
Translation
Supplementary materials
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
History Asian
Moozzi2