The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let other see your tears
Flower blooms...
3:00 a.m. on December 8th, 1941.
Simultaneously with the outbreak of the Pacific war,
a coded cable arrived,
announcing the successful landing on the Malay Peninsula.
The addressee was Lieutenant-General Sakai,
commander of the 23rd Japanese Army.
At once he sent his men,
off to the border of the Kowloon Peninsula.
To his forces, numbering about 30,000 troops,
he ordered the start of the Hong Kong offensive.
Episode 6
The Fall of Hong Kong
In preparation for the seizure of Hong Kong,
the Japanese army had had gathered intelligence,
creating detailed plans
and making timely arrangements.
The enemy had prepared a line of fortifications
on Kowloon Peninsula:
from Shau Kei Wan to Golden Hill,
to Shing Mun Reservoir.
On this mountain ridge, to the south of the recess,
is the heavily fortified position, dubbed "Gin Drinkers Line."
Gin Drinkers Line, so peculiarly named after the soldiers'
tendency towards too much Gin,
is a well thought through
line of defensive fortifications.
The enemy commander, Major General Maltby,
anticipating the outbreak of the war,
bolstered the Gin Drinkers Line yesterday
with the fresh British 2nd Royal Scots Battalion.
Moreover, the 2nd and 14th Punjab Battalions from India,
with the 5th and 7th Rajput battalions, were redeployed as well.
It appears, the odds are decisively stacked on our side.
Let us fight the enemy fair and square
with time-proven tactics.
How many days will it take for the 1st artillery regiment to arrive in a position where they can shell the enemy?
They'll probably take care of it in a week.
You think they'll make it under a week?
They'll have to.
Good.
Set the deadline for breaking through
the Gin Drinkers Line to one week!
We'll center the shelling
on a mountain pass next to Golden Hill.
I would ask the artillery detachments
to target the middle of this area.
Let's hammer them at full might with our 24 cm howitzers.
If we break through in just one place, the rest of the line
would be exposed in the flanks and rear.
Until then, deploy the division's main force
to the east and west of Tai Mo Shan.
All at once,
they'll topple the Gin Drinkers Line.
Yes, the same tactics we used
in the Russo-Japanese War to seize Port Arthur.
Hong Kong is made up of two administrative subdivisions:
the Kowloon Peninsula, bordering
the Chinese mainland, and Hong Kong Island.
Facing them are the forces under Major General Maltby:
from Britain, India, and Canada
two battalions each, numbering a total of about 12,000 men.
The meticulous preparation paid off,
as when the Japanese finally applied the attack plan,
they met no resistance whatsoever
from the British defenders.
However, the British Army as well
still had an ace up their sleeve,
which is the defensive Gin Drinkers Line.
Only having thoroughly flattened the British positions with unrelenting shelling, ordering the infantry to advance -
such was the operational plan
the Japanese came up with.
With that prospect in mind,
the front line battalion commander
sent out a subordinate, the First Lieutenant,
on a reconnaissance mission,
in charge of the forward unit.
They were tasked with probing
the British positions in the highlands.
Lieutenant, there it is...
Yes. Artillery observation post.
Alright,
let's get a closer look.
Watch out!
Under a moonlight that bright,
the enemy will see you immediately.
Look, the heavens are on our side.
This lieutenant was an officer who had risen from the ranks.
His battle experience
made that possible in due time.
No one's manning it.
What could be the meaning of this?
Breaking through the Gin Drinkers Line starts
with this observation post's wipeout.
And that's something we can do.
Lieutenant, are you serious?
We've the element of surprise.
Don't go. It's reckless.
There are only 21 of us here. Besides...
"Besides" what? Spit it out.
Yes. You were tasked with a reconnaissance mission.
This is insubordination.
Drop it. We're just doing a bit of mole extermination.
However...
Only he, who remains at all times composed
is good at decision making.
Yes.
You enter the battle prepared for anything.
You take decisions without hesitating.
Fortune smiles to the daring ones,
so I don't think you are to blame.
I knew you'd understand.
Will you join me now?
Yes.
We'll make short work of it.
The shortest work, sir.
Gather!
Listen, I jump in first,
then you jump after and follow my footsteps.
Anybody outside our line is an enemy!
Thank you.
What's the Japanese troop count?
Probably 200-300, up to 400-500.
Our garrison is 100 men at best.
Ask the battalion commander for reinforcements at once!
Use the phone.
Okay!
Hello.
Hello!
Keep calm. No need to panic.
Battalion commander, sir!
We've an emergency!
What is it? Calm down.
Okay.
Our reconnaissance party clashed with the enemy.
A fierce firefight ensued.
Damn it.
Indeed. Things are not going according to plan.
I believe, they're after the glory of beating others to it.
What's done is done.
Order the 3rd Battalion to attack immediately,
with the 2nd Battalion covering them.
Commander, sir.
Doing so would upset
all the army's operational planning.
Scouts are not lambs for slaughter.
No, but still...
The division commander was rash to...
I take full responsibility.
It's an order.
They've no shred of military discipline!
Make sure to rebuke them all,
as soon as this recon party is back!
Roger!
An army must, at all times, base all its actions
on the prudent operational plan.
Arbitrary actions are damnable!
Alright, let's get in there.
Charge!
Commander-in-chief!
Reinforcements! Please send in reinforcements!
We're six feet under if you don't!
Just try and listen to this rumble!
Impossible. The Japanese engaged us here as well!
No time for a counterattack. Disengage and fall back!
You order us to fall back, and yet, all the retreat routes
are now in Japanese hands!
This is why I loath these mole fortifications!
Forward!
Division commander!
Look there.
They bagged the bastards.
Ridiculous!
Tide Cove
Shek Tau Wai
Kam Tin
Inlet Hill
Tai Mo Shan
Lin Fa Shan
Needle Hill
Buffalo Hill
Gin Drinkers Line
Tsing Yi Island
Kai Tak Airstrip
North Point
Nicholson Island
Port Area
We don't want the enemy to reoccupy fortifications
we secured with so much trouble,
so I asked the front line commander
to stay put for the time being.
At least until this key position
is duly secured.
If we leave it up to them, we can shove
our operational plans to where the sun doesn't shine!
Yes, in truth, we must give them an earful.
Insubordination is grave!
However, they made it possible for our army
to capture in a span of one night
what would have taken a week.
Why, then, do you suppose we're preparing
the battle plans for? For leisure?
By dismissing these scraps for glory,
our battle order sinks into chaos!
Can't you see the silver lining?
Going off-script can also pay off.
Besides, it took a great deal of weight
off my own shoulders.
Isn't that right, sir?
Well, at any rate, reprimanding this reconnaissance party
should be our first priority.
Regarding that,
if we examine our current situation,
they have indeed opened a large gap
in the enemy positions on Gin Drinkers Line.
All over the front line, the British troops
are reported to be slowly falling back.
In the wake of this, all the front line commanders
insist that we take advantage of it
by immediately resuming our advance,
and seizing as much land from the enemy as we can.
Sir.
What about you?
I commit to it.
Alright.
We shall bring forward
an emergency change of plans,
and launch an all-out attack along the entire front!
Let's redeploy our entire army to the Hong Kong Island.
Our new ally Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek
promised to attack the Japanese
from behind on the Kowloon Peninsula.
This option is favorable to a futile defense of peninsula
with more bloody battles.
Alright.
I'll order all the troops on the Kowloon Peninsula
to withdraw to Hong Kong island.
Tide Cove
Inlet Hill
Tai Mo Shan
Lin Fa Shan
Needle Hill
Buffalo Hill
Gin Drinkers Line
Tsing Yi Island
North Point
Nicholson Island
Port Area
The conquest of the Gin Drinkers Line,
which was initially believed to take a week or more,
was completed in just three days.
Kowloon Peninsula firmly under their control,
the Japanese troops
entered the continental part of Hong Kong unopposed.
At 9:05 a.m. on December 13th,
the Japanese military representatives
with some English women in tow,
landed on Hong Kong Island,
tasked with encouraging a capitulation.
However,
the British reply was
"Never".
With a single word, the commander
ruled out the surrender as a possibility.
The Japanese renewed their attack
with continuous raids.
The scale of the disaster
dwarfed anything seen before.
Then, on December 17th,
the Japanese army once again
put forward a surrender offer.
However...
The Governor-general of Hong Kong
as well as the Commander-in-Chief
rejected flatly any kind of negotiations
about surrender.
It is absolutely out of the question.
Moreover, I take this opportunity
to declare that we will no longer listen
to any proposition from the Japanese army,
pertaining to this matter.
A squall is likely to come soon.
The moonrise is late tonight.
At 9 o'clock tonight, commence the crossing.
As a matter of fact, my division,
includes a Los Angeles Olympic Games medalist
in breaststroke swimming, Lieutenant Koike Reizo.
We'll form a volunteer division with the Lieutenant as its core and have them swim across to distract the enemy.
We've no need for that.
In that thick black smoke, the British can't see us
rowing right past them even 50 meters away.
Besides, this rain renders the sea surface
impenetrable to the eye.
We'll repeat
what we did to conquer the Gin Drinkers Line.
Alright, make arrangements for a massive landing.
At 9 p.m., the Japanese army
started the crossing towards Hong Kong Island,
virtually unnoticed by the British.
Not even when the Japanese soldiers
closed to 90 meters away.
Second artillery observation post speaking.
Nothing out of the ordinary going on.
- such was the report, made during the landing.
The Japanese army landing was a complete success.
However,
the British troops counterattacked fiercely,
as their escape route was cut off.
The power plant, considered a vital position,
was defended by a hastily assembled volunteer unit, comprised of about 70 British and French businessmen,
living in Hong Kong.
All had previous combat experience, but still, the youngest
member of this formation was a 55 years old veteran.
Nevertheless, even after fully relieving
the Indian Rajput battalion of fighting,
this old mens' company managed
to hold onto the power plant for a whole day.
It's nothing like how it was during World War I.
They gave me this medal
for what I did in the Spanish Civil War.
The Indian Rajput Battalion is retreating in full!
And with their tails between their legs!
Let them! We will defend this place until death!
Keep it up! Chiang Kai-shek is already leading
his large army to our succor!
The Japanese army's back will be smashed!
However,
the promised allied army of Chiang Kai-shek,
whom they put their reliance upon, never came.
It marched in the distance, far beyond the front line,
west to east, just to disappeared again into the hinterland.
The British troops were plunged into despair.
Governor-General, after a long struggle, the reservoir
east of Mount Nicholson fell to the Japanese.
In want of fresh water and supplies,
the civilians are fleeing Hong Kong in rapid succession.
Prolonging the fight any further is impossible.
Resisting any further would only
open the way for more civilian deaths.
December 25th, time is 5:20 p.m.
The Governor-General of Hong Kong
and the overall commander of the British forces
Major General Maltby settled for surrender.
At the Peninsula Hotel on the mainland part of Kowloon,
they met with the Japanese army headquarters.
It was exactly on the day of Christmas.
And then, to flickering candlelights,
as though in the celebration of the holy night,
the British signed a capitulation.
The Governor-General of Hong Kong especially
took this defeat intensely.
Stop it!
Don't picture me!
Soon after, the Fall of Hong Kong,
which was believed to take four weeks at least,
was achieved in almost half the time.
A great victory achieved that promptly
was a sum of small details that the commander, leading his unit forward, must steadily keep in mind.
This one time, the young offensive mindset
of a junior commanding officer
availed him to cast off the shackles
of an overly cautious high command's strategy,
thus opening the way to victory.
When a subordinate's vigor speaks aloud,
can you adjust to the situation at hand
and fan that vigor further,
eventually spreading it across your entire organization?
The ability of a senior commander
to give such an overruling order is what victory hinges on.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
In order to ensure a surprise landing
on the Malay peninsula,
the Japanese set their sights on Britain's famed
unsinkable battleship Prince of Wales,
spotted patrolling off the coast of Malaya.
Aiming to live up to its prestige,
Prince of Wales stands proudly,
prepared to repel an attack from any direction.
In response to this, it's engulfed in unrelenting
swarms from the sky by the Japanese Mitsubishi G4M's.
Episode 7
High Seas Naval Battle for Malaya
Witness in the next "Decision":
High Seas Naval Battle for Malaya.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation by
Quality Checking by
Supplementary materials by
Video by
Perevodildo
Ziusudra and Paul Geromini
History Asian
Moozzi2