The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Episode 25
The Final Decision
On the morning of April 27th,
a trilateral joint declaration
from the UK, the US, and China was announced.
The Potsdam Declaration that Japan received last night.
Then, this morning, the head of the intelligence bureau
from Suzuki Kantaro's cabinet, Shimomura Hiroshi
was admiring the tenacity of a small bird, who never ceased
to forage for food even amidst these ravaged lands.
Good morning, sir.
Is that you, Oyadomari? Good morning.
Yes. Important news, sir.
Important news?
At 6 this morning, a tripartite declaration
by the US, UK and China arrived from San Francisco.
The US, UK, and China?
Are you sure it's not US, UK, and the Soviets?
It's US, UK, and China, sir. Confirmed.
And what's in it?
A demand for our unconditional surrender.
It has 13 points in it.
Most of it aligns with the previous Cairo Declaration.
That's true. What are your thoughts on it?
Not as an intelligence officer, but as an individual.
As an individual, I see it in the same light
as a military intelligence officer.
Oh?
We cannot accept it.
I wouldn't be so sure of that.
Sir?
Upon a closer look,
this declaration is very harsh
on our top brass militarists,
but it offers the common people
more civil liberties than they currently have.
It's just one big ploy.
They're calling for immediate surrender.
I'm inclined to see it as our chance.
Surrendering to the US, UK, and China?
Correct.
Among our military top brass, there's no one in sight
courageous enough to accept this demand for surrender.
They don't seem to understand
that we no longer have any other options.
Our military is stalwartly bellicose, and the cabinet
is just trying its best to pass the blame.
Meanwhile, our chances are dwindling.
No. It's not just about our chances.
It's about preserving countless civilian lives.
The United States also informed Japan's populace of that
by distributing leaflets along with bombs.
Military Police
Still, the cabinet decided to portray the declaration
as a plot to cause civilian unrest.
Later, they decided to shrug off the declaration for now,
presuming it to be an underhanded attempt by the US
to force Japan to capitulate hastily.
However, isn't this problem too well-known
to try and shrug off?
I believe, pretending we know nothing of this crucial issue in the morning newspapers will only arouse more suspicion.
If most of the ministers
also share this view, I shall respect it.
But if we were to acknowledge it,
I would only accept it in a decisively condemning light.
We can't afford a decline in morale.
A boost to the fighting spirit is what we need now!
But if we do that, our current efforts to negotiate a peace
through the Soviet diplomats will come to nothing.
What? You're still trying to negotiate a peace?
We can't hope for a reasonable peace
if we don't show them our willingness to fight back!
Notwithstanding the fact that the Soviet representative
also attended the Potsdam Conference,
the Japanese government was still hoping to conclude a conditional peace through the Soviet diplomats.
There were also talks about dispatching
Konoe Fumimaro to Moscow as a liaison.
The US intelligence department chief
Captain Harry Cunningham declared this:
"Japan's entire population
has been effectively put on the front lines.
Presently, there are no non-combatants in Japan.
It is now a battle of annihilating as many enemies as we can, men and women alike, in the shortest term possible."
While that's how they see it,
the people of Japan are still kept in the dark
about the actual situation.
I think it's time for us to let them know.
Should any of you have any reason to oppose that,
besides your personal disapproval,
I'd like you to let me know it openly.
It's the people who are bearing the main brunt.
Minister! What is that "bearing the brunt" bull?!
The people are ecstatic to die.
That's absurd!
Because you're just a civilian,
you've no notion of true patriotism!
I can by no means work under you! Excuse me!
We really are in trouble.
There's much more to our troubles than this.
If the mainland becomes a battlefield,
all elderly, children, and weak will be massacred.
"I won't be fussing over those
who may start burdening me in the future."
I heard one of our general say that.
What?
They intend to massacre their own people?
What are they even thinking?
Thus, innocent people were squeezed between a rock and a hard place, where both friend and foe wanted them dead.
And as if to follow through with that decision,
one more calamity would befall them.
At 8:15 a.m. on August 6th, 1945,
for the first time in human history,
an atomic sun dawned upon Hiroshima.
In an instant, 240,000 people
perished or were injured here.
But it did not end there, as on August 9th, around 11:00 a.m. a plutonium bomb was also dropped on Nagasaki.
Here, another 100,000 people
perished in an instant.
But what surprised the Japanese high command the most
was the sudden declaration of war by the Soviet Union,
whom they previously tried to get
to mediate peace between Japan and the Allies.
At 14:30 on August 9th,
the first of a series of cabinet meetings was held.
Once Foreign Minister Togo finished explaining his position,
Prime Minister Suzuki Kantaro stood up.
As could be inferred from Minister Togo's presentation,
these are truly desperate times now.
I would like everyone of you to put forward all the questions and opinions you have.
Our goal today is to determine our course of action
in regard to the trilateral declaration.
At present, no matter how much the three countries talk about the safely of the Imperial Family,
and what favorable conditions they offer,
unconditional surrender is unacceptable.
Of course, with the atomic bombings
and Soviet entry into the war,
if we look at it with a cool head,
we have no prospects of victory.
Still, if we want to preserve the honor of the Yamato people,
we should look for some opening while we keep fighting.
If we go on the warpath of seeking to win with our backs to the wall, we won't necessarily face utter destruction,
but instead, the situation
on the battlefield may turn to our favor.
The basis for the existence of that chance being...?
A decisive battle on the mainland!
I'm sure, that's where we'll get our chance!
It's where our army would prove its worth!
No, given the current realities of warfare, you can't do any fighting without mobilizing the entire nation's effort for it.
In war, you don't send the army and the navy
to fight each on their own.
Even before the atomic bombing and the Soviet entry into the war,
the material situation on the homefront was already desperate, not allowing for any continuation of the war.
In fact, if we look at our navy, it stands no chance
of scoring any victory on the US or the UK.
This is not the time to be particular about honor.
I think it's about time we left the sour grapes
and wishful thinking behind,
and switched to a discussion
from a realistic point of view.
Thus, the cabinet was split on those who advocated accepting the joint trilateral declaration,
like Foreign Minister Togo
or Minister of the Navy Yonai on one side,
and Minister of War Anami
with Minister of Munitions Toyoda in the opposition.
Going back and forth, the hot debate
was being fought until after 22:00.
However, even that was ultimately inconclusive.
So, what conclusion did the cabinet arrive at?
No, no conclusion was achieved yet.
By the way, chief,
what is your own stance on it?
Should we accept it?
Should we refuse?
As for myself...
No.
I may have my own thoughts on that matter.
But I'm also the cabinet's spokesman.
My duty is to only inform you
of the cabinet's collective opinion.
More importantly...
On my way here, I learned something by looking at the sago palm in the garden, adjoining the prime minister's residence.
Yeah. That big sago palm, right?
As expected, both the trees and the leaves
were burned to the ground in one of the air raids.
But when I looked at it today,
amidst those scorched trunks,
I noticed some new green shoots sprouting.
The Japanese people are the sago palm.
No matter what befalls them,
one day, new shoots will bloom.
We can't let the root rot set in!
They have to survive, in some form or another.
Yes. Yes, I'll go there at once.
What is it?
At 23:50, the supreme war committee would assemble.
Eh? This late?
Yes.
For a little longer,
I'll have to to keep watering those shoots.
Where, sir?
In the palace.
Palace? Which means, it's an Imperial Council?
Look, we have the sago palm here as well.
Thus, at 23:50 on August 9th,
an Imperial Council was convened, petitioning the Emperor
to pass a decision and issue an Imperial Decree.
The various ministers awaiting the supreme conference were a motley crew.
But their thoughts were universally directed
at the outcome of the Imperial Council.
Shimomura, may I ask something?
Has someone petitioned His Majesty
for an Imperial Decree like that ever before?
Never.
Up until now, even if it was called an Imperial Decree,
it was in fact just a summarized opinion
of His vassals that His Majesty would authorize.
Never before has His Majesty been forced
to make a decision Himself, like in the current case.
Things are truly grim for us.
Hmm. So I thought.
This is unprecedented.
Trying to rectify the chain of previous
bad decisions must be painful for Him.
Aren't stars beautiful?
When you visited the palace the other day,
what was it you told them?
About sago palms.
Oh? So it was you who launched that anecdote?
That time, I told them that no matter
what happens to the old leaves,
as long as the roots haven't withered,
new shoots will always sprout.
"No matter what happens to the old leaves?"
Thank you for waiting.
The Supreme War Council is now over.
A cabinet meeting will now be held in the conference room.
We will now voice our opinions, one by one.
Once that is done, an Imperial Decree will be issued.
The gist of what He said is,
"when we look at the actual state of the nation,
it is evident that prolonging the war any further
will not only lead to the destruction of Japan,
but would also knock humanity as a whole
back into the middle ages.
It's this time when one has to endure the unendurable, suffer the insufferable, and accept the Trilateral Declaration.
If that's the only way to end the war, then so be it."
Furthermore, His Majesty
expressed sympathy for soldiers
from the Army and Navy alike, alive or dead,
as well as to everyone else
who had somehow suffered from this war.
Thus, the decree was passed.
However, in some parts of the Army and Navy, the opposition was still vocal on the question of conditions,
under which the Trilateral Declaration would be accepted.
And so, on the 14th, another Imperial Council was convened, with all the ministers attending.
There, at last, it was decided
that they'd accept the unconditional surrender.
I apologize for the last time.
Is this the draft for an Imperial Edict?
Yes.
When the time comes to publish this decision,
I need to somehow get even the common people to understand it clearly, which is somewhat tricky.
And which medium do you plan to use to announce it?
Newspapers and radio.
I've arranged things with both.
You can leave everything to me.
There's a problem with that.
Did something happen?
A Jewel Voice Broadcast, right?
Yes.
I just learned that a portion of the officers
are trying to thwart it.
Oh? Thank you for letting me know.
Please take some countermeasures.
No countermeasure is needed.
His Majesty's life depends on this decree,
so I will also protect it with my life.
The other day, when I received
His Majesty's decree, I pondered deeply.
Because it's His final decision,
it's a matter of life and death.
So until the final judgment is passed,
there ought to be some turbulence along the way.
When your life is at stake, you tend to make decisions
that deviate from your true intentions.
I myself also contributed to that turbulence.
Yes, but everyone else came to think
they're doing it for the good of the nation.
However, there are more ways than one
to do something for the good of the nation.
Make no mistake, though -
this decision is for the supreme commander to make.
Is that to say, your current life-threatening assignment is to pass His Majesty's words to the people whatever it takes?
Yes.
At 10:00 a.m. on August 14th,
an unprecedented recording in Japanese history was made, the "Jewel Voice Broadcast."
Yabe,
is it correct that you and me
are the only ones who know that the recording was placed
in a safe in the Ministry of the Imperial Household?
Yes.
Someone might try to arrest us tonight.
Huh?
I won't tell them anything,
even if it will cost me my life.
I want you to keep silent too.
Certainly, sir.
Cabinet Minister Shimomura?
That is me.
Alright,
take him to the place.
Shimomura Hiroshi?
Come with me for a moment.
I brought Shimomura Hiroshi, sir!
Well done.
Are you the head of the intelligence bureau
Shimomura Hiroshi?
That is correct.
We have searched the car just now.
The Jewel Voice recording is not here.
Where did you hide it?
What do you gentlemen want that record for?
I want to bide our time for a couple days more.
We'll use that time to convince His Majesty
that the military can be trusted.
You think you can do it in just a couple of days?
That is for me to handle!
Just tell me where the recording is.
I can't tell you.
Then, want us to frisk you?
That was when minister Shimomura
was preparing to face
the tragic consequences of his decision.
But at the same time,
he thought of the mainland defense strategy
that Minister of War Anami bet his life on.
"Just because you bet your life on it,
doesn't mean your judgment is correct."
What would be the supreme commander's decision?
Stop it!
Dealing with Shimomura now wouldn't do us any good.
If he won't spill it, search inside the Ministry!
Okay!
Until our work here is done,
herd them all into that room.
Okay. Roger that.
They walked the NHK Director Yabe
through all the rooms in the Ministry,
pressing him to reveal the location of the recording.
But he kept pretending he doesn't know.
In addition, some of the rebellious officers
raided the NHK studios at dawn on the 15th,
desperately trying to get airtime for themselves, but to no avail.
They eventually returned to the Imperial Palace
and committed suicide.
We have resolved to pave the way, for a grand peace,
for all the generations to come by enduring the unendurable
and suffering what is insufferable.
Having been able to safeguard and maintain our sovereignty, we are always with you, our good and loyal subjects...
The other day, remember how I told you that the supreme commander's decision is a matter of life and death?
That's what I think too.
But now I believe that alone is not enough
to attach credibility to your judgment.
Everyone was betting his life on it.
Starting with His Majesty, to Anami, Yonai, and Togo.
However, why does everyone come to a different conclusion when putting his life on the line?
That difference is the cornerstone of our sovereignty.
The spirit of what we call "Japan."
Our country of Japan is really
all about the people remaining in it.
They haven't grasped this underlying idea.
Without a country, there can be no sovereignty, no nothing.
And the most important thing now
is to leave that country alone.
As long as this country lives,
Japan will surely blossom once again.
And it's up to us to observe those flowers closely.
However, in order to see them blossom,
we need to learn to step back.
Relinquishing your present for the sake of the future
is the one true decision.
And also
the most courageous one.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Thank you for making it through this series with us!
Editing, OCR & timings
Translation
Supplementary materials
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
History Asian
Moozzi2