"Star of the Giants"
omoikondara shiren no michi wo
If you have it in you, head down the road of trials.
yuku ga otoko no dokonjyou
And show them what men can do!
makka ni moeru oujya no shirushi
Burn bright like a true champion
kyojin no hoshi wo tsukamu made
until the Star of the Giants is in your hands!
chi no ase nagase
Go all out until you sweat blood!
namida wo fukuna
Don't wipe away your tears!
yuke yuke hyuuma
Go, go, Hyuuma!
donto yuke
Head to your future!
Shine on! Star of the Giants!
The Giants aren't budging an inch!
And standing front and center is Hoshi Hyuuma, who just isn't letting up!
But now, his magic ball, the Big League Ball 3, seems to be losing its power.
A perfect game is still possible!
Stop it, Hoshi!
You can't throw any more!
Your body won't take much more!
Strike! Batter out!
Come on, go for
the perfect game!
Just one more! One more and the
Giants will have a perfect game!
Just one... just one more...
But if the Giants want
their perfect game,
they'll have to get through the
Chuunichi Dragons' final pinch hitter.
None other than Ban Chuuta,
Hoshi Hyuuma's former best friend!
The star I've been
chasing this whole time,
the great Star of the Giants,
is shining before my very eyes.
And... and with
this left hand of mine...
With this left hand,
I'll make that star mine.
Listen up, Ban!
You've got this,
just swing the bat!
I made you hold that handstand to push you to your limits.
Surely you know that much!
I know Coach has a reason behind
this weird plan of his, but dammit...
My whole body hurts!
I can barely see straight!
Can I even hit that
pitch of his like this?
Play ball!
Hyuuma, your left arm... it's...
Let's finish this, Ban.
Here it comes!
Damn... my vision's going...
Strike!
There's one strike
from Big League Ball 3!
Just two more strikes to go!
Ban, keep your eyes forward!
That throw was weak!
This time for sure!
Dammit...
I... I can barely feel my hand...
Here comes another
Big League Ball 3!
Ball!
Hoshi is showing some fatigue in
this face-off against the final batter.
And he's thrown his third ball!
It's another Big League Ball 3!
And the ball's
way off its mark!
If Hoshi gets hurt, baseball
as we know it will be over.
I just... I just have to get to
the grounds as soon as I can!
1-2!
Damn... just holding the bat is enough to make me feel sick.
Dammit!
Come on, you've got this!
Just two more strikes!
Just two more!
Your body is falling apart
before my very eyes...
I'm... I'm...
No, I'm sure you've got
it much worse than me.
I hope this endless pain you're suffering through gets you a perfect game.
Please win, Hoshi.
Please win, I'm begging you!
Dammit!
That's another one.
Ball!
Ban, get a hold of yourself!
What's wrong, Hoshi?!
1-3!
Things have taken
quite a turn!
A perfect game is right under his nose, but Hoshi's starting to lose his control.
If he throws another ball, all the
work they've put in will go up in smoke.
And Ban Chuuta is exhausted
after Coach Hoshi's strange plan.
However, Hoshi Hyuuma is also on the verge of collapse after a tough game.
Time out!
Hey, Hoshi,
get it together, will ya?
Just two more throws!
Hey, Hoshi,
what's with you?
Wh-What's wrong,
everyone?
What are you saying?
I've got this!
What's the matter, Hoshi? Why're
you struggling against a guy like that?
Get a hold of yourself.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Hey, Hoshi, don't worry.
Just give it your all.
We'll be here,
backing you up.
Hey, keep your eyes
peeled for the winning ball.
Just leave it to me.
Chou, as long as you don't do one of your signature slip-ups, we're all set.
Alright, you've said it now!
It doesn't matter where
it flies, I'll catch it!
So send 'em my way!
Listen, Hoshi, leave
the winning ball to me.
You've just got one more.
Right, Mori, it's all you.
Okay.
Hey, Hoshi, as your catcher,
you could at least tell me what's going on.
You've been ignoring my signs and throwing weak pitches.
Why haven't you been
throwing any strikes?
C'mon, tell me.
I'm very sorry.
It's just that I don't know
what he's got up his sleeve.
It's got me on edge.
So, did you find anything out?
They've seen through
Big League Ball 3.
Th-They what?!
While I don't have
time to go into it,
think about all those who
have hit Big League Ball 3.
Ako from the Hanshin Tigers.
Hiramatsu from the Taiyo Whales.
Ooishi from the Hiroshima Carps.
All pitchers!
Big League Ball 3's fatal flaw
is the slow swing of a pitcher.
I was only able to take them out with
weak balls on the edge of the strike zone.
Coach Hoshi made Ban hold a
handstand to dull his senses and swing.
He wants to settle this
with a decisive pitch.
Ban, listen up!
The pitcher's after a perfect game!
He's not gonna
throw another ball.
He'll be throwing for a strike!
Don't let this chance get away!
Keep your eyes on it and swing!
And then hit it!
Make sure you do!
The ball... pass me the ball...
The ball... give it here.
Play ball!
Dammit...
It's on!
I feel it!
And he hits!
And it just skims third base!
Foul! Foul!
The perfect game
was almost lost!
The dream continues,
but it was a close one!
Their fierce stand-off has
me on the edge of my seat!
It's currently 2-3!
The last pitch!
It's time for the grand finale!
They know this pitch
decides everything!
Will it be a perfect game?!
Or will Chuunichi's
Ban stand in his way?!
Only the last pitch can tell!
Just one... just one more pitch.
The fated pitch is upon us.
Will Hoshi get his perfect game?
We're back at it
after a long pause.
Wh-What do you
think you're doing?!
Your ticket!
Show me your ticket!
Hoshi hasn't moved an inch,
eyes fixed on his former friend.
All 50,000 spectators in the stadium have held their breath and can't look away.
Everyone's hearts are beating in unison
with Hoshi, like we've all become one being.
I'm...
Hoshi has raised his head.
Hoshi has his left
foot on the plate!
I'm...
He begins his motions
of the final pitch!
I'm...
Hoshi!
I'm gonna win!
Hoshi swings both his hands back!
Hoshi, you have to stop!
You have to!
And he lifts up his leg
and pulls his left arm back!
Will he finish it with
a Big League Ball 3?!
Hoshi, stop this!
I'm...
gonna win!
Stop it! Stop it!
Somebody! Somebody stop him!
Hoshi lowers his arm and sends
the pitch towards the home plate!
Here it comes!
And there it goes!
Hit it, Ban! Hit it!
And he hits!
It goes to left of center field!
It's going with some force!
Will it break through?!
Left fielder is
making a run for it!
And so goes the center!
It's not slowing down!
Will this game be perfect?!
And it goes through!
It's through!
The ball's rolling
towards the outer fence!
There goes the
perfect game!
Pinch hitter, Ban Chuuta, gets a perfect hit on Big League Ball 3!
And the runner is...
Where is he?
He's—
D-Damn it!
Ban! Get up!
On your feet, Ban!
Quickly!
Out!
We did it! I feel like
I can do anything!
Go on! Take 'em! Take 'em all!
We did it!
Sir...
It's okay. It's all over now.
I didn't take into account
your running power.
The flaw in my plan was my failing
to consider the strain I placed on you.
It's... it's my fault.
S-Sir...
It's... It's my fault.
He's done it!
He's finally done it!
This is a monumental moment
for Japanese baseball!
Following on from Fujimoto, this is only the
second perfect game the Giants have ever had!
The man who has devoted his entire life to baseball has finally done it!
For someone with a small body, he's performed a massive feat!
He's the star!
He truly is the star of the Giants!
Hey, Hoshi!
Hoshi, what's wrong?!
- Hey!
- Hoshi!
Seriously?
Hoshi, are you alright?
Hyuuma!
Father...
- It's Hoshi.
- It's Coach Hoshi...
That's his father, right?
Hoshi...
Hyuuma.
You've done well.
You put your life
on the line and won.
And you've truly
surpassed me.
This is the winning ball.
With this, our father-son battle has finally come to an end.
D-Dad...
How long has it been
since you've called me that?
Forgive me, Hyuuma.
I'm sure... to you...
I've never been a
real parent to you.
At least... at least...
Let me atone for my sins...
Let me carry you,
just for today.
Just like I did when
you were a child.
Thank you... thank you, Dad...
Hyuuma, you put your life on the line and beat your father fair and square.
You've become a fine man.
But Hyuuma,
the star you've been after this whole
time is proof your life will start anew.
I know that the path
ahead is treacherous.
But I know you'll conquer it!
That's right. You've finally obtained the star you've been longing for your whole life.
No matter where life takes you, I know you'll do well.
Set your sights on a new star.
Set your sights on a new star!
If you have it in you,
head down the road of trials.
And show them what men can do!
Burn bright like a true champion
until the Star of the Giants
is in your hands!
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Head to your future!
If you put your life on the line,
you can do anything.
With the discipline
instilled by your father,
a strong will to live,
and a flaming-hot fastball,
you press on until you
fulfill your promise.
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
The end
@InkaSubs
Head to your future!
The end
If you have it in you,
head down the road of trials.
And show them what men can do!
Burn bright like a true champion
until the Star of the Giants
is in your hands!
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Head to your future!
After three and a half years, Star of the
Giants has finally come to its conclusion.
Thank you for the
support over the years.