If you have it in you, head down the road of trials.
And show them what men can do!
Burn bright like a true champion
until the Star of the Giants is in your hands!
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Head to your future!
[Episode 3]
[Showdown With Sadaharu Oh]
Impressive.
That's #4 in overall performance batter for you.
Indeed, when Oh-sama hits the ball,
it flies away like a ping pong ball.
Dad.
I understand why you brought me here.
Really?
That there is Sadaharu Oh,
the Hero of Koshien.
And the man who will soon rise
to the position of a shining star.
What's do I care for "stars"?
Dad, are you really trying that hard
to attach me to baseball?
I'll go home first.
Dad!
Tsk.
Oh-san, just because we share the same roots,
I'm having to suffer
through the ordeals of baseball too.
Ah!
Oh!
Hanagata!
Well, good job and all.
May I ask for a favor? Please.
W-What the...
But we came here first!
Shut up! I said get lost, so get lost!
Aren't you guys getting carried away a bit?
Funny you ask that! Takes some nerve
to be picking holes in Black Shadows!
Hey, everyone!
Yeah!
Fine, let's do it! Are you in?
You came later so piss off!
Shithead, you're messing with us?!
Hoshi, don't look down on us!
Oh-san, please keep going
and show me more of your batting.
You ass!
Uh!
What are you doing?!
Interesting. You wanna do it?
Hey, people!
Crap.
Alright!
I rushed out into the field
and forgot to remove the cast.
Get him!
Uh! The cast!
Shit...
Oh-san!
Stop it, everyone!
But look, Oh-san...
What will we do
if someone gets hurt in a petty fight?
I-It's not a petty fight!
It's the one most important fight in baseball,
for the right to use the field!
You chill down too!
Eh?
"You chill down too," just like that!
Shit...
Come on, we're leaving.
Wait!
Come back and fight, you coward!
What do you say, Hoshi-kun?
Don't you wanna join our team
and beat that coward Oh?
Even if you're trying to fight us,
you don't have the nerve to take Oh on, do you?
Hey, Hanagata-san,
can we really let him go like this?
Don't worry. That guy is certainly
on a collision course with Oh.
Dammit! What's the point of this thing?
Oh my, what's the matter, Hyuuma?
Did something happen? Tell me what it was!
Akiko, I can't take it anymore! I can't!
I keep torturing myself with baseball,
For dad's sake,
I even agreed to wear this thing.
But now I'm at my limit!
I'm fed up with all baseball players!
They call him a star, but he's just a coward!
Just wants to make a name for himself!
Hyuuma, what happened there?
There's no point in telling you anyhow.
But I swear - even without becoming that kind of star,
I'll do what it takes to make you happy!
Fine. I'll tell father you want to quit.
Here, this is for you.
Oh? Now that's a rare sight.
Sweets in our ran-down shack!
Dad quit drinking, remember?
So he can now buy those.
Now, try some.
I-I'll probably pass.
Why so?
I just can't eat the sweets dad bought with money he used to spend on drinks.
Hyuuma...
Akiko, I...
What happened?
Hyuuma! That's...
Dad quit drinking for me.
So I can't let dad down either.
I'm home.
Hyuuma, wanna go train again?
Okay!
Hyuuma!
Good.
You can do better!
Catch!
Not there yet!
Here, a towel.
You should take off the cast
and wipe yourself normally.
But... there's...
It's fine!
He's asleep already.
Akiko, don't do what you weren't asked to do.
Father!
But he should be allowed to remove it
at least when going to sleep!
Akiko, you stay out of this.
Father... That's going too...
Silence!
You're cruel. So cruel!
If mother was still alive,
she'd definitely object it too!
Shut up!
Akiko, it's alright.
I can't afford slacking off.
Hyuuma...
Well, goodnight now!
I hate you! I hate you, father!
You're the worst!
Mother. What did you ever find
in a man like him...
In this baseball demon?
Lock it back.
Lock it back!
Akiko!
You wench!
Dad, you didn't have any reason to hit her!
You keep silent.
Come, it's time for the morning pitching.
Wait, father! Please let Hyuuma
have a break just today!
What are you saying...
Dad!
Get off me!
I can put up with you mistreating me,
but when you also do that to Akiko, I...
Opposing me out of the sibling's solidarity?
Akiko is already having to put up
with a lot of things ever since mom died.
It's hard enough for her as it is,
with your drinking and baseball obsession!
Oh, shut it, you!
Hyuuma, enough already.
Dad, you should allow
your children more freedom!
I'm already fed up with baseball.
You imbeciles!
You're helping yourself to sake
whenever something happens.
But what should we do?!
You sassy bastard!
You're not my child if you hate baseball!
Leave and never come back!
Dad!
What are you doing?
Hyuuma!
Even when you're not addicted to drinking,
you're addicted to baseball!
Eh... Shut up!
I don't wanna see my dad like that!
Hyuuma!
Let him! My only friends are sake and baseball!
I know exactly how you feel.
D-Don't touch me!
Hoshi-kun.
Don't talk to me in that funny voice!
I'm not touching baseball ever again!
I see. However, our baseball is a means of war.
What did you say?
I said it's the means of waging war.
It's a way of pulling the would-be stars
down from their stardom.
Listen. We, the Black Shadows,
will challenge Oh's team.
With you as our champion.
Eh?
Hoshi-kun, with my help, your disgust for that coward Oh will hit him with full force!
Oh Sadaharu, huh?
Guys, you following me, a high school student
everywhere is troublesome...
Please ease it off a little!
By the way, Oh-kun,
after you graduate next year,
surely, you'll turn pro, won't you?
Unless you're enrolling in a college?
Which team will you join?
That'd be Giants.
That's admirable! Giants, after all?
Hey, answer me!
Answer me first!
What do you think, Hoshi-kun?
Wouldn't it feel nice
to shine as a hero of Koshien yourself?
Hm. Even though he's such a coward!
Exactly! So why don't we beat him
right in front of the reporters?
So you're a fan of Giants, Oh-kun?
So, you're joining Giants. Is that certain?
Yeah, of course it'll be Giants!
Dad said that the Giants
are a constellation shining in the sky.
But dad himself
fell from that constellation once.
So the next player to climb
to that glorious constellation is Oh?
How about that?
Do you want to confront Oh, Hoshi-kun?
Gather together that frustration
you've accumulated up to now
and unleash it all at once at Oh!
You can do that, can't you?
W-Wait!
Why are you trying to set me after him so much?
If I'm being a delinquent,
I would never be a helpless delinquent!
I'll be a delinquent who's strong in everything!
For that, we need to defeat
Oh's team spectacularly.
And let them report it to the whole world!
Really, please give me a break!
Everyone, we're starting!
Alright, we're all ready!
Sorry, but you're not having it your way.
Eh?
That guy again!
Oh-san, it was us who came first this time.
But you guys have just arrived, didn't you?
Look over there.
Those bastards...
Isn't Sunday the most important day
to control the field on?
But how about this, Oh-san?
If we hold a match between our two teams,
both could use it at the same time.
Would you like to play?
Oh-san, what do we do?
Well, if you guys are okay with it,
I don't mind either.
Alright, it's settled! We'll decide
who bats first with rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors!
We'll take the field first!
Hey, everyone!
Yeah!
Alright!
Okay, Hoshi-kun, pitch for us, will you?
Sounds exciting!
Alright! I'll be an umpire!
Hey, Hoshi! Give them hell!
C-Crap, I'm still wearing the cast.
But I really don't wanna take it off.
I feel that by taking it off,
I'll sever myself completely from dad.
Alright, I'll pitch it with the cast on!
Play ball!
Strike!
2-0!
Strike! Batter out!
I don't know, it was kinda impossible
to catch the timing.
Tsk. That loose ball?
Oh, you'll hit it! We know you will!
Oh-san, punish their insolence!
We believe in you, Oh-san!
That pitcher is not throwing
any ordinary balls.
It's as if he was deliberately driving slowly
a sports car that can go all 300km/h.
How unusual...
I've never met a pitcher like this before.
Strike!
Just as I thought,
it's not some ordinary slow ball.
When it actually reaches the batter's box,
it gets even more eerie and powerful.
2-0!
What's wrong, hey! The Hero or Koshien!
Oh-san, don't let us down!
Just hit it!
If a pitcher throws as hard as he can,
but can only achieve this much speed,
he's not supposed to have
so much precise control over it.
Timeout.
Timeout!
What's wrong? Why isn't Oh hitting?
As expected of the prodigy Oh.
He could see that it's no mere slow ball.
But could it really be
because of that weird cast?
Not even in my wildest dreams I'd be throwing fastballs even at one tenth of Hoshi's speed.
You can do it!
Ah! It's flying over there!
C-Crap!
Yeah, we've seen it!
You hit a home run for us!
Impressive!
Manager, it's much different
from what you told us!
Why won't Hoshi take off that cast?
I don't get it!
Idiot. He's not the kind of guy
who'd take it off even if you force him to.
It's good enough as it is now.
It's going exactly according to my plan!
I did not lose.
I'm just confined in the cast that only lets me
throw at one tenth of my strength.
Even so, how did that bastard
pull off that enormous home run?
Umpire! We're changing the pitcher.
Hoshi for Toyama.
What did you say? Changing?
It'll be alright, let me pitch more!
I can suppress every other batter
with my control alone!
Sorry to disappoint,
but that's not happening.
We can't afford being smashed
by another huge home run like that.
Shit...
Shit! Suit yourself!
I don't care anymore.
You call yourself a man after that?
Well, if you wanna flee, go ahead!
Flee? Me?
He's just the type I thought him to be.
Play ball!
Oh-san, smash them again!
Timeout!
Well done. You pitched four good balls
and now we have bases loaded.
Pitcher change!
Right fielder​ Hoshi will pitch once again.
Eh?
What's wrong, Hoshi-kun?
You're not feeling confident enough
against Oh even with bases loaded?
Dad, I wanna compete with my true strength.
As much as I hate baseball, I hate
being made fun of and losing even more!
Play!
Now I'm not letting you hit
a home run like the last time.
I'll show you my true fastball!
Ah!
Dammit!
Shit!
Calm down! Calm down!
I gotta stop them!
At least the one on the third base...
It was an unbelievable blazing fastball...
My hand is still a little numb.
Damn it all!
What's the matter, Saburo?
We have a pitcher and we have a catcher!
Third base is in the catcher's responsibility!
How gutless are you
to be afraid to pick up the ball?!
Damn, that was scary.
His ball is that incredible!
We've no need for wimps like you.
Get lost!
Y-You don't get it, Hanagata-san!
The reason I'm covering my eyes with my mitt is because I can't stand seeing anyone's poor play.
What the hell is this hack blabbering about?!
Wanna do it?
I'm 100 times better at fighting than at baseball.
Interesting. It'll be useful for me as a newbie delinquent to look at how senpai does that!
Eh? Delinquent?
Umpire, if we let this delinquent team
continue playing the match,
Oh-san's good name would end up smeared.
Please interrupt the match at once. I beg you!
Alright.
Black Shadows!
You started a brawl in the middle
of a sacred match!
I score you with forfeiting the match!
What? Seriously?
Oh-san, let's go back.
Hey, guys. Although it ended in this,
this was a very eventful
and moving day for me.
See you.
Wait!
You mean me?
You're smiling sincerely,
but you aren't supposed to!
As a hero of Koshien, you couldn't respond to my ball with anything better than a bunt?
Wait! Wait!
If you're pulling out,
I want you say it clearly: "I lost!"
Not even the renowned
heavy hitter from high school
can just quietly sneak back home
after failing to hit my ball!
So, Oh-san?
Hoshi-kun, right?
Maybe it's just my imagination,
but didn't you gain your baseball skills
just training with your coach and no one else?
So what, even if I did?
I think, he is probably
an excellent coach.
But baseball is a team sport.
If, without understanding that truth,
as a pitcher, you'd try to win
with nothing but the strength of your ball,
engulfed in that confidence,
you'll forget to prepare for defense.
So that's why you hit a bunt?
A commendable observation.
But it was still cheap!
Why? Why didn't you just swing at it?
Hm.
If I could determine your line of pitching during the first two throws, I might've done that.
However, if I'd have let that real pitch of yours go by, the catcher would've been in danger.
That's why I opted out for a bunt,
rather than a riskier swing.
Then, you just did it on the spur or the moment,
concerned about the opponent catcher's safety?
No, that's not what I meant to say either.
Well, let's meet again someday.
I lost.
I lost thoroughly!
I threw the ball
with all my strength at our catcher,
who'd been protected
by Oh from the opposing team.
I never took the catcher's safety in consideration.
I'm defeated... Completely!
Baseball is a severe sport!
But also a wonderful one!
Dad, I'm finally starting to grasp
the essence of baseball!
Baseball is something worth betting
a man's life on. Isn't that right, dad?
[Next episode]
[Episode 4]
[Deadly Knockout Technique]
A deadly batting technique.
Hanagata Mitsuru's terrifying batting ball
is confronted by Hoshi Hyuuma.
Hyuuma is hit with Ittetsu's fireball.
Next week's Star of the Giants:
Episode 4 - Deadly Knockout Technique.
Please look forward to it!
If you have it in you,
head down the road of trials.
And show them what men can do!
Burn bright like a true champion
until the Star of the Giants
is in your hands!
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Head to your future!
Subtitles by [Anonymous Albanian Forklift Operators]