STAR
OF THE GIANTS
omoikon dara
If you set your heart on the road less traveled
shiren no michi wo
You must have a man's courage
yuku ga otoko no dokonjou
The mark of a king, burning a bright red
makka ni moeru oja no shirushi
Till the day you reach the Star of the Giants
kyojin no hoshi wo tsukamu made
Sweat, bleed, and never reveal your tears
chi wo ase nagase namida wo fuku na
Go, go, Hyuuma!
yuke yuke hyuuma
Go further than ever before!
donto yuke
Subtitles: Iquix (weleaveshadows)
191!
What's wrong?
Don't you think it's pathetic that this
is all that makes you give in?
Throw with your whole body! All of it!
Dammit...
Alright!
Now here comes 189!
What are you doing?
Stand up, Hyuuma!
Throw the ball!
Throw it!
The son of Hoshi Ittetsu never lets himself lose!
Dammit...
Aim for
the Star of Glory!
T/N Note:  The Tokyo Big6 is a championship between six colleges in the Tokyo area.
Nagashima hits his eighth homerun!
T/N Note:  Nagashima Shigeo was a famous baseball player.
He played for the Yomiuri Giants during his professional career.
This is his eighth homerun in the Big6!
The hero of the championship, Rikkyou University's third baseman, Nagashima!
Holding his victory in his hands, Nagashima looks ecstatic!
- Nagashima-san, what team did you choose?
-  Please tell us!
Kawakami-san, what do think of the up-and-coming Nagashima-kun?
T/N Note:  Kawakami Tetsuharu was a famous batter, known as the "God of Batting". He played for the Giants until 1958.
- He's so dreamy!
- He really is...
Nagashima's a real looker, isn't he?
At the end of 1957...
It was decided that the star
athlete of the Tokyo Big6...
...Third Baseman, Nagishima...
...would be admitted into the Giants.
The new star of the Giants:
The Golden Rookie, Nagashima.
What followed the announcement was the
greatest debut of any famed third baseman.
Nagashima's name was on the lips of everyone,
regardless of their age and gender.
His reputation kept growing...
...and his popularity climbed with each passing day.
However...
There was one person who couldn't
be bothered to listen...
A lone young boy.
You're such an idiot.
There's no way Nagashima would do something like that.
He'd pull the coolest home run
and get it on his first try!
You got that right.
He is the Golden Rookie.
But y'know, his opponent is Kaneda.
T/N Note:  Kaneda Masaichi was a famous Japanese pitcher who played for the Kokutestu Swallows. In Nagashima's debut match, Nagashima was struck out by Kaneda four times.
He can't win that easy.
Stupid! No matter what you say, it's gonna be Nagashima.
Nagashima's gonna win!
Hm, of course, but what can one say?
T/N Note:  He's imitating a sports reporter. I tried.
The truth of the matter is...
...not one person will know the outcome until
it happens, is that not true for every match?
Shut up!
Stop talking about Nagashima!
You bastard...
Stop messin' around!
What the hell's wrong with
talking about Nagashima?
That's right! That's right!
Don't butt in on other people's conversations
just because you hate baseball!
It's freedom of speech!
Nagashima's gonna win!
Didn't I tell you to shut up about him!?
Bastard...!
Dammit!
How's that!?
Why is it Nagashima...?  Why is
he the greatest third baseman...?
Pops could've...
He could've...
What're you spacing out for, Hyuuma?
There's only twenty-nine left! Come on!
What was that throw? There was no power in it.
A pitcher can't look away for even a second!
They always throw the ball with everything they have!
Are listening to me, Hyuuma!?
Pops...
Why do you always train me so hard?
Is baseball really worth all that?
I don't want to be like you anymore.
Well, well, now this is a surprise!
Playing catch at this time of night?
Guess there's some real
weird people out there, huh?
Ain't that the truth?
Is this one of them scams?
Gonna raise your boy into some kinda
Nagashima-like baseball star and rake in the dough?
Nagashima would get angry if he
was forced to be with some poor family.
T/N Note:  He also mentions that Hyuuma and his dad live in a tenement.
- Dammit...!
- Hyuuma!
Serves you right!
What're you doing!?
You idiot!
The devil's fastball, also called the masoukyuu...
T/N Note:   "Masoukyuu" is a shortened version of
"aku[ma] no [soukyuu]" (the devil's fastball)
...I thought I told you never to use it!
B-But they treated us like we're poor!
That's no excuse!
Get on your knees and apologize!
Swear that you will never do that again.
I won't!
What did you say!?
Father!
I know that you're frustrated! You have to be!
Don't you think I know?
The greatest third baseman...
Anytime you hear about Nagashima...
...you always get bitter and drink because you–
Father, don't be violent!
I know what you did back then.
You were supposed to be the greatest
third baseman ten years ago!
Stop it!
Don't talk about it!
No, I'll say it! You bet I'll say it!
All those times you've told me
not to use the masoukyuu...
...you've been—!
You've been—!
Shut up!
Shut the hell up!
Father! Stop it! Stop it, please!
It's selfish...
It's selfish to force me to live out your dreams!
It's so selfish!
How dare...
How dare you say that to me!
- Stop it! Father!
- Let go of me!
Hyuuma!
Hyuuma, run and get out of here!
Pops, you idiot!
You coward!
I...
...I hate the kind of baseball Dad makes me play.
I hate Kawakami and Nagashima.
Tomorrow: A Party to Celebrate Nagashima's
Admission into the Giants.
Now then, everyone watching from
home, thank you for waiting.
We will now conduct an interview
with Third Baseman, Nagashima.
How about it? Anything to say?
Yes.
The Giants have a rich history behind them.
As long as I'm allowed to join their ranks,
I will do everything in my power...
...to live up to their name.
And now, former second baseman
and team senior, Chiba...
...will entrust him with the Giants' number three jersey.
Take care of it.
I will!
Hey, Kawakami-san, between you as first baseman and Chiba as second...
...both of Japan's greatest first and second
basemen are from the Giants, correct?
Exactly!
And now with the introduction of Nagashima-kun...
...it's very possible that the nation's
greatest third baseman...
...will come from the Giants as well.
No, there's no doubt.
Nagashima-kun, do your best.
The greatest third baseman, huh?
If it wasn't for the war...
...then one might have already existed.
Hoshi Ittetsu.
Hoshi-kun, the third baseman who never was...
Where are you...
...and what are you doing now?
The third baseman who never was, is that it?
Shit...
Hey, old man, don't you agree?
He actually talked back to me.
Still, I...
It's already set, ain't it?
Nagashima's gonna win.
That's what I'm saying. That much is obvious.
You bastard!
But you know? No matter what they say,
I'lll be sure that damn kid makes it big.
What?
I'll make him into a real pitcher!
Kawakami-san, don't just stand there
and smoke, help us out a bit.
Oh, I know!
Would you let us take a few pictures...
...of you shaking hands with Nagashima
in front of the Giants' flag?
Please do!
I see. Alright, then.
Come over, Nagashima-kun.
Yes!
It's the masoukyuu.
Hoshi...
Could Hoshi Ittetsu really be here?
Masoukyuu?
Hoshi?
What are you talking about?
You see, about that...
Damn kid, stop moving!
A kid like that...
Kawakami-san...
This is unbelievable.
What's going on?
Hey! What's your name?
Why would you do something like that?
If you're silent, we can't understand!
Anyhow, if this kid really was
the one who threw that ball...
...then he's a bonafide genius.
Do you understand what you just did?
If you injured Nagashima...
...then you'll be sent off to juvie.
Wait a second.
Are you...?
Is it possible that your name's Hoshi-kun?
Hell no!
Show me your hand.
These calluses...
It's almost like he's been playing
baseball for twenty years.
What about Nagashima!?
What about Kawakami!?
What about baseball!?
Hoshi-kun, wait!
D-Dammit.
It's terrifying that he can throw
the masoukyuu at his age.
Nagashima-kun, I'll leave the rest to you.
Where are you going?
I need to know more.
I'm following after him.
Dammit...!
Dammit!
The Giants' third baseman who never was, Hoshi Ittetsu.
What kind of life are you living now?
Hoshi-kun...
...you always were a man of bad luck.
You joined the Giants in 1942 during
the height of the Pacific War.
You were a prodigy of a player.
I believed...
...that you were going to define the future of the team.
However...
...right before the team's first official match...
...you were drafted into army and brought into battle.
In the midst of it...
...you injured your shoulder.
You injured something worth more than your life, and then you returned.
1948.
You rejoined the Giants.
Normally, a person who's injured their shoulder...
...loses their ability to play.
But what a guy!
You were a genius from the very beginning.
Thinking back on it...
It was a match...
GIANTS: RED AND WHITE MATCH
...near the beginning of that year's season.
You guarded third...
...and I guarded first.
Play ball!
Hoshi's shoulder...!
He won't make it!
Is it an out?
Out!
To make the ball he threw from first look
like it was about to hit the runner...
That's impossible.
Was it pure luck, or...?
O-Out!
It wasn't just luck.
It must be a throw Hoshi came up with.
What a genius idea!
However...
Just as expected, Kawakami.
You saw right through me.
Yeah, I might've been the only one.
It's a technique I came up with to
compensate for my shoulder.
But it'll only work once.
Exactly. The ball won't hit the runner,
even if it looks like it will.
If the runner figures that out, they'll
make it to the base no problem.
Is that what you wanted to say?
But that's not how it'll go.
If I were to hit them sometimes, then...
What!?
Hoshi-kun, there's no doubt you're a genius.
The masoukyuu is a miracle you made happen.
However..
Let me give you some advice.
Hoshi-kun...
...leave the Giants!
What did you say!?
Those who disgrace the team's name...
...no matter how talented they are...
...cannot remain on the team.
Kawakami...!
Don't you understand...
....how useful the masoukyuu will be...
...when the Giants enter their golden age!?
Are you—
Are you too much of an idiot...
to understand that!?
Hoshi-kun...
Sawamura Eiji, in the days before he died in the war...
T/N Note: Sawamura Eiji was a Giants pitcher who died in WWII. The Sawamura Award is given to Japanese pitchers in his honor.
...left these words behind:
"The pride I feel standing on the mound as a member of the Giants...
...has never once allowed me to throw a beanball."
I see...
That's all it is.
The masoukyuu is just a beanball by a different name.
Hoshi-kun.
If things had been different, then there's no doubt...
...you would have become the greatest third baseman in history.
I get it.
This is goodbye...
...Kawakami-kun.
Hoshi-kun!
Hoshi-kun...
Watch out!
Stop that! It's dangerous!
Excuse us for causing so much trouble.
We're truly sorry.
- It's really no problem.
- Yeah, it's fine.
Nee-chan, I can't count on you for anything!
Why'd you let Pops drink?
I'm done with you!
What're you doing?
Take a look!
All of this is your fault!
He really outdid himself this time...
But how is any of this my fault?
Don't play dumb!
You threw the masoukyuu...
...at Nagashima-sam when he doesn't know anything.
Why wouldn't Dad get mad?
- Y-You guys saw that?
- Yes.
The broadcast switched away before it was shown...
...so we couldn't see who threw the ball...
...but Dad knew the moment he saw it.
That doesn't mean...
He didn't have to do all this, did he?
You idiot!
I've fallen, but I'm still Hoshi Ittetsu.
You know what would happen if they traced that bullshit back to my son?
...I'd be embarrassed to see my old Giants teammates!
- What was that about the Giants?
- What? The Giants?
Sorry for bothering you, or somethin'.
It's all calmed down now, so...
...please feel free to leave.
You're lying!
Pops, you liar!
The reason you did all this...
...isn't because I threw the ball.
It's not because of that.
It's because it's the ball you came up with...
...and Nagashima saw through it, just like that!
Pops, you...
The third baseman who never was...
...lost to Nagashima!
You lost!
Look, it's just like I said.
You say that, but Hyuuma...
You're frustrated too, aren't you?
You're sad, aren't you?
Shut up, stupid!
It's too late to wipe away your tears.
It's written all over your face!
Idiot! Stupid!
Nee-chan, you idiot!
Moron!
Ugly!
No one's ever gonna marry you!
It's just so sad.
Dad, you always thought that...
...as long as you had the masoukyuu...
...you could make yourself believe that...
...you were the greatest third baseman, didn't you?
So that's how it is.
Still, what a horrible way to live.
...Hoshi-kun wouldn't want to see his old teammates right now, would he?
I guess I'll go back for now.
This house is cursed by baseball.
Every day since I was born...
...let alone play...
...all I've ever been allowed to do is this.
I-It can't be!
A ball from that hole...?
Is it a fluke?
Dammit! I wanted...
...to play cards...
...and spin tops too!
But even if I wanted to...
...you'd only let me do this!
For five years.
Six!
Seven!
Training.
It was horrifying training that allowed
this miracle to happen.
If his speed and control were off by just a bit...
...then the ball would go in a
completely different direction.
I can't back down now!
Batting is the same.
If the ball isn't hit in just the right way...
...then it'll fly in the wrong direction.
Hoshi Ittetsu...
To see if you're qualified to raise a genius like him...
I, former pro...
...Line Driver Kawakami, will test you!
Watch out!
Pops!
Oops, I forget this wasn't a stadium.
Amazing...!
How amazing was that!
It was like a magic trick.
Just as expected!
You caught it and got into a throwing pose without even thinking.
I'm glad!
Hoshi...
...this time for sure...
...I'm counting on you to raise the greatest pitcher out there.
For the Giants of tomorrow, that is!
Hyuuma, you screwed up, didn't you?
To think that you'd send a ball back in that direction...
Y-You're wrong, Pops!
Someone hit it back from outside!
Don't be stupid.
The only batter in Japan who could do something like that...
...is Kawakami Tetsuharu.
Kawakami...!
Just like we thought...
That man from behind, he...
Look, Hyuuma.
That constellation represents every position, each member of the Giants.
Once in the past, I was one of those shining stars.
But as I am now, it's out of my reach.
Hyuuma!
Climb until you reach it!
Make yourself the brightest star...
...right in the dead center!
Hyuuma, my boy!
Aim for the star of glory!
If you set your heart on the road less traveled
omoikon dara
shiren no michi wo
You must have a man's courage
yuku ga otoko no dokonjou
The mark of a king, burning a bright red
makka ni moeru oja no shirushi
Till the day you reach the Star of the Giants
kyojin no hoshi wo tsukamu made
Sweat, bleed, and never reveal your tears
chi wo ase nagase namida wo fuku na
Go, go, Hyuuma!
yuke yuke hyuuma
Go further than ever before!
donto yuke
Subtitles: Iquix (weleaveshadows)