[STAR OF THE GIANTS]
If you set your heart on the road less traveled
You must have a man's courage
The mark of a king, burning a bright red
Till the day you reach the Star of the Giants
Sweat, bleed, and never reveal your tears
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Go further than ever before!
[Devil's Plaster Cast]
Stop!
We'll get you!
Stop right there!
Please show forgiveness!
If I join your gang,
I'll get spanked back at home!
Think you can get away after
turning down an offer from Akagawa?!
Quit messing with me!
Please show forgiveness!
You should have seen this coming to you!
Who did it?!
This bastard Hoshi!
I'd like you to stop hindering my nap.
Keep it quiet down here.
That's what I threw this one for.
I'm fed up enough as it is
with dad raising a ruckus every night.
To show up and rebel against me...
Hoshi, you've got some nerve, too!
Let's get him...
That's right!
He's a goner!
You bastard!
Keep going!
Is this enough to send you trembling in fear?!
I have on my side the advantage
of having a perfect aim.
So, wanna continue?
Who wants to visit the hospital first?
Damn you.
Won't scare me with your cheap gimmicks!
Wanna go or not, decide right now!
You'll regret this!
You saved us, Hoshi.
He kept scapegoating us time after time.
But the amazing Hoshi is always there to help!
Forget it.
Didn't even do anything special.
He's a formidable fellow, this Hoshi.
I'm home!
What did you do this for, dad?
Found yourself a bottle
to spend another evening with?
Why are you letting this happen, Akiko?
You have any idea what you've done today?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about what you've done
at the riverside today.
Ah, that thing?
You must have seen yourself then -
nothing serious.
Cretin!
How many times do I have to tell you this?
You can't be showing off your strength in public.
Is it that hard to understand?
Have you forgotten?
Enough already, I understand that much.
Na-ah, you don't understand a thing.
Look there, at that star.
Your aim is to climb up to that constellation.
The summit of professional baseball.
As the Star of the Giants, you're bound
to start shining among their ranks.
But until that day comes, you have no choice,
but to practice strenuously
without anyone finding out.
I refuse!
What?
Baseball this, baseball that!
I'm not...
I'm not some marionette of yours!
Hyuuma!
Screw the constellations.
Screw the giants.
What I really need
is a way to make dad and sis happy.
Sis?
Hyuuma.
I cannot reproach you for hating baseball.
But please, stop quarreling with your father.
Not my fault dad is so selfish.
Just 'cause he failed at it himself,
he now wants me to give it a try.
Say, but isn't that excusable for him?
If you take his baseball away,
what's left of father then?
What do I care for that baseball junkie?
Idiot!
To let you inherit his baseball
has been dad's dream all along!
To me too...
baseball seems like a wonderful
world of opportunities!
After all...
Father is so passionate about it.
I heard you.
Very well.
I'll do it.
Really?
I can do it.
But remember, sis.
I'm only doing that for your and dad's sake.
Hyuuma...
Hyuuma.
Come closer.
What is it, dad?
Listen, Hyuuma.
This is a device I developed myself
to facilitate your covert practice.
What's that contraption?
Now, extend both hands to me.
Like this?
Dad, what's this for?
Listen well,
I want you to endure this.
[Sumidagawa Elementary School]
Okay, and now...
We'll add one more on the top.
Come on, you're all supposed
to hop easily over this.
Begin!
Alley-hop!
Alley-hop.
Hoshi, you okay?
Nothing serious.
What just happened?
Hoshi, who always had
the most developed reflexes in this class,
suddenly trips over today?
And now, we proceed to gymnastics on the mat.
We'll start with Hoshi
demonstrating you what to do.
Want me to do it?
What's the matter?
Usually, you're glad to help.
No problem!
Damn it!
Hey, Hoshi, are you even trying?
Hoshi! Enough, you can stop.
Something's clearly wrong with your body today. Stop!
Hoshi...
Damn, damn it all! It was dad's fault!
Made an utter fool of myself today!
Damn him!
That sure was a pitiful performance today.
Well, trust me to help. I know
just the place where you can get your fill...
I mean, your dad spends all his money on booze,
so no wonder you're malnourished.
This time you've been so hungry,
you couldn't even do your famous handstand!
Got you covered, covered.
Got you, alright?
You don't know what you're saying!
My dad would never spend his last copper
on booze over spending it on provisions for kids!
He doesn't earn much, but he has a big heart!
But aren't you the one always complaining
about how unbearable your da is?
That is but the evidence
of how much I value my dad.
You can say whatever on my account,
but if you dare badmouth my dad,
I'll shut you up!
Hey you, looking for a fight?
Look!
What now? I'm supposed to be impressed?
Trying it on would be more compelling.
Like this. What do you think?
Hooligan chief Akagawa, what do you think?
Can you do a handstand like this?
Hoshi, do you mean to say
you were doing handstand with this thing on?
Well, whatever.
But if you don't want to reap my wrath,
you'd better be hush-hush about this whole thing.
I'll be the hushiest guy around!
Alright...
Major League preparation plaster cast.
That's one fine invention dad came up with.
Seems like he's not actually half-bad.
Hanagata!
Have you seen it just now?
The guy you tasked me with recruiting.
Terribly sorry I couldn't be
of any service this time.
No-no, that was actually a good progress.
Just getting him to show us this dreadful Major
League plaster cast is quite an achievement.
You proved yourself worthy of being a scout
for our Black Shadows baseball delinquents team.
The way things are looking now,
we must do our damnest
to get him to join our baseball team.
I know just a method for that.
Hey, I'll need you to put on one more play.
Would you do it, Akagawa?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Hey, sis.
Know where dad went?
You seem mighty impatient!
What's wrong?
As if anything is right at all!
Today I'm giving dad
a decisively rough side of the tongue!
There's no way I can keep wearing
this plaster cast!
While vaulting over the horse,
I tripped over and fell flat.
And while doing handstand, everyone
burst laughing at my crooked handstand!
No wonder at all.
After all, this stupid plaster cast
reduces my strength to one tenth of it!
There's no way he left without you noticing.
Tell me, where did dad go?
Father has not returned from work yet!
After enchaining Hyuuma
in this excruciating plaster cast,
he couldn't bear to be dawdling around.
He is your father, after all.
Whatever suffering you're going through,
he is experiencing it as well.
Okay? Please.
At least when father is at home,
put on that plaster cast.
I was sure he's drinking his day away
just like always.
Was already thinking through
the ensuing quarrel.
Thank you, Hyuuma.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
I worked not one, but two shifts today.
Go buy some meat and cook it for Hyuuma.
And now...
Hey, Hyuuma. Until dinner, we're having
a pitching practice in the backyard.
But what about "not letting others
see my hand in baseball, ever?"
Don't you always say that?
We'll do it with plaster cast on.
This way, everyone would think
you're just some sub-par baseball player.
Hyuuma...
Alright, let's play a quick one.
Okay, Hyuuma, go ahead.
Who'd think it would come to this.
Before, he did nothing but boozing.
But now they're playing catch ball every night.
Moreover, now that I look at it,
pops and son's play is getting better by the day.
Crap, we've got an audience.
Like father like son, after all.
Both are butterfingered in baseball.
Dad would even go to such extremes,
just to keep the whole thing a secret.
Don't rely on fingers only,
throw it with your whole body.
In the end, what the worth of such pitcher?
It's a kindergarten level!
You're so obnoxious!
Watch closely, as I'm throwing a blazing fastball
​ that'll blow you away!
All I need to do is to free myself
from this damned thing!
Hyuuma!
Don't tell me
you were seriously about to show everyone
the plaster cast just to put them in place?
Isn't that so?
I won't show it to anyone.
That's better.
What terrifies me
is that you may disclose yourself to the world,
while you're still too green.
Remember? Your conquest
is none other than the Star of the Giants.
Hanagata, something wrong?
Have you seen it? Hoshi can throw like that
even while wearing a plaster cast.
I can't even imagine what his throw
would be like without the cast.
Don't you worry. We'll definitely
recruit Hoshi for Black Shadows.
I doubt that my strategy is in any way faulty.
'Cause it ain't!
Thanks for the meal!
Who'd think such breakfasts
that we spend together as a family
would become a usual thing!
Someone used to spend his every morning
in the bed with a hangover.
Mother is definitely
watching over us with a smile.
Don't be playing shy, dad.
Say, doesn't it taste better
without the reeking of sake?
You rogue!
What now? Hooligans chieftain
Akagawa again? What do you want?
This weird plaster cast you're wearing today -
turns out, it did quite a number on me.
I went to see a doctor the other day,
elbow and shoulder are badly damaged,
might as well require a costly treatment later.
Hyuuma!
You incorrigible idiot!
Father! Please stop!
Beating me up won't fix anything!
What?!
If it came to this, I'll have you know,
I got a ton of grievances against you, too!
He says he has some grievances
against his daddy!
Highly amusing! Let's hear it!
Dad is a baseball junkie.
A baseball idiot!
A baseball-fixated loser
who never succeeded in it!
Hyuuma, no more! Father, too! Please!
I didn't want dad to feel bad for me,
so I was feigning a carefree face while eating.
But look!
Actually, every second
of holding the bowl like that,
is a struggle against that devil's
plaster cast that pulls my hand back.
Can you see all this cold sweat?
Crap!
I'm fed up! Screw it!
I've had enough of sacrificing myself
to dad's pipe dream!
I see. Are you saying you won't follow me
on this path any longer?
Did I not make myself clear enough?
Enough, out of here!
He who doesn't obey his parent, should leave!
Would leave gladly!
Hyuuma!
Let him!
Hanagata's plan going swimmingly.
I'm the best scout the Black Shadows
could ever have!
Stop!
Petty bandit wannabe is caught red-handed!
Oh god... Save me, someone!
If you hit me with a hand
that's been forged by that plaster cast,
you'll make a hole in my head!
Damn you, just as it seemed that things
are finally starting to look up at home...
It's all your goddamn fault...
Damn!
But it's too late now.
It's all over already!
Nope, it's all merely starting.
Hoshi, we have already prepared
a warm welcome for you.
Hey, don't you know it's dangerous?
Ground is limited here,
not much we can do!
Are they doing this on purpose?
What do you say, Hoshi?
Feel like joining us yet?
Told you I detest baseball!
Hey, keep the balls coming!
Okay!
Throw even faster!
Keep throwing! More!
Hey, drop it!
We can't work like this!
Dad... Slaving even his Sunday away.
Hey, will you ever stop?
Watch out, Yose!
Didn't they ask you to watch out, Yose?
I'm trying my best, but our pitcher's ball is just too feeble.
Not the pitch I'm used to.
Hey, throw more!
Wait! I will throw this one.
Scaredy cat!
What?
You're still wearing a plaster cast.
Hey, why won't you unleash
your unabated formidable strength upon us?
Could it be that you are that afraid
of competing with us head to head?
Damn you!
What now, scaredy cat?
Afraid, after all?
And so, the dread of open confrontation
has been too unbearable for Hoshi.
We'll have to make do without him!
Dad, even if we fought over it,
taking off that plaster cast now
somehow feels like betraying dad
past the point of no return.
It hurts!
Those brats are just messing with us for fun!
Show them!
Let's go!
Let me, too!
Get them!
Stop it, stop!
Like it?
[Construction Site]
Hey, you'll hurt yourselves!
Stop it! Stop right now!
Hey!
It's getting scary!
Hey! Stop the car! Reach for the brake!
Save us!
Quickly! Throw off the plaster cast!
Dad...
Throw it off!
This way!
Dad.
Let me have my plaster cast back.
Hyuuma...
Hyuuma!
Dad. Starting tomorrow,
I'll put my soul to training.
I still need more forging.
It seems like Hoshi is about to return home.
What'll you do?
Can't be helped.
But later on, I'll exhaust my every approach
to recruit him for Black Shadows.
Hanagata...
[Next Episode]
[Confrontation with Sadaharu Ou]
Baseball is something worth
betting a man's life on.
About that, young boy Hyuuma
learns from a high school player Ou.
Next week's in Star of the Giants:
Episode 3,
Confrontation with Sadaharu Ou.
Look forward to it.
If you have it in you,
head down the road of trials.
And show them what men can do!
Burn bright like a true champion
until the Star of the Giants
is in your hands!
Go all out until you sweat blood!
Don't wipe away your tears!
Go, go, Hyuuma!
Head to your future!