In the midst of
the Jinshin War...
A boy was born with a horn
on his forehead. It was proof
that the god of the northern
sky had given him life.
The boy's name was
Utsu no Miko.
Utsu no Miko
Heaven Chapter
A man is always a lonely warrior
Born from a dream
A long time ago this land too
Was a desolate wasteland
When I fall asleep in your arms
Even the wounds in my heart
Ache less, thanks to your motherly care
And they start healing up
I'll never give it up
I wish I could forever stay young
And shine just like I do now
I'll never it give up
Staying free
And living as I wish
In the time when the Imperial Court was trying
to consolidate power and control the people,
a group resisting that trend gathered on Mount Kongo,
under the leadership of En no Ozunu.
Utsu no Miko was also one of those ascetics, the so-called Oni.
Come on, turn!
Fuhito, prepare to die!
Where am I?
The Lifeless Wasteland?
The place where the dead still cling to their memories of life.
The sound of a flute?
It's a tune I've never heard before,
but for some reason it touches my heart.
It feels familiar, somehow.
This is the Lifeless Wasteland, where those who have lost the will to live gather.
Why are you here?
I'm on a spiritual journey,
looking for someone.
A spiritual journey?
When I meet that person,
when I come into contact with his pure way of life,
I can then be restored
to the Heavenly Realm.
Upon hearing my flute,
he will be able to play along with me.
You must be the one I'm looking for.
I'm Utsu no Miko,
a Mount Kongo trainee.
Who are you?
Utsu no Miko...
Utsu no Miko!
You must find your path again!
Ah, he's regained consciousness!
Miko...
I-I...
No, you shouldn't move yet.
An arrow pierced your shoulder,
and the river washed you away.
Master Ozunu saved you.
It was reckless of you to fight the Minister by yourself.
So it was just a dream?
Miko is a god's son.
And who am I?
Kijimuna! You startled me.
It's because I was in such
a hurry to get to you.
What is it?
That tune Miko's playing on his flute these days...
I've heard it somewhere else!
They say that the princess' beauty
isn't like a human being's.
Even the prince who rules
the capital was captivated by it
and asked for her hand several times.
But the princess keeps refusing everyone.
However, rumors say that she will return to the Moon when it's full.
So court soldiers have surrounded her residence to prevent that from happening.
She belongs to the Heavenly Realm?
Yes. She was born from
a bamboo stalk, after all.
Who is there?
Please forgive me. The beautiful sound
of your flute drew me here.
I'm Kagami from Mount Kongo.
Mount Kongo?
Is there a man by the name of Utsu no Miko there?
Y-Yes.
Please give this message to Utsu no Miko.
Tonight, by the time the Moon is full...
Kagami!
If you love Miko, you don't have
to give him that message.
Tonight, the Moon will be full.
Before that, I wish to see Miko,
the partner destined for me by the gods.
Utsu no Miko, is there nothing I can do to meet you?
Stop!
Utsu no Miko?
Miko!
Thank you, Utsu no Miko.
Now I can be restored
to the Heavenly Realm as a god.
Miko, come to the Heavenly Realm with me.
Princess,
I cannot come with you now.
But I promise I will, when I accomplish
all my earthly tasks
and attain the powers of a god.
Miko?
Utsu no Miko, the Oni from Mount Kongo,
has rebelled repeatedly
against the Imperial Court.
We can no longer turn a blind eye to it.
Utsu no Miko should be captured and sentenced to death!
But will Mount Kongo comply?
The prestige of the Court is at stake.
We'll make them comply!
Take that! There! Now!
When it stops snowing,
they'll come again.
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
Don't worry. This much won't be enough
to make Mount Kongo waver.
We challenged the Imperial Court to a fight
on behalf of those suffering from oppression.
We attempted to build a fair government.
Still...
Master Ozunu, please tell me.
What about the salvation of the people?
Where is Buddha's mercy?
Isn't it meant for the poor and miserable?
I apologize.
Perhaps the time has come.
The god of the northern sky is your father.
You were given life when the cosmos and the Earth became one.
You've done well enduring the worries and suffering
that are innate to humanity's chaotic nature.
Now is the time for you to leave
my side and start a new journey.
Utsu no Miko, set forth on a journey in the Heavenly Realm!
See the gods and heed their words!
Find Buddha and talk to him personally!
You will find your answers yourself!
Miko!
What did Master Ozunu say?
How should we deal
with the Imperial troops?
We'll ambush them!
Isn't that right, Miko?
We're being expelled from Mount Kongo.
Are you serious?!
Why?!
What's the meaning of this?
He told me to go
to the Heavenly Realm.
The Heavenly Realm?!
You mean, that Heavenly Realm?
Where the gods and Buddha reside?
We're going to the Heavenly Realm?
Kijimuna, you're coming with us!
Wh-Why do I have to go?
This is Master Ozunu's decision.
We depart tomorrow.
Hey, are you seriously going to bring all that along?
We've never been to the Heavenly Realm, so who knows what we'll need?
Right, Kusuri?
We haven't even attained enlightenment,
yet we're going to the Heavenly Realm?
Miko is the son of a god,
so it should be okay for him.
Master Ozunu will figure it out.
What an easygoing guy you are.
Do you think Miko will want
to see Princess Kaguya again?
Yeah. After all, their encounter on Earth was fleeting.
Hey! Kagami can hear you!
She's seriously worried
about that Princess Kaguya.
Hey!
If Miko marries the princess from the bamboo stalk,
what should I do?
Hey! Kijimuna isn't here!
She has a mind of her own.
This is the ship of Amaterasu,
which can cross the sky.
If they chant this incantation—
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen—
those who board this ship will be safe.
With it,
you can travel across time and space
and carve out your own destinies.
The doors of this altar
must never be opened.
If you break that prohibition,
you will wander the Heavenly Realm
in this ship until the end times.
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha.
Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen!
Miko is leaving!
They've departed!
Miko, allow me to be honest.
I'm worried about this.
Is the Heavenly Realm
a continuation of this world?
You don't even know that?
Kijimuna! When did you get here?
Who let you on board?
I may have been reduced to this,
but I'm still a god. It was easy!
We have to use our spiritual power and cross
the invisible boundaries to reach
the Heavenly Realm.
This journey is nothing like one on Earth.
We must all act as one.
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
If you err, we'll be lost forever
in between the two realms!
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Utsu no Miko, head toward the northern star.
Meet your father,
the god who bestowed life upon you, and understand his mind.
Do it to set your own course
for the coming era.
Wh-What's that?!
Not good!
Wh-What should we do?!
We must not resist.
H-How can you say that?!
Everything we experience here is new.
If we live in fear, we cannot survive.
Where do you come from?
The Earthly Realm.
We travel to find knowledge.
The Earthly Realm?
That must mean you have received
judgment from King Enma.
We are not dead!
What?
How could a living soul
find its way here?
No one can enter this place
as flesh and blood!
Exactly!
Silence!
I can feel the spirits of the dead in you.
We were alive when we departed
the Earthly Realm, and we still are.
There are no spirits of the dead among us.
You don't seem to have
any evil within you.
Utsu no Miko, what brought you, an Earthling, to a place like this?
I worship the gods and Buddha.
Under the guidance of En no Ozunu,
I am undergoing training
to become a god.
He said, "A god"?!
Forgive my rudeness,
but may I know your name?
King Rahu Asura.
The leader of all Asura.
King Rahu Asura?
Leave here immediately.
This world is not as simple as you think.
Still, I was told this is a world of peace and compassion.
The Heavenly Realm may indeed be
a dazzling and fascinating place.
But that is not all.
King Asura, please tell me
about the Heavenly Realm.
This happened 10,000 years ago.
Taishakuten came to visit and asked
for the hand of my daughter, Shachi.
At his best, Taishakuten is broadminded.
At his worst, he is impulsive and cruel.
As a single father, I really wondered
if he could be a good partner for my daughter.
Then one day...
When Shachi went out alone
to play in the stardust,
Taishakuten took her by force.
After that, she was at the mercy
of his emotions.
My beloved daughter
was violated and disgraced.
The Asura Clan
believed in respecting
the other party's volition.
Thus, we took up arms
and went to war with Taishakuten.
Until one day,
the gods of the Heavenly Realm
turned their backs on the Asura Clan.
We ended up getting exiled.
Why? Taishakuten is obviously
the one to blame here!
King Asura, I will meet with Taishakuten.
What?!
Utsu no Miko, what are you going to do
when you meet Taishakuten?
I will ask why things had to be done the way they were, on your behalf.
And then I promise that you'll be
reinstated in the Heavenly Realm!
So you intend to influence the minds of gods and Buddha in the Heavenly Realm?
Utsu no Miko, you may go now.
Miko?
What happened to us?
I will respect your resolve.
King Asura...
Miko, what are you thinking?
You're thinking about Princess Kaguya, aren't you?
You fought for the oppressed,
shouldering their suffering.
For now, at least allow
yourself that dream.
We're entering the Moon!
The Moon Palace!
I can see the Moon Palace!
Kagami, Miko went to the Moon Palace.
I know.
Are you okay with that? It means Miko will meet Princess Kaguya again.
I'm always praying that Miko's dream comes true.
What a kind-hearted woman you are.
Why did you become an oni
at Mount Kongo?
Princess, Utsu no Miko, who has traveled
from the Earthly Realm, is here.
Please come in.
Princess, it's truly been a long time.
Utsu no Miko?
Yes.
You just said it's been a long time.
Have we met somewhere before?
Princess, did you forget our parting on the night of the full moon?
The night of the full moon?
Yes!
You and I had a fleeting
encounter that night!
What is going on?
What has the princess been through to make her forget me?
Miko has been very quiet
ever since he returned.
That must be quite shocking for him.
The princess doesn't remember a thing about him.
I wonder what happened.
There are so many things we don't understand in the Heavenly Realm.
The Celestials call it the Wailing Planet.
To me, it looks just like Miko's tears.
What happened to King Asura...
What happened to the princess...
Why is the Heavenly Realm
such a cold place?
What is the gods' design for it?
Miko! Grieving that much is unhealthy!
Kijimuna!
What's all the ruckus?
M-M...
Miko disappeared!
Miko, where are you?
Miko...
Watch out, Kagami!
Kagami!
Miko, weren't we always together?
In happy times and sad times alike?
But if the princess regains
her memory, Miko will be...
Where are you, Miko?
Miko!
What's that?
Who are you?
Are you the one who truly understand Miko's heart?
Miko is stronger than me
in every aspect.
That's why he has to suffer a lot more.
And when he is suffering,
only I can give him peace.
Now that you can't change anything,
aren't you just convincing
yourself of that?
Without expecting anything
more than that?
Of course.
When you learned that the princess
doesn't remember anything about Miko,
you secretly rejoiced in your heart.
How can you say that?!
While claiming to be devoted to Miko's happiness,
you actually feel the opposite.
Who are you to be saying that?!
I am you.
Your own heart.
I wonder why I feel at peace
when I look at the Wailing Planet.
Utsu no Miko,
I am very sorry.
I just can't remember you,
no matter how hard I try.
Your story sounds a lot like a dream.
May I?
Are you talking to me?
What seems to be the matter?
Where...
Where am I?
It seems you're telling the truth about
not knowing what the pleasure quarter is.
Pleasure quarter?
Here, men and women
forget their sufferings
and lose themselves
in fleeting pleasures.
Now that I think of it,
I haven't seen you here before.
I came from the Earthly Realm.
I went to see Kaguya,
the princess of the Moon Palace.
However, the princess didn't have any...
memories of me.
This is not such an uncommon occurrence here in the Heavenly Realm.
The princess was once sent to the pleasure quarter too, for toying with the hearts
of the men who had feelings for her.
Having witnessed her grieving,
the gods have given the princess
another chance.
She would be reborn as a princess in the Earthly Realm,
and by meeting a young man with a pure soul there,
she could atone for all her sins.
The princess...
It was you, wasn't it?
The one who saved Princess Kaguya, restoring her to the Heavenly Realm.
The reason the princess
doesn't remember her past
is that the gods wanted her
to start with a clean sheet.
So that's why I had to meet her?
I see.
Knowing that gives me
some peace of mind.
Now...
Let us make love, the flower of life.
If I make your heart tremble, I might also return to the Heavenly Realm.
Now, let us have some wondrous time.
What seems to be the matter?
I'm sorry.
But...
Kaguya?
No, there's no way it's her.
And yet, what a strangely familiar flute.
Who could be playing it?
Kagami?
Kagami!
Miko!
Miko...
Never...
Never leave me again!
Why are you here?
I don't know myself.
I was here when I woke up.
Miko, what happened to us?
Perhaps,
it was another trial given to us by Master Ozunu.
Utsu no Miko...
We're heading for the Heaven of the 33,
the stronghold of Taishakuten and his clan.
Miko!
Miko, look there!
It's a deep-seated grievance
that has become an evil spirit!
Careful! It's sucking us in!
Chant the incantation!
Rin. Pyo. To.
Sha. Kai.
Jin. Retsu.
Zai. Zen.
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai.
Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Tell me, O evil spirit,
what is the grievance that tortures you?
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin.
Retsu.
Zai.
Zen!
Calm your anger!
Such overwhelming power of hatred...
It's you,
King Asura!
Why did King Asura block our path?
His hatred remained in this land
and took the form of an evil spirit.
That's how deep King Asura's anger is.
Then, Miko, is this island his...
This is probably King Asura's residence
when he lived in the Heavenly Realm.
This is cruel. Too cruel.
We split up here. Kijimuna and I
will go to the Heaven of the 33
to fulfill my promise to King Asura.
I will face Taishakuten and ask
for the king's reinstatement.
What about us?
Wait for us to come back.
In the meantime, try to soothe
King Asura's anger with your prayers.
Got it.
Miko, be careful.
Okay.
This is the Heaven of the 33.
A golden phoenix is descending.
Well, isn't it a ship?
Who might you be?
I wish to speak to Taishakuten.
Can you tell me where to find him?
The king likes to hunt.
Taishakuten went
to the star hunting grounds.
Star hunting grounds?
A place for enjoyable hunting.
Master Miko, let's wait until he returns.
Going there defenseless is dangerous.
You saw that lighting, didn't you?
I know. I never intended
to meet him in person.
We'll fly after Taishakuten
with our astral projections.
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Attack!
Catch that one!
Is that Taishakuten?
Incredible.
Something over there!
Master Miko!
Are you okay?
Didn't I tell you it was dangerous?
No need to worry.
He only shot my astral projection.
Taishakuten is truly fearsome.
Master Ozunu...
In this world of raging gods and Buddhas,
am I a fool for trying to challenge
the king of the gods,
Taishakuten himself?
I don't care if I'm a fool or not.
I am Utsu no Miko, a courageous soul from the Earthly Realm.
I have come to meet Taishakuten!
Open the gate!
I wonder if Master Miko will manage on his own.
I just hope he doesn't get too reckless.
Maybe I should've gone with him, after all.
The mere thought of meeting Taishakuten
face to face gives me chills.
I saw her at the star hunting grounds.
Do you think she came
from the Earthly Realm?
Yeah.
Who are they talking about?
K-Kagami!
Utsu no Miko, you are permitted to meet with Taishakuten.
Taishakuten makes his appearance!
Utsu no Miko?
Yes.
Come closer.
Who are you?!
Wait, please!
I came to the Heavenly Realm
with my body of flesh and blood.
I understand your suspicion
at my lack of a spiritual body.
But let me reassure you
that I can be trusted!
Why did you come
to the Heavenly Realm?
To learn something, no matter how small,
that would be useful in the Earthly Realm!
I want the Earthly Realm
to be a paradise where everyone can live prosperously.
Paradise?
Do you really think that is possible?
It has been a long time since the gods and Buddha left the Earthly Realm.
As long as a human remains a human,
there won't be a paradise on Earth.
There has to be at least something we can do to help the people!
Those in power keep hoarding infinite wealth for themselves,
while the common people are suffering in misery!
Why did the gods decide to turn a blind eye to it?!
Those in power are only a handful in the sea of suffering.
As long as there is an Earthly Realm,
there will be no peace for anyone in it!
I know you're worried for Miko and all,
but sneaking out like that really is unfair.
I'm sorry, but...
If you go, you'll just be a hindrance to him!
A-Anyway...
All we can do now is wait.
So pretty!
K-Kagami!
Kagami...
I have a favor to ask of you.
Can you restore King Asura
and his family to the Heavenly Realm?
King Asura!
He said "Asura."
Can I?!
Why are you working with the likes of him
on restoration to the Heavenly Realm?
I want to know what you think of it.
Can't everyone let bygones be bygones
if the laws of the gods
and Buddha permit it?
Is this what the gods judged?
I want to hear your thoughts!
Wait, Utsu no Miko!
Are you trying to defy the gods' decree?
I'm not!
But as someone from the Earthly Realm,
I can understand King Asura's suffering!
Taishakuten defiled King Asura's daughter.
As a parent, his outrage is entirely natural.
If anything, the one to blame for it is clearly you, Taishakuten!
You foolish lowlife!
You have no idea what it's like to control the enraged spirit of a god!
You couldn't even control the pacified soul of one!
Taishakuten!
No! Begone! Begone! Begone!
Why...
Why was King Asura punished?
Why was Taishakuten forgiven?!
Please forgive us!
Kagami!
Miko!
Miko! Help me!
Kagami...
Kagami!
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Master Miko.
Kijimuna!
Taishakuten...
Taishakuten took Kagami!
If I... If only I was in my normal form...
Taishakuten…
You'll pay for this!
Where am I?
I swore that my body and soul would always belong to Miko.
Why is this happening?!
Miko...
Kagami.
Whenever I needed something,
you were always right there, by my side.
We sought strength together
in times of trouble.
We laughed together in times of joy.
We were the best of friends.
At times, we were even closer than siblings!
Why is my mind in such turmoil?!
I can't believe it.
Why would Taishakuten...
I don't want to believe it either.
But the fact is, he took Kagami.
How could a god do such a thing?
Gods are...
essentially, the same as humans.
Back then, I cornered the king,
so he even ran out of his stronghold!
I saw it! When the king appeared,
he was riding his horse like mad.
I may have planted seeds
of doubt in the king's heart.
To pay me back, he took Kagami.
Unforgivable.
Just as Asura cried out in fury when Shachi was taken,
I am crying out now!
But Miko, how can you fight a god?
If you start a fight with a god here,
forget reinstating Asura.
Even staying in this realm
will become difficult.
When I think about how Kagami feels in captivity,
my whole body trembles with anger!
This hatred...
cannot be quenched
except by fighting him!
But Master Miko, you can't defeat
Taishakuten in a battle.
I'll go there.
I want to make it up to Kagami.
It's the best I can do right now!
Wait!
Master Miko!
Miko!
You, who can feel my anger...
You who can feel this rage, enough to shake the heavens and split the Earth,
condemn the crimes
of the savage gods!
Pass your judgment on Taishakuten!
Come on, get lost!
You're not passing through here!
I did not come here to deal with you! Open the gate!
Who do you think you are?!
We have an intruder!
He's inside the stronghold!
Get him!
Stop him!
Out of my way!
Don't try to stop me!
No time for this!
He landed on the top of the tower. There!
Follow me! Get him!
Hurry up!
He's over there!
Nowhere else to run!
What was that?
Where are you, Taishakuten?!
What?
33 Gods!
33 Gods,
don't stand in my way.
I will face Taishakuten, no matter the cost!
We don't care about your nonsense.
You are not supposed to be here.
Go back!
Go back now!
Why, O gods?!
As gods, you must know
the reason I'm here!
Why are you still blocking my path?!
I won't back down,
even if my body shatters into pieces.
Taishakuten!
Come out now!
Come and face me!
Lord Taishakuten...
What?
If you want to pierce my body with lightning, do it!
Do you think something like that
will pacify my heart?!
You abducted Kagami!
Why?!
Taishakuten!
Tell the truth!
I don't know.
Don't tell me you don't know!
You had a reason for what you did...
at the star hunting grounds!
I don't know!
How cowardly.
Is that an act befitting a god?
What I hunted there was a swan.
Not a woman named Kagami!
Coward!
Is that the answer of a god?
If you're a god, your sins won't be judged, is that it?
Unforgivable!
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen!
It can't be...
It can't be Miko!
Amaterasu's ship?
Master Miko! Grab on!
Don't let Utsu no Miko escape!
Miko!
King, should we let them leave?
Utsu no Miko...
Forget about them.
Master Miko!
Kusuri... You came for me?
Miko, we all felt the same way as you.
Please understand that.
Miko!
For me... For me, Miko fought against a god,
knowing that the odds were impossible!
Miko!
We won't meet again.
K-Kagami!
The Heavenly Realm was
ruled by violent gods,
the kind Utsu no Miko
had never anticipated.
Will Miko be able to overcome
these difficulties and get
Kagami back?
Miko's journey in search of
his father in the northern sky
continues into eternity...
Love is everything
Wrapped in the palm of your hand
It makes us question the meaning of life
If in a single tear
There's a past that we can't take back
Then sure enough
There's a new tomorrow
Beyond the door of sadness
Ah, your eyes... ah, more mysterious
Than even the blue stars light-years away
Every blink of your eyes makes time stop
Shattering it into a myriad of fragments
Episode 6: "Vengeful Gods Hunting"
The Army of the 33 Gods
is pursuing Miko.
With Uokai's strength resurrected on their side, the heroes enter a new battle.
Will Miko be able to take Kagami back?
Find out in Episode 6:
"Vengeful Gods Hunting."
Next Episode
Vengeful Gods Hunting
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 7: "A Pity! A Divine Being Is Dying"
Miko's anger is his only weapon
against the savage gods.
He fights his enemies and his anxiety
as the son of a god.
In the Heavenly Realm that has now become a battlefield,
the sincerity of the dream-interpreting maiden turns into flowers and scatters.
Look forward to Episode 7:
"A Pity! A Divine Being Is Dying."
Next Episode
A Pity! A Divine Being Is Dying
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 8: "Phantom of the Flower Forest"
Challenging gods while aiming to become one himself,
Miko is injured in a fierce battle
and collapses.
But he keeps moving,
even when he can't stand.
Can there really be salvation
on the path Miko had chosen?
Look forward to Episode 8:
"Phantom of the Flower Forest."
Next Episode
Phantom of the Flower Forest
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 9: "Crossing the Sea for Love"
The thousand-slashes sword is born
from a heart of resentment.
It is the sword of universal creation
that brings everything back to life.
Upon seeing Princess Saho, who persists in her love despite betrayal,
the doubts disappear from Miko's heart.
Look forward to Episode 9:
"Crossing the Sea for Love."
Next Episode
Crossing the Sea For Love
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 10: "Purification by the Sun"
To know a god's heart,
Miko endures a raging god's spirit.
To connect with the dreams of the oppressed people, he prays for a pacified spirit.
Miko puts his all into this final battle.
Look forward to Episode 10:
"Purification by the Sun."
Next Episode
Purification by the Sun
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 11: "The Dance of Reunification"
Miko and Kagami suffer and seek each other,
because they believe in each other's love.
The lives of young people
who endure trials in shackles
are enveloped and cherished by
the compassion of the great Bodhisattva.
Look forward to Episode 11:
"The Dance of Reunification."
Next Episode
The Dance of Reunification
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Episode 12: "Falling Leaves Return to the Roots"
What is a finite life?
Miko puts himself in his new role and questions his way of life.
Desiring happiness for the people,
he burns with scorching flames.
Each of our young heroes is burned by the hands of Mahavairocana.
Look forward to Episode 12:
"Falling Leaves Return to the Roots."
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
Next Episode
Falling Leaves Return to the Roots
Episode 13: At Journey's End, Our Noble Miko...
As Miko burns his small life to challenge
the mighty power of the Heavenly Realm,
he seeks the truth at the end of a journey of hardship.
Make the gods aware of your life as a single human.
Look forward to the final episode:
"At Journey's End, Our Noble Miko..."
Next Episode
At Journey's End, Our Noble Miko...
Rin. Pyo. To. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen!
Next Episode
At Journey's End, Our Noble Miko...
Translation
Timing
Editing & Typsetting
QC
Encoding
Odyssey Anime
Perevodildo
ninjacloud
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair
Paul Geromini
Topper3000
anonymous