The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
October of 1944. A landing party and a convoy fleet,
led by Field Marshal MacArthur, assembled in the Leyte Gulf.
The 2nd Fleet under Vice Admiral Kurita Takeo
was dispatched on a mission to destroy this American Fleet.
Composed of the battleships Yamato, Musashi, Nagato,
as well as the heavy cruiser Atago and various screens,
Japan's crown fleet, numbering 39 ships,
sortied from Brunei Bay in Borneo.
Mindoro
Luzon
Palawan
Philippines
San Bernardino Strait
Samar
Leyte
Surigao
Surigao Strait
Brunei
Mindanao
Borneo
This plan was called "Sho: Part 1."
It was a contingency plan,
devised by a cornered IJN, to restore its position.
Ozawa's Task Force
To be precise, using the aircraft carrier
Zuikaku as his flagship,
Vice Admiral Ozawa was to deploy
his task force of 17 ships as a decoy
north of Luzon Island with the intention
of luring away the American TF 38.
Kurita's Fleet
Nishimura's Fleet
In the meantime, Kurita's Fleet
was divided into two.
Vice Admiral Nishimura's 2nd Squadron was to pass through the Surigao Strait and infiltrate Leyte Gulf from the south.
The main force of Kurita's Fleet, however,
was to pass through the San Bernardino Strait
and reach Leyte Gulf
by creeping along the coast of Samar.
Shima's Fleet
In addition, Vice Admiral Shima's 2nd Striking Force
was to reinforce Nishimura's 2nd Squadron later.
Episode 22
Battle of Leyte Gulf (Part 2)
However, their voyage was a series of misfortunes.
First, having just barely entered
the Palawan Passage on October 23rd,
the flagship Atago and the heavy cruiser Maya
sank after getting torpedoed by a US submarine.
Takao was also all but wrecked.
Several Japanese cruisers approaching!
Attack immediately! Attack and attack more!
Next, on the 24th,
in the Sibuyan Sea, 260 combined sorties
by American carrier-based planes
sunk the super-heavy battleship Musashi.
Heavy cruiser Myoko also came under attack.
Fire!
Stop shooting the main battery!
Still, even such heavy blows could not undermine
the morale of the crews on the 23 remaining Japanese ships.
That's because it was still possible for them to lure Admiral Halsey's "Big Blue Fleet" into a decisive naval battle.
On the dawn of the following day, the 25th, having skillfully passed though the demanding San Bernardino Straits,
they emerged off the coast of Samar Island,
which commands the entrance to the Lamon Bay.
The prelude to the Battle of Leyte Gulf, which we now know
as the IJN's most spectacular battle ever, was over.
It sure is quiet...
50 more kilometers to Leyte.
It's like there's no welcoming party at all!
Maybe they were tricked when we showed them
that we're turning back into the Sibuyan Sea.
Yeah...
More importantly, I wonder how is Ozawa's Fleet doing?
We haven't heard from them at all.
We could check on them from the signal room.
Sir. A signal from Kumano.
What is it?
Enemy ship at 110 degrees.
Enemy ship?
Enemy fleet spotted! 125 degrees. Distance - 37,000!
Hey, there's no way we could be that close to the enemy.
Are you sure you didn't mistake it? Take another look!
It's there. There! Ah!
There's a carrier too. We're in luck!
This alone makes coming here worth it!
What a relief. Sir, we'll get them, won't we?
If we see a convoy, we'll strike a convoy.
If a battlefleet shows up, we'll strike that.
Whatever we can get.
Sir, we're finally doing it, aren't we?
You idiot. What's there to cry about?
It was only natural.
They ran drill after drill,
preparing for a decisive battle with the enemy fleet.
But it was never a battle between fleets, per se.
Even if the order to attack a convoy was anticlimactic,
they were happy to finally let the battleship Yamato see some action.
After all, it was the IJN's cherished dream come true.
All ships into battle formation!
Line at 130! Turn to 110 degrees!
However, the Japanese weren't the only ones
to discover their enemy.
American spotters from Sprague's Taffy 3
could now see them too.
This means... We're like a shooting gallery to the Japs!
Alright! Dispatch all planes and set up a smoke screen. Order everyone to run for cover in that squall to the east!
Right, and give me the phone!
Which is the closest fleet?
Task Unit 77.4.2, call sign Taffy 2.
Stump! Rear Admiral Stump! Sprague speaking!
Not yet?
A little more!
Let's shoot!
Wait I said!
Let's shoot! Shoot!
Still not there, sir?
The destroyer is still not in position?
According to the tactics that Vice Admiral Kurita
had drawn in his mind,
battleships and cruisers would first wreck the decks of the enemy aircraft carriers,
so that the destroyers could then
use torpedoes to deliver a coup de grace.
Accordingly, they were now waiting
for the destroyers to be fully in position.
Let's shoot!
Oh! They're making their getaway.
Please let us shoot!
Sir!
Yes. Commence bombardment!
Fire!
1 minute and 7 seconds.
Yes!
The world's first super-heavy anti-ship cannon
on the battleship Yamato was fired in search of its first prey.
It takes 1 minute and 7 seconds
for a 1.5 ton shell to reach its target.
Plenty of time to change your course.
Impact!
First shell landed.
We came under fire from their main armaments!
At this rate, they'll bulldoze us in no time!
Please come quickly!
Sprague, listen! Don't give in to panic.
We're not leaving you to your fate.
Stay sharp, Sprague. Do what you have to!
Maybe it's not that bad, after all.
This isn't the time to relax.
They're just adjusting the range.
We're in a squall, sir.
It's like one big smoke screen for them.
We can't hit a target that we can't see.
It'll stop soon.
Though the main US Fleet was already informed of the situation, Vice Admiral Kurita still had a free hand.
However, this squall had truly become a godsend
for the US Navy, allowing them to prolong this battle.
Meanwhile, the American side used the pause to regroup
and increase their distance from Kurita's Fleet.
The screen of destroyers was finally set up.
Its finally our turn to retaliate!
Look for the big one first.
Okay. Their cannon has got to be ridiculously big!
Too big for its own good.
Even when a shell does find its target,
it just pierces through with no damage.
Well, isn't it about time?
Heavy cruiser ahead.
Distance 18,000!
Alright, attack with all we got!
Enemy cruiser is approaching!
Prepare to attack!
There are some gutsy men among the Americans too.
Fire!
Thus, the battle off Samar
was descending further into a free-for-all.
Fire!
Okay. Starboard now!
Good, let's find another target now!
Impact!
Yahoo!
Now, where's the next Jap?!
The enemy has it in them.
It was a textbook torpedo attack.
That's true.
Torpedo spotted!
Full to port!
Torpedo spotted from starboard!
A pincer movement?
Maintain the course!
It's like they're alive.
We can't steer to the right or left.
We have to follow their course
until the torpedoes run out of propellant.
So they've driven us out of line of battle, after all?
Chased away by torpedoes,
Yamato had to leave the line of battle.
The aircraft carriers Gambier Bay,
Fanshaw Bay, Kalinin Bay,
along with the destroyers Hoel, Samuel B. Roberts,
and Johnston, were either sunk or severely damaged.
Hits were also scored
on the other 4 ships of Taffy 3,
who were trying to set up a smoke screen
as best they can.
Rear Admiral Sprague,
who has been soliciting his allies for help all along,
went all the way to the top and reached out to Vice Admiral Kinkaid, in charge of defense of the Philippines.
However, Kinkaid was far away from the scene.
While he was relieved, having wiped out Nishimura's Fleet,
an escort carrier stationed in the bay
suddenly came under attack from a Japanese fighter.
Those were the Asahi and Kikusui units of the Kamikaze corps that sortied from Davao Base that day.
The attack of the Kamikaze corps paralyzed Vice Admiral Kinkaid, making him unable to dispatch a relief force.
Additionally, Sprague's fleet
sent a distress signal to Admiral Halsey.
Mindoro
Luzon
Palawan
Philippines
San Bernardino Strait
Samar
Leyte
Surigao
Surigao Strait
Brunei
Mindanao
Borneo
Kurita's Fleet
Nishimura's Fleet
Halsey's Fleet
Admiral Halsey was also too far away.
When Halsey, who saw
the enemy carrier fleet as their main objective,
was informed of the discovery of Ozawa's Fleet,
he brushed off Vice Admiral Kinkaid's request for protection
and steamed north in search of Ozawa's Task Force.
Thus, Ozawa's Fleet brilliantly fulfilled its decoy role,
luring Halsey's fleet away from the actual fighting.
One enemy aircraft carrier on fire!
Admiral Halsey, another telegram for you.
Kinkaid's complaints again?
Not that, sir. A transmission from Admiral Nimitz
at the Guam HQ.
What does Nimitz want? Read it.
WHERE IS REPEAT WHERE IS TASK FORCE THIRTY FOUR
We're fighting our asses off down here!
THE WORLD WONDERS
What? The world wonders?
What's that supposed to mean?
Does he think I'm dancing the hula-hula here or what?
That bastard!
He's just asking for help.
Nimitz and others don't know shit
about what's going on here!
What do we do?
Carney, we might as well help them out a little.
That's a real shame, though. I was looking forward
to seeing which trick Ozawa has up his sleeve this time.
Then, leaving Admiral Mitscher to handle the rest,
he personally led Task Force 34 back south.
Sir, things went almost exactly as we planned.
Ugaki, we've finally done it.
Right. At last, Yamato's super-heavy gun
got its chance to shine.
Sir, allow me...
Thank you.
What are the enemy losses?
3 to 4 enemy aircraft carriers are sunk,
including USS Enterprise.
Plus 2 armored cruisers.
The enemy has 1-2 carriers left at best.
I see.
All that's left for us is to raid Leyte Gulf
before the enemy reinforcements arrive.
No, actually, I was just considering our options...
Considering?
Haven't we done enough?
We got our long-awaited decisive naval battle.
And we won it.
Indeed, it was a terrific struggle.
If we proceed to raid Leyte now,
the relief fleet might really come.
The enemy is also tenacious. If they encounter
our fleet in this condition, they could savage us.
You're right, they might very well savage us.
However, we have orders to raid the Leyte Gulf itself.
I know that. Should we press on now,
at risk of losing the rest of the Japanese fleet,
or should we preserve it instead
to prolong the defense of Japan proper?
I won't stand for it.
After making it this far, isn't it just one last push?
We're entirely in the dark on that matter.
How are things going on Ozawa's side?
For Nishimura's Fleet we only know
that it was destroyed, but no details.
Where could the enemy be now?
What are our allies doing?
Indeed, there was no proper attempt to gather intel.
We have nothing.
And what became of Ozawa's Fleet?
I have reasons to believe that this is a fake telegram.
The enemy produced it.
A cleartext telegram from Halsey, saying
"I'll go there in 2 hours."
He'll go to their rescue in 2 hours?
Yes. It's a feint they often employ.
It's not unfamiliar to our side either.
Guess we're in trouble.
At that time, they did not yet know that Ozawa's Fleet performed its decoy role flawlessly, luring Halsey away.
Nor did they have any idea
that the Kamikaze corps' attack was successful.
We should proceed to raid Leyte.
That was the whole point of the current operation.
However...
Well, it's not like this matter is for me to decide.
How was it? Did you learn anything?
Nothing, sir.
I see. Still nothing?
Alright. Reverse course.
Okay!
Full to starboard!
Sir, what are you doing?
The enemy is that way!
Thus, without ever entering Leyte Gulf,
Kurita's Fleet suddenly reversed course and withdrew.
Japanese fleet retreats to the north!
That's ridiculous...
Their move to reverse course and retreat
before ever entering the Leyte Gulf
surprised the Combined Fleet Headquarters
in Hiyoshi above anyone else.
Combined Fleet Headquarters
Immediately upon learning
of Kurita's Fleet reversing course,
they radioed out a telegram of encouragement.
"With consideration to the damage, sustained by each fleet
and the sailors' hardships,
we believe you had every reason to take that decision.
But we also think that the enemy's predicament
is twice as bad as ours.
In this time of indecision, one has to be decisive
and muster the courage to break through indomitably.
You should press on with our hallmark strategy,
regardless of the losses.
Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet
from the signal room."
However, there was no fleet in sight, cutting through the waves in response to this encouragement.
They say that Kurita’s decision
to reverse course while on the enemy's doorstep
will forever remain a riddle
in the history of naval warfare.
But at that time,
Vice Admiral Kurita’s mind was preoccupied
with the thoughts of a decisive naval battle
and the satisfaction with today's battle results.
Mindoro
Luzon
Palawan
Philippines
San Bernardino Strait
Samar
Leyte
Surigao
Surigao Strait
Brunei
Mindanao
Borneo
Kurita's Fleet
But the lack of fuel and reliable information
on the movements of both enemies and allies,
was probably another recurring theme in everyone's mind.
This teaches us that important decisions
always require reliable information.
And the question of how to gather that accurate information
should be a central factor in taking any decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
June 1944.
Tasked with reinforcing Iwo Jima,
Lieutenant General Kuribayashi,
along with 22,000 troops,
began the construction of a base.
Lt. General Kuribayashi,
originally stationed in Chichijima,
was the closest corp commander who could be found.
He sees through the American plan to occupy Iwo Jima
and goes to Iwo Jima himself to command the defense.
Episode 23
Battle of Iwo Jima
Don't miss the next decision:
Battle of Iwo Jima.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2