The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
The reason the war in the Pacific started was because of Japan's southern strategy to acquire oil deposits.
Planning to cross the seas
and land right on the enemy's heads, this operation
was truly unprecedented in its scale
in the worldwide history of warfare.
For that operation, Lieutenant General Imamura
received under his command various task forces -
land, naval, aerial - each branch of the Japanese military
joined his 16th Army.
A large-scale combined operation was started.
On January 2, 1942,
Japanese troops occupied the Filipino capital of Manila.
Harnessing that momentum,
they turned their eye to the east of Borneo,
where just across the Makassar Strait,
the island of Celebes was targeted for the next operation.
As part of this Celebes Island operation,
the Southern Detachment of the Navy
drew up a plan for an attack with paratroopers.
Overseeing the preparations was Vice Admiral Tsukahara,
Commander-in-Chief of the 11th Air Fleet.
Our main body of several thousand troops
will head to Manado on the west coast.
But some detachments
would also land in Kema from the east.
We'll squeeze the enemy from both sides.
At the same time, the paratrooper battalion
lands in Langoan,
so as to capture Langoan's air base
and the freshwater supply in Kakas.
Are you suggesting we paradrop the troops
right on the enemy positions?
The enemy would be distracted, softened up for them.
He, who makes the first move, wins.
For the Japanese navy paratrooper corps,
being in the lead for this operation
meant announcing themselves to a world
they were unfamiliar with.
Episode 10
The Navy Paratrooper Corps
Let's win first, before making any more plans.
I know it's well planned out, but still, isn't it too reckless
to just drop the paratroopers right on the enemy's heads?
The mission of holding out in a pocket
would be extremely dangerous
for our paratrooper battalion with so few troops.
I am fully aware of the risks.
Please reconsider their drop zone.
My unit doesn't fear death.
But seeing to it that their lives aren't wasted...
It's already decided that capturing Celebes with the forces of the paratrooper battalion is the best plan.
But it is still possible to change the drop zone!
What matters now is to decide
on how to carry out the existing plan.
Our current preference is this strategy.
Nothing but that!
The value of paradrop tactics
is in catching the enemy by surprise,
thus seizing the initiative at a moment's notice.
Such has been proven in this war by countries like Germany.
Inspired by their successes, the Japanese navy
also gave birth to their own paratroopers corps in 1941.
While maintaining secrecy, the men comprising it
were put through life-threatening drills.
While the navy paratroopers were starting their descent
at 4 a.m., January 11th of 1942,
a coordinated naval landing right in the face of the enemy
was commenced both from the eastern
and the western coasts of Celebes.
Hurry to the airfield!
Hurry up to the airfield, before anything else!
Don't abandon the paratroopers at the enemy's mercy!
Don't let the paratroopers get captured!
Bluer than indigo,
To the skies, to the skies!
In an instant, it is full:
Countless parachutes open up
What a glorious sight it is,
Like the bloom of pure white roses!
Look at that! Parachutes are dropping from the sky
Look at that! Parachutes soar into the sky
Look at that! The parachutes soar into the sky
Manado
Kema
Kakas
Langoan
January 12th, 11:30 a.m.
The ground troops finally managed to link up
with the navy paratroopers.
No more than 31 hour had passed
since the operation started.
Murai, you son of a bitch!
Tateno, you son of a bitch.
That was one damn fine paradrop.
No, all thanks to your guys.
That assault was something.
I couldn't wait until we finally met.
Our guys rushed like hell.
Yeah, it's been damn ages.
Last time, in the military academy...
We used to gaze at the sky a lot.
Uh-huh. Good times.
The success of our paradrop
is rightly your success.
What are you talking about?
This was achieved through the close cooperation
of both our Special Navy Landing Forces.
Japan's paratroopers experiment
yielded a complete success.
For that feat alone, the paratroopers were
at the time dubbed
"The Divine Soldiers from the Sky,"
and enjoyed quite a following.
Mr. Paratrooper, swing me!
The paratroopers are all the rage,
wherever they go.
These days, they're Divine Soldiers from the Sky.
That's because their parachutes are a sight to behold.
Hey, you shouldn't be jealous of them.
I'm not. I know there's nothing to be jealous of.
Mr. Paratrooper, swing! Please swing me!
This makes the ground troops look like dirt.
Hey! Aren't we all comrades in arms,
sharing the same blood and flesh?
How can you say that?
Are you a paratrooper?
Oh... No, I'm not.
This here is a paratrooper.
Mr. Paratrooper, you absolutely must tell us about yourself.
Hey-hey, drop it.
I beg you! The children are getting under my skin!
I'm not a good teller...
You don't have to mind me.
I know how to be a good sport.
Quicker, quicker!
Murai, I'm sorry.
Whatever, I'm getting pretty used to it anyway.
Eh?
Mr. Paratroop! Mr. Paratroop, raise me!
Alright, come closer.
Up you go, kid!
Paratroopers are not doing it alone.
The soil of this goddamn Celebes Island
is soaked in the blood of our land assault troops as well!
Who's there?
Stop it! Break it up!
What is your unit?
Airborne corps.
A paratrooper, huh?
I was just...
I know already!
Return to your unit.
Return at once!
I was just...
No need. I know exactly how you feel about this.
These damn paratroopers are unbearably selfish!
They think they captured it all by themselves!
But when I think of my comrades
that lost their lives here, I can't stand it.
I understand. But what do you suppose we do about it?
If we leave it as it is,
both sides would have to sustain damage.
Isn't there any way we...
Your emotions are no mystery to me.
But all we do is just fall from the sky on our parachutes.
There must be some mistake in the way we do it now.
This whole "Divine Soldiers from the Sky" baloney
troubles us just as much.
That's just what I've been telling them.
But when I think of my subordinates, I cannot sleep.
Listen, Murai. You're just getting
unreasonably anxious over trifles.
Time will settle this by itself.
You think so?
So you still cannot understand how I feel about it?
Hey,
we're on the battlefield!
We may both get sent
to the front line tomorrow already.
Every single day, we put our lives on the line!
We've no time for such things.
Wait! Murai!
"Divine Soldiers from the Sky?"
Is this really the hero
that our warring nation craves?
Hey! Think you're the cream of the crop
just cause you're a paratrooper?
You prick! Quit pretending there are no other soldiers
but those with parachutes!
This hero is product of fantasy.
I have nothing but pity for him.
Sir, if we leave things as they are, the chasm between
the two branches will become ridiculously wide!
We have to think of some cure, and fast.
I believe, it'll have a lasting impact
on all our operational plans hereafter.
The paradrop operation
has been an astounding success.
Its few downsides can be safely overlooked!
I understand. But sir...
Battalion commander, the subject is exhausted.
Concentrate on current operations!
Roger.
The operation was successful beyond any expectations,
allowing us to hasten the fall of Java by a whole month.
It was because we we focused on the strategy.
This issue doesn't require any immediate decision from us.
The paratroopers will move on
to execute other operations.
Eh? The paratroopers corps is being transferred?
Apply your mind to the operation,
Battalion Commander.
For about a month more,
the paratroopers were staying on Celebes Island,
until finally, further south, the new battlefields
of Timor and Tarpan were calling out to them.
With the departure of the paratroopers,
the conflict between the ground forces and the paratroopers
seemed to have petered out by itself.
Hey, a few words please. Don't you have
some interesting story about the paratroopers battalion?
How about this?
While exchanging emotional handshakes with the paratroopers at the Kakas airfield, how did you feel? Do tell.
I got nothing!
Hey!
If you're so obsessed with writing about paratroopers,
why don't you go ask them directly?
Let's restrain from violence!
How would you feel if you had to chase after them, huh?!
I just wanted a story of camaraderie
between the paratroopers and you, ground forces!
Ptui! Camaraderie?
...with our paratroopers, that make the world envy us...
Camaraderie my ass!
Enough.
If you excuse me.
Apologize.
But... But Ensign...
Apologize!
I was wrong!
Take a look at this.
Wreathes are abound on the paratroopers' graves.
But not a single one on the ground troops' graves.
Does that make it any clearer for you
as to why that soldier before cried?
Yes, I got a story. There was a soldier who landed
with a parachute. He treated me with 5 of his cigarettes.
He was also very gentle when holding my child.
He was kind. A hearty soldier, however you look at it.
Please make sure to write my story.
They're an intrepid bunch.
They need a lot of strength to handle a parachute!
If you look at the local press,
the paratroopers are currently the only talk of the island.
Because they know acting this way would delight your ilk.
I know it's in your nature to always pick
the flashiest of stories for your job.
However, we, ground troops also had our share of fighting.
We shed the same blood,
crawled under the same bullets as our comrades.
Doesn't that make it clear to you,
where the animosity and hatred are coming from?
Come in.
Did you lose composure again?
Sir, yes sir!
How come the soldiers who fought conventionally
have to pick a fight with paratroopers nearly every night?
The guerrillas here received a professional drilling.
Make sure to take every precaution.
Roger.
Wait a minute!
I'm worried about that glee of confidence in your eyes.
You may think you're sufficiently prepared,
but you shouldn't get too carried away.
The objective of your mission is not to purge
all the guerrillas with one big sweep,
but instead - to wear them out with piecemeal patrols.
Roger!
It's of utmost importance to decide
when to stop the pursuit.
You absolutely shouldn't chase them too deep.
Ensign Murai's men were ordered by the
battalion commander to go on a garrison security duty.
Their task was handling the remnants of the Dutch troops,
who kept waging a guerrilla war inland of Celebes.
One should never forget that a soldier is still a human.
There's some bizarre mood in the air.
Well it's the first time in a while, isn't it?
No.
We're playing the leading role this time around!
We will become the talk of the town after this!
The fighting that day
was as though the soldiers
were venting the grudges of the past.
This resentment, that's been secretly mounting
in their chests for months
suddenly gushed forth in one big violent stream.
With a tremendous vigor,
they fought to destroy the guerrillas for good.
We're playing the leading role this time!
Focus on the operation.
Without focusing on the operation,
you can't get anything done.
No paratroopers to get in the way!
This time, they have no choice but to write about us!
Oblivious even to the fear of death,
the soldiers behaved, one might even say, way too violently.
They didn't know where to stop.
When chasing the enemy into the woods,
you can't go too deep.
In this suppression operation, the attacking side
suffered 7 casualties, including the platoon commander.
For a lopsided battle like that,
that casualty rate was abnormally high.
His subordinates became forgetful of a timely decision.
Unable to contain this urge, they kept charging forward
ruthlessly against their certain death.
What made them behave this way?
The astounding success of the Celebes operation
furnished the Japanese troops with great confidence
in the subsequent southern operations.
And yet, however insignificant, this particular battle,
is bound to make us give another thought
to the commander's words, said prior to it:
Focus on nothing but the operation.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
January 1942. Japanese forces occupy Manila,
the ultimate target of the Philippines campaign.
However, Supreme Commander General MacArthur's forces,
cornered at the Bataan Peninsula make a counter-attack.
The operation suffers a setback.
In the enormous dark jungle,
the Japanese army is suffering from starvation and malaria.
Their commander Lieutenant General Homma
is making a rash decision.
Episode 11
The Fall of Bataan and Corregidor
Don't miss the next week's decision:
The Fall of Bataan and Corregidor.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
Ace.Hiromichi Kato and Tak Pui Lo