The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
How many months have passed away from home?
Ready to face the same fate with the horse,
Attacking and conquering mountains and rivers
Blood flows through the reins I took up
In a pillbox we captured yesterday,
we are snoring loudly today
My dear horse, did you sleep soundly?
Tomorrow's fight will be tough
With its lyrics filled with love for a horse during wartime
and a playful melody, this song
was warmly received by the masses.
It would fall to the creator of these lyrics,
Lieutenant General of the Japanese army
Kuribayashi Tadamichi,
to send the world quivering in their boots
during the battle of Iwo Jima.
Located a measly 690 nautical miles from Tokyo, this island
is the southernmost of the Ogasawara Island Chain.
As the name implies,
it was originally only used as a sulfur (Iwo) mine.
Okinawa
Tokyo
Tinian
Guam
Saipan
Mariana Islands
Ogasawara Island Chain
Chichijima
Hahajima
Iwo Jima
On June 8th, 1944,
Chichijima
Hahajima
Iwo Jima
Mariana Islands
Ogasawara Island Chain
Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
was appointed the 109th Division commander,
tasked with organizing the desperate defense of this island.
Episode 23
Battle of Iwo Jima
Pleased to be working with you.
The pleasure is mine.
Never before had the Japanese army known an officer
who'd shake hands with subordinates.
During his time in the US and Canada as a military attaché,
Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
learned to be quite a dandy, and was in this regard a unique officer in the otherwise excessively formal Japanese army.
May we go on a tour through the island at once?
As you wish.
The airfield right in front of us is the Chidori Airfield.
Further in the distance, in the center,
is the Motoyama Airfield.
From the west, there's Mt. Osaka, Mt. Moto, and Mt. Tamana. Mt. Moto is the northernmost border of the island.
The longest point from the foot of Mt. Moto over there
is Mt. Suribachi in the south, in 8.3 km.
That narrow gorge near Chidorigahara is only 800 m.
I see. This place is a tough nut to crack.
Yes.
Yet, the enemy wants it badly.
To them, it's like an unsinkable aircraft carrier.
Also, it's a perfect springboard
for launching air raids on Tokyo.
Air raids on Tokyo?
It won't be long before they start doing that, yes.
By that time, the US Army leveled
the Marshall and Caroline Islands.
And was now poised for a strike on Saipan.
Ever since the fall of Saipan, it was only natural to expect a US attack on Iwo Jima next, which offers an air base,
laying twice as close to the Tokyo Metropolitan Area.
It being just a matter of time was apparent
to Lieutenant General Kuribayashi all the way through.
Then, can we look at the next installation?
Of course.
Salute!
Well done.
I'm not seeing any rivers at all.
The island has no freshwater.
No freshwater? But how...
Rainwater is all we got.
We collect it during squalls for later use.
Usually, you'd expect to find the
109th Division Commander Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
in the Ogasawara Island Chain headquarters on the nearby Chichijima, where it'd be easier to contact him.
However, having seen through the inevitable
American invasion of Iwo Jima,
he decided to personally take command
of the defending army.
During the next week, Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
toured the entire island with inspections.
The flat landscape.
Caves cut in sulfur.
Finally, a humid jungle.
Meanwhile, American bombers and fighters
kept showering Saipan
in bombs and machine gun fire.
Iwo Jima was almost entirely flat, the only exception the 169 m high Mt. Suribachi in the south.
This kind of flat terrain makes for a good airfield, but when it comes under attack, it's ridiculously difficult to defend.
Kuribayashi's plan was to build an underground base,
Mt. Suribachi
Chidori Airfield
Mt. Moto Airfield
Mt. Tamana
Mt. Osaka
Northern Airfield
Mt. Ama
Mt. Byoubu
East Coast
North Coast
West Coast
South Coast
from which they'd wage a guerrilla campaign,
devastating the enemy.
They settled on a depth of 30 meters
to construct this underground base on.
This large space on the 3rd underground floor is the hospital.
Hospital?
And these will be used
for communication between pillboxes.
The total length is expected to be about 25 km.
I certainly like your idea, but I really don't think
you should go that deep.
There's no point building a shelter
that can't withstand a 250 kg bomb hit.
However, the geothermal activity is high under this island,
with a lot of sulfur dioxide emissions.
The other day, as we were digging a well, just 10 meters
into the ground, it was already 45 degrees hot
and the rubber sole on the soldiers' shoes started melting.
Back then, because of all the poisonous gases,
we couldn't work for longer than 5 minutes on end.
Yes. Exactly so.
Iwo Jima is probably the most unsuitable place on earth
for any kind of underground works.
Still, we'll do just that.
Once Saipan falls to the enemy,
they'll rush full speed to here and Okinawa.
Here in particular, because we stand exactly midway
between Saipan and Tokyo.
They'd want it at any cost
for raiding our mainland.
If we want to protect our mainland,
we can't stop at anything, however hard it may be.
Please, help me achieve it.
What's worse, all the construction work
had to be done manually.
Hey, hang on!
Okay, next!
They could only work for 3 to 5 minutes at a time.
Staying there any longer was too unbearable.
Nevertheless, the construction progressed steadily.
This way, the pillbox is too exposed.
You'd better dump more sand here.
Yes! Understood.
Those enemy planes. They're not here just to scout.
They're always taking pictures.
For example, if they see a pillbox here, and a trench there,
they'll mark those as targets in advance.
That's why the camouflage is so important.
Sir!
Air raid! Enemy plane coming!
Report to your stations!
Hey!
Hang on!
That night, Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
wrote a letter to his wife.
"I will be brief.
I'm sure all of you are the same as when I left you.
I'm doing fine so far,
though one can hardly lead a life more hellish.
The enemy air raids are becoming an everyday routine.
Before long, they'll land on the island in force.
The defenders are all unwavering
in their resolve to gain glory in death.
And of course, so am I.
In the end, we're all just weak humans.
When standing face-to-face with death,
his family is the one thing on everyone's mind.
And so, please keep yourself safe
and live for as long as you can.
I'm grateful to you
for propping me up through all these years.
Above all, take good care of the children for me."
Though he told them he's prepared for the worst,
the reality of Iwo Jima was even direr than that.
With this letter, he made it clear to his family
that his bones would be buried here on the island.
Ogasawara Island Chain
Chichijima
Hahajima
Iwo Jima
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
Tinian
The US Army seized Saipan, Guam, Tinian, and the rest of Mariana Island Chain
to use them as a springboard
for air raids on Japan proper.
The next step would be capturing Iwo Jima,
offering a base right on the way.
The course of their intentions has been made clear.
Aiming to bolster the defense of Iwo Jima,
the Army high command
dispatched to the island a tank unit under
Major Nishi Takeichi, the Olympic gold medalist equestrian.
A famous pilot, Rear Admiral Ichimaru Toshinosuke,
along with marines and a construction battalion of the 27th Air Squadron under his command,
also disembarked on the island.
Consequently, the defenders of the measly 20 square kilometers that is Iwo Jima,
mainly - Kuribayashi's 109th Division,
numbered 15,500 Army personnel
and 7,000 Navy personnel.
After the reinforcements had finally been stationed,
senior officers held a strategy meeting.
As a division commander,
I couldn't be happier to have your support.
That's because I still need several official approvals,
authorizing me to defend this island to the last.
As you have already seen, this island is indeed devoid of any natural fortress features that favor the defender.
Only the flat open terrain.
That's why I built a fortress of our own, underground.
And my goal is to defend this place
for as long as I can, until the very last man.
Indeed, I was deeply impressed
by the terrific fortifications you've erected.
So, what kind of strategy would you employ
when the enemy attacks?
Before, our army's conventional wisdom dictated
that in the case of island defense,
a beachfront tactic is to be adopted,
where we deploy our line artillery on the shore
and use it to shell any fleet that approaches.
I plan to deviate from that.
Why is that?
The artillery at our disposal only includes 12 320-mm guns,
22 150-mm guns,
and some other guns less than 15 cm in caliber.
With these, you can't hope to seriously damage any warship, let alone sink it.
Therefore, our plan is to let them land, lure them to the center of the island, and squash them there.
Very well. I support it.
Thank you.
Which brings me to one more favor I'd like to ask for.
Whatever happens, don't order a banzai charge.
If I may, what do you mean by that?
No matter how few soldiers you have left,
keep manning your positions and don't attack.
Lately, we've been encouraged to order a desperate charge
with a "banzai" shout when the end is near.
However, this tactic only hastens the ultimate defeat.
Our mission is to protect the island for as long as we can,
be it even for a day or half a day more.
Please keep this in mind.
The final decision will only be passed down by me.
Until then, defend your positions
and fight with a goal of attaining a 10:1 casualty rate.
I shall follow your orders to the letter.
Now, the focus shifted from defeating the enemy
to defending the island for as long as possible.
This strategy was a result of careful deliberation
on how to delay the decisive battle for the mainland.
Kuribayashi may have also entertained
the idea of leading a suicide charge
while chanting "banzai,"
scattering their lives like cherry blossoms.
Perhaps, he was also once determined
to go down in the most honorable fashion.
However, he made a decision
to leave honor behind.
On February 19th, 1945,
morning came to Iwo Jima.
On the ocean surface, glittering in the morning sun,
the 3rd, 4th, and 5th US Marines divisions,
the landing party of 75,144 men total
congregated in an enormous formation.
The landing support force under Rear Admiral Mitscher
included 17 fleet carriers
and numbered 495 ships total.
The number of amphibious support personnel
climbed all the way up to 111,300.
Secretary of the Navy Forrestal
was also closely involved with the operation.
Their plan was to forcefully overrun the area in one fell swoop.
After we've expended so many shells in these last 3 days,
it's no wonder the Japanese took flight.
No, they've not gone anywhere.
They are just lurking in a cave somewhere.
Over the course of 3 days leading up to this day,
the 20 square kilometers of Iwo Jima
have been subjected to the heaviest bombardment yet.
120 tons of bombs. 2,254 rocket shells.
100 napalm shells also rained from the sky.
The 5th Fleet showered the island in 38,550 rounds,
fired from guns ranging from 16 inches to 5 inches.
Once the bombardment was concluded, the first wave
of 500 landing craft with 15,000 marines went ashore.
Start the attack!
Commanded by Lieutenant General Kuribayashi,
the operation has achieved its desired effect.
The death toll for the American side
was 2,420 men already.
Other losses included 35 tanks and other armored vehicles,
as well as 100 landing craft.
By evening, over 30,000 men of the US Army
landed on the island, along with their materiel.
The US landing party advanced on Mt. Suribachi first, then Chidori Airfield, Cliffs of Byoubu, and Motoyama Airfield.
Lieutenant General Kuribayashi's strategy
of using the caves for uncontested movement
produced the expected effect,
stopping the US Marines in their tracks.
Still, on the 23rd,
after a day and night of brutal fighting,
at last, the marines raised a flag atop Mt. Suribachi,
the highest peak of Iwo Jima.
All the Japanese troops, opposing them
died in a banzai charge.
Mt. Suribachi has fallen.
Way to go, boys!
In just a few more kilometers,
the rest of the island will fall.
However, it took them 23 days
to cover said few more kilometers.
The signs of fatigue finally set in
among the Japanese troops,
who had used up all of their
water, provisions, and ammunition.
It was around this time, when the encouragement from the mainland had arrived in the form of a radio broadcast.
Still,
how many were there left
able to answer this call?
Before long, the caves in the north
became the only remaining holdout.
So Lieutenant General Kuribayashi
telegraphed his farewell to Tokyo.
"The war has reached the final stages.
All bullets have been fired, not a drop of water is left.
As we prepare to stage the final battle,
to all those remaining in the fight,
I hereby bid my eternal farewell."
"All units will attack at midnight on the 17th,
fighting to the last man."
Thinking it dishonorable for him to return home,
he issued an attack order,
fighting at the front line until the very end.
On the morning of 27th,
joined by his Chief of Staff Takaishi and Staff Officer Nakane, he used a pistol to finish off his injured body.
Even knowing they would ultimately fall,
he kept morale high and casualties low
by expressly forbidding any banzai charges.
The Lieutenant General's decision to take personal command and keep fighting to the bitter end
resulted in the American losses exceeding
those of the Japanese Army for the first time in the war.
Accordingly, that decision and his commander's attitude
are still highly regarded even to this day.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
On April 1, 1945, American troops began landing on Okinawa.
Fed up with the Okinawa garrison commander Lieutenant General Ushijima's self-sufficient approach,
the Combined Fleet Headquarters dispatch Yamato,
along with her 2nd Fleet to assist them.
Thus, the world's biggest super-battleship Yamato
set out on a one-way trip to Okinawa.
Episode 24
The End of the Combined Fleet
Don't miss the next decision:
The End of the Combined Fleet.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
JMS Translation