The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Kamchatka
Okhotsk Sea
Aleutian Islands
Kuril Islands
Paramushir
Pacific Ocean
Attu
Kiska
Amchitka
Operations at Midway and the Aleutian Islands were carried out in June 1942 by the main force of the Japanese Navy.
The Midway Operation ended in a devastating defeat for the Japanese armed forces, the first one of this war.
Kiska Island
Kiska Volcano
Kiska Bay
Little Kiska Island
But the Aleutian Operation achieved the occupation of Attu and Kiska without any resistance from the US whatsoever.
Episode 16
Evacuation of Kiska
Kiska Island is about 40 km long and 10 km wide.
It is enclosed in ice and snow all year round.
Even in the summer, a thick fog enshrouds it
with the temperatures often dropping below freezing.
Originally, the Japanese operational goals for the Aleutians
were to deny the use of the northern naval bases
by American task forces.
Here, on Kiska Island, the northern sea garrison commander Major General Mineki
was stationed with about 5,600 Army and Navy personnel.
Sir.
The Northern Army's reconnaissance aircraft reports:
apparently, at some point, the enemy built
an air base on the neighboring island of Amchitka.
What?
It seems, the Americans went on the offensive everywhere
after the battle of Guadalcanal in the south.
Have they finally reached the north too?
Amchitka is about 90 nautical miles away from Kiska.
Attu
Kiska
Amchitka
Naturally, the air raids on Attu Island
will also be more intense now.
Kiska and Attu are important northern bases for us.
We have to protect them at all costs.
Air raid!
The Imperial Headquarters immediately began bringing in
reinforcements to Attu Island and Kiska Island.
On May 11th,
Escorted by the US North Pacific fleet
under Rear Admiral Thomas C. Kinkaid,
approximately 11,000 US troops
began landing on Attu Island.
Commanded by Colonel Yamazaki, the garrison
of about 2,500 Japanese soldiers fought back fiercely.
But on May 30th, at last, it was annihilated.
For the first time, the Japanese Army
used the phrase "honorable death" to describe this event.
The US Army that recaptured
Attu Island from the Japanese,
set up a naval blockade in the Northern Pacific
to starve out the isolated island of Kiska.
Finally, the Imperial Headquarters approved the evacuation of the isolated island of Kiska with submarines.
In other words, the retreat order was issued.
The US Pacific Fleet watched the island closely,
making any evacuation efforts extremely difficult.
The enemy attacks are more intense by the day.
It's only a matter of time before they land on Kiska too.
We must complete the evacuation
of the island garrison before that happens.
The enemy is on high alert.
They already sunk several of our submarines.
How many have escaped via submarines?
Out of 5,639 men...
820.
So only 15%?
A submarine can only take
up to 80 men on board at a time.
Staff Officer Fujii.
Sir?
Head to Paramushir.
I need you to convince the Northern Army Headquarters
to evacuate the island all at once with the surface fleet.
This needs to be done as soon as possible.
This is probably the last time
we can speak on the matter of evacuation.
On June 16th, the submarine carrying Staff Officer Fujii
safely left the Kiska waters.
On the 20th, it arrived at Paramushir on Kuril Islands.
In the Paramushir port,
part of the Northern Fleet,
the 5th Fleet, under the command
of Vice Admiral Kawase was anchored.
The local commander urges for an evacuation
by means of the surface fleet.
The way things have been up to now,
our submarine fleet took a serious beating.
The evacuation via submarines has to stop either way.
Will a large enough fleet really be able to sneak
past the enemy's watchful eye and make it to Kiska?
That is the main problem.
Add to that, there's no hope for air cover.
This plan
is straight-up madness.
On Kiska, 5,000 of our comrades
are holding out in spite of the enemy onslaught.
Was one Attu Island not enough?
It takes 10 days at least to get to Kiska and return.
Because any large formation would have to bring along a tanker,
this operation is unfeasible by the surface fleet.
I can't say I have much confidence in our navy.
If only we had someone who could thread the needle
with such a big formation, we could do it.
Unfortunately, in our entire fleet...
There is one.
Call him. Kimura the Mustache.
Rear Admiral Kimura was the seafarer who transferred his flag to the light cruiser Abukuma some mere 10 days ago
to assume command of the 1st Destroyer Flotilla.
He was known as Kimura the Mustache.
I accept it.
Thank you.
You'd do us a great favor.
The enemy has excellent radar at their disposal.
We also have an ace up our sleeves.
Oh?
It's one of Japan's oldest stealth techniques:
disappearing into the mist.
What?
The fog is thick around Kiska Island.
If we make use of the fog,
we'll have the upper hand.
I see.
Thus, the daring plan for the evacuation of Kiska that relied solely on the North Sea fog, was set in motion.
In an evacuation operation,
the fog is our closest ally.
But this fog will become thinner by August.
If we're doing it, we have to complete it by mid-July.
How many Daihatsu-class boats do they have there?
Probably around 10 are operable.
If so, boarding alone would take a long time.
Alright, let's carry them on 12 ships.
The biggest hurdle here is appointing
the location and time for our rendezvous with the troops.
If we choose the wrong spot,
we won't make it out of Kiska alive.
The venue is Kiska Bay.
Kiska Island
Kiska Bay
Little Kiska Island
The rendezvous time
is 5 days after our Rescue Fleet sails.
In the next 3 hours after the sun sets.
And if the fog clears and we can't approach Kiska?
Tell them to be prepared for it every day at the same time.
Evacuation is a covert operation.
Exercise extreme caution when contacting them.
The Rescue Fleet sets sail from Paramushir on July 7th.
Our garrison will assemble at Kiska Port
at sunset on the 11th.
Do not leave a single soldier behind.
When will the rescue fleet make it here?
They won't come here just for us.
They're leaving us to the same fate as Attu.
July 7th, 1943. The Rescue Fleet
under Major General Kimura,
composed of 2 light cruisers, 10 destroyers,
one tanker, and one escort ship.
With a total of 14 ships,
they left from Paramushir Port on the Kuril Islands.
The fog looks excellent.
No, don't get too optimistic just yet.
But even under the cover of fog,
if the enemy spots us, our goose is cooked.
Stay 500 nautical miles away
from the enemy air base.
Attu Island
Kiska Island
Japanese Fleet
As planned, the rescue fleet has reached the point
500 nautical miles southwest of Kiska on July 12th.
After refueling, they set course for Kiska.
However, when it was time to carry out
the evacuation, the fog cleared up.
Indeed, what is it if not an ironic quirk of nature?
Sir.
Our resolve is to do it or die trying.
Let's do it!
Sir. All the ships are urging to break formation.
The fog might return by the time we get to Kiska.
Why don't we return to safety
and wait for another chance?
Impossible. We haven't enough fuel.
Then, why don't we withdraw to Paramushir
and try again another day?
We won't be able to do that either.
With current fuel shortages,
they won't have enough for a formation this big.
Are we marooning the Kiska garrison, then?!
Sir.
Sir, what's your call?
Turn back.
If we turn back now,
we can come again another time.
Later that day, the Kiska garrison,
waiting intently for the appearance of the rescue fleet,
received a telegram,
signaling the cancellation of their evacuation.
Once again, the Kiska garrison plunged into desperation.
The scenes of their comrades on Attu Island going down in a banzai charge
were brought back to life in their imagination.
Alright.
How about this?
Making use of this opportunity, why don't I move here?
Then, don't mind me attacking here.
Good move, but it's too little too late.
Oh? Well, that's quite a pickle!
I was a little careless there.
Spotting the enemy's carelessness
and exploiting it is the key to victory.
Huh?
Sir.
What is it?
The sea between Paramushir and Aleutians is in fog.
How many days will it last?
Sir. Five days...? Probably five days at least.
Alright!
Is that so?
What day is it today?
July 19th, sir.
At this point, let us leapfrog to the events of July 30th,
about 10 days after July 19th,
so as to peek at the situation on the American side.
From the 30th on, the American North Pacific Fleet
was pounding Kiska daily with naval artillery fire.
The US Commandos were finally about to invade Kiska.
The Kiska Island environs were entirely blockaded
by the American North Pacific Fleet,
rendering any possible relief efforts
of the Japanese fleet utterly futile.
On August 14th, the US Army
finally launched the landings on Kiska.
A total of 91 ships supported the landing.
Over 34,000 troops took part in the operation.
Where the hell did the Japanese go?
Probably headed for the hills.
On Kiska Island, they found nothing but 3 stray dogs.
The Japanese garrison evacuated in full.
In this operation, due to multiple instances of friendly fire
erupting from tension and panic among the troops,
the American losses were 25 dead and 31 wounded.
In a major blockade running operation,
the entire 5,000-strong Japanese garrison was evacuated to safety from right under the nose of the US Fleet.
The mystery of their escape
was shrouded in thick North Sea fog.
Let us once again return
to the Japanese perspective on July 19th.
Sir!
What is it?
The sea between Paramushir and Aleutians is covered in fog.
How many days will it last?
Sir. In any case, I believe
this is the final fog of the summer.
Alright.
Is that so?
What day is it today?
July 19th, sir.
On July 22nd, just as the thick fog reappeared, the Rescue Fleet left Paramushir for the second evacuation operation.
This fog is perfect for us.
Let's just hope it doesn't clear up.
Aboard the light cruiser Kiso, Staff officer Fujii
prayed for the safety of his comrades on Kiska Island.
This time for sure, we'll pull it off
without a hitch. Just you wait.
If the enemy lands, these fellows ain't having it easy.
You guys make sure to survive, you hear?
The rescue fleet set sail from Paramushir!
Are you sure?
We're finally going home this time!
Is it true?
Thank god!
I'm fed up with Kiska!
I received a telegram saying they left today!
The men of the Kiska Island garrison were delighted.
However, the entrance to Kiska Bay
was still observed closely by two American destroyers.
Around that time, one American reconnaissance plane
detected with its radar what seemed like seven Japanese ships 200 nautical miles southwest of Attu Island.
Attu Island
Kiska Island
The US North Pacific Fleet gathered at the point designated by the reconnaissance plane on July 25th,
prepared to ambush the Japanese fleet.
Attu Island
Kiska Island
American North Pacific Fleet
However, as it turned out later,
they unleashed hell on a Japanese ghost fleet.
The American fleet, operating the reconnaissance plane
never realized their radar malfunctioned.
What their radar mistook for the Japanese fleet
was just an echo from a nearby island.
In this attack, the US Fleet bombarded
the cold North Pacific waters with over 1,000 shells.
At that time, the Japanese Rescue Fleet
Japanese Rescue Fleet
Attu Island
Kiska Island
was leisurely resupplying and biding its time
at a distant point about 500 nautical miles
southwest of Kiska Island.
Dammit! The fog cleared up again.
Second verse same as the first.
Maybe we were too late
and the foggy season has elapsed already?
Sir, if we keep things as is,
an enemy scout plane will spot us in no time.
If we come under attack, it's over for us!
Sir.
The Kiska Island garrison contacted us.
They report that the weather on the 29th
is definitely going to be foggy.
Still, it's hardly believable
that such fine weather can turn into fog.
No, it's a prime opportunity.
March towards the Kiska Island.
Sir!
That's like jumping straight into the enemy's claws.
If the enemy fleet appears, we'll engage them,
buying time to complete the evacuation.
On July 29th,
Attu Island
American North Pacific Fleet
Kiska Island
Japanese Rescue Fleet
miraculously, the fog once again
covered the North Pacific.
The attack on the Japanese ghost fleet exhausted their fuel,
so all ships of the US North Pacific Fleet
gathered at a point 105 nautical miles south-southeast of Kiska Island, preparing to refuel.
Thus, it so happened that Kiska Island
was not watched at that exact moment.
Exactly as Rear Admiral Kimura planned,
the rescue fleet rushed through the fog into Kiska Bay.
Ships are coming!
Japanese ships are here!
They came for us. We can go home now!
Sir, can you see it?
The happy faces of our men!
That's a relief. Such a relief!
The last Daihatsu boat left the shore!
Major General, thank you for your patience.
You did well.
The Kiska Island garrison of about 5,000 men evacuated without leaving a single man behind.
The whole operation took a mere 55 minutes.
Can you really call this, the evacuation of Kiska, that'll stay in the annals of military history, just a stroke of luck?
During the first evacuation attempt,
had Rear Admiral Kimura made a reckless choice
and decided to risk it,
he'd unmistakeably end up drawing the attention
of the watchful US Fleet and getting annihilated.
A commander cannot afford to lose his composure
even when worse comes to worst.
Only when he looks at all the possibilities
and makes composed decisions that lead to success,
can a commander's true merit be manifested.
On August 1st, the rescue fleet
made it safely to the Paramushir Port.
Even after that, the US Fleet continued to bombard
the ghost garrison on Kiska Island just like before,
inspiring great fear in three left behind dogs.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
October 1944.
In the face of the great number or relentlessly advancing US troops,
the Japanese Army decides to unleash an unprecedented ramming attack on the military forces of the world.
Christened as the Special Kamikaze Squadron,
While praying for the safety of the motherland
and carrying 250 kg bombs underneath,
a great many young men
lose their lives in pursuit of the enemy carrier.
Episode 17
Birth of Kamikaze Corps
Witness the next week's decision:
Birth of Kamikaze Corps.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2