The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Prior to the start of the Pacific War,
in October 1941,
a conference on the Southern Strategy
was held at the Army War College for several days.
Within the Southern Strategy,
the leading role in capturing the Philippines
was allocated to the 14th Army under the command
of Lieutenant General Homma Masaharu.
To this end, the 5th Air Group was attached to them.
But the strategy also had an important problematic point.
Namely, the question of whether the U.S. Army in Philippines would choose to fight in the capital, Manila,
or retreat to defend the Bataan Peninsula.
The task of the 14th Army is to crush the enemy
in the Philippines and flatten his main operational base.
The main operational base being
the capital of the Philippines, Manila.
I want the 14th Army's main force
to land at the Lingayen Gulf 10 day after the war starts
and occupy the city of Manila within the next 35 days.
However, according to plan, after completing
the first stage, 48th Division and the 5th Air Group
are to be diverted for the Java and Malay operations.
Trouble may arise when that happens.
Is the goal of the Philippine operation
to capture the capital city of Manila, or is it
to deal a devastating blow to the enemy forces?
Please clarify that for us.
I believe, the enemy would be very likely to retreat to the Bataan Peninsula, like during the American-Spanish War.
Yes. If the enemy forces concentrate in the Bataan Peninsula, they'd be difficult to destroy.
Moreover, if the 48th Division and the 5th Air Group
are pulled out to participate in the Java-Malay Offensive,
our own ranks would be rather thin.
The Bataan Peninsula is a natural fortress.
We'd be in trouble if they're all driven to there.
I think we should think through
how to fight them in Bataan.
No, I think the probability of that is too low.
The enemy forces would be mostly made up of locals,
therefore MacArthur must be considering
a defensive battle in Manila.
The Philippine Operation
is to be followed closely by the capture of Java.
For that reason, we must strive to capture Manila
in the shortest time possible,
so as to dispatch the 48th Division to Java sooner.
In case the enemy escapes to the Bataan Peninsula,
I suggest that we carefully smoke them out later.
Very well.
On November 3rd, draft outline of this operation
was submitted to the Chief of Staff, General Sugiyama.
Office of the Chief of Staff
First operational goal:
crush the enemy in the Philippines
and raze to the ground his main operational base.
Second operational goal: in cooperation with the Navy,
the Army must land on Luzon and promptly seize Manila.
You didn't write in any provisions
in case the enemy retreats to the Bataan Peninsula?
That decision rests entirely
with the commander of the 14th Army.
I didn't see any need to write it in.
14th Army Strategy Draft
Episode 11
The Fall of Bataan and Corregidor
On December 8th, upon receiving the news
of the successful surprise attack on Pearl Harbor,
the massive 11th Air Fleet's land-based formation
of Zero fighters commenced a surprise attacks on American Air Force bases in the Philippines - Clark Field and Iba.
About a hundred grounded American aircraft,
waiting for orders, were wrecked.
Within just a day after the outbreak of the war,
American Air Force presence in the Philippines was no more.
Subsequently, the main force, led by the 14th
Army Commander, Lieutenant General Homma Masaharu,
formed a large transport fleet of 76 ships.
It was escorted by the 3rd Fleet
under the command of Vice Admiral Takahashi
and was heading towards the southern waters
in the watertight formation.
The weather on the day of landing
would be the decisive factor in its success.
It'll be fine. The troops are in high spirits
and are already betting at who'll get to Manila first.
The morale is as high as it can get.
However, MacArthur also had plenty of time to bolster
his defenses and is definitely expecting our arrival.
Bataan is the problem.
"We'll think about it when we get there"?
Not necessarily, sir.
Either way, if we're quick enough to overwhelm Manila,
we won't give the enemy the time to escape.
The 14th Army's main force was split into two groups.
They landed on December 22nd in the Lingayen Gulf
and on December 24th in Lamon Bay.
From south and north,
they launched their march straight to Manila.
It's the Japanese!
Turn back!
Faced with the thunderous advance of the Japanese army,
US Army of Philippines
couldn't put up much of a fight at all.
The enemy has no more
than 5 divisions in the Central Region.
Of those, 3 already suffered devastating losses.
What is the Intel on the enemy forces in Manila?
We don't have the exact Intel yet, but a part of those
was already hit considerably hard at the Agno River.
In that case, the enemy is probably planning
to hold on to Manila?
There are, however, reports of small portions of enemy forces gradually retreating towards the Bataan.
Finally, they've decided to barricade at the Bataan.
The Japanese offensive is closing in on Manila
from the north and south.
It was now apparent to anyone
that the fall of Manila is but a matter of time.
General Douglas MacArthur, the commander
of the United States Army Forces in the Far East
Is now faced with an important strategic decision.
Charge!
The Japanese army advances faster than expected.
The enemy is covered by a considerable air force
and has many tanks and field artillery in his arsenal.
Very well.
Declare Manila an open city
Immediately evacuate all our troops in the south
to the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor Island.
So we're enacting War Plan Orange?
Yes. Move the military headquarters to Corregidor.
We'll hold fast to that area
until the relief army arrives from the mainland.
Holding fast to the Bataan Peninsula
and Corregidor is definitely a viable strategy.
However, if San Fernando, the entrance to the Bataan,
is captured first, we'll be cut off from the peninsula.
Yes.
They won't even let us catch our breath.
Until the evacuation is completed,
we have to hold the Japanese back here.
Understood. With the honor of the
US Army of Philippines at stake, we'll do it!
Manila has been declared an open city.
And at 6 a.m. on January 1st, General MacArthur
ordered the destruction of the Calumpit Bridge.
The entire army had to complete the evacuation by then.
Such was his order.
Then, all the US military facilities in Manila
were burned down.
"Open City." What this means is, a cloth was hanged out,
indicating that the city is defenseless.
All the while the long convoys of trucks, chock-full with soldiers, weapons and ammunition hurriedly passed by.
Bataan Peninsula
Manila Bay
Calumpit
Pampanga River
Sir, as expected, the enemy retreated
to the Bataan Peninsula.
The 48th Division Commander
strongly suggests that we hinder the enemy's retreat to Bataan Peninsula, putting Manila off for later.
A report from the reconnaissance plane.
The enemy forces are retreating
to the Bataan Peninsula one after another.
They're seemingly moving from the direction of Manila.
This is bad. Now that it's vacant,
rushing to Manila is pointless.
No, the enemy is counterattacking over and over again.
They may not be necessarily retreating to Bataan.
No, it's apparent they're retreating.
We must blow the Calumpit Bridge to prevent their retreat
and defeat them decisively in the Luzon Plains.
No, it may be a trap.
Sir.
The Imperial Headquarters
are counting on us to crush the enemy
and quickly seize Manila.
Order the 48th Division to crush the enemy at Cabanatuan,
then immediately advance on Manila.
This moment had been anticipated for a long while.
Lieutenant General Homma pondered it for a moment,
but ultimately followed the orders of his superiors
to fulfill the soldier's duty.
As instructed by the Imperial Headquarters,
he headed for Manila.
Meanwhile, the US Army of Philippines
safely concluded the withdrawal to the Bataan Peninsula.
On January 2nd, Manila surrendered.
The Japanese troops marched through the city.
This, however, was not the end of the Philippines operation.
That's because
most of the US Army of Philippines managed to barricade itself on the Bataan Peninsula and in Corregidor Fortress.
Ensuring a complete control over Manila Bay
was seen a stepping stone
in ensuring unchallenged occupation of Manila.
So in order to secure Manila Bay,
the Bataan Peninsula and Corregidor Island,
guarding the entrance to the bay
Lingayen Bay
Corregidor Island
Manila
Lamon Bay
Mindoro Island
Visayas
Samar Island
Panay Island
Leyte
Masbate Island
Luzon Island
Agno River
along with the US Army of Philippines,
had to be subjugated.
In other words, Bataan must fall no matter the cost.
Charge!
The Bataan Peninsula is 48 km long and 24 km wide.
Its west and south are protected by cliffs,
inaccessible from the sea.
And the entire peninsula is covered in jungle,
rendering it a perfect natural fortress.
Moreover, the US Army of Philippines there
numbered over 80,000 troops.
Don't worry. We'll hold out for three years at least.
Charge!
As planned previously, 48th Division
was transferred to take part in Java operations.
On January 1st, the unit
that disembarked in Lingayen Gulf
was the 65th Brigade, 3000 soldiers
under the command of Lieutenant General Nara.
After only a short rest,
having to rely on an inaccurate 1:200,000 scale map,
they've been assigned a mission
to pursue the fleeing enemy on the Bataan Peninsula.
The Japanese side didn't see General MacArthur's evacuation to Bataan as a strategic retreat,
but only as a mere rout.
The Japanese troops underestimated the US Army
of Philippines, who retreated to the Bataan Peninsula.
And soon, they received
a devastating blow where they least expected.
On February 8th, Commander of the 14th Army,
Lieutenant General Homma
gathered his staff officers for a strategy meeting
to discuss the ways to to carry out the operation.
We're now standing on a critical juncture.
The question is, do we resume the attack at once,
or do we take another moment to regroup?
I'd like to hear your opinions.
We must attack relentlessly!
That's impossible. With our current
fighting strength, we'll only be wiped out!
No, we can do it!
Up to now, each unit handled its own operational planning,
but this time, it's coordinated by military headquarters.
By concentrating our attacks
on the east and west coasts, we'll ensure success.
Attack is the best defense.
We'll engage in piecemeal attacks,
until reinforcements arrive and we can go on the offense.
However, the soldiers are exhausted
and we're suffering huge losses.
It is better to let troops recuperate
before drawing any further plans.
Opinions were divided into two camps,
and a heated debate ensued,
dragooning the commander into making a decision.
On February 10th,
the commander made a decision
and telegraphed it to the General Staff Headquarters.
"We stopped attacking.
The soldiers have exceeded their physical limit.
I can't bear to have them fight in this condition any longer.
I'm prepared to bear this shame
as a military commander
and dare to urgently ask for reinforcements."
However, at the General Staff Headquarters...
Why is the 14th just dawdling around? They're a disgrace to our armed forces! Order the renewal of the attack!
When our Southern operations
are progressing so smoothly,
the Philippines operation being the only one stalled
is a major problem!
The Southern Expeditionary Army Headquarters
also want the attack to continue.
You didn't write in any contingency plan
in case the enemy withdraws to the Bataan Peninsula?
That decision rests entirely with the commander
of the 14th Army. I didn't see any need to write it in.
It was mainly the General Staff Headquarters that advocated the capture of Manila as the primary objective.
As well as their superiors,
Southern Expeditionary Army Headquarters.
However, there was no changing
the commander's decision now.
About a week later, Lieutenant General Homma sent a telegram to the Southern Expeditionary Army commander.
Its contents were the same as before -
"halt the attack and send in reinforcements."
The next day,
the Southern Expeditionary Army Headquarters
sacked several officers of the 14th Army,
of ranks going from Chief of Staff downwards.
And appointed several new staff officers from the General Staff Operations Division to the 14th Army in their stead.
Planning of the second
all-out offensive on the Bataan Peninsula
was now in the hands
of the Southern Expeditionary Army HQ.
A truck road was constructed through the jungle.
30,000 reinforcements, mainly made up of the 4th Division, have also arrived.
The night before the the second all-out offensive,
the roaring of cannons ceased
and everyone had a quiet night.
Having received a sufficient training,
the soldiers were full of confidence.
You could even say, the night before the battle,
they went to sleep with an easy mind.
The following day, April 3rd,
the Japanese army unleashed the second all-out offensive
upon the Bataan Peninsula.
Charge!
On April 9th, the US Army of Philippines
on the Bataan Peninsula was finally crushed.
The number of POWs exceeded 70,000.
Not one and not two of them
were emaciated due to hunger and malaria.
Manila Bay
Balanga
Mount Mariveles
All that remains is just to attack the enemy
on Corregidor Island.
But before that, we gotta quickly transport
70,000 POWs into the rear.
Most of the POWs are severely malnourished,
or sick with malaria and dysentery.
Yes. That's why leaving them like this
would mean certain death.
But in the rear, there'd at least be a field hospital.
I want first aid stations
to be set up every few kilometers on their way.
But sir, we've 70,000 POWs on our hands.
Commandeer as many trucks and trains as you can.
Understood. I'll get to it right away.
Good. Thank you.
However, in contrary to the commander's wishes,
the Japanese army only had a few trucks
and even procuring a train posed a challenge.
As a result of that, the POWs had to walk
88 kilometers through the scorching heat.
The number of POWs
who collapsed on the way due to exhaustion,
compared to what it would've been
if they were left on the mountain top on Bataan,
seems relatively low,
with a death toll of only 2,300 men.
However, the US Army
still came to call this a Bataan Death March.
By that time, General MacArthur already
transferred command to Major General Wainwright.
He evacuated from Corregidor Island to Australia.
But not before reassuring the Philippine partisans
with his famous "I shall return,"
standing for "I'll return" in English.
Those words made the Allies spring to action.
After the fall of Bataan,
Corregidor Island was next on the line.
The US Army of Philippines
was no longer capable of resisting.
On May 6th the short-lived resistance
of the Corregidor Island also ceased,
marking the completion of the Philippines campaign.
However, shortly afterwards, the commander of the 14th
Army was transferred to serve in the reserve force.
Following the orders of the Imperial Headquarters,
Lieutenant General Homma captured Manila.
But being considerate of his subordinates, he gave up
on the commander's pride, and requested reinforcements.
In order to avoid unnecessary casualties,
he evacuated the POWs from Bataan and Corregidor.
However,
as demonstrated by Lieutenant General Homma
in the unforgiving battlefield,
many of these decisions,
dictated by the kindness of commander's heart
end up presenting him
in a mushy and effeminate light,
unbefitting a commander.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
The mission of the Japanese Navy submarine I-168 was
to deliver the final blow to the aircraft carrier Yorktown,
damaged in the Battle of Midway and listing to port.
Having to rely on nothing
but a single nautical chart and the crew's beliefs,
she traverses the depths of the Pacific Ocean, I-168.
Finally, Yorktown is caught in her periscope.
Four torpedoes were fired.
The next Decision: Submarine I-168. Don't miss it.
Episode 12
Submarine I-168
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2