The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Having emerged victorious in the Battle of Midway
and gained the upper hand, the US Navy
was planning to make use of that momentum
to seize the initiative in the Pacific War for good,
and was about to launch
a major counterattack against Japan.
August 6th, 1942.
A convoy of 31 ships, carrying 19,000 Marines,
protected by an escort fleet of approximately 60 ships,
with three aircraft carriers and one battleship as its core,
was sneaking north through the South Pacific.
Episode 13
First Battle of the Solomon Islands
The purpose of capturing Tulagi and Guadalcanal
is primarily to ensure a safe corridor
between the United States and Australia.
Secondly, it will serve as a foothold
for the subsequent capture of Rabaul.
Thirdly,
it will curb any further Japanese expansion south.
As the recon aircraft reports,
the Japanese airfield under construction at Guadalcanal
hasn't received a single plane yet.
But they can always send some from Rabaul.
That's why we have the Coastwatchers
from the Australian Navy Intelligence for.
To be precise, these "Coastwatchers" were the civilians,
mobilized to defend the vast Australian coast -
farmers, pastors, government officials, miners, etc.
They mixed in with the local tribes,
lurking in the jungle.
They were tasked with providing hour-by-hour intel
on the movements of the Japanese army.
The distance from Rabaul
to Tulagi and Guadalcanal is about 560 nautical miles.
With the range of the enemy planes in mind,
they'd only be able to harass us from above
for 20 or 30 minutes at best.
However, it will take our troops
four days at least to complete the landing.
What will we do if the enemy attacks in waves?
Our side had already lost Lexington in the Coral Sea
and Yorktown at Midway.
What would we do if we lose any more flattops?
Flattops are vulnerable to bombing.
As the commanding officer in charge of landing,
I cannot send some 20,000 Marines to their death!
We need cover from a flattop!
And I'm speaking not just as the commanding officer
in charge of the Carrier Task Force.
If we lose two more of our three remaining flattops
in the Pacific... No, if we lose even one, the war is lost too!
Then, just cancel this operation altogether!
You go tell that to Admiral Nimitz in Hawaii,
or Vice Admiral Ghormley.
Now, now, no need to get so worked up.
The operation has started already.
One way or another, why don't we carry out
the landing operation as planned,
and reconsider things later,
if the situation so warrants?
Are you scared?
Aren't you scared?
I just try not to think too much
about what comes later.
We're not some Tarzans.
How are we supposed to fight these guys?
Japanese soldiers can dive for miles underwater
while breathing air through reed stalks.
Barefoot or in rubber-bottomed sandals,
they can sneak through the jungle silently.
They can climb trees like monkeys.
They're terribly cunning,
and thanks to their spartan lifestyle,
they can travel much farther than us.
They can survive on measly rations
and endure any pain, no matter how severe.
To tell you the truth, I'm scared too.
They're no ordinary humans.
Werewolves, if anything.
August 7th, 3:00 a.m.
Northwest of Guadalcanal Island,
the American convoy was approaching Cape Esperance.
Protected by an escort fleet,
it split into two groups, enveloping Savo Island,
sitting at the entrance to a narrow strait.
They were approaching Lunga Point on Guadalcanal
and Tulagi on Florida Island.
At the same time, the construction of a Japanese airfield
on Guadalcanal was completed.
Today, our Guadalcanal airfield is expecting the arrival
of the 6th Fighter Air Group from Rabaul.
The transfer of land-based attack aircraft
from Misawa Air Group is also scheduled.
Until then, the airfield construction team
will conduct rifle training. Is that clear?
Yes!
Good! At ease!
Roger!
At this time, the Japanese garrison on Guadalcanal
was comprised of about 2,000 construction workers
and 230 soldiers of the landing force.
Then, there were also about 700 Japanese troops in Tulagi.
The American-Australian fleet
shelled the seaplane bases on Guadalcanal
and Tulagi on Florida Island prior to the landing.
The Imperial Headquarters expected
that the US Army's counterattack,
with consideration to its initial operating capacity,
would come in the latter half of 1943.
However, the counteroffensive started sooner than expected.
When this news came
to the Japanese air base at Rabaul...
We should immediately dispatch our entire air force
and counterattack the enemy landing party!
I think the enemy's plan is either a probing attack,
or the destruction of the airfield.
Enemy at point-blank range.
Defending telegraph room to the last.
Schedule 2nd Air Wing with 27 land-based bombers
and 1st Air Wing with 18 Zero fighters
for departure at 07:30.
3rd Air Wing with 9 naval bombers
should depart as soon as it's ready!
Eighth Fleet Headquarters
At the same time, the 8th Fleet under the command of Vice Admiral Mikawa,
newly established after the Battle of Midway,
was also about to head out for Guadalcanal.
The distance from Rabaul to Guadalcanal
is about the same as from Tokyo to Shimonoseki.
We can't rely on support from the air force
However, our fleet has also just been formed and
doesn't have a single serious naval maneuver under its belt.
And because the distance is so great, we might
come under attack from enemy aircraft while on the way.
We should go there fully prepared for that too.
Ever since the Battle of Midway,
our navy has been scared out of their wits.
What is Secretary Yamamoto's opinion?
No objections.
Even if I'm opposed to the decision
of Imperial Headquarters and Combined Fleet command,
I intend to carry out this operation within the scope of the discretionary operational freedom delegated to our fleet.
Vice Admiral, we're doing it, aren't we?
What do you say, Staff Officer?
If the Vice Admiral is resolved,
I can't voice any protest.
However...
However, what?
Please decide on our further steps depending on the results
of the aerial reconnaissance and enemy attacks.
All right...
Senior Staff Officer?
We have not yet sailed the surface of that sea even once.
One way or another, it'll be a violent operation.
We can't help but to conduct it violently.
Good. This would become the first night battle of fleets
in the history of naval warfare. We'll do it violently.
Order the flagship with all the senior staff,
as well as the 6th Air Group to sortie immediately.
For the Japanese side, the loss of Guadalcanal
would mean a serious threat
for the security of the New Guinea area.
24 torpedo and conventional bombers
heading towards Tulagi and Guadalcanal.
This intel was then sent to the headquarters
of the Pacific Fleet in Hawaii.
And with powerful transmitters, rerouted to the US Task Force, operating off the coast of Guadalcanal, alerting them.
At noon, we expect an attack on this ship
from 24 enemy aircraft.
To the right, above us. Enemy aircraft!
Good!
The damage suffered by the Japanese side
in this battle was as follows:
5 land-based bombers, 5 carrier-based bombers,
plus two crashed Zero fighters.
The American-Australian losses were
11 fighters, one dive bomber,
plus severe beating sustained by the destroyer USS Jarvis.
The enemy aircraft carrier is the problem.
We need to be prepared
to repel at least one enemy aircraft raid.
If that happens...
We won't have a carrier on our side.
We risk total annihilation.
Whatever it takes,
we can't let the enemy discover us.
A surprise attack is our only way forward.
Enemy patrol forward-to-right!
All right, make it seem as if we're heading northwest.
Full to starboard! Hurry!
Enemy patrol plane no longer in sight!
Captain, restore the normal course.
Roger!
I need the rest of you to gather in the briefing room!
We escaped the Bougainville Strait and are about
to infiltrate the central waterway at high speed.
We're entering it through the right of Savo Island.
Solomon Archipelago
Bougainville Island
Isabel Island
Malaita Island
Tulagi
Guadalcanal Island
San Cristobal Island
First, we'll deal a surprise blow to the ships
currently moored in Guadalcanal,
Isabel Island
Malaita Island
Tulagi
Savo Island
Guadalcanal Island
following it up with an attack on the enemy in Tulagi.
Then, we'll quickly withdraw to a point
where we'll be unreachable by the enemy planes.
Enemy patrol aircraft!
90 degrees to the right and approaching!
3 cruisers, 3 destroyers.
2 seaplane tenders.
Course - 120 degrees. Speed 15 knots.
This one is persistent...
You'd like to change course once again?
It takes too much time. Harass them with the 8-inch guns,
since it doesn't matter at this point.
With this, we can be sure that the enemy planes
will show up in a couple of hours.
Chokai, Aoba, Kako, Kinugasa, Furutaka -
order each heavy cruiser to launch their patrol seaplanes.
Investigate the enemy position.
Order each ship to be on the lookout for enemy aircraft.
However, the scout plane from the Royal Australian Air Force who spotted the Japanese fleet
continued to scout the area assigned to it even after that.
And at around 14:30, it returned to its home base
in Milne Bay on the southern tip of New Guinea.
From there its crew reported to Townsville
and to MacArthur's Headquarters in Australia
the composition of the unidentified Japanese fleet.
Which translated into a delay of nearly 8 hours.
Seems like we're doing all right so far.
I don't think I ever had a day
that's been as long as this one.
We can now be sure of our victory tonight.
All right. Listen to my directives.
Sir!
Directive: as per the tradition of our Imperial Navy,
we'll only be contented with a decisive victory in the field!
When we plunge into the battle,
I need everyone to be calm and collected.
I'm counting on you to do your very best!
Telegram to Admiral Ghormley.
Our mission of supporting the landings is concluded.
"Our mission of supporting the landings is concluded."
Lost 21 out of our 99 carrier-based aircraft.
"Lost 21 out of our 99 carrier-based aircraft."
On account of enormous quantity
of enemy torpedo and conventional bombers present,
the immediate withdrawal of our fleet
seems the most appropriate to me.
Besides, we're running short on fuel. I request that
a refueling ship is dispatched our way as soon as possible.
Actually, they had enough fuel to operate for 4 more days.
Still, the American escort fleet,
which included an aircraft carrier, withdrew.
Admiral Fletcher, having previously lost
the aircraft carriers Lexington and Yorktown
during the Battle of the Coral Sea and the Battle of Midway,
was now unwilling to accept responsibility
for the potential loss of any more carriers.
Report from Aoba's recon aircraft.
Three enemy cruisers.
Patrolling the sea southwest of the Savo Island.
Good.
From now on, at a speed of 30 knots
and a course of 95 degrees,
we'll dash towards the berth in Guadalcanal Island.
10 degrees to the right!
Three cruisers. Proceeding to the right!
Copy that!
Prepare for night battle!
Ready to launch!
Fire!
Return fire! Fire!
10 minutes have passed.
It's our grand victory.
Turn sharply to the left.
Mount a surprise attack on the enemy troops in Tulagi!
Attack! Attack!
Current time is 00:10.
Tell me frankly what you think.
We must withdraw immediately.
We're running low on torpedoes.
I believe, the enemy task force is near San Cristobal Island.
So it's a question of distance and time?
Even if we rush it to the utmost, it would take us two hours
to reorganize the fleet and reach Lunga Point.
The sun rises over the Solomon Archipelago after 4 a.m.
It'd be impossible to escape the enemy carrier's retaliation.
Two hours, huh?
Let's do it!
The enemy transport fleet
should be completely exposed now!
You said it yourself.
If we're discovered by an enemy carrier,
we'll be annihilated.
Withdraw all formations.
Course 320 degrees. Speed 30 knots.
Isabel Island
Malaita Island
Tulagi
Guadalcanal Island
San Cristobal Island
Rennel Island
But at that time, the American aircraft carrier was trying
to get as far away from Guadalcanal Island as she could.
Vice Admiral, let's attack once again.
If Chokai goes there alone,
she'll have enough time to escape.
By leaving the convoys intact, we're giving the enemy
a chance to lick his wounds, Vice Admiral!
Have you considered the effect of that
on future operations?
We can't afford losing
an important warship in a reckless attack!
Thus, the first night battle of fleets
in the history of naval warfare
ended with a one-sided victory for the Japanese side.
However, the American convoys
in Guadalcanal were left completely intact.
Considering the tremendous effect the steady flow
of reinforcements, ammunition, and provisions
had on the ultimate victory in the battle,
one can't help but to question,
was this decision really correct?
When making a decision, one mustn't let
concerns of immediate victory or damage lead him astray,
but instead, he should be concerned with future prospects,
never losing sight of the overall picture at hand.
This naval battle let the Japanese side bask in glory.
However, before long, it'll become one of the major causes
of the tragedy that is to befall Guadalcanal.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
In the skies over the Pacific,
Kato's Falcon Squadron engages in an aerial battle
that would later be renowned as miraculous.
They seize their chance thanks to some prompt decisions
and display glorious team work
with their Army Type 1 Falcon Fighters,
paving the way for the success
of the Japanese army's operation.
The feats of the Kato's Falcon Squadron commander,
who was as free as the wind,
all the way until his tragic death in the Bay of Bengal
will be depicted in the next episode of Decision:
Kato's Falcon Squadron.
Episode 14
Kato's Falcon Squadron
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding