The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
In February 1943,
following the complete withdrawal
of Japanese forces from Guadalcanal,
the American strategy in the Pacific has entered its final stage,
with air raids on the Japanese mainland now being mounted regularly.
The decisive factor in their success
was the introduction of the B-29 long-range bomber.
It was capable of carrying up to 5 tons of bombs
to an unprecedented operational range of 5,600 km.
The Japanese Archipelago is less than 2,500 km away
from Saipan in the Mariana Chain.
With the B-29's operational range in mind,
Korea
Japan
Philippines
Truk Archipelago
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
Guam
the need for an air base on Saipan arose,
in order to continue the bombings of Japan proper.
This was how the US set its sights on the Mariana Islands.
Episode 20
Battle of the Philippine Sea
Thus, the Americans appointed Admiral Spruance
the overall commander of the invasion forces.
Those included Task Force 58 under Rear Admiral Mitscher,
with 8 large capital ships as its core.
As well as the V Amphibious Corps
under Marine Lieutenant General Smith.
A formidable force, numbering 775 vessels total.
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
A force twice the size of the Japanese fleet
that once tried to seize Midway
mobilized all its resources towards capturing Saipan.
On the Japanese side, however,
Vice Admiral Ozawa led a force of 73 ships,
comprised of 9 aircraft carriers, 7 battleships,
11 heavy cruisers, 3 light cruisers, and 32 destroyers.
A fleet of 450 carrier-based aircraft
was also hurriedly assembled.
They were looking to restore the position of the IJN
with one decisive battle after a chain of defeats.
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
Philippines
Tawi-Tawi
Bismarck Archipelago
Celebes
Moluccas
New Guinea
Filled with conviction that, "The Empire's fate depends on the result of this one battle," like in the Battle of Tsushima,
they headed for Saipan from the Island of Tawi-Tawi.
Keep going, keep going!
Bring it on!
Your right, hey!
Move, move, move!
Left, right, work!
Come on, you can do it!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
It's no good, after all.
The one with a shorter reach but a stronger punch loses.
Yes. You mean the match just now?
The Japanese carrier-based planes
can cover over 480 km of distance.
Meanwhile, our operational radius is less than 320 km.
If the Japanese use their longer reach
to fight us from the distance, we'll be helpless.
However...
The fighter with a shorter reach
tries to close the distance.
In other words, we have no choice,
but to approach them first.
I don't think Admiral Spruance ever allowed that.
Naturally, our fleet's main assignment
is the capture of Saipan. That's why
we can't leave the vicinity of Saipan.
However, if we maintain the status quo,
the Japanese planes will attack us with impunity.
Like a guy with a longer reach.
Rather, we must proactively confront the Japanese fleet.
I don't want to send that merry bunch to their death.
I'm afraid, Vice Admiral Ozawa
is indeed considering these out-ranging tactics.
According to reconnaissance photos taken over the Marshall Islands and the documents we captured,
the enemy is more than double our size.
The only way to win this battle
is to attack from outside the opponent's reach.
Fortunately, many of you, 1st Mobile Fleet's officers
are veterans of the attack on Pearl Harbor.
We're also deploying cutting-edge aircraft
such as the Suisei and Tenzan.
I can't say our crews' training is brilliant, but I want to believe that your sound guidance will lead them to victory.
By the way, once the enemy is spotted,
we take off at once, right?
Correct.
Well, about time we paid them back for Midway!
The actual naval battle will probably start tomorrow.
For now, let's just have a grand banquet,
and listen to Chief's "Flower Girl of Shanghai" song.
Right, right!
Very well, let's sing!
What is it?
Sir!
A transmission from the
3rd Air Fleet commander Omori.
Read it.
Enemy fleet spotted 200 nautical miles west of Saipan.
Dispatch attack aircraft at once.
What?
Oh? Found them already!
Speak of the devil! We have the initiative now!
Alright! Prepare to sortie at once!
Alright...
Wait.
Chief...
Chief!
It's a perfect opportunity.
What time is it now?
Sir.
It's 4:30 p.m.
If they sortie now, they'll reach the enemy by twilight.
Yes...
And then, it'll be night by the time
they make their journey of 150 nautical miles home.
Wing Commander.
Yes?
Can our pilots land at night?
They've never been trained for that.
Attack is a good idea
when it's not so foolishly wasteful.
We'll have yet another chance.
As a wise man once said, let's sleep on it.
Tell the seaplanes to patrol as usual.
Okay!
A red lantern
sways faintly
Girl selling flowers in the evening Shanghai...
This humane decision,
made out of consideration for his subordinates -
will, unbeknownst to anyone, eventually lead
to a fateful turn of luck with tremendous ramifications.
At 4:22 a.m. on June 19th,
Ozawa's fleet continued on its course from yesterday.
Sticking with their habitual out-ranging tactics,
they launched their search aircraft.
At 6:30 am, they spotted the US Fleet
450 km away from the vanguard unit.
At 7:30 am, starting with 68 planes
from Kurita's vanguard unit,
a total of 246 aircraft,
the force surpassing even the one participating in the air raid on Pearl Harbor, took off from multiple ships.
Sir, that's an unusual thing to see.
What is?
Normally, after all our planes are airborne, you'd say,
"My job is done," and proceed to read Dostoevsky.
For some reason, I just don't feel like it today, Chief Navigator.
Is it because you cancelled the sortie yesterday?
Perhaps.
Uh... What do you mean?
No, it's nothing.
Just my shoelaces being unruly today.
By that time, his ominous premonition
was already starting to come true.
It's the Japanese flagship. Taiho. Launch!
Launch!
Ship Surgeon. Surgeon!
I'll be fine, don't worry about me.
It's nothing. Our Taiho has a displacement of 34,000 tons.
She's not afraid of a torpedo hit or two!
And they're about to pay for this soon.
Rear Admiral Mitscher,
maybe you should cut down on smoking?
Now, when exactly did you become my wife?
I didn't, but your real madam asked me.
Right, right. Why did I think
I could escape her out here in the sea?
We're risking enough as it is.
We were on the verge of coming under attack
from Japanese planes on Guam Island.
Fortunately, our Hellcat fighters smashed those on the ground. Nothing would take off from there any time soon.
Which means our flank facing Guam Island is secure.
But the threat from Admiral Ozawa's fleet remains.
Well, that's the gist of it.
Where could they be?
Whoever has the element of surprise,
will knock the other out.
Just found something. A large formation
of Japanese aircraft is detected 240 km to the west.
240 km?
Alright, dispatch all available aircraft!
Roger!
Rear Admiral Mitscher just sent out
450 of his combat-ready planes.
Thus, what you could call the first face-to-face encounter
between the Japanese and US fleets since Midway,
the Battle of the Philippine Sea kicked off.
Taking advantage of their radar modules,
Hellcats found the Japanese formation effortlessly.
Like a pack of vultures,
they swooped down upon the enemy.
The few Japanese fighters that barely made it to the sky above the US Task Force 58 found themselves ravaged
by new weaponry, the Magic Fuse Shells,
capable of exploding when passing near the target.
The American pilots christened this encounter
"The Great Marianas Turkey Shoot."
Thus, through the first day of attack,
Ozawa's Fleet lost 193 of its aircraft.
And the aircraft carriers Taiho and Shokaku
were sunk by submarines.
The Japanese assault resulted
in a measly 17 enemy planes downed
and minor damage sustained
by battleship South Dakota and 5 other vessels.
Vice Admiral Ozawa transferred his flag
to the aircraft carrier Zuikaku.
And until the battle resumes on the next day, he temporarily withdrew to the northwest with all the remaining warships.
We can call it here for the rest of the day.
Please let us make another round
of the Great Turkey Shoot!
Quit saying such nonsense.
We owe it to a lucky punch today.
Mr. Ozawa is an unpredictable fellow.
Besides, Tom, you have a mother
waiting for you in Arizona.
You know that much about me?
You are all like family to Admiral Mitscher.
Sir!
Vice Admiral Ozawa always mourned the untimely death
of his beloved subordinates in the form of a letter.
Oddly enough, both opposing commanders
shared the sentiment of loving their subordinates
and valuing their lives deeply.
Come in.
Okay.
I apologize for the delay.
No, don't worry.
That makes it 330 letters total. I'm sorry.
Captain. Do you have that naniwabushi
record in your cabin?
Huh? Naniwabushi?
Preferably by Torazo.
What do you need it for?
This guy here liked Torazo
and was humming it all the time.
Chief...
If you don't have it, no worries.
I can sing it myself.
Having seem through Vice Admiral Ozawa's plan
to withdraw and let his men rest for a day
before renewing the attack, American forces
pursued desperately the fleeing Japanese fleet,
aiming to further their triumph.
Until finally Rear Admiral Mitscher’s Task Force 58
got readings of Ozawa's battered fleet
350 km to the northwest.
350 km to the northwest means...
This is their location.
Yesterday, with a bit of luck,
we pulled off a counter-punch.
But luck or not, the enemy is now staggering.
We've gotta keep hitting.
Alright, let's do it!
Chief of Staff, dispatch all aircraft!
Sir, I cannot allow that.
If we send them out on a round trip of 350 km now,
we'll have to recover them at night.
I know that.
Then you know that our pilots
weren't trained to land at night.
Still, if they slip away now,
we'll lose our chance for good.
We mustn't give Ozawa the time to recover.
But the attacking party won't be able to return.
You're sending them to their death.
No, I know we'll be able to recover them,
one way or another.
Dispatch all aircraft.
War is an excruciating business.
We can't mix it with personal emotions.
Launch all 216 aircraft for an attack!
Okay!
Wait. Once all the aircraft are airborne,
turn the fleet northwest and steam there at full speed.
We'll try to shorten the return distance
as much as we can.
Sir!
What's wrong? You're as pale as death.
Reconnaissance aircraft requested a data correction:
the Japanese fleet is not 350 km away, but 480 km instead.
What? That's absurd!
But that means a 130 km longer round trip!
Yes.
Let's recall the attack aircraft now.
No, proceed according to plan.
40 degrees to the right! Enemy planes!
The enemy is being pretty persistent.
Yes.
But will they manage to return safely after this?
Pretty sure they don't usually practice night landing.
Warned in time about the approach
of the American planes thanks to radar,
commander Ozawa launched 75 aircraft
as combat air patrol and and waited.
His battleships leveled their main guns
against the incoming torpedo bombers.
In a blink of an eye, 20 planes were downed.
Still, the American pilots did not give in
and kept playing by their own rules,
sinking the aircraft carrier Hiyo.
Aircraft carriers Zuikaku, Jun'yo, Ryuho, Chiyoda
and others received multiple direct hits.
By the time the enemy planes withdrew,
Ozawa's entire fleet had only 35 planes left.
The Commander-in-Chief
of the Combined Fleet Toyoda accepted the defeat
and ordered Vice Admiral Ozawa to retreat.
Sir. The first wave of returning attack planes is approaching.
Oh? They managed to return?
Good.
Illuminate all ships.
Light a welcoming fire for those returning.
Doing so will make us an easy target.
So be it.
Our pilots were risking their lives there.
Will we make them risk their lives here too?
Sir...
During the Bougainville campaign, Vice Admiral Ozawa
turned on searchlights to help a single recon plane return,
knowing full well that the enemy is right in front of them!
I will now follow his example!
Move it, move it!
Some probably had to ditch their planes.
Yes, I've arranged a search.
Good.
This battle was, in effect, the final battle
of the Japanese Combined Fleet in the traditional sense.
It would also have a colossal effect
on the subsequent course of war.
What's more, this battle was the last engagement of the war in which Japan and the US fought on an equal footing.
This important battle forced both commanders into exactly the same position, and demanded both to make a decision.
The snap decisions made by each commander at that time
revealed a major difference in thinking
that would turn out to have a major effect on the fates
of both armies... No, of both respective countries.
What is it, if not a testament
to the decisive role of humanism
in telling right from wrong
in a situation where hard decisions must be made?
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
October 20, 1944.
General MacArthur, along with 200,000 troops,
was about to return to the Philippines,
where he had once left.
The Japanese fleet that challenged
that invasion force to a decisive battle
included the battleship Musashi,
with her hull fully painted in pale gray.
Determined to draw the attention
of all enemy planes on herself,
Musashi donned her burial gown before heading to Leyte.
Episode 21
Battle of Leyte Gulf (Part 1)
Don't miss next week's decision:
Battle of Leyte Gulf.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
History Asian
Moozzi2