The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
A large invasion force, led by General MacArthur
was approaching the coast
of the Filipino island of Leyte.
On October 20th, 1944,
as the troops were just about to disembark,
General MacArthur announced the landings
from on board the cruiser Nashville.
It was a moving moment for him.
On March 11th, 1942,
having promised them, "I shall return"
amidst starvation and a rain of Japanese shells,
he bid farewell to his subordinates
and Filipino refugees on the Bataan Peninsula.
2 years and 7 months passed since then.
General MacArthur speaking.
People of the Philippines:
I have returned.
I have returned!
By the grace of Almighty God our forces stand again on Philippine soil, consecrated in the blood of our two peoples...
The Japanese were now determined to challenge the
US Fleet that they spotted previously to a decisive battle.
For that, the contingency plan Sho Part 1 that was being developed for the previous 2 months, was activated.
Kurita's Division of the Combined Fleet
was dispatched on a mission
to destroy the American transport fleet
currently in Leyte Gulf.
Episode 21
Battle of Leyte Gulf (Part 1)
Stationed in Brunei Bay in British Borneo, Kurita's 2nd Fleet
complied with the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet Toyoda's orders to infiltrate the Leyte Gulf on the 25th
and held a strategy meeting
with all the ships' captains present.
As you may already know,
in the upcoming operation,
Luzon
Mindanao
Borneo
Brunei
Palawan
Mindoro
Philippines
San Bernardino Strait
Surigao Strait
Leyte
Samar
the newly formed 3rd Fleet,
led by Vice Admiral Ozawa,
Ozawa's TF
using the remaining aircraft carriers,
including Zuikaku, as a decoy,
will be deployed in this region
in order to draw away Halsey's Force.
Meanwhile, the 5th Fleet
under Vice Admiral Shima
will join forces with our 2nd Southern Fleet
at the Surigao Strait, the entrance to Leyte Gulf.
Shima's Fleet
Kurita's central force under Vice Admiral Kurita,
including the 1st Night Battle Unit,
Kurita's Fleet
will infiltrate Leyte Gulf
via the San Bernardino Strait.
Nishimura's Fleet
The 2nd Night Battle Unit
will support them from the south.
Alright, I got that.
Still, I can't get behind the goal of attacking
the transport fleet, given in the previous explanation.
For that, a single attack from an aircraft carrier
would be more than enough.
I agree.
What are the higher-ups thinking?!
The complete destruction of the enemy's
main combat fleet should be made our #1 priority.
And yet, we're being sent to attack the transport fleet?
Do they really think that it's the best our 2nd Fleet can do?
That's right.
A decisive fleet battle is what it was born for!
I think so too.
Therefore, should the enemy's capital ships appear,
we're allowed to suspend our hunt for convoys
and focus on attacking those.
Still, the current war situation
doesn't allow for an open engagement.
What do you think, Musashi's Captain?
You've been silent for a while.
I stand in opposition to everyone else here.
It pains me to say so, since I've been entrusted with a ship that was bred for a decisive battle, with her 46 cm cannons...
But I believe the age of decisive naval battles
ended with the Russo-Japanese War.
What?
Presently, it's the decisive aerial battle
that everything hinges on.
Rather than glomming onto
the honor of a decisive naval battle,
we should now be concerned
with improving our damage control and offensive abilities.
Even knowing that the enemy's task force
had set up a web,
we're heading to Leyte naked, without a single plane
to support us - that's what concerns me.
"Honor," you say?
That's ridiculous!
What are you even saying?!
Our navy's traditions are not a joke!
That timidity will get us nowhere!
Nonsense!
Say something! Hey!
Gentlemen, do I have some amazing news for you.
A special attack corps that'll ram the enemy ships
with 250 kg bombs strapped to their Zeroes was formed.
We've nothing to fear from even a hundred enemy carriers,
with this deadly attack that'll only use fuel for one-way trip.
The argument of captains who glommed onto
the decisive battle doctrine
was finally brought to a definitive end
with the news of the creation of kamikaze corps.
Captain of the battleship Musashi, Vice Admiral Inoguchi
felt that the notion of a decisive naval battle,
so persistent in the heads of his colleagues and superiors spelled worrisome... No, spelled ill omen in big letters.
Captain.
Yes?
Did something happen?
No.
Anyway, what did you want?
We've finished the refueling works.
Oh. Thanks for your work.
Isn't there really something?
Soon, we're going on a sortie as naked as a jaybird,
knowing full well the enemy's air raid is coming.
There won't be any decisive battle,
just us suffering enormous damage.
But sir...
Exactly. No "but" can do. We've got orders.
What's worse, all I can think of is our Musashi.
And I shouldn't be thinking so much.
What will you do, as an executive officer?
Follow the orders and do whatever is in my powers.
The limits to what I can do are in reducing
the damage to our second fleet as much as possible.
Sir...
Captain!
Have you heard it already?
A suicide corps - kamikaze.
Yes.
They know they won't return alive!
Won't return alive, huh?
Executive Officer Kato.
Immediately repaint the hull and deck.
Huh?
This decision to repaint the ship -
what on earth is it supposed to signify?
Too slow! Finish that part quicker!
Warrant officer Arakawa?
What is it?
Why is it only us who smartens up?
Why aren't others repainting too?
Quit shooting the breeze and finish it!
Don't you two understand?
Our captain is the 4th one we ever had,
the XO is the 2nd. You know that?
Yeah... So?
4 and 2 make up the word for "burial robe"!
Eh?!
Whatcha so shocked about?
You're in the army!
We're wearing burial robes at all times.
And don't forget to change your underwear today!
The captain already finished preparing.
Ah, why don't I help as well?
You idiot, quit worrying!
I'm telling you, our Musashi
is an unsinkable battleship.
She won't go under. Even after you hit her with 5 or 6 torpedoes, she'll keep running like clockwork!
At 8:00 a.m. on October 22nd, 1944,
Luzon
Mindanao
Borneo
Brunei
Palawan
Mindoro
Philippines
San Bernardino Strait
Surigao Strait
Leyte
Samar
main force of Kurita's fleet of 27 ships, including
Musashi, Yamato, and Nagato, left Brunei Bay.
Kurita's Fleet
They were to sail west of Palawan Island
and south of Mindoro Island.
Then pass through the San Bernardino Strait
and reach Leyte Gulf
by creeping along the eastern coast of Samar.
This sortie required them to cover
about 1900 km of distance.
At noon, as Kurita's Fleet was in Palawan Passage,
the Commander-in-Chief of the combined Fleet Toyoda
sent them a telegram, commending the struggle
of the decisive battle force...
I want our soldiers to regain their resolve
to overcome all hurdles we encounter.
Fight with purpose -
answer the divine call and beat off a mighty enemy.
However, right off the bat, the Japanese fleet
was spotted by American submarines Dace and Darter.
Captain, can you see anything?
What is it?
A cruiser, probably?
Anything else?
A cruiser, alright. Some destroyers too.
Plenty of them!
Yeah...
What is it?
Pretty.
Pretty indeed.
A battleship, sir?
A real shame we have to sink that baby.
Let's start with the 1st cruiser in line.
Okay!
Ready to launch!
Isn't it pretty?
Yes. A wonderful sunrise.
Full to starboard!
Even though they're the enemy,
they're damn good.
Takao was hit by a torpedo!
Depth charges!
It's not depth charges. We hit them!
4. 5, 6 hits!
There she blows!
They got Maya too!
Launch the rescue.
Right off the bat, Kurita's Fleet
fulfilled Captain Inoguchi's grim prediction.
Heavy cruisers Atago and Maya were lost
and Takao was severely wrecked.
With many more trouble expected to come
in the journey still ahead.
Reported sightings of the Japanese fleet off the southern tip of Mindoro by an American patrol plane
were immediately passed to Admiral Halsey, exercising direct command from the aircraft carrier Lexington.
Time - 8:37 a.m.
Attack! Just attack! There is only the attack.
Thus, with an order from Admiral Halsey,
they Battle of Leyte Gulf started in earnest.
Launched from aircraft carriers of Bogan's Task Group 38.2
Intrepid, Cabot, and Independence,
31 fighters, 16 torpedo bombers, and 12 dive bombers
set out to search for Kurita's Fleet.
Look, I'm counting on you.
Seems like we'll meet them soon enough.
I know it's a shame that your first time won't even be against a real warship, but you should bear with it.
It was to become her first actual combat deployment.
The world's first super-heavy anti-ship gun. The pinnacle of various navy departments' technological advancements.
Are we all ready, locked and loaded?
Yes. The burial robe is also applied.
Burial robe?
You're the 4th captain of Musashi, I'm the 2nd XO.
Together, 4 and 2 are "death."
I see.
All crew on board also understands how you feel about this,
as a captain of the punching bag ship.
In that case, tell them to try to save as many lives
as possible, when emergency comes.
Sir...
Enemy naval aviation!
Large formation, 90 degrees to the right!
As the saying goes, in the Ganryujima duel,
Kojiro was the one attacking against the sun.
Fire!
Keep firing!
Please stop! Not the main battery!
Stop firing the main battery!
Although a certain shock wave was to be expected
when firing her 46 cm main battery,
the actual impact was so strong,
it rendered all the other guns on board unusable.
The traditional decisive naval battle doctrine
turned out to be fatally flawed.
However, even after several strafing and torpedo attacks,
Musashi's performance was unimpaired.
The confident appearance of the unsinkable battleship Musashi who simply shrugged off the first torpedo hit
produced the opposite effect on the American pilots, who now began to target Musashi with rekindled determination.
The enemy is clearly targeting us.
Unsurprisingly so.
At 12:30 p.m. 65 aircraft of the 3rd wave and 25 aircraft of the 4th mounted another concentrated attack.
Without any friendly air cover, the naked Musashi ended up
receiving 5 torpedo hits in this concentrate barrage.
And after 5 more conventional bombs hits,
Musashi no longer had any life in her.
Captain Inoguchi was also seriously injured.
Thus, at 2:00 p.m.
her speed dropped to 6 knots
and Musashi left the battle formation.
If the enemy comes once more, it'll be over for her.
Yes. We've no more shells.
No people either.
Come get your meals!
A meal?
Ah, that reminds me,
I've only eaten half of my breakfast.
You cooked it damn well amidst all this shooting.
We didn't even have enough hands
to form it into rice balls.
Well, whatever, just eat it.
You can't do any fighting on an empty stomach.
Thanks a lot.
Hey,
we can eat now.
Man, it really is good!
And I thought I won't get to eat ever again.
Are you okay?
I'm good, sir.
Hey, what about the night meal?
Think we'll make it to the night meal?
Don't you wanna live some more?
Well, in the end I couldn't do anything to help you...
Forgive me.
And I was rude to you before. Forgive me.
It's definitely over.
Even Musashi has her limits.
Still no command to abandon ship?
Abandoning ship without an order
is a violation of military discipline.
Warrant Wakamizu!
Lieutenant Sugano?
Gather the surviving anti-aircraft gun operators on the aft deck.
Sir. Roger that.
Anti-aircraft operators, gather on the aft deck!
What was it that the 7th anti-aircraft division commander
Lieutenant Sugano had on his mind?
While he was concerned with saving as many survivors as possible from Musashi, who was dead in the water,
why was the high command taking its time
with the order to abandon ship?
Everyone's fierce struggle today was remarkable.
I thank you for your hard work.
Still, it was to no avail, and most of our personnel
is either injured or killed, including the 1st gunnery officer.
I can't stand the thought
of bringing everyone even more suffering.
Before long, Musashi will sink.
However, no abandon ship order has been issued.
Abandoning ship without an order is shameful for a soldier
and against military discipline.
Still, we can't afford increasing our casualties any further!
I'm taking responsibility for all of you,
anti-aircraft gunners.
Grab whatever you find and flee!
This decision saved a great many lives.
May I?
Come in.
I must apologize.
I gave the arbitrary abandon ship order.
Please punish me.
No, you did well.
I was busy writing a last will
and missed my chance.
You knew exactly what I wanted to do.
Thank you.
Well, my last will is finished.
Executive Officer Kato, please do me the honor.
You guys hurry up too!
Then, if you excuse me.
Counting on you.
I'd like to follow your example and stay too.
What are you saying?
Only me and those unable to leave should stay.
But sir, because I wasn't trying hard enough...
Abandon ship.
It's an order.
Thanks to the resolute decision of Lieutenant Sugano,
a mid-level officer, no time was wasted
and the lives of many sailors were saved.
Thus, Musashi who was once touted as unsinkable, sunk.
Falling victim to the decisive naval battle doctrine, she failed to fulfill the very battleship role she was designed for.
As per Vice Admiral Inoguchi's decision,
her sacrifice in the form of becoming a punching bag ship,
so to say, helped limit the damage to the fleet as a whole.
Furthermore, the abandon ship order given by Lieutenant Sugano, perceptive of his superiors' intent,
that saved many of the sailors' lives is still remembered
as a brilliant decision by a mid-level officer.
In addition, some say that Musashi's captain
Vice Admiral Inoguchi followed her fate
and took his own life with a determined harakiri.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
The Japanese fleet that was supposed to infiltrate Leyte Gulf
came under intense attack from the US Air Fleet.
That resulted in sinking of the flagship Atago
and battleship Musashi.
The Japanese Central Force, led by Vice Admiral Kurita
with Yamato as his flagship
immediately launches a counterattack,
letting all hell break loose off the coast of Samar.
Next week's decision, depicting Kurita's puzzling order to reverse course: Battle of Leyte Gulf, Part 2. Don't miss it
Episode 22
Battle of Leyte Gulf (Part 2)
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2