The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
The Guadalcanal campaign, that would later come to be remembered as the nastiest engagement of the Pacific War,
was reaching its zenith in November 1942.
With the American mastery of sea and air
being practically uncontested,
the relief efforts couldn't make it to the front lines.
30,000 Japanese soldiers were still on Guadalcanal.
But hunger, malaria, and death plagued the island.
So they were left no choice, but to patiently wait for relief.
The Japanese side was denied any other means of supply,
except covert nighttime submarine delivery.
That's when, as a last ditch measure,
the plan to use fast destroyers
to supply the troops via oil drums was devised.
To be precise, watertight oil drums, filled with provisions and medicine, were tied together with a rope.
The destroyers would then jettison those
into the sea near the shore.
Episode 19
Battle of Tassafaronga
Prior to her departure on November 28th,
in the officers mess of the flagship Naganami,
on anchor in the forward base of Shortland,
a final banquet was organized for the captains of the recently formed task force of 8 destroyers,
including the commanding officer, Tanaka Raizo.
With the local planning officer
from the Imperial Headquarters also attending.
A total of 1098 drums have been loaded.
With exception of the patrol ship Takanami, the flagship Naganami, and the Makinami,
each one of the 5 ships, Oyashio, Kuroshio, Kawakaze, Suzukaze, and Kagero are loaded with about 220 drums.
That's good. But as I've just noticed, torpedoes and cannons can't be used with all those drums around.
We'll leave the fighting to the patrol ships.
They'll buy us time to drop the drums safely.
And then, we'll have a free hand
to do the one thing we excel at.
So we're like a shipping agency now.
The petty officers also complained this morning:
"Rear Admiral Tanaka drilled us so intensely, we even earned the nickname of the Devil's 2nd Torpedo Squadron,
all that to become a shipping agency?"
You've complained about it too, haven't you?
Still, you can't feed the soldiers in Guadalcanal
with just half a loaf of bread.
Yes. I understand that myself, sir.
Furthermore,
it's 300 nautical miles from Shortland to Guadalcanal.
If we don't make it back to this halfway point
150 nautical miles away before daybreak,
the enemy will chase us from their base on Guadalcanal.
That's why it's essential that we drop the drums
off Guadalcanal by midnight.
That's my only request.
The rest is up to you.
Commander.
What is it, staff officer?
From what I've heard so far, it appears that you're
not expecting to encounter the enemy at all.
I never said that.
Of course, they might show up.
No, I'm sure they will.
Then tell us the plan for a case like that.
In a case like that, I trust these gentlemen
to handle the situation.
They're worth their salt.
That's just irresponsible!
When you walk, do you command your feet
"right foot forward, left foot forward" each time?
If you didn't like my feet metaphor,
let's change the subject.
When the enemy swings his sword at a kendo master does he command his hand to "block it this way" each time?
Doesn't his hand go there automatically?
Whether or not his hand will manage to receive it
depends on regular training.
That's exactly why I've been drilling
this 2nd Torpedo Squadron like mad.
They're no mere shipping agency. You'll see.
Chief Navigator.
Are you sure that nautical chart is accurate?
Good question.
After all, those Brits produced it 15 years ago.
It might very well be off in certain spots.
Hey, hey. Are you sure we're not heading
into one of those "certain spots"?
As long as we see the sun, we won't get lost.
Oh, just you leave it to me.
Well, leave the boat to the boatman, they say.
Though it makes perfect sense to us,
that heated exchange between Chief Tanaka
and the HQ officer yesterday was helluva fun.
An HQ upstart with no notion
of the actual situation, that's who he is.
Chief Navigator, the sun!
Finally out? About time!
Time?
12:03.
A bit off, after all.
Change of course!
Bearing - 175 degrees.
Full to starboard!
I hope the enemy shows up soon.
Enemy plane!
331 degrees 20 minutes!
B-17 bomber! One plane!
Prepare for anti-aircraft combat.
All crew, anti-aircraft combat!
Man your positions!
They saw us.
I suppose.
At the same time, the American side knew about the Japanese relief fleet, supplying Guadalcanal at night.
Guadalcanal
Bougainville
Shortland Archipelago
Savo Island
Their sailors nicknamed it "The Tokyo Express"
and harassed it relentlessly, sinking many of the convoys.
Among those was Task Force 67, led by Rear Admiral
Carlton Wright from on board USS Minneapolis,
consisting of 4 heavy cruisers,
1 light cruiser, and 6 destroyers.
A fleet numbering 11 ships total
that had already caught wind of the Japanese strategy
of supplying Guadalcanal with drums,
delivered by the 2nd Torpedo Squadron,
was waiting for its chance to strike.
As reported previously, the enemy numbers 8 ships.
We'll go with the strategy that Togo
once used in the Battle of Tsushima.
However, since the enemy excels at night battles,
we'll illuminate them with flares
from our cruisers' seaplanes and destroy them.
Going with "a rat in the trap," right?
The Japanese proverb goes,
"A cornered rat will bite the cat." Be careful.
Moreover, even though it's just a destroyer squadron,
it is the 2nd Torpedo Squadron, drilled to hell and back.
There's no telling what they'll do.
However, we have radar.
Something that's still completely unheard-of in Japan.
They rely on their eyes,
even when night fighting.
As you all know, in a naval battle,
he who spots the enemy first has the upper hand.
Of course, the Japanese fleet also changed its course.
They decided to infiltrate
the Guadalcanal area from the front.
4 nautical miles west of Savo Island,
they've been approaching on a 180 degree course.
What time is it?
22:00, sir.
2 more hours?
Yes. It seems, we'll finish the mission
without the enemy discovering us.
Sir. A transmission from the 8th Fleet HQ.
What is it?
From radio traffic monitoring, we've concluded that the enemy is informed of your fleet's actions.
If the enemy engages you, forget about supplies,
concentrate on destroying the enemy.
I see. If we encounter the hostile fleet,
jettison the drums and fight with all we got?
Yes.
Good job. Please inform the other ships too.
Roger. Will do.
I hope they don't find us before we drop the provisions.
The soldiers on the island are waiting.
We'll be sure to run as fast as we can until then.
How about sinking them, instead of running?
Priorities first. We're a shipping agency today. Our priority is the soldiers on the island. The customer is king and all.
Those guys are quick to escape.
You still haven't found the Japanese?
Just a little more time...
They know that if they don't come by midnight,
our land based planes would be after them.
And if they left that area, they must come here.
Yes...
The Lord is smiling upon us.
Under this rain cloud,
the Japs can see out to 4,000 meters at best.
While we have radar with 24,000 meters of coverage.
That difference of 20,000 meters
can give us a crucial edge over them.
Is this...
Yes. This certainly is the enemy ship, 6,300 meters away.
At a point about 8 nautical miles from Tassafaronga.
Alright, prepare for battle!
Man your positions!
Eight ships. Once they're in position,
we'll wipe them all in one fell swoop.
One last push. The island is visible already.
It seems, the enemy never got on our tail, after all.
No, we've certainly been caught.
But we still have no idea where they'll come from.
It's a fight between a blind man and a seeing one.
If we can just deliver 10 days' worth of supplies...
Yes, understood.
Prepare to drop. Signal every vessel!
Even knowing that the Americans have them on their radar,
Tanaka's Fleet drew closer to the island.
At exactly 23:16...
45 degrees to the left! Two black shapes!
Looks like an enemy destroyer.
Good. The blind just became sighted.
How far are they?
6,000 meters!
Alright, we got it!
Report to flagship.
Start a simultaneous torpedo-cannon attack!
Chief navigator, bearings!
Roger!
7 destroyer-like enemy ships.
Cardinal direction - 45 degrees to the left.
Enemy speed: 24 knots at 50 degrees!
Prepare long lances at 50 degrees!
Adjust the settings. I'm counting on you!
Why do you press forward without breaking formation?
This way, we'll be standing naked in the enemy's sight!
Yes. However, our supply mission comes first.
Jettisoning the provisions now would be a terrible waste.
Our soldiers are waiting there.
Our mission is to sink as many enemy ships as possible!
We'll do that too.
But now, let's focus on supplies.
Can you even hear yourself?!
The enemy is right in front of us!
We'll drop the supplies as close as we can.
There, the island can already see us.
They're signaling.
Just a little closer to here!
Please, Navy boys!
The enemy has 11 ships total.
Captain, wanna have a shot from our usual bottle?
No, I'm on duty today.
Wait until we complete the delivery.
Can we fire, Captain?
Patience! Just a little more.
Savo Island
Guadalcanal
The Japanese haven't noticed us yet?
Yes. And we can see the side
of their first ship clearly. Let's shoot.
Wait. We'll annihilate them together
once all ships are in range.
I hope they'll be alright after coming that far.
But look there.
The enemy surrounded them.
Ah! Could it be that our boys are still unaware?
Hey!
Idiot. Think they'll hear you from here?
They're sacrificing themselves for us!
That's ridiculous.
How can you call yourself a commander?
The battle is all about waiting for your chance!
Don't tell me you've forgotten such a rudimentary thing.
Planning officer, enough already.
The torpedoes are incoming.
Turn the rudder.
The enemy made their move!
Rear Admiral, it's time to make a decision!
Planning officer, this decision is mine to make.
Okay. Do it.
All ships fire at once.
Closest target first.
Look at that, the enemy is going for it.
But that alone won't be enough.
Rear Admiral! Take a look at that!
Takanami won't last much longer!
What is wrong with you...
You saved us!
Thank you!
We've finished dropping the provisions!
Good. Signal all ships...
Charge the enemy with all we got!
Open fire!
Now captain?
Go ahead!
Finally!
Set depth to 3 meters! Target the third ship.
I can't see anything behind such high splashes!
Alright! The one that just fired. Shoot at that ship!
We can almost see the whites of their eyes.
Prepare for a concentrated attack!
The torpedoes of the well-drilled 2nd Torpedo Squadron
were powerful and accurate.
Because of that, all cruisers except Honolulu
have been hit with one torpedo at least.
On the American side, one heavy cruiser was sunk,
with 3 more getting thoroughly thrashed.
They knew that the rearguard was still encumbered.
These guys knew what they needed to do
without any orders from above, planning officer.
Captain, we have to save Takanami now.
They've done well, but Oyashio and Kuroshio have already beaten the enemy off. We can . Send them there.
Roger. I will pass down the order.
How did it go? It's become a little quiet, I see?
We won.
The enemy is all but wiped out.
Oh?
We won?
Of course.
And what are our losses?
Only Takanami.
That's a relief.
Chief Surgeon, the Oyashio and Kuroshio are coming
to Takanami's rescue now. You should come with them.
By god, when I get there I'll make sure nobody is slacking off. My revenge for having nothing to do when we drill.
By the way, any idea where Captain is?
Yes. Sleeping in front of the Chief Navigator's cabin.
Sleeping?
Captain.
I came to raise a toast with you.
You don't have to refuse anymore.
You're off duty now.
...scenes
Because if not, my wise teacher,
I'll remember our expedition
And think of you...
Thanks!
Thank you, guys!
Sir.
Right. You did well.
I have to apologize. I was so arrogant.
I now understand the meaning of your metaphor,
of giving orders to your right and left leg each time.
If only we could have saved Takanami...
Thus, the Battle of Tassafaronga
was over in mere 30 minutes.
It is said that Admiral Nimitz instructed all his Navy officers and men to "train, train, and train again,"
deeply impressed by the successes of the Japanese destroyer squadron.
Alongside his strategy of trusting the skill of his subordinates,
gained through rigorous drilling, and leaving everything
to them with full confidence, the commander
also made several very humane decisions
which earned him the respect of others.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
July 1944.
American forces began advancing
towards Saipan Island.
Capturing Saipan Island would provide a base from which the B-29 long-range bombers
could attack the Japanese mainland.
The Japanese answer to this has been
a concentrated sortie by the Combined Fleet
under the command of Vice Admiral Ozawa.
Episode 20
Battle of the Philippine Sea
Witness in the next decision:
Battle of the Philippine Sea.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2