The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
July 1944.
As a result of the devastating defeat at the Battle of the Mariana Islands and the annihilation of the Saipan garrison,
the US forces were now
the undisputed masters of the sea in the Western Pacific.
Then, in September of that year, the 7th Fleet,
under the Supreme Allied Commander Douglas MacArthur,
rallied in Leyte Gulf, south of the Luzon Island.
Determined to meet them head-on,
the Japanese Combined Fleet initiated Operation Sho Part 1 -
by mustering all their remaining forces
and starting their advance towards the shores of Leyte
in the early hours of October 18th, 1944.
Our nation's future strength hinges on this one battle.
However, the enemy task force that invaded Leyte
numbers over 700 vessels.
As for the planes, at least 1000
by the most conservative estimates.
On the other hand, our 1st Air Fleet
can barely field 100 operable planes.
As arranged previously, Kurita's and Nishimura's fleets
will depart towards Leyte from Borneo and Brunei Bay.
Ozawa's fleet
Luzon
Manila
Kurita's fleet
Mindoro
Samar
Panay
Leyte
Negros
Suluan
Nishimura's fleet
Mindanao
Ozawa's fleet, now designated as a decoy unit,
advancing from the Bungo Channel to the sea northeast of Manila no longer has any air cover.
Samar
Leyte
Panam
Negros
Suluan
Nishimura's fleet
They'll be feinting the enemy camp on their own.
In this time of extreme emergency,
the only possible course of action for our 1st Air Fleet
is to teach our pilots a new strategy
of strapping 250 kg bombs to their Zeros
and trying their utmost to sink one warship each
by ramming into them in a suicide attack.
I would like to hear your opinions on that.
I cannot approve of that.
And the rationale is?
During the Russo-Japanese War, even the hands on the sacrificial ships that went to blockade Port Arthur were ordered to return.
In the current conflict as well - the midget submarines
in the attack on Hawaii and Pearl Harbor.
The pilots knew they'd return home
if the surprise attack succeeded.
That's why both Admiral Togo and Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto approved the execution of those plans.
Sir, the history of warfare of the world knows examples
of desperate missions, but none of them were pure suicide.
No matter how poorly the war is going,
a suicide corps that turns its men into flying bombs
stands in defiance of the last 70 years
of Japanese naval tradition.
It's just as you said. This is a heresy
that disregards all rules of military conduct.
Sir.
The prospect of victory is no longer feasible,
so why don't we at least deal the biggest blow we can?
If we frustrate the enemy's fighting spirit,
they would be willing to conclude the war sooner.
If we don't cut it short here...
If we don't conclude the war, our homeland of Japan will be reduced to ashes and the nation will be no more.
This is no longer about the strategy.
It's a prayer for the people who yearn for peace.
A vow to save them.
Even knowing they'll remember me as a wicked and inhuman commander in 100 years, I'd still give that order.
It's because I believe
that we have no other way to save Japan.
Sir. I will also follow your lead and act upon it.
Episode 17
Birth of the Kamikaze Corps
Fighter crews, gather in briefing room #1!
Attention!
The fighter corps is ready.
We've received an order to form a special attack corps.
The special attack corps will specialize in suicide attacks,
where they strap 250 kg bombs to their Zeros
and ram the enemy ships.
I will hand out this paper now.
Those who wish to volunteer, write your name on it.
Those who don't, leave it blank.
Put it in the envelope
and have your officer hand it directly to me.
NCOs submit your paper to your superior.
This way, nobody but me
would know if you volunteered or not.
If due to health concerns,
family circumstances, or any other reason,
you can't volunteer,
don't worry about it one bit!
Submit it after careful consideration.
May I remind you,
this corps becomes active starting tomorrow.
Hey, what will you do?
I don't know yet...
The valiant taste death but once, they say.
No time to do it like now.
They say, the fool is cured only in death.
Might as well go out with a bang!
Navy Lieutenant Seki Yukio
Lieutenant Seki, can we talk?
This is First Lieutenant Kuno.
Come in.
I brought something special from my reserves.
How does that sound?
Oh? This is quite a luxurious item.
Where did you manage to find it?
A present from my classmate
who brought it from Singapore.
Then, to us.
Let's pray for each other's luck.
So the judgment day is finally here.
Lieutenant Seki.
May I tell you how I truly feel about this?
Yes. Go ahead.
I don't subscribe to those ramming attacks.
What?
Vice Admiral Onishi probably approved these ramming attacks believing we'd only ever use this tactic once.
But I know - once this tactic is introduced,
there will be no stopping it.
It'll spread to all the other Navy Air Corps as well.
I fear that as a result,
even if it started as a volunteer system,
it will eventually become a strategy
that everyone would be coerced into.
There's a grain of reason to what you say.
But if we want to prevent them... No.
Supposing we put the ramming attacks
on halt for now, do you have any other good plan
for extricating our country from this state of the war?
Kuno, you actually value your life, don't you?
Lieutenant Seki...
I didn't want to die either,
up until about 10 minutes ago.
But now I made up my mind.
I would like to volunteer for the special attack corps.
So that's what you actually came for?
I could only tell you how I truly feel about it
because I made up my mind already.
You rascal! Even tricked me into speaking my mind!
So how is it? How many applicants did we get?
Every single one of them.
The young and hot-blooded Yokaren trainees
The seven buttons anchor the cherry blossoms in our chests
We fly forth today as well, to Lake Kasumigaura...
Lieutenant Seki came to see you.
Come in.
Hey. Have a seat now.
I'll have one, thanks.
By the way, when our special attack corps is formed,
it'll be the first one of the kind.
So choosing a leader
for such an unprecedented unit is especially difficult.
I consulted with various staff members...
What do you say?
Will you accept this position?
I'd be honored to.
I see. So you will accept it?
We judged that a military academy graduate
should be the first to take the reins.
After all, it's a matter of commanding the front line troops.
We're counting on you, Lieutenant Seki.
4 vehicles from the special attack corps,
newly formed on Mabalacat air base in the Philippines,
escorted by 4 fighters from the interception squadron
on the 20th of October at 5 p.m.
were reassigned to the base on Cebu Island as part of the 201st Air Squadron under Wing Commander Nakajima,
who just returned to the base from Manila.
In view of the current war situation,
we decided to form a special ramming corps
of 26 carrier-based fighters within the 201st Air Squadron.
It will be christened
"Special Kamikaze Attack Corps."
This attack corps will be subdivided into four units:
Shikishima, Yamato, Asahi, and Yamazakura.
Its commanding officer is Navy Lieutenant Seki Yukio.
The mission of this attack corps
will be to devastate the enemy surface fleet.
We hope to see some favorable results
before the planned engagement in the Leyte Gulf.
The Yamato Unit will transfer to Cebu Base on October 20th,
so as to put the tactics into practice from Cebu.
That's quite impressive.
Did you graduate from a music school,
First Lieutenant Kuno?
No, sir. My big sister was learning to play
and I was simply imitating her.
I should be ashamed.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
An important connection between music and piloting has even been proven scientifically.
It's not uncommon for the fighter pilots
to also be piano prodigies.
Wing Commander,
I'd like to ask for a favor.
What is it, Ensign Uemura?
I'm not getting excluded
from the Special Attack Corps, am I?
What do you mean by that?
Sir.
I'm a recent academy graduate
still mentored by First Lieutenant Kuno.
I don't have a lot of flight hours so I was worried
about getting excluded from regular missions.
Marines and students
don't get selected for the suicide corps.
If you're here, you have enough flight hours.
You've nothing to worry about.
Play us another tune.
Okay.
Enemy task force of 6 aircraft carriers is located
about 60 nautical miles east of Suluan Island.
Roger.
3 kamikaze planes, 2 interceptors. Suicide squad commander is First Lieutenant Kuno. Prepare to sortie at once!
Ah! Grummans are here!
Remove ordnance from kamikaze planes!
Disperse the vehicles!
Start up!
Prepare to take off!
Start up the kamikaze planes!
Pursue the enemy, don't let them slip!
Chase the enemy planes at once.
Find their mother ship!
Yamato Unit of the Special Kamikaze Corps takes off!
Thus, the Special Kamikaze Corps
went out on its first sortie.
However, hampered on the way by the bad weather,
2 planes had to return unable to find the enemy.
Only the First Lieutenant Kuno's plane never returned.
Did he feel too guilty for not finding the enemy,
or did he do it as a silent protest to the ramming attack,
unprecedented in history?
In any case, First Lieutenant Kuno never returned.
And so the IJN never revealed to the public that he was in fact the first ever pilot to carry out a kamikaze mission.
Was it because they failed
to produce any spectacular results?
Or perhaps because First Lieutenant Kuno
was fresh out of the academy?
The reasons for that
are shrouded in mystery even to this day.
Transmission from Shikishima Unit.
Enemy task force still not found.
Running short on fuel,
but will continue the search.
The weather seems to be bad today as well.
Only 3 more days until Kurita's fleet reaches Leyte.
If we don't find and hit the enemy carrier
within the next 3 days, this strategy will be a failure.
Seki also took it to heart.
He's desperately looking for them every day.
The Shikishima Unit that sortied from the Mabalacat Base
was spending days in the air, searching for the American task force,
but still never managed to locate it.
They couldn't help but to double back empty-handed.
We couldn't find them today either.
We're deeply sorry.
Will you be alright?
First Lieutenant Kuno,
I'm going your way too. Just you wait.
26th, 0600.
The first attack corps sighted an enemy task force
off the coast of Suluan Island and immediately engaged.
Kamikaze unit, prepare to sortie!
On behalf of 100 million of our people,
I'm praying for your success today,
Shikishima Unit of the Kamikaze Corps takes off!
On October 25th, at 7:25 a.m.,
the Kamikaze Corps with its commander, Navy Lieutenant Seki in the lead, took off from the Mabalacat Base.
Even before the Shikishima Unit,
at 6:30 a.m. on the 25th,
6 planes from the Asahi and Yamazakura Units
took off from Davao Base in Mindanao.
Motoko. Motoko, you used to laugh a lot
when you looked at my face.
You used to sleep soundly in my embrace.
Sometimes, I'd even bathe you myself.
When you grow up and start wondering about me,
ask your mother and your aunt Kayo
to tell you everything about me.
I wanted to see it myself,
as you grow up and find happiness.
But knowing that I die while I'm still a stranger to you,
I won't feel any sadness.
When you grow up and want to see your father,
come to Yasukuni Shrine.
There, if you pray earnestly enough in your heart,
your father's face will definitely appear before you.
I will always be near, watching over you.
You should become a kind person, loved by others.
When you grow up and start wondering about me,
please ask them to read this letter to you.
To Uemura Motoko. From father.
Transmission from the Shikishima Unit.
1010: in the sea east of Samar Island, 4 to 5 battleships,
plus over 30 cruisers, destroyers, and other vessels.
In the air above them,
spotted over 20 Grummans heading north.
Shikishima Unit reporting. 1040. Located one formation about 90 nautical miles from Tacloban, at 85 degrees.
4 carriers, 6 cruisers and destroyers.
Proceeding to strike immediately!
Plane 1, commence attack.
Plane 2, commence attack.
Plane 3 follow suit!
Thus, the Special Kamikaze Attack Corps was born.
And until the end of the war, more than 2,500
young bright lives would be wasted one after another.
I speak to the souls of the fallen kamikaze.
I bow and thank you for your spirited fight.
You believed in our ultimate victory,
and scattered your lives like petals in suicide attacks.
Even so, we found ourselves being unable
to live up to that conviction of yours.
With my death, I would like to apologize to the heroic spirits of my former subordinates and their families.
Those passing their judgment upon others
have to be prepared to be judged themselves.
Even knowing their sentence shall be that of death.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
April 1943.
To encourage all the Japanese front line bases,
struggling under the American onslaught,
the Commander-in-Chief
of the Combined Fleet Yamamoto Isoroku
embarked on a front line inspection,
notwithstanding the risks involved.
A unit of 16 Lockheed P-38's
was the first one to receive that intel.
So it proceeded to pounce on
Yamamoto's plane in the sky over Bougainville.
Episode 18
Operation Vengeance
Don't miss the next week's decision:
Operation Vengeance.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2