The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Air raid! Air raid!
Start up! Start me up!
Episode 15
Rabaul Air Corps
First observation post reported 50 aircraft passing by.
Plus 30 planes in a new formation.
Continuing the observation.
So it's over a 100 planes...
Damn it. Their numbers are growing by the day.
What about our planes?
Sir. Already at less than half strength.
They're here!
After the withdrawal from Guadalcanal Island,
the Rabaul Base on New Britain Island
served as a front line base,
protecting the southern resources in Japanese hands.
But by the summer of 1943,
the US Army had wrestled the mastery of sea and air
in the Rabaul area out of Japanese hands.
Chiefly, the US military aimed
to stop any resupply from the sea.
In other words, they planned to destroy the Tokyo Express.
Its sheer size allowed the US Army
to switch to offensive operations.
The Rabaul Base was the primary fulcrum
of Japan's Southern Strategy,
which is why air raids against it
were being launched daily.
The 26th Air Squadron Command
Commander!
Is the Combined Fleet Headquarters still idle?
Presently, it seems reinforcing Rabaul
is not among their priorities.
The Rabaul Air Corps will have to make do
with what they currently have.
They've got cold feet!
Wing commander!
You don't have to go that far.
But Wing Commander,
the recon aircraft reports
that here in New Guinea,
between Lae, Port Moresby, and the Guadalcanal Island,
the enemy had amassed over a 100 planes on their airfields!
It's obvious they're poised for an attack!
Do you think we should leave them be?!
Wing Commander!
Wait.
Aviation Staff Officer!
I will now return to the headquarters on Truk Island.
I hope to meet personally
with the Combined Fleet Commander-in-Chief Koga
and tell him how desperate things are on Rabaul.
It'll take too long!
By the time you'll reach Truk,
it'll be too late to do anything!
Enemy mobile task force with transports
are already being seen
off the coast of Bougainville and in the Coral Sea!
Hey, look.
Huh?
Scout to base. Scout to base.
This is Yame's plane of 305th Air Squadron.
Enemy task force spotted:
2 aircraft carriers, 2 cruisers, and 6 destroyers
moving east-northeast in a circular battle formation.
Squad Commander, judging from the recent air raids
and the enemy fleet maneuvers,
their plan is to land either on Bougainville
or here on New Britain next.
Let's strike first! If we miss our chance to attack now,
we'll come to regret it later.
Yame managed to find the enemy?
It's a task force with 2 aircraft carriers
south of Rendova Island.
I see.
Headquarters! Headquarters!
Yame's plane speaking.
Observing a separate formation.
I'll draw closer to confirm the composition
of the transport fleet.
Yame, turn back! Don't overdo it.
I guess, the enemy really is landing somewhere today.
It's gotta be either Bougainville or New Britain.
If we let them pull that off,
they'll have us on a silver plate!
Damn it... If only we had more planes!
Do those mainland pricks
really understand the situation?
Do they perhaps think that we have
hundreds upon thousands of planes here in Rabaul?
Commander, what was the Combined Fleet's
answer to our proposal?
The strategy meeting is underway.
Stick to the designated strategy.
What are they thinking?!
If we delay for any longer,
Rabaul will repeat the fate of Guadalcanal.
Headquarters! Headquarters!
About 20 more enemy ships in a separate convoy.
Several Grummans ambushed me from behind!
Yame? Yame! Are you okay?
Yame! Don't die!
Lost contact!
Blazes...
To hell with it!
Wait, Sasagawa!
Sasagawa!
Sasagawa, hold it!
Commander, please let me do it!
I cannot let Yame die alone!
Negative! No unauthorized actions!
Commander, I'm not afraid to die.
It's better than doing nothing.
Sasagawa, I understand well how you feel.
We're all comrades who swore
to stick together even in death.
But we're also bound by the military discipline.
Unauthorized sorties are unacceptable.
Listen, Sasagawa.
Just dying is easy.
And we should at all times
be prepared to ram the target, if needed.
But that doesn't mean risking our lives recklessly.
Yame knew full well he wasn't going to return home
when he took on this recon mission.
If we truly want to avenge him,
we all have to value our own lives a little more.
It won't be long till we get our chance
to die together. You hear, Sasagawa?
Yes.
Yame.
Yame!
We'll definitely join you later!
I'm Yonezawa of the press corps.
Yes, come in.
The Combined Fleet on Truk Island
seems rather reluctant to act upon the request from Rabaul.
Have one.
After securing Guadalcanal and the surrounding islands,
the enemy will target Bougainville or New Britain next.
Are we really just going to give up on Rabaul,
like we did with Guadalcanal?
I'm a mere fighter pilot.
We don't get a say in strategic decisions.
No, just think about it: if a strategy disregards completely
the wishes of this foremost base,
it means the Combined Fleet has lost their nerve
ever since the Midway debacle.
What happened at Midway
is supposed to be a national secret.
Only the situation at Rabaul is passed on truthfully.
Such is the duty of the press corps.
If you get a chance, please tell the people on the mainland
to send in every plane they can.
After all, we're the Rabaul Air Corps
that once was glorified in songs as invincible.
Every fighter pilot longed to be enlisted in the Rabaul Corps.
Who's there?!
Sir! Yamaguchi of the maintenance crew.
What happened?
This frame took a beating during the daytime air raid.
But I think we can patch her up
if we replace the engine.
Presently, every single plane is precious for this base.
I hope to make it into a fine Zero fighter
by tomorrow morning to please the crew.
Solomon Archipelago
New Guinea                         Rabaul                      Bougainville Island
New Britain Island
Guadalcanal Island
Guam Island
Truk Island
At the same time, at the Combined Fleet
Headquarters on Truk Island.
A formation of 2 aircraft carriers, 3 cruisers,
4 destroyers, and 10 transport ships is heading north.
Sir! Rabaul’s patrol aircraft spotted
a separate fleet off the Shortland Island.
I see. What's the fleet's composition?
Found an enemy task force: one aircraft carrier,
2 cruisers, and 5 transports.
Also observing ships following after.
So it's either Bougainville or New Britain next.
Sir! Please dispatch the planes and fleets
from Truk Island to Rabaul at once.
If we act now...
Only if we act right now, will we make it in time.
Sir!
Our men on Rabaul are only waiting for your decisive order!
Their morale is still strong.
Now's the time to mobilize
all of our fleet's resources and hit the enemy!
I also support the aviation adviser's point.
Hit the enemy coming from the sea in the sea.
This is the iron rule of battle.
What's more, the Rabaul base
keeps making increasing requests nigh daily.
Dispatch our air wings and fleets to Rabaul!
The enemy is aiming either for Bougainville or New Britain.
We've no time to hesitate.
If we let them land unopposed now, we'll regret it later!
Sir, this may present a chance for us
to avenge Midway and the Solomon Islands!
Sir, let's go for it!
The troops' morale is at a historical high.
Let's give the arrogant and disrespectful enemy
a taste of our fighting spirit!
Someone call Vice Admiral Ozawa here.
The Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet Koga
finally decided to respond to the desperate requests
from the Rabaul front line base.
The Third Fleet under the command of Vice Admiral Ozawa.
All the air wings of this fleet
were sent to Rabaul.
Strategical decisions require quick and bold action.
In that sense, this decision
did little to slow down the Americans.
In the early morning on the day
Ozawa's fleet arrived in Rabaul,
using the bad weather from the previous days
to camouflage themselves,
the American fleet of 18 transports and 9 escorts
initiated a surprise landing on Cape Torokina
on the west coast of Bougainville Island.
It happened on November 1st, 1943.
Reinforcements arrived,
as promised by the Combined Fleet Commander.
Yeah.
70 fighters from Zuikaku of the Ozawa's fleet.
70 Zero fighters from Shokaku.
30 torpedo bombers from Zuiho.
Aside from those, a total of 180 more aircraft
should arrive by the 3rd.
What's wrong?
Aren't you happy to see the reinforcements arrive?
I am. But it's a shame they didn't arrive just a day earlier
to prevent the enemy from landing in Torokina.
I see. So you've received a transfer to Rabaul?
Glad to see you're doing well.
Now, let's pray that your luck in battle
never runs out. And drink to it.
There's something I need to ask.
I know.
"Why didn't they dispatch Ozawa's fleet
before the enemy landed in Torokina?"
Yes.
I'm hearing rumors of you distinguishing yourself as a pilot.
I'm proud to have such a brilliant nephew.
Answer, please.
At times, you can be intimidating too.
Even if you aspired to be a lawyer before,
now you're a military man to the marrow.
How many years does it take to become a full-fledged pilot these days?
Huh? Like the one such as you.
Sir. That'd be five years at least.
Five years, huh?
We wouldn't want our excellent pilots that take five years to train to lose their lives willy-nilly, would we?
The face of warfare is defined by airpower now.
Do you think the conclusion to this war
will be written here in Rabaul?
Sir?
Making use of his numerical advantage,
the enemy is now trying to mount a major counteroffensive.
At times like this, perhaps retreating to regroup
is preferable to just mindlessly attacking with all you've got.
U-Uncle!
It's so easy to relax with a relative,
I unknowingly ended up just speaking my mind.
Well, let's have a toast.
Yes, Sir. Let's raise it.
Idiot. Didn't you call me "uncle" just a moment ago?
We might never meet again.
Ensign Koga, what were you thinking,
volunteering for such an assignment?
Rabaul is no longer the carefree paradise
like in the songs they sing back on mainland.
That was because the commander of the 305th
is my mentor Kamijo.
Commander, Nida's plane speaking!
Enemy plane 30 degrees forward to the right.
Fine!
All pilots, enter the clouds dead ahead
and make a reverse sweep.
Proceed!
Our silvery wings come together at the Southern Front
The unshaken defense of our Sea Eagles
At the enemy's front line of human bullets
Honor is with us. We are the Rabaul Naval Air Corps!
The Rabaul Air Corps launched a promising
and fearless attack both on the sea and on land.
At the time, the results of that battle were announced by the Imperial Headquarters with great fanfare.
However, in the face of the immeasurable
quantitative advantage of the US Military,
Rabaul’s air power was being gradually depleted.
The air battle off the Bougainville Island
was still in full swing on November 13th, 1943,
when an unbelievable happening befell
the airmen of the Rabaul Air Corps.
The headquarters of the Ozawa's 3rd Fleet,
which came from Truk Island with reinforcements
suddenly made a 180
and began pulling back towards Truk Island.
Same as before, it's just us now.
An order has been issued
for all the operable aircraft at Rabaul Base
to immediately attack and destroy the enemy surface fleet
heading north through the seas west of Bougainville Island.
At the moment, I have nothing new
to say to you before a sortie.
But I pray sincerely that you fight bravely and reap success.
Commander!
Commander, please let me ride it with you. I beg you!
Cretin! You're still injured. Back off!
But... Stick together even in death...
Eguchi, I'll be waiting for you at the Sanzu River crossing.
You come join me as soon as that arm heals up!
Commander!
Everyone, make sure to give Rabaul a look.
It might be your last one.
Flight Lieutenant Kamijo, my uncle asked me if I thought the conclusion to this war would be written in Rabaul.
Koga, you're concerned about the Ozawa's fleet
being pulled out of Rabaul.
But I saw it coming.
Saw it, sir?
In his heart of hearts, your uncle,
the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet
knows that seizing this chance quickly
is even more important in defense than in attack.
In that sense, it's us, the ones who have been constantly pressing for Ozawa's Fleet to be dispatched from Truk,
who are at fault for rocking the boat
and disconcerting your usually cool-headed uncle.
Commander!
You heard it, everyone?
It's now up to us to write a conclusion to this battle!
But that doesn't mean you should be in a hurry to die!
Live to fight another day as best you can!
Commander! Enemy task force spotted!
Enemy planes, upper right!
That's it! Let's do it!
"We're engaging the enemy."
Anything after that?
Not yet.
I'll live to fight another day!
Hey! Flight Lieutenant Kamijo!
Commander!
Live to fight another day.
You must live to fight another day!
That's the spirit of the Rabaul Air Corps!
On February 1st, 1944, the US Army made one big leap
and landed on the Marshall Islands.
On February 17th, that same task force invaded Truk,
Marshall Archipelago
Truk Archipelago
following it up with air raids on Tinian and Saipan.
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
Tinian
Guam
Rabaul was left far behind the front lines,
fully isolated and neutralized.
Mariana Archipelago
Saipan
Tinian
Guam
Marshall Archipelago
Truk Archipelago
Rabaul
Amidst this all-consuming trend
of things going downhill everywhere,
wouldn't any kind of decision at all
seem ultimately futile and powerless?
Maybe that's another one of those things
that only heaven knows.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
July 1943.
The Japanese army garrisons
the Kiska Island with 5,600 soldiers.
Yet it's on the verge of being crushed
by the concentrated attack of the US Army.
Major General Kimura receives the order
to rescue the entire garrison.
He'll attempt a daring and fearless plan to hide in the fog
and sneak away from under the wary enemy's nose.
Episode 16
Evacuation of Kiska
Witness the next week's decision:
Evacuation of Kiska.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
瑞鶴の海鷲