The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
May 1942.
Aimed at securing the hold on Rabaul bases,
and opening a prospect for attacking the Australian north,
Port Moresby Operation was started.
Its first step was the capture of Tulagi island
by the special landing party that started from Rabaul.
However,
having been warned in advance of the Japanese attack,
the Australian garrison had already been evacuated.
The island was entirely deserted.
6:30 am on May 4th.
Upon learning of the Japanese occupation of Tulagi Island,
the US Mobile Task Force commander, Rear Admiral Fletcher
immediately dispatched the air wings
of the Lexington carrier,
ordering them to commence the attack.
Episode 8
Battle of the Coral Sea
At that time, on the Japanese side,
in his Rabaul headquarters,
the Commander-in-Chief of the 4th Fleet,
Vice Admiral Inoue,
executing the overall command of this operation,
was expecting reports from the front line.
What are the losses?
Destroyer - 1, minesweepers - 2,
as well as one submarine chaser.
But if we were attacked solely by carrier-based planes...
It means that the American Mobile Fleet
has advanced deep into the Coral Sea, around here.
Yes...
The enemy Mobile Fleet must definitely be
within 200 nautical miles of Tulagi.
However, our own Mobile Fleet is currently refueling
about 360 nautical miles north of Tulagi Island.
One might conclude the enemy
is fairly well-informed about our operations,
but that's also their weakness.
As long as the enemy knows
that our operation's objective is Port Moresby right here,
their movements are rigidly confined
to the Coral Sea.
A telegram from the Combined Fleet
Commander-in-Chief.
The elusive American carriers
that have been pestering us since the war's outbreak -
dealing with them now
would be immensely rousing for our morale.
On May 6, with orders to deal a decisive blow
to the American Mobile Task Force,
under the leadership of Rear Admiral Takagi Takeo,
the Japanese Mobile Task Force advanced into the Coral Sea.
From the bridge of the brand new carrier Zuikaku,
the pride of the Japanese Navy,
together with Rear Admiral Takagi,
Commander of the 5th Carrier Division
Rear Admiral Hara was overseeing the operation.
Will we be able to spot them?
That's something I'm fearing myself.
Tomorrow night, upon passing by
the southern tip of San Cristobal Island,
we would enter the Coral Sea from the east.
It's like looking for a single fish in the entire Pacific Ocean.
Exactly so.
Guinea
New Britain Island
Solomon Sea
Japanese Fleet
Solomon Islands
Coral Sea
Bougainville Island
Guadalcanal Island
Tulagi
Combined ABDACOM Fleet
(US / Britain / Australia)
Meanwhile, Yorktown and Lexington -
two carrier flagships of the American Mobile Task Force
linked up with British-Australian Combined Fleet,
about 360 nautical miles south of Guadalcanal Island,
preparing for a decisive face-off with the Japanese fleet.
The supreme commander
of the American Mobile Fleet, Admiral Fletcher
held a strategy conference
aboard aircraft carrier Yorktown.
Intelligence says,
the Japanese forces, aiming to land at Port Moresby
are expected to pass through
the Solomon Sea on 7th or 8th.
Then, what about the Japanese Mobile Fleet?
It is beyond doubt that they are moving southwards,
west of the Solomon islands.
However, there's still no exact data
of their current position.
At any rate, this is about
who discovers the enemy carrier first.
Even if just a minute or second faster.
In a carrier battle, even a single moment matters.
Both the Japanese and the American fleets
wanted to seize the initiative.
Hence both were combing through the area like mad.
Two next days - the 5th and the 6th of May,
were entirely uneventful.
Perhaps, the enemy is hoping
to strike at our landing party tomorrow,
as we would be passing through Solomon Sea?
No, more likely... The day after tomorrow,
in the Coral Sea, as we would turn to Port Moresby.
In case they choose the day after tomorrow,
tomorrow they would probably be
operating here on the southern side.
This is all like one big game of hide-and-seek.
That's the point - whoever finds the enemy first, wins.
Tomorrow, we need to catch the enemy by the tail
and deliver a decisive blow!
What if we don't find them at the estimated location?
In that case, we would also have
to turn west and cross the Coral Sea.
At the same time, the Japanese convoys, carrying
Port Moresby assault party, together with their escorts,
centered around aircraft carrier Shoho
to protect them from anything,
were sailing south through the central part
of the Solomon Sea.
Until sometime after 9 am an enemy aircraft was spotted
and the whole fleet was brought into full alert.
All crew! Man your stations!
Direction - 90 degrees! Height - 4 degrees!
Only one aircraft!
After it!
Thus, the time was gradually drawing near
for the first in history carrier-on-carrier battle.
It was shipborne!
The enemy carrier should totally be near here!
Make every precaution so as not to reveal us
to radio detection, only then search for the enemy!
Roger!
Report from Shokaku's recon aircraft!
Discovered enemy aircraft carrier!
400 nautical miles southwest of Tulagi.
Carrier fighters, carrier bombers,
all aircraft take off!
The enemy fleet!
At the Japanese camp on Rabaul...
The enemy is to 170 degrees from Rossel Island,
82 nautical miles away.
We have concluded
that the enemy split his task force in two.
First, we should attack the enemy
in the direction of Rossel Island with all our might.
Meanwhile, escorted by our mobile fleet,
the convoy evacuates to the northwest.
However, the 5th Carrier Division has been
400 nautical miles southwest of Tulagi for a long time.
They had already commenced
an all-out attack on the enemy.
Huh?
That is a refueling ship!
Where are the damn carriers?
Carriers!
Around this time, on the Japanese side,
tasked with escorting a transport convoy, carrier Shoho
was already under heavy attack
from carrier-based aircraft of the American mobile fleet.
Captain! A fire broke out!
What?
Damn it!
The loss of the aircraft carrier Shoho
is on us, the 5th Carrier Division!
Mistaking a tanker for a carrier
is a display of utter incompetence!
Even so, it's taking everyone pretty long!
Communications department,
what are you waiting for?!
Tell them to return home immediately
after dropping the payload!
We'll never make it in time
if we keep dawdling!
Make arrangement for the returning attack vehicles
to be swiftly housed!
We need our entire mobile fleet
to and chase the enemy to the northwest
and smash them at full speed!
We'll be sure to avenge Shoho tenfold!
And yet, we have obviously
wasted too much time already.
Sir,
let's do it.
A night attack!
That one is dangerous.
We'll be fine.
Our 5th Carrier Division has brilliant pilots.
The Japanese commander's worries
were not entirely unjustified.
The 5th Carrier Division
was formed immediately prior
to the outbreak of the war.
The training that pilots received was severely insufficient,
rendering night attack in particular a fool's errand.
However, the 5th Carrier Division commander,
Rear Admiral Hara coerced everyone into it forcibly.
We can do it if we're resolute enough.
All right. If that's what you believe in as a commander.
Order:
The main force
would perform a night attack against the enemy mobile fleet
that showed up in the northern part of Coral Sea.
Using our fleet's brilliant pilots,
we'll organize the groups of 6 carrier-based bombers
and 9 carrier-based fighters per ship.
Take off as soon as the preparations are finished.
Attack with full resolve.
The Japanese planes
are yet to catch any glimpse of us.
Today, our mobile fleet is sailing
under the protection of the goddess of victory.
Sortie immediately!
There's a squall below.
Not much we can do now!
Captain! Above to the right, enemy planes!
Crap!
Damn it.
How did they manage to find us?
All planes! Drop the torpedoes!
Just as all our fighters are away,
they're having a free rein!
Look for that carrier! Carrier!
There's gotta be a carrier nearby!
Find it!
5th Carrier Division reports!
Still unable to discover the enemy.
Receiving heavy fire from enemy fighters.
Trying to engage enemy fighters.
Close to annihilation.
Damn it all. Any idea which way our hometown is?
I'd rather go home now and jump in a hot bath.
Captain,
at this rate, we can only hope for one,
nonsensically giant bath.
Yeah, and what's worse, it's ice-cold.
Captain!
60 degrees to the right, locating friendly carrier!
What?
Oh! I see, I see.
Deploy landing gear at once!
Captain!
This is an enemy carrier!
What!?
The markings on the deck
and the bridge shape are not right!
Enemy!
It was the enemy!
They're finally back!
Sirs, enemy carrier in the immediate vicinity!
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Other vehicles also saw it clearly.
All right!
Night-time attacks are demanding.
Can't be helped now.
How about tomorrow?
Battle of the Coral Sea entered its second day.
Too impatient to wait for the dawn,
both Japan and the US
dispatched their reconnaissance aircraft
in search of one another's carrier.
Ah! The enemy carrier!
I think there's a carrier!
Shokaku's reconnaissance aircraft reports:
Observing enemy carrier.
Will maintain visual contact.
Position in relation to us - 205 degrees. Distance -
235 nautical miles. Course 170 degrees. Speed 16 knots
Japanese Fleet
Solomon Islands
Coral Sea
Solomon Sea
Guadalcanal Island
Tulagi
Combined ABDACOM Fleet
(US / Britain / Australia)
Carriers - 2, battleship - 1.
Heavy cruisers - 2, light cruiser - 1.
Plus six destroyers!
Captain, we now have barely enough fuel for the return trip.
We made a sufficiently detailed report,
so it should be fine.
Good.
I'm breaking visual contact with the enemy
and returning us home.
At almost the exact same time, American reconnaissance
aircraft also discovered the Japanese mobile fleet.
The weather is turning volatile.
It's best that we show our allies the exact way.
Reconnaissance aircraft reports:
Canceling our return.
Will guide our attack squadron instead.
Rest is up to you, attack squadron!
Captain, our fuel is no more.
Squadron, proceed to attack!
Fire!
Full starboard!
Hurry!
Indeed, this storm must be a God's providence.
Rather, Shokaku is not depending on anyone else
to stand out against the enemy.
They sure did quite a number on us.
But look.
As soon as the battle is over,
carrier Zuikaku appears on the scene.
Communications department!
Report to Rabaul for Fleet Commander:
The attack unit returned at around 11 am
and was housed.
Currently consolidating what's left of our forces,
but no prospect for re-attack today.
In addition, the exhaustion
of both the offensive ability and the fuel supplies
renders the nighttime high-speed navigation too risky.
The one who received the report
was the Commander-in-Chief of the 4th fleet, Inoue.
Nothing we can do about it,
if even Shokaku came under attack.
Order them to hold the attack and head north.
Moresby Offensive is postponed!
What? They postponed the Port Moresby Operation?
Let's order them to pursue the enemy!
Upon receiving the order
from the Combined Fleet Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto,
the 4th Fleet Mobile Task Force headed south
at full speed when it was 2:00 am on the 9th.
And yet, they never managed
to catch up with the American task force.
Immediately upon hearing this report,
Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto
rearranged the 4th Fleet,
appointing its Mobile Task Force elsewhere.
The reason was because the day was drawing near
for Operation Midway, planned next, to take place.
But at the same time,
he was dissatisfied with his commander,
who was constantly letting the victory slip away.
Damage-wise, both the Japanese and US sides
suffered approximately the same losses in this battle.
When you get overly concerned
with your allies' safety,
you overlook the importance of damaging the enemy,
and let the operation deteriorate into a stalemate.
This time, the 4th Fleet of the IJN emerged victorious
tactics-wise, but got beaten strategy-wise.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
The reason for which the war on the Pacific was let loose
was the acquisition of the oil-rich southern regions.
In the invasion of Java Island,
Japan sent ahead three forward battalions,
tasked with securing the targeted oil fields.
The commander was hoping to thus negate
the possibility of the enemy sabotaging it.
The Indonesian National Independence Movement
also took advantage of Japan's invasion.
Don't miss the next week's decision:
The Fall of Java.
Episode 9
The Fall of Java
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2