The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
Having set the Pacific ablaze with a successful surprise attack on Hawaii, the Japanese army
capitalized on that momentum with advances on Hong Kong, the Malay Peninsula, the Philippines, Celebes, Borneo, and so on.
The stage was set for the capture of Java.
The ultimate goal of Operation Java
was the acquisition of abundant oil resources.
British Borneo
Dutch Borneo
As well as connecting the islands of Sumatra and Java
into one big defensive ridge.
At that time, the island of Java
was part of the Dutch East Indies.
These days, we know it as Indonesia.
British Borneo
Dutch Borneo
Philippines
Celebes
Java
Sumatra
Malaya
French Indochina
Firstly, the coveted oil fields and air bases
of Sumatra and Palembang were captured
by the combined forces of three Japanese
forward paratrooper battalions.
Episode 9
The Fall of Java
From the General Staff's point of view,
among all Southern Strategy operations,
the capture of Java was likely to pose the biggest challenge.
The most pressing concern was the possible destruction of oil installations before the Japanese army takes over.
Through the efforts of 3 paratrooper regiments,
both the oil field and air base were captured intact.
Likewise, the Japanese army had previously conquered Sumatra, completing the isolation of Java.
Lieutenant General Imamura arrived in the area
with his 40,000 strong 16th Army.
On February 27th, they began their march
through the island of Java.
The combined allied forces in Java were under the supreme command of Dutch Lieutenant General ter Poorten.
Defending Java were the combined ABDACOM forces:
Dutch, British, Americans, and Australians,
as well as local conscripts.
A joint force of 80,000.
Meaning they outnumbered the Japanese 2 to 1.
However, the combined Dutch command
was facing the risk of an uprising of 50 million dissidents
suddenly taking up arms against them.
By that time, in Indonesia,
under the joint leadership of Sukarno and Hatta,
the National Independence Movement,
resisting Dutch rule, was thriving.
Anticipating the Japanese army's approach,
Rear Admiral Doorman of the Dutch Navy
ordered the combined allied fleet to set sail.
But it was destroyed effortlessly by the Japanese fleet
during the Battle for Surabaya, off the coast of Batavia.
However, among the ships then anchored at Bantam Bay
watching this battle unfold with bated breath,
four Japanese transport vessels
were hit by torpedoes.
Ironically enough, those friendly torpedoes passed right under
an already foundering American cruiser.
Among the hit vessels was Sakuramaru, carrying Lieutenant General Imamura, the 16th Army commander.
To his sheer surprise, Lieutenant General Imamura,
found himself swimming through the warm southern waters.
However, Lieutenant General Imamura
casually switched ships, and on March 1st,
the Japanese army launched a full-scale landing
on the island of Java with all available forces.
The main body of the 16th Army was split
into three formations, each one making steady progress.
With Bandung as their goal, all three were advancing.
All forces have successfully made it ashore!
What is the battle situation?
It looks exceedingly favorable for us.
You could even say too much so.
I see.
Both sides are conserving themselves
right until the battle's conclusion.
Roger.
We don't fight to kill as many as we can, but to force
a surrender with minimal casualties on our side.
Relax, it's still a long way off.
Unaware of the Japanese army's calculation, the combined forces commander ter Poorten was worried sick.
We're reviewing combat reports
from each of the districts.
The Japanese forces number 30,000 to 40,000.
Can't we get reliable information sooner?
As usual with coalitions, it always takes some strong time to relay information.
Exactitude! Exactitude is what we need!
What about the local populace?
Why not employ them
for obtaining reliable information?
Yes. Well, as a matter of fact...
What is it ?
Landed in the Kragan Cape area -
around 50,000 Japanese.
50,000?
And apparently, 80,000 more Japanese
are landing in Bantam Bay.
80,000?
What? 200,000?
Putting together various reports from the locals,
they established that
the Japanese numbered 200,000 in total.
These estimates
were grossly inflated by the natives
and in this fashion passed on to the Dutch.
It was believed until the very end
that the 16th Army numbered up to 200,000 troops.
The Dutch efforts at gathering intelligence
were not only curtailed by the natives,
but also by their own lackluster methods.
The Natives from the National
Independence Movement made every effort
to expedite the Japanese army's advance
and ensure a success for the operation.
Any new intel on Japanese activity?
We need to know.
What?
You want to know about Japanese activity?
Good luck with that.
The newspaper has yet to hit our desk.
On the frontline, the enemy is not putting up
much of a fight. It's a bit anticlimactic, even.
The less resistance we meet,
the less casualties we take.
A new tank model?
So, as of March 3rd, we have received a report
that no Japanese troops have yet landed on Java proper.
Eh? What a load of bull!
It's a Japanese tank!
In order to break the morale of the Dutch forces,
Lieutenant General Imamura
launched a massive deception campaign.
The Japanese army in Burma
seems to have entered Rangoon unopposed.
No way!
Did he just say Rangoon?
In Britain, Churchill's cabinet
has assumed responsibility for the fall of Singapore.
It appears that they will resign in full.
The natives found the broadcast
absolutely delightful.
The Japanese troops have furthermore solidified the natives' support for their campaign.
However, as they were approaching Bandung,
the resistance of the combined Dutch forces
increased drastically.
It was at this point in time, when the Japanese army's steady advance seemingly ground to a standstill.
On March 7th,
a suicide corps was formed
with more than 700 Japanese soldiers.
They were to infiltrate the suburbs of Bandung.
With those begrudging Indonesians,
even guerrilla warfare seems like a pipe dream.
Even if I order my Dutch troops to surrender,
the troops of other nations are free to disregard
a ceasefire order from me, if they so desire.
Commander.
As long as our fellow Dutchmen stand tall and fight,
fellow British and Australian soldiers
won't back down.
Although the words of Major General Sitwell,
Commander-in-Chief of British-Australian forces
channeled determination,
he was out of touch with the brutal reality.
Major General Pesman, tasked with the defense
of the Northern-Central district of Bandung,
surrendered willingly in just under few hours
after the Japanese suicide corps' attack had started.
Have you checked it's a herald from Pesman,
from the Northern-Central district of Bandung?
Yes. Without a doubt, he is a truce bearer.
All that, despite the determined resistance
they've been mounting...
I believe, the enemy is setting a trap for us.
Consequently,
we may have to level the city.
We have no choice but to set it on fire.
Sir.
I understand what you're getting at.
The casualties on our side are mounting.
The enemy will continue to resist
and won't come out of the city,
probably preparing a fortified position
for a decisive showdown.
However, that would entail
massive collateral damage on the locals.
No, we will evacuate as many as we can.
Sir, please make a decision.
Time is running out.
Even if it increases the strain on our own forces,
the local populace must be protected.
Burning the city is unacceptable.
By inflicting such a suffering on them here,
we'll alienate them for the rest of the occupation.
We didn't come here to make the locals suffer.
Roger!
Okay, let's rope the secret service agency in.
With an interpreter to escort him, a Japanese military officer disguised himself as a civilian.
As a part of a big ploy, he had already infiltrated Bandung and was awaiting for an opportunity.
On March 7th, before the Japanese troops
overwhelmed Lembang,
upon getting the order
from his military commander, he enacted the plan.
First Lieutenant of the Japanese Army Yanagawa.
I'd like an audience with the Supreme Commander
of the Allied Forces on Java, Lieutenant General ter Poorten.
What?!
The Japanese army had taken the Island of Java
completely under control.
Stifling Bandung as well.
I suggest that you surrender immediately.
Prolonging resistance any further is futile.
On March 8th, the Dutch combined forces
finally laid down their arms.
The Bandung District Defense Commander
Major General Pesman,
Governor-General Tjarda,
and Lieutenant General ter Poorten,
as well as the Army Chief of Staff
Major General Bakkers - 4 men in total
came to Kalijati
to meet with the Commander-in-Chief Imamura.
The scene of destruction in the Bandung area
presents a sorry sight.
It is needless to subject the locals
to more misery.
I wish to surrender Bandung on good terms.
The surrender of Bandung is besides the point!
What the Japanese military demands
is a complete, unconditional surrender.
The Bandung Radio Station
finally broadcast a ceasefire order to all forces.
Thus, the capture of Java, which was expected to pose
the biggest challenge of the entire Southern Strategy,
thanks to discretion in planning
and the cooperation of the natives
unexpectedly ended in a complete success,
achieved with limited casualties.
On March 10th, commanded by Lieutenant General Imamura,
the 16th Army triumphantly entered Bandung.
In the entirety of the Pacific War, no other operation was so warmly welcomed by the natives as Operation Java.
This and the fact it met all the objectives according to plan,
made it truly a one-of-a-kind operation.
Some say, the overarching decisions
of Lieutenant General Imamura,
in considering the natives' interests all along,
by not resorting to the tactics of complete annihilation,
highlighted his humanity.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
One of the Southern Strategy operations
was the capture of the Celebes.
This time as well, the paratroopers were its vanguard.
Although a cooperation
with the ground troops was promoted,
the proud Skyborne Soldiers,
the paratroopers
were mostly disdainful of ground troops, giving gradual rise to animosity.
But at a later point, this would spark
into a brazen decision, causing a major blunder.
The next decision:
The Navy Paratrooper Corps. Please look forward to it.
Episode 10
The Navy Paratrooper Corps
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2