The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
The Japanese Army Type 97 Fighter.
This fighter plane boasted high maneuverability,
but the tradeoff had been
its extremely short cruising range.
Dauntless
Spitfire
Hurricane
Type 97 Fighter
Cruising range (km)
For that reason, ever since 1939,
those responsible for air operations
in the Imperial Headquarters Army Department
were desperately trying to modernize it
in accordance with contemporary warfare.
As a result of countless modifications and experiments,
a newly-designed aircraft was born, furnished with
the same engine as the Navy's cutting-edge Zero fighter.
Two 12.7 mm machine guns.
A top speed of 515 km/h.
The fatal flaw of the previous model,
a short cruising range,
was rectified through the installation
of an auxiliary drop tank under the wing.
This is the pride of Japan on the world stage,
the Type 1 Falcon Fighter.
The commander of the 64th Squadron,
Major Kato Takeo
took it upon himself to display the efficiency of the "Falcon"
by initiating an intense flying drill with his unit.
Episode 14
Kato's Falcon Squadron
First, in December 1941,
the 64th Squadron under the command of Major Kato
supported a large invasion force
on the Malay Peninsula under the command
of Lieutenant General Tomoyuki Yamashita.
They flew from Phu Quoc Island in Indochina
to Nakhon in Thailand.
Gulf of Thailand
Phu Quoc Island
Nakhon
Gulf of Thailand
Phu Quoc Island
Nakhon
After completing its mission,
the Kato Falcon Squadron
Gulf of Thailand
Phu Quoc Island
Nakhon
Malay Peninsula
Kota Bharu
proceeded further south
to a forward Kota Bharu base in Malaysia.
Gulf of Thailand
Phu Quoc Island
Nakhon
Malay Peninsula
Kota Bharu
The tremendous pace of their advance
would later be called miraculous.
Our landing party continued its blitzkrieg, advancing all the way to the Perak River on the Malay Peninsula.
However, if the enemy destroys the bridge over it,
it'll delay the fall of Singapore, the ultimate goal
of the Malay blitzkrieg, by three months at least.
Our Falcon Squadron will be tasked
with preventing that act of sabotage
by keeping a constant air patrol
from the Alor Star air base.
To destroy the bridge, the enemy
would be likely to use planes from Kuala Lumpur.
However, those giving orders in the army aviation division
don't realize that we here at the Falcon Squadron
aren't about patiently waiting for the enemy to come out.
We'll take the initiative
and smash the enemy aircraft in Kuala Lumpur.
This is my impromptu order.
Is that clear?
Yes!
Hey, Takayama. Let me take a picture first.
Roger!
The engine roars like thunder
The Falcon conquers the edge of the clouds
The Rising Suns shining on our wings
And the Red Eagles drawn on our chests
Those are the symbols of our fighters
This is Kuala Lumpur.
Fine, let's do it!
Dammit...
Fine, then.
I'll take you to hell with me!
Captain, comrades... Goodbye!
The assault on Kuala Lumpur
was Major Kato's unauthorized order.
But contrary to the expectations, the commander's ability
to stay collected and adapt to the situation at hand
was praised by the Southern Expeditionary Army's Commander-in-Chief in a congratulatory telegram.
Hey, Takayama. This photo I took of you
ended up becoming your last one.
Just you wait.
You won't be alone in death.
On January 9th, the 64th Falcon Squadron,
commanded by Major Kato
proceeded further south to the air base in Ipoh.
From this base, they raid Singapore daily.
Aided by allied heavy bombers,
they succeeded in bombing the Singapore Air Base.
Still, without encountering the enemy fighter unit
with the Hurricane as its core,
the Falcon Squadron's decisive battle
didn't really feel all that decisive.
On January 29th, in order to support the Japanese Singapore bombing unit that sortied from Kota Bharu,
Major Kato was about to take off
with a handful of other planes from his squadron.
Still not fixed?
Yes. We needs just a little more time.
We don't have it. I'll go ahead.
Omori, catch up with us later, will you?
Roger! Will do.
However, upon arrival, they never found
the allied bombers they were supposed to support.
So they had no choice but to return.
I'm coming late. I gotta catch up
with the commander and the others.
Ah! It's our bombing unit.
Oh? But the commander isn't here to support them!
Damn it. If it came to this, I'll deal with you alone!
The commander is in a bad mood and won't talk to me.
Just as I thought.
Because we failed to support them...
Yes. He wouldn't even eat his dinner.
It's Omori!
Huh?
I fought back with just one plane.
Then, what about our bombers?
Two planes.
...Got shot down?
Forgive me if you can...
This blunder will stay with me forever.
Captain, sir. An emergency telegram arrived
from the bombing unit that sortied to Singapore today.
Read it.
In that telegram, they thanked Sergeant Major Omori
for courageously supporting them and shooting down two Hurricanes with just one aircraft in the process.
It was noted that the two downed allied bombers made an emergency landing, and all their crew members were safe.
Really? So they've been rescued?
Thank god. Thank god!
With Kato's Falcon Squadron spearheading the way,
in the face of the Japanese aviation corps' success,
the systematic resistance,
put up by the Royal Air Force had all but disappeared.
Consequently, Lieutenant General Yamashita Tomoyuki's unit, tasked with overrunning the Malay Peninsula
was now also one step closer to Singapore.
However, in their daily battles,
the Kato Falcon Squadron
kept suffering considerable losses.
Around that time,
the plans were being drawn
for the capture of the Palembang oil fields intact
by the forces of the Japanese Army's first paratrooper unit.
On February 5th, Major Kato
rushed to the Cruz base alone
to meet with the 3rd Squadron Commander.
Enemy troops are concentrating in Singapore.
Palembang should be captured
before Singapore surrenders.
As the aerial photography shows,
the enemy air base in Palembang is hidden in the jungle.
On it, they amassed about a hundred planes,
ranging from big to small.
In order to ensure a safe landing for the paratroopers,
first, we must secure air superiority by dogfighting.
Please assign that mission to my squadron.
Your squadron has lost
a considerable part of its strength in the previous battles.
You can barely provide any support
with your current strength.
Indeed, our strength has waned.
However...
Our spirit is still strong!
We'll succeed, I'm sure of it.
Please let us do it!
I feel like I can't stop you anyhow, can I?
Sir!
Ipoh
Malay Peninsula
Thus, in preparation for the air battle for Palembang,
Kato's Falcon Squadron
Kuala Lumpur
advanced further south,
making Kahang its forward base.
Kahang
Our squadron will work in cooperation
with the light bombers of the 3rd Air Corps.
We need to destroy the enemy planes in Palembang.
Whatever happens, we have to succeed.
To that end, I expect everyone to distinguish himself,
putting on display the true strength
of our entire unit until the bitter end.
They started by conducting a raid
on the British base in Palembang.
And later, on February 4th, the Falcon Fighter Squadron
sortied to support the paratrooper units.
Through their determined effort,
the successful occupation of Palembang was achieved.
The Falcon Fighter Squadron
had no time to catch their breath.
With the conclusion of action in Palembang,
they were transferred to Chiang Mai, Thailand.
From there they started raiding
the Akyab base in Burma on a daily basis.
Man, I'm tired.
Completely exhausted.
Right. Good job, everyone.
Here's the next order.
The squadron should immediately
hit and expel the remaining enemies in the area.
Eh? There's still more to do?
At war, you have to work around the clock.
Being at all times on the call is our ultimate mission.
Dammit! We keep beating them,
but they keep coming back!
At that time, Major Kato was showered in letters of admiration for his remarkable achievements
and was promoted to Lieutenant Colonel.
On May 21st, he was pursuing a British bomber,
but lost sight of it over Chittagong.
Ah! Shimizu!
Shimizu, I'll be sure to come back for you. Just you wait!
Tomorrow in the afternoon we're moving out
and transferring to the Toungoo base.
By then, I'd like to send a search and rescue mission
after Lieutenant Shimizu.
Right. Roger that. I'll have the local volunteer army
do their best to find him.
Please do.
Near noon on the next day, the 22nd,
the Falcon Squadron
completed preparations for moving to Toungoo base
to continue destroying the Allied Air Force from there.
They were just waiting
for Lieutenant Colonel Kato's sortie order.
Lieutenant Colonel, it's time to leave.
Let's wait a little longer.
The commander sure is taking his time.
It's two hours past the scheduled time already.
Shimizu, please come back safe.
Lieutenant Colonel, you have to leave now.
Hm.
Ah! Lieutenant Colonel!
It's Shimizu! Shimizu is back!
Watch out! It's the enemy!
Dammit!
Start me up!
Oh! Commander!
Dammit! I'll avenge Shimizu!
Shit...
Commander!
Finally, the 64th Falcon Squadron Commander,
Lieutenant Colonel Kato Takeo
found his eternal rest
deep on the seabed of the Bay of Bengal
on May 22, 2:30 p.m.
However, Lieutenant Colonel Kato kept on living.
His indomitable fighting spirit and determination
lived on in the hearts of his men.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
Summer of 1943.
The Japanese forward base at Rabaul
is constantly under attack from the American army.
Even the task force that was supposed to bring in reinforcements abandoned the men of the Rabaul Air Corps
as they found themselves amidst the American forces,
advancing like a tidal wave.
Unsurprisingly, they never made it back home.
Episode 15
Rabaul Air Corps
Look forward to next week's Decision:
Rabaul Air Corps.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Song Translation
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2
pittman789