The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let others see your tears
On March 16th, 1945, with the fall of Iwo Jima, the US Army
secured a foothold for the invasion of mainland Japan.
Aiming to strengthen their position for a future invasion,
an order to capture Okinawa was handed to the Commander-in-Chief of the US 5th Fleet, Admiral Spruance.
Under his command was the Fast Carrier Task Force,
led by Vice Admiral Mitscher.
Aside from that, was Task Force 54 under Rear Admiral Deyo: 10 battleships, 9 heavy cruisers, and 23 destroyers.
As well as British Carrier Force 57
under Vice Admiral Rawlings from the Royal Navy.
An enormous war fleet that totaled 1,317 ships,
1,727 carrier-based aircraft, and 452,000 personnel.
In contrast, the Japanese Combined Fleet Headquarters,
that was confined to the mainland,
could only send a Surface Special Attack Force of the battleship Yamato,
the light cruisers Yahagi, and 10 destroyers.
It was all that's left of the Combined Fleet that used to be
Japan's pride ever since Admiral Togo started the tradition.
Episode 24
The End of the Combined Fleet
Meanwhile, the US Marines approached Okinawa
on April 1st, at 4:06 a.m., exactly as planned.
Okinawa
East China Sea
The landing party, under Lt. General Buckner, commander of the Tenth Army (TAF), began disembarking.
Hey, it's eerily quiet down here.
You think the Japs are gone?
That's really strange. I thought their forte
was fighting on the beaches.
Garrison commander Lieutenant General Ushijima,
who opted for a defense in depth,
was patiently waiting for the US Army
to proceed southwards.
However,
this passive approach didn't sit well
with the Combined Fleet High Command.
So they decided to dispatch the 2nd Fleet, including Yamato,
that was standing by off the coast of Mitajiri.
On April 6th, a strategy meeting was held on board Yamato
to work out the upcoming sortie.
That day, the special attendants
in charge of maintaining the morale
were Chief of Staff Kusaka and Staff Officer Kami
from the Combined Fleet Headquarters.
As just explained by the Commander-in-Chief,
we will only load enough fuel for a one way trip.
I would now ask you to look
at the documents you've been handed.
Before we begin this strategy meeting,
I have a question.
Go ahead, Senior Staff Officer Yamamoto.
Thank you.
My question is, seeing how you've come here
all the way from the Combined Fleet Headquarters today,
would you explain to us their intentions?
Yes. Let's hear it out.
Yamamoto.
It's alright.
Naturally, I have no objections to the special attack itself,
but the ultimate objective of this order is unclear to me.
The order goes,
"destroy enemy ships near Okinawa."
There's your objective.
But sir, is that objective really achievable?
On the 8th, it'll already be a whole week
after the enemy has landed.
Considering the resourcefulness of their CBs,
they'll have the air base repaired by then
and will unleash the full force of their air fleet upon us.
Besides, we estimate that the enemy
has over 10 aircraft carriers in the area.
By setting our time and course right into the enemy's ambush, we'll just serve ourselves up on a silver plate.
Exactly.
Even if we wanted to lure the enemy our way with a decoy,
so as to prevent the troops from landing, the 8th day is too late!
Aren't headquarters just clutching at straws,
calling things such lofty names as "Special Attack Fleet"?
They definitely aren't!
Isn't it just a thought exercise from headquarters?
What?!
I have all I need to know.
Perhaps you're right, after all.
Ito, the proposal to use Yamato in this way also faced strong opposition within the Combined Fleet Headquarters.
With barely any fuel and no air support.
They can tout it as unsinkable all they want,
it's still a plan of desperation.
Well, even though you know that, I want you to understand the circumstances that made this plan our only option.
It has been a long time since we last drank together.
Okinawa is a crucial position. Losing it now
would mean the inevitable defeat of Japan in the war.
We'll lose even if 100 million
go out on a suicide attack at once.
The reasons for it are aplenty.
But I'm not here to talk about that.
Just think of it as a forerunner
to that 100 million suicide attack.
Also, the Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet Toyoda
said he wanted to let the flowers
of our precious Yamato bloom at least once.
Let her flowers bloom?
Do it.
Eh?
If we make it out, why don't we go get
Togakushi soba again one day?
I'd sure like to.
Come in.
Ah. Sir!
You don't mind me?
Of course not.
I'm at your service whenever you need me.
You sure cleaned it up nicely.
And this one has such a fine face.
With it, I feel at ease.
Are you still smoking these days?
Yes. No matter what I do. I can't go
without at least 100 a day.
That's way above the ration, I reckon.
I got this one from the enemy.
Thank you, sir.
Say, Yamamoto.
You probably see my decision to accept
this suicide assignment as erroneous?
No.
You don't need to be concerned about that.
I hear that your son
also volunteered to join the special attack.
That's true. But I came here to tell you
that there's one more agenda I'm pursuing.
Huh?
Certainly, we may get sunk on the way, just as you say.
But I want to lead us to the shores of Okinawa.
Floating or beached, I want to fire our battery
of the world's largest 46 cm cannons one more time.
That's what I thought too.
Let's make it there, whatever it takes.
Whatever it takes!
Yes!
In response to the HQ's thought exercise,
the 2nd Fleet made a secret decision before sortieing.
Vice Admiral Ito signaled to the armada his instructions,
worthy of a historical sortie
that would be remembered for years to come.
"A miraculous feat lies right ahead of us.
The prosperity of the motherland hinges on this one battle.
Let everyone fight hard, fight ferociously,
and reduce the enemy to nothing.
Show everyone that the Naval Special Attack Corps
is a force to be reckoned with."
By the time they exited the Bungo Channel,
Yamato was already shadowed by an enemy submarine.
Cape Toi
Kyushu
Mitajiri
Shikoku
This ill omen was a precursor
to the difficulties still ahead.
Around that time, the task force in charge of supporting the Okinawa landings under Admiral Spruance
came under attack from 400 Japanese kamikaze planes
that took off from Kanoya and other bases.
He was swamped with commanding and administrative work, so he was having a late dinner.
I apologize for interrupting your meal.
Never mind it. What did you want, Davis?
I've just completed this report.
They sure gave us a run for our money today.
Who knew the Japanese still have more of such pilots.
Yes. I was just as surprised.
So that's the promised gift
from Tokyo Rose, the kamikaze?
That time around, the damage from the kamikaze attack
was: 3 destroyers, 1 LST, and 2 ammunition ships sunk.
The light carrier San Jacinto, 15 destroyers,
and 4 minesweepers heavily damaged.
In the confusion,
the battleship North Carolina, the light cruiser Burnett, 2 transport ships, and one LST were damaged by friendly fire.
One more transport ship
was reportedly damaged in a collision.
That said, there's also some news that'll cheer you up.
Oh? What is it?
Your beloved one is coming.
Beloved one?
Yes. Yamato has finally left port,
as reported by the submarine Threadfin.
I see now. My beloved one indeed.
How should we welcome her? Signal a strategy meeting.
Is this all the reports on the Japanese fleet we have?
Yes, sir.
Very well. Then, we can draw
2 conclusions from from these reports.
First one is that Yamato is out of port.
The other one is that the enemy's surface fleet
has been reduced to a dozen of ships.
Yes, sir.
So tell me this, Davis.
We are now faced with one choice to make
and one predicament to solve.
The choice being "by what means
should we go about defeating Yamato?"
And the predicament being
determining Yamato's true destination.
I understand why you see Yamato's destination as a problem.
But what do you mean by "choosing the means to..."
Should we sink her with an overwhelming air attack,
like what happened with Musashi and Prince of Wales?
Or should we give her one more naval battle?
You mean a surface fleet engagement?
As this report states, the enemy is completely exposed,
without a single plane to cover them.
But in a surface fleet engagement, Yamato will have a chance to use their cannons, the largest in the world.
Still, that's what I'll do.
Eh?
Ever since the Prince of Wales
sank at the hands of an air attack,
it is unthinkable that you can conduct
a decisive naval battle without airplanes.
And yet, Admiral Spruance elected to settle it
with an old-fashioned decisive naval battle of surface fleets.
Who knows why he made such a decision?
Admiral Spruance's decision to dispatch a surface fleet
to engage Yamato in a decisive naval battle was transmitted
to the Gunfire and Covering force 54 under Rear Admiral Deyo and Fast Carrier Force 58 under Vice Admiral Mitscher.
That's ridiculous! The defining force
of modern naval warfare is aircraft carriers!
Isn't that right, Burke?
A surface engagement or not, our Air Fleet
is only delegated the auxiliary role of dealing light jabs?
The old man must be going senile.
Yes, sir.
The honor of defeating Yamato,
the embodiment of the Japanese naval spirit,
naturally belongs to carriers,
the embodiment of the American naval spirit!
It has to be our Task Force 58!
What's a good way to do it?
Sir, Admiral Spruance allowed us to make a jab.
Not an uppercut, for sure. But with enough speed,
even just one jab is enough to knock the opponent down.
That's the "31-knot" Burke I know!
Okay, got it. I'll let the admiral know.
Rear Admiral Deyo reports. It seems that everyone
is in high spirits and celebrating already.
They wanted to give you a thousand thanks.
I see, they're happy with it too?
Well, it's only natural.
Battleships should fight other battleships.
I know we should support the landing party, but their skills would blunt from shooting at land targets all the time.
It was 38 years ago.
When I just graduated from the Annapolis Naval Academy
I went to Japan with the Great White Fleet expedition.
There, I've met Admiral Togo himself.
And it was not just me. He was an object of admiration
for all of us naval officers.
We were also taught Togo's stratagems.
And we went to see Japanese sumo.
That's when... they're fighting naked?
Right. And when you defeat a mentor who taught you,
they call it returning the favor.
And then, the one defeated
should give his blessing to his trainee.
To think you know even such minutia...
That's exactly what I want to do now.
Return the favor to the Japanese fleets
that Togo brought up.
With no way of knowing that Admiral Spruance made
that kind of decision and was now preparing to meet her,
Yamato proceeded on her peaceful voyage.
The clouds are thick today.
If this keeps up, the enemy
will have a hard time attacking us.
Enemy aircraft!
General quarters! All hands!
Prepare for anti-aircraft warfare!
Contact! 31 degrees 22 minutes north latitude,
129 degrees 14 minutes east longitude!
Yamato-class battleship - 1 or 2, 8 destroyers.
Course 300, speed 12 knots!
A full-scale air raid is coming now.
With their course of 300...
Where is Yamato going, really?
Doesn't seem to be Okinawa.
Maybe Sasebo?
We can't let her escape!
Is there a way to chase her?
Well... Our planes can probably catch up with her.
The rest of the battlefleet, though...
Impossible, then?
Sir.
Vice Admiral Mitscher on the line.
Thank you.
Hello, Mark?
Hello, Ray.
Doing it with a surface fleet, after all?
Mark, of course we will.
Really? The enemy seems to be heading to Sasebo.
Can you catch up with them?
What do I say? Can we catch up?
Hard to tell...
At that time, an internal conflict
was tearing Spruance apart.
But someone had to make this decision.
If they miss their chance now,
would they come across Yamato ever again?
But at the same time, it pained him to let Yamato
fall prey to aviation.
Hello? Hello! Ray, are you there?
Please let me sink the world's biggest battleship!
Fine. Do it!
Okay!
What should we say to Deyo?
Nothing. Let them proceed as is.
Even a fella as aggressive as Mark
can't do it in this weather.
The clouds are low and the visibility is just 5 or 6 miles.
This incapacitates their planes. They can't dive safely.
All combat-ready aircraft
of TF 58.1, 58.3, and 58.4 take off immediately!
Time is 9:40 a.m.
If you take off by 10,
you'll make it there for the enemy's lunch.
But you'll come with some gifts.
You're uninvited guests, after all.
And then, don't come back
until Yamato hits the seabed!
I'll say it once again.
Don't come back until Yamato is on the seabed!
Incited by "31-knot" Burke's inflammatory speech,
280 aircraft took flight.
Just as Admiral Spruance noted,
that attack was anything but easy.
Some later compared it to swimming in pottage.
Enemy contact! Larger formation than before!
Enemy planes approaching!
General quarters!
335 degrees!
Next target: 250, 85 degrees!
Fire!
So I guess we won't get to become the Okinawan shore battery.
Yes. We failed to keep our mission secret.
You haven't smoked at all today.
I decided to abstain until we become a shore battery.
Just as I thought.
You didn't want to jinx it?
April 7th, 2:23 p.m.
30 degrees 20 minutes north latitude,
128 degrees 4 minutes east longitude.
200 nautical miles north
of Tokunoshima Island in Kyushu region,
in the East China Sea, at the depth of 480 meters,
Yamato found her final resting place.
Thus, the Japanese Combined Fleet, proud of its glorious traditions, dating back to Admiral Togo himself,
Yamato
Yahagi
Isokaze
Asashimo
Kasumi
Hamakaze
has well and truly found its end here.
The Japanese Navy doctrine of heavy ships and big guns
was mercilessly swallowed up in the whirlpool of history.
But at the same time, we can reflect upon
the horrible consequences of such a reactionary approach.
As well as upon the decisions taken by the Americans
and their firm determination to act upon it afterwards,
without which any decision making is ultimately pointless.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled numerous lessons on how to live.
Morning of July 27, 1945.
A joint declaration from the US, UK, and China -
the Potsdam Declaration was radioed to Japan last night.
And to add to her miseries,
an atomic bomb is dropped.
Would we accept the Potsdam Declaration,
or defend the mainland to the last?
Witness the hardships and decisions of the intelligence bureau chief Shimomura from Suzuki Kantaro's cabinet
in the next Decision:
The Final Decision.
Episode 25
The Final Decision
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Editing, OCR & timings assistance
Translation
Quality Checking
Supplementary materials by
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Perevodildo
Ziusudra
History Asian
Moozzi2