Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Only Honmaru gets to do that - unfair!
I want to go to school and study with everyone, too!
Not happening! The school will make a big fuss
if someone finds out you're a magician.
Don't get any wrong ideas
just because my dad and mom are an exception.
See you!
I go to school, too!
Want to become old and scary?
Honmaru is Scrooge!
Whaddya just say?
Got a problem with me?
Stop it, Taru!
Trunsform!
I swallowed Taru!
This way, can go to school
toge-ge-gether with Honmaru!
He's babbling from inside my belly!
Honmaru can't stop me,
I'm going to school!
Episode 5
Preparing for the Test with Magic
Listen here, Taru.
Our teacher is actually a mighty dreadful one.
You should be quiet as a mouse!
Got it!
Just-in-time safe!
Good morning, Edojo Honmaru-kun.
Hi! Looking supero-pero!
Come on, Taru!
I asked you to shut it!
Honmaru-kun!
Yes!
You're a 5th grader already.
Yet still ignorant of what a proper greeting sounds like.
Start over, earnestly this time!
Teacher! Good morning!
That's better.
If you don't hurry,
the class will start without you.
Excuse me then!
Stand!
Bow!
Good morning!
Sit!
Everyone...
Would the person in charge of classroom cleaning
like to hear some feedback?
Yes...
How many times do I have to tell you?
Treat your classroom duties seriously!
I'm so sorry, teacher!
When you're the one in charge,
compromises are unacceptable!
Yes...
Very well. Return to your seat.
See? That's what I told you about,
our teacher is dreadful.
I'm in school!
Taru! For the last time, be quiet, please!
Honmaru!
Wi-thout-a-so-und!
That was when Regent Shotoku came into play.
School boring.
Right, go see what Iyona is up to.
Taru! You promised me to keep quiet, remember?
I am in boredom,
figured to peek out just a bit.
You risk getting spotted,
so stay hidden for now.
Scrooge! Scrooge!
Will use these then.
~Sneak Peek!~
Iyona looked this way.
And smiled!
Iyona-chan...
Taru, how did you see it?
If you wear these H-Filtering Magical Goggles
and cast a spell of ~Sneak Peek~
it allows you to see through many things.
Can see through more layers
by number of times you say the spell.
Can I borrow them, too?
School boring.
I'll make myself friends to play with.
Taruru.
Hey! What are you trying to do, Taru?
Let's play together, people!
Yo! How about a round of sumo?
I'm in, I'm in!
Okay...
Hey... Can't you keep it down?
If you make that much noise,
everyone is going to notice!
Can't you just be quiet...
Good, good! That's the way!
Don't give up, Taru!
Smashed him!
Taruruuto's victory!
You showed him, Taruruuto!
You seem to be having lots of fun, Honmaru-kun.
I'm screwed...
Is my class really that entertaining?
Yes. Even more than that!
Don't try to talk your way out.
'Kay.
All of your enthusiasm during the class
should be devoted to listening to the teacher.
Is that clear?
Yes!
Free supplies of the box, enemy's back exposed!
Counterattack time!
The hell you did this for, Taruruuto?
Seriously? You can't just play possum like that!
That's cowardly, Taru!
Honmaru-kun.
Yes?
Playing with a doll during the class, talking back
to the teacher, and now also throwing supplies around?
No... I'd never...
do that...
You must be a degenerate
to be still playing with dolls at your age!
If you want to be punished that badly,
I'm taking this doll as a fine.
Cute.
Taru is finally keeping it quiet?
That's right!
I can check how he's doing with Magical Goggles.
And the spell was something...
~Sneak Peek!~
I can see right through!
I see. So that's why he was calling them
H-Filtering goggles!
But boy do I tell you, Taruruuto sure is making himself comfortable, sleeping in a place like that.
Mama.
Taru-chan?
Mama! Mama...
Yes, yes.
Must be hungry, are you, Taru-chan?
Want some of my milk?
Could it be that Taruruuto
just flustered her somehow?
Alright... ~Sneak Peek!~
Teacher, is there something wrong?
Are you not feeling well enough?
Nothing of the kind...
I'm perfectly fine.
I can't believe Taru got so carried away,
he mistook it for mama's breast!
He's still a baby, after all.
Wait a minute...
If I can look through teacher's clothes all I want...
Teacher, are you sure you don't need any help?
Don't do it, Iyona-chan!
Turn away!
Honmaru-kun, anything wrong?
Honmaru-kun! What's the matter? Hang on!
The hell? He fainted while looking so strangely delighted?
Ominous, even.
This is the face of someone
with unambiguously lewd thoughts.
What halfwit would do that during the class?
Silence!
Can't we have any silence at all?
Everyone seems to have grown audacious enough
to run about clamorously during the class.
Tomorrow's arithmetic test
should take you down a peg!
If there's even a single student scoring less than 30 points,
the whole class owes me 30 bunny-hops at the schoolyard.
And then, I'll also have everyone
do 100 push-ups extra.
Got it?
That's just impossible...
What you gonna do about it?
Things deteriorated into this because of you.
Thanks a lot!
You keep saying that all the time.
And you keep scoring zero on every single test!
The whole class is jeopardized!
You realize that, Honmaru?
Whaddya say?
Do you really think I will score zero again?!
Wha...
What's the deal with all those cold gazes?
You know I'm not the kind to try to pass,
ticking at random!
What do I do now?
I'm the least confident towards tomorrow's test!
At this rate, everyone will want me
beaten to a pulp!
How do I bail myself out?
Bail out to a pulp!
I swear, Taru!
Speaking of, Taru still has this one very useful magic!
Say, Taruruuto, don't you wanna go hang out
at the teacher's house?
Want!
Our teacher to my liking!
But you know, she is called "Dreadful Teacher" for a reason.
Chances are, she's not particularly hot about letting us in...
Don't you think we could use
Taru's Time-Freezing Magic again?
We could, could!
With it on our side, there's nothing easier
than getting into the teacher's house!
Honmaru, I like! Wonderful plan!
Let's go, let's go!
You want is so bad?
Well, I guess we don't have a choice!
Oaya Mari
Honmachi, house 3-8. It's here!
We've found it at last,
the teacher's house!
And now, the rest is up to my sensei,
the Great Magician!
Time is 3:45.
On my belly, too.
Alright. Seems good so far.
We're going in, Taru!
I'm so sorry, teacher!
It was Taru who instigated me
to peek into the test answers with magic!
I yielded against my better judgment!
Honmaru!
Here-here-here-here!
Oh, my bad, the time is frozen, alright.
You cheeky one.
Didn't have to make such an intimidating face.
Scared the daylights out of me.
Honmaru...
It's a welcoming face!
This is the best one yet!
Surprised!
We don't have time for this tomfoolery.
Taru's magic wears out in just 10 minutes.
I gotta find the test answers soon!
Seems fun, Honmaru.
I can do this too.
There it is!
Bra-up!
Bra-ra-rup!
What are you doing, Taru?
Honmaru is playing fun games! I can too!
What does it have to do with me?
Clean up this mess at once!
Honmaru want to play with me, too!
Can't I trust you to not make a fuss
even at a moment this important, Taru?
Our 10 minutes will expire any moment now! Look.
Well, what do you know,
we still have about 10 minutes left.
Honmaru, less hurry, more play!
Alright...
Since there's still time,
might as well play a little prank on teacher's face!
A mustache, maybe?
Me too, me too!
Alright...
Oh my, Honmaru-kun...
But the time is not out yet...
The clock hand only moved now!
I get it.
When I stopped the time,
I guess I stopped your watch as well.
10 minutes ran out already?!
Hold it right there!
Honmaru-kun.
You shouldn't be that impatient.
You came for some intense preparation
for tomorrow's test, didn't you?
And I was so engrossed in my training,
I didn't even notice when you showed up.
Ah...
Terribly sorry!
My place is in such a mess.
How odd.
I clearly remember putting those in the drawer.
Me help!
And you are...
Me Taruruuto!
Honmaru's friend.
Where could I have seen you before?
Now, let's start studying, shall we?
Yes...
Do your best, Honmaru.
I believe in you!
I don't understand...
Really? But that's exactly what I taught you in the classroom
the other day, Honmaru-kun.
Maybe you did, but...
You're not trying hard enough!
Got it.
Here, shouldn't signs be inverted?
Like this?
That's right. And the next operation is...
Also right.
You can do anything if you try.
Can you believe it?
Arithmetic is much easier than one would have thought.
That's the spirit.
Make sure to keep it up till the end. Here.
Don't startle me like that, Taru.
Honmaru, do your best...
Easy for you to say,
you don't have to cram anything.
It's that late already?!
A curry!
You must have worked up
quite the appetite by now.
I called your home,
so your late return is excused.
Hooray!
Smells good!
Looks delicious!
Something on my face?
No...
It may not look like it,
but cooking is actually another one of my passions.
Delicious. Delicious, Honmaru.
Come on, get to eating! Eating!
Okay!
So? You like it?
I really do!
It's delightful!
If Honmaru doesn't want, I'll have it.
I haven't eaten even a spoonful yet!
Now, now. There are still plenty of refills.
No need to fight over it.
Now, may I have your plate?
Sure thing! Refill!
Me refill too! Here, here!
Sure, sure.
Thanks for the delicious meal!
...meal.
Teacher's curry the best!
I would have never thought this teacher of ours
is so good with cooking!
This teacher and one in school
are totally different teachers.
I love a kind teacher like that!
A kind one...
Here, shouldn't signs be inverted?
Like this?
That's right. And the next one...
Like that?
Also correct.
Nothing is impossible if you try.
What happened, Honmaru?
Alright, I'll study even more at home.
Good luck to you, Honmaru!
I believe in you!
Don't disturb me now, Taru.
By dint of my own studying, I will overcome the test,
without resorting to cheating!
Come on, let's do our best!
Jaba Jabao-kun.
Here.
31 point.
Harako Tsutomu-kun.
Yes, ma'am!
99 points.
Honmaru, don't panic.
Honmaru! The "true-or-false" section
was my only hope, and I passed!
Ijigawa Rui-san.
Yes!
82 points.
OH MY GOD!
I, the Great
have let slip such a substantial mistake!
No doubt, the first and the last ever,
earth-shattering, worst ever test score of my life!
This Harako again,
ain't he being too full of himself?
What a prick.
Hey, Honmaru!
The only remaining problem is you!
Alright, if it's less than 30 points,
we're all doing our bunny-hops on top of you!
Shut it, already!
We'll talk when we finally hear the score!
I'm going to enjoy it, Honmaru.
If it's under, you're going under, too!
Edojo Honmaru-kun.
Yes!
32 points.
Did it!
What do you say now?
Can you even comprehend my might?
Can. You. Comprehend. Might?
Splendid, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan!
A guy breaks into tears over scoring 32 points...
Fabulous, isn't it?
The ultimate manifestation of my talent!
Banzai! Banzai!
Damn! Losing even to Honmaru,
what a miserable crappin' life!
Unfair!
Hey! This is a big deal, Taruruuto!
As a reward for rubbing his shoulders,
dad gave me a treasure map!
If we find this treasure,
we'll be dirty rich!
I can eat all the takoyaki!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
The Great Quest for Treasure!
Don't miss, fru-ru-riends!
Episode 6
The Great Quest for Treasure!!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume