Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Get over here!
Wait, Taru!
Run!
Taru!
Yay!
Hey, Taru! Dad is taking a nap! It's dangerous!
Honmaru's papa play with us too!
Hey Taru! Have you forgotten?
You don't wanna bother dad
when he dozes off during work!
Don't you know all hell
will break loose if he wakes up?
Ah? This isn't a picture book manuscript.
Dad writes for grownups too, huh?
Episode 74
Ria's Love Story
Once upon a time, in a faraway land...
There lived an honest man named Gosuke-don.
Ouch.
Gosuke-don was ever so slightly obtuse.
But he was an honest hardworking man.
Gosuke-don!
Gosuke-don's friend, Jaba-don,
had just found himself a wife.
What is it?
Wanna go home?
That's right.
I sure want meself a wife too...
Thank ye very much for today's bread.
The sunset is the most beautiful today! So bright!
Gosuke! Gosuke! Gosuke!
Ah, Headman.
The sunset is beautiful!
Look, it's bright red! Looks so nice!
Right?
You cretin! It's bright red
because my storehouse is on fire!
Instead of loitering there, come quickly, Gosuke!
Gosuke! Save the heirloom that's been passed down in my family from inside that burning storehouse!
You can't be serious, Headman!
Gosuke will burn to death for sure!
Silence! If this keeps up,
my valuable heirloom will turn to ashes!
A man as obtuse as Gosuke
will definitely make it out alright!
I understand. Well, here I go.
Gosuke! Don't go!
Stop it!
Ha! That man is always so dumb.
Alright! Now just come out with it!
Ah! I forgot...
Heirloom, heirloom...
What's a heirloom?
Gosuke-don had never heard this word before.
Gosuke!
It's burning down!
Oh! Gosuke!
And he's carrying something!
Thank you, Gosuke! You've brought the hanging scroll,
which is my heirloom, right?
Yes, Headman!
Thank God! Gosuke, hurry up, show it to us!
Okay.
Hair!
Gloom!
Cretin, cretin, cretin, cretin, cretin!
I was an idiot for asking you!
Ah! The storehouse! It's burned
down completely! The damage is irreparable!
Because of this, this year's land tax will be twice the usual!
We can't sustain that!
Gosuke! It's your fault!
You're playing dirty, Headman!
Shut up!
Um, Headman, what do I do with this heirloom now?
Do whatever with it, just get out of my sight!
Thank you very much.
Ah! Gosuke! Hang on!
Hot... Hot...
He was a rather obtuse man.
I don't know how to read,
so even if I have a book, I can't understand a thing.
This looks like an interesting sign.
Still, if the land tax is doubled this year...
What do I do about this?
Gosuke-don was unable to think any further than that.
And yet, he thought...
Until he fell asleep on the spot.
I'm a bit screwed.
Before you, the Great Magician...
Ria Kinakamo!
Hey, hey! Pops. Pops, hello!
Jeez...
Gramps!!
Awake now?
Yes. Who might you be?
Alright. Let's start over, with passion.
Before you, the Great Magician... Ria Kinakamo!
Earlier, you summoned me
with the "I'm a bit screwed" spell.
I'll make your one wish come true.
Ask for anything.
He's so surprised, his eyes turned into dots.
Gosuke wasn't surprised.
He simply had dotty eyes.
Um...
Yes?
You see, I want a wife.
A wife...
Ah, you mean a spouse?
Okay, Yahook up with me-kun should help.
What is this?
You use this arrow to pierce a woman's heart,
to make that woman fall in love with you.
Then, you marry her
without waiting another moment, okay?
I've never shot an arrow before.
Well, aren't you helpless.
You draw a bow like this,
and aim it at the heart of the woman you love.
Release your right hand to let the arrow loose.
The hut of the woman?
And what if that woman
doesn't live in a hut?
Oh, you're really not making it easy for me!
The heart is the organ inside you.
It's located in the chest, around here.
You aim to here, like this.
See? Here.
I'm hungry.
What's going on?
My chest suddenly feels so dense.
What is this pleasant warmth
spreading through my chest?
From just looking at this man's face,
my heart is pounding...
Are you okay?
This well-proportioned square head...
The round and cute eyes...
The more you look at it,
the more appealing his big face becomes.
Um...
His slowly moving mouth...
His peaceful and carefree composure...
Ah! How come I never noticed
that a man so wonderful was right here...!
I love you.
Jaba-don!
Please meet my wife too.
I'm Ria. Nice to meet you.
What a beauty!
How'd you do it, Gosuke?
I can't take my eyes off her!
E-he.
Don't give me that "E-he"!
How could a man like you find himself
a wife that gorgeous! Answer me!
Don't hurt my Gosuke-san!
You don't deserve to be any closer
than several miles from him!
My Dear!
Jaba-don!
Ria, save Jaba-don.
But he was bothering you...
Jaba-don is a dear friend of mine.
Ria...
What a forgiving man...
He wants me to save Jaba-don,
who just strangled him mere moments ago.
Gosuke-san... No, Gosuke-sama!
I just fell in love with you once again.
Sure!
Jaba-don!
Honey!
Ah, my Okio-chan!
We're sorry, Jaba-don.
Please forgive us for this misstep.
Jaba-don-san, forgive me!
My heart was so selfish before.
But with his warmth,
bit by bit, he made me open up to the world.
Gosuke-san,
I am happy.
I offer my gratitude to the heavens,
for the chance to live with you...
I love you, Gosuke-sama.
What did you say?!
Gosuke found himself a beautiful wife?!
Yes. Precisely so.
Nah, that's some steaming nonsense!
Anyone but Gosuke...!
Be careful.
Yes, Gosuke-sama.
Beautiful!
What did I tell you, Headman?
That damned Gosuke, finding himself
a dazzling lady... Unacceptable!
Hey, Gosuke!
Ah, Headman!
Honored to meet you, Headman.
I am Ria, the wife of Gosuke-sama.
I must greet them appropriately,
lest I bring shame upon Gosuke-sama.
Nice to meet...
So bouncy...
So pretty! Gosuke receiving her as a wife
is a terrible waste! Impossible beauty!
Gosuke, remember how you failed to carry my heirloom
out of my burning storehouse the other day?
Yes.
As a punishment, your land tax is 30 times the usual this year! And you're to bring it to me by tomorrow!
30 times the usual?
You can't even understand!
That's cause you've never seen so much in your life!
It'll be 180 bushels of rice by tomorrow!
There's no way you can gather that much!
However, being compassionate as I am,
in lieu of rice bushels,
I'll accept your wife as payment!
Then, I'll forgive your land tax fully!
Are you kidding me?!
Jeez, you're annoying!
Have you ever tried to think before talking?
Taking advantage of Gosuke-sama's good nature...
Ria...
Gosuke-sama...
Don't give me that look.
It can sadden even me...
That's right, I shouldn't lose my temper, right?
I shouldn't fight others.
I must pacify my heart...
You pest! Gosuke, are you
giving your wife any discipline at all?!
We apologize.
"First of all, apologize calmly," right...
I'm sorry, Headman-chan.
Eh?
Headman-chan?
It was because Headman-chan yanked
my hand so suddenly, that my hand accidentally slipped.
But dear, I'm not going to become yours.
Why's that?!
Well, because it's clear as a day that Gosuke-sama
will collect 180 bushels, 30 times his land tax by tomorrow.
Are you not right in the head?!
There's no way in hell
someone as clumsy as him can do it!
And what'll you do if he does?
Gosuke-sama's so humble that
he doesn't stand out particularly.
But really, he's a wonderful person.
He's nothing like you, who let the village headmanship go to his head.
What? Are you saying that if it wasn't for the headmanship, I'd be inferior to Gosuke?
Isn't that obvious?
That's exactly why
I'm so enchanted by Gosuke-sama!
Alright, I get it!
Supposing Gosuke is as great as you say
and he manages to collect 180 bushels by tomorrow,
I'll let that dunce replace me as the village headman!
Thank you very much
for making Gosuke-sama the next village headman.
However! If he fails to collect it,
you'll be mine, you hear?!
Is that clear?!
Yes.
You're the witnesses, got it?
Yes!
Everyone, please remember
what you just heard, will you?
Okay!
What can they ever pull off with just one person?
This unearthly beauty is already mine!
Gosuke, have you really made such a reckless promise,
even though the rice has already been harvested?
Tonight will be the last night
you two will spend together, then?
You poor fellow.
Tonight is our last night...
Huh?
Ria, be happy...
What are you saying now?
That's so depressing.
Now then, why don't we do some work?
What are we going to do so late at night?
The light of compassion that nurtures life,
please bestow a piece of the sun's blessing upon us!
Ria!
Okay! I'm counting on you, everyone.
Okay!
Raincloud Taro!
Gotcha!
Do your best!
You can do it!
Right, keep it up!
You... Can...
Your... Best...
Amazing!
But it's still not nearly enough.
Don't you worry.
I'll just use the Growth Spray
Exponential Growth Formula.
Double!
Wow! It's just like magic!
Well, I'm a magician, after all.
That was the first thing I said...
You can't...
You can't be serious!
I'm just seeing some dream...
A nightmare right now! That's it!
It's real rice!
Headman, you gotta keep your promise.
Rice? Rice...
We're all witnesses, remember?
What'll you do?
This can't be... This can't... Ah, rice...
After that, Gosuke-don, now the village headman,
lived happily ever after with Ria.
That's what you'd think,
but Ria's magic only lasts ten days.
Huh?
I see...
I fell in love with this man
because of Yahook up with me-kun.
Well, I've got bad news for you.
Unfortunately, I can't marry you.
As promised, I made your one wish come true.
But with this, my work here is done.
I gotta return to the Magic Realm soon.
See you.
Gosuke-don couldn't understand what was going on.
As usual, his eyes were like two dots.
What's wrong with me?
The magic of love had been dispelled...
And yet, I can't stop crying.
Ria...
No! I have to return home now.
Turn back the clock to return to the place where we met
Don't worry.
Once I return to the Magic Realm,
I will completely disappear from your memory.
So we could start over once again
I know for a fact that you can find yourself a wonderful wife.
That's what I want...
I'll be praying for that too.
Your eyes...
Gosuke-sama...
Because I need to forget them,
Thank you.
And goodbye!
Good day, nice to meet you-yu-yu!
Even though I was the one who said goodbye...
From the bottom of my heart,
Ria...
I'm screaming in pain
After that, Gosuke had apparently married
a beautiful and kind woman.
I don't want to leave the warmth in my heart
And then...
Village headman, I beg you!
Please subsidize my land tax this year!
I see you in the city...
Okay.
Thank you very much!
I see myself in the rain...
Subsequently, Gosuke's personality
won him the trust of the villagers.
Eventually, I'm cooling down in time
And as the Great Headman,
he lived with the villagers happily ever after.
Turn back the clock to return to the place where we met
So we could start from the beginning over once again
That's what I want...
Honmaru! My Cook-san is amazing!
Well done, Taru!
With that cute Cook-san on our side,
we've nothing to fear from Harako's cooking!
Take one straight stick...
Is it a leaf?
It's not a leaf...
It's a frog now!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Episode 75
Taruru! Cook-san
Taruru! Cook-san.
So delicious!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius