Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Let's hurry up to the park to play, Taru!
Yeah!
Are you taking my screen time?!
Look where you're running!
What?
Watch it, watch it!
Nannosho's Gang Leader is back! Make way!
Now, please proceed, Leader!
Watch it, watch it!
Damn this prick Zakenja...
Acting so full of himself just 'cause he knows some kenpo.
So full-full-full of himself!
Before he riles me up even more,
let's hurry up and go play some.
Play some, play some!
Episode 56
Honmaru, a Tearful Decision!
Nannosho Children's Park
Well, we sure played quite some!
That was very refreshing.
Honmaru, belly hungry, let's go home soon.
Sure. Mom is probably already
waiting for us with dinner ready.
Iyona-chan!
Iyona was playing around too?
No. I'm returning from cram school.
Ah! Me too!
Even this late, you've been there?
Well, that's only natural.
If I don't study hard and get into a good school,
ain't no way I'll find myself a good man, right?
It may be dangerous, so I'll walk you home.
Would you really?
It's a feint to suddenly bring you to a deserted place
and force a kiss... Don't come close, Honmaru!
But I mean, man... Iyona-chan is so cute,
she's actually at risk of being targeted by some weirdos.
And me? Me?
Honmaru, Honmaru! Hungry, hungry.
Can't be helped, then.
Taru, you go home first.
Okay! Hungry going first!
Dinner! Dinner!
Is it alright to send Taru-chan home by himself?
It's okay. Taru is also a boy
and our house is just a hop, skip and jump away.
This is a shortcut, Iyona-chan.
I did it!
Now it's just the two of us - me and Iyona-chan!
Moreover, we've taken a route through this deserted park...
Evening dates are the best ever!
Honmaru-kun, I'm scared.
You'll be alright.
I'm here for you.
Honmaru-kun!
Just like that!
Honmaru-kun, I'm scared.
Honmaru-kun...
Ijigawa! Since when have you been here?!
From the very beginning, you dimwit!
Thanks for going to the trouble
of bringing us some cute gals.
What the hell do you guys want?!
Don't try to act cool.
I'm just telling the girls
we too would like to get along.
These guys are drunk as hell!
Hey there, ladies. How about a date with us?
Honmaru-kun!
Don't you touch Iyona-chan!
About time you got lost already!
Honmaru-kun!
Stay with us for a bit, will you?
Please stop it!
Let go!
Stop!
Shut it! If you got a problem, I'll hear you out anytime.
And this!
Hey-hey, what's the matter?
Shit... If only Taru was here,
he'd think of something with his magic...
Somebody! Help!
Wait.
What?
Did you lay your hands on the students of Nannosho
on my territory?
You're not getting away with it.
Zakenja?
What? These are elementary graders?
See, brats, since you're grade schoolers, maybe you should
have been at home licking on candies in peace and quiet.
You're the ones who had better be quiet!
Just some posers who are all bark and no bite.
Ah! Zakenja-kun, you're so dreamy!
Thank you.
I don't need no gratitude.
That was so cool!
Your timely appearance saved two beauties from unspeakable harm! What a spectacle... Right, Iyona-chan?
So Zakenja-kun is actually a good person, right?
A good person?
I'm the Nannosho Gang Leader.
I'm just making sure the bastards from the other schools
don't lay a hand on Nannosho's students.
That humility is also so captivating!
Leader-sama, may you walk me home
just in case someone else tries to lay a hand on me?
I'm on my way home myself. I don't mind.
You'd also walk Iyona-chan home, wouldn't you?
Wait!
Honmaru-kun?
Zakenja is dangerous.
His actions are too unpredictable.
So far, letting you walk us home was by far more dangerous.
You're so weak you can't protect anyone!
What did you say?
What a bunch of nonsense.
Ah! Wait a minute, please. Zakenja-kun!
Hey, Leader!
Ijigawa, you idiot...
Are you okay?
Currying favor with Zakenja...
That unfathomable asshole!
Honmaru-kun, you shouldn't
speak so badly about Zakenja-kun.
Why so?!
You're supposed to know
better than anyone else what a thug he is!
This Zakenja is the most despicable type of cretin!
But if Zakenja-kun didn't come,
what would've become of us?
He merely showed up to flaunt his strength as always!
What's with all the cockiness?
If only I had Taru here with me, I'd show these thugs...
You'll go as far as blaming Taru-chan
for your failure, Honmaru-kun?
No, that's not what I meant.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan, hurry up!
If you don't hurry, Zakenja-kun will leave!
Goodbye, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan!
Honey, isn't Honmaru late?
Yes...
Honmaru? What's the matter?
If you don't come soon,
the side dishes will get cold.
I'm really pathetic.
I can't even protect the girl I like...
Why did I offer to walk her home?
In the end, we just had to rely on Zakenja Nezo to save us!
Compared to him, what I did
was just self-righteous lip service.
It's only natural that even Iyona-chan decided to forsake me!
I'm just so pathetic...
Why am I so pathetic?
Without Taru around, I'm completely helpless.
I lost...
I lost entirely to Zakenja Nezo!
Honmaru, what happened?
Dad...
I want to be strong.
I won't stop at anything,
so please give me special training! Please!
Dad!
I understand.
I heard you, so go eat your dinner now.
Dad...
Yay! Special training, special training!
Alright. Today we're going to the mountain
to practice in seclusion.
Let's go, Honmaru!
Okay, dad!
I'll call your teacher just in case.
Be careful, Honmaru.
Yay! Practice, practice!
Me go to mountain too!
Taru?
I want to try my own strength,
following in dad's footsteps as far as I can.
Without relying on magic.
Honmaru don't need my magic?
See ya.
Honmaru...
Honmaru don't need my magic!
Don't need me!
Idiot!
Even if we're far apart,
we're still friends, remember? Don't cry, Taru.
Okay! We're friends so it stands!
A month or so later,
I'll definitely come back stronger.
It's a promise.
Until then, please wait quietly at home.
Me promise too.
I won't say goodbye, Taru.
Come back soon, okay?
Honmaru!
Let me tell you, Zakenja-kun really is so cool!
Compared to that, Honmaru
is just pathetic, right, Iyona-chan?
The boys in our class are all
good-for-nothing wimps, how sad!
Don't lump us in the same bucket as Honmaru!
What a gutless wreck.
Be there even 100 or 200 delinquents,
none shall lay a finger on Iyona-san on my watch.
No help from Zakenja needed whatsoever.
Which reminds me, what happened to Honmaru today?
Honmaru went to mountains to train with papa.
Eh? Honmaru-kun did?
What's that training bullshit?
I bet it's because that Honmaru would rather run away
than live in the shadow of Zakenja!
Honmaru didn't run away!
Taru-chan!
Oh?
Ugh! You talk big, as if you're any better!
Jabao! Ever since you've been dethroned
as a gang leader, you've been laying pretty low!
What did you say, Ijigawa?!
Oh no! Zakenja-kun, please help! Jabao is at it again...
Let's keep jokes as jokes, Ijigawa.
Honmaru didn't run away! Didn't run...
Honmaru-kun, it was my fault.
Honmaru-kun was just trying desperately to save us.
Stop it!
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
However,
all I did was...
Honmaru will come back a month later
when he becomes strong.
Honmaru promised. Cheer up, Iyona.
The one suffering the most
from Honmaru's departure is Taru-chan...
Even when me and Honmaru are apart, we're friends.
So I don't feel sad. Don't cry, Iyona.
Thank you, Taru-chan.
Honmaru-kun...
I believe, ru-ru-ru
Honmaru's big sparkling star...
Is behind the cloud, mama's cloud
So cold! Will this really help me become stronger, dad?
I miss you
I love you, yu-yu-yu
Honmaru's big sparkling star...
But sometimes, failures too
Dad!
Why don't you just climb back up, Honmaru?
Iyona...
Happen to him, and that makes me a little sad
Want you forever by my side
Honmaru, we're friends. Friends.
Want you forever by my side...
Nannosho. It's here.
Yay! Iyona, come to the classroom!
Taruruuto! The teacher will scold you
for running in the hallway!
Show more respect, Harako.
You're talking to Zakenja-sama!
Why do I have to greet your sorry ass every damn morning?
Don't you care about whatever happens
to your daddy's company?
How cowardly! Brandishing the power of your daddy,
the head of Zakenja Concern!
This world only respects power. And I'll use
whatever power I have available. Wouldn't you do the same?
Come on, come on! You guys don't just ogle idly!
Express your greeting to Zakenja-sama!
Okay! Me express greeting! Zakenja, sup!
Hey! You don't greet Zakenja-sama with "Sup!"
Sup won't do? Then,
I wish you a good morning, rub-rub.
Are you looking down on me?!
Me licking down on you.
Taru...
Taru-chan!
I ain't kidding around!
Stop!
Violence is the worst way to go, Zakenja-kun.
Hey, what's going on here?
Ah, Oaya-sensei!
Who are those two?
It's been a while.
Zakenja-sama.
You guys are late.
It's been a while!
What?! How do you know these two
whom I specifically summoned from China?
How do I know?
Rui, how do I know?
Taru, do you really know those guys?
I don't.
I see. Taru doesn't really know them,
but just said "It's been a while," parroting him!
And then Zakenja blew a fuse from misunderstanding that!
You jerks are making fun of me.
You're not getting away with it!
Stop the fighting right now!
I see what you're up to!
I understand.
Wouldn't a match instead of a fight content you?
Yes... I think I said this before.
Alright! Let's hold a martial arts tournament
between the Classes 5-1 and 5-2.
A martial arts tournament?
It's when you fight with your bare hands.
Interesting! Yay!
We'll hold the matches in a three-on-three format.
The winner gets to enslave the loser.
Do you agree?!
Alright! I accept it!
Harako Tsutomu will crush Class 5-2 and you in particular!
Okay, it's settled.
The representative of Class 5-2 is Kaze Kumagoro.
I've transferred to Class 5-2 today.
The name's Kaze.
From now on, I'm an elementary student.
Next is Asuka Ryu.
Same, except the name's Asuka.
Nice to meet you.
Finally,
That'd be me, Zakenja Nezo!
Alright!
From Class 5-1, the Whole World's Junior-ish
Martial Arts Champion Harako Tsutomu!
As well as...
Now it's not just Zakenja.
Those two are no mountain yokels either.
In a fight against any of them,
you can die multiple times over! Shit...
Isn't there anyone else?
Me fight too! I join the tournament. I join!
Taru-chan, don't say nonsense!
Who would be the remaining one?
Honmaru will fight too!
But isn't Honmaru...
I heard that wimp ran away with his tail between his legs.
You've gotta be kidding, little one.
Honmaru not ran away!
Honmaru will be back in a month, stronger!
He promised to me!
That's right.
Honmaru-kun is no wimp.
I'm sure he'll keep his promise.
Very well.
I can wait for a month.
We'll hold a martial arts tournament in a month.
However, with or without Honmaru,
it will come to the same thing.
Your class is getting drowned in a sea of ​​blood,
and you will become my slaves.
Yay! Me fight! Everyone, root for me!
But Taru-chan...
Don't worry about anything, Iyona-san.
One way or another,
I'll have to take out all three of them by myself.
All according to plan.
I'll beat up those who defied me
in front of the whole school.
I'll demonstrate my power to everyone.
For that purpose,
I even summoned those two from China.
Stand up! If you want to be strong, stand up right now!
Honmaru!
Taru...
I'll keep my promise to you.
You'll see!
Honmaru, please come home soon!
Harako is already on his last legs.
He can barely stand.
I can't bear to see it!
Everyone, please wait for me.
In this mountain retreat,
I found something that convinced me!
Hey, Nezo!
I won't let you have a free hand!
Honmaru...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Clash! Martial Arts Tournament!!
Episode 57
Honmaru, wait for me-me!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius