Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
What the...
Thanks for all the support over the years, guys
Special thanks: Hisashi Eguchi
That was lame!
That's our Oaya-sensei!
Sensei amazing!
This is the ultimate superhuman performance!
Demonstrated by Oaya Mari-sensei!
Episode 87
The Most Important Kiss❤
Spectacular, spectacular!
'Twas rightly marvelous, big boss Oaya-sensei!
Isn't Oaya-sensei a truly resourceful woman?
Marry a woman like that and you'll get folded in two,
even if you have a body of steel!
You ain't talking ill of her! Not on my watch!
And now, the performance
everyone's been waiting for...
Allow me to introduce Harako Tsutomu!
What's taking him so long?
What's going on?
Harako! Enough with
the preludes, come out already!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Brought to you by Harako Tsutomu:
The Magic of Love and Fantasy!
Harako Special: Atomic...
A Very-Very Atomic Thunder Magic Show!
On Stage!
Hey! Harako, I've been waiting!
As expected, shining like a star
in everything you do!
Now, everyone, please let me introduce my assistant.
Please, come on!
Iyo...
Iyona-chan!
Why is Iyona-chan assisting Harako?
What's more...
She's looking so risque!
Yeah! Harako, Iyona, do your-ru-ru best!
And now, the star winner of the Special Jury Award
at the World Junior Magic Contest
will present to you his miraculous magic.
Harako amazing!
Spectacular performance, Young Master!
It's a great success, Harako-kun.
I'm glad everyone enjoyed it.
This is also the merit of having
you as my wonderful partner.
Damn you, Harako!
You did all that just to get
a head start on Iyona-chan!
Honmaru, we'll do a magic show too!
Alright! We gotta make it
even more well-received than Harako's!
Yeah!
Oh-ho! Look who's dashing onto the stage!
It's Edojo Honmaru and Taruruuto!
And they're going to perform in...
Honmaru, Taru-chan, good luck!
Taru-sama, I've been waiting!
Away!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, what should I do?
Eh? What to do? Well, it's a magic show, so...
Taru-chan, just do something
that'll surprise everyone a great deal.
Fine, I'll surprise everyone!
His stupid magic again?
Taru will be sure to put on some mind-blowing magic.
That's what we wanted to see!
Everyone surprised, Honmaru!
Taru! Listen, you...
You guys would be more fitting not on a magic show,
but on a comedic duo show, don't you think? Huh?
Harako! Even if we lost the magic show duel,
we won't lose in any other discipline!
Oh?
Is that to say you're challenging me to a duel?
Very well. I accept it, Honmaru.
Doing a duel!
Sounds interesting.
It'd be even better
if everyone else could partake too.
I agree too!
So, what kind of duel will it be?
Ladies and gentlemen,
the steward of this convention, Ryoguchiya Korekiyo,
never overlooks anything.
I'm excited to announce that as today's main event,
we've prepared a large obstacle race! Yessir.
If that's the case, I support it too!
Korekiyo, what's the main prize? I can consider
putting my guts into it, depending on what it is!
Alright, here's your prize: Matsugoro's original
Kansai-style takoyaki, all-you-can-eat!
I'll do it!
Isn't it kinda childish and lame, somehow?
In that case, how about we reward the winner
with a kiss from the person they like the most?
And the designated person can, by no means, refuse!
Mari-sensei...
Yes, yes, yes! I agree!
Do it! Do it!
Wait a minute! While we are above suspicion,
Honmaru and Taru will be sure to use magic to cheat!
What did you say?
Am I wrong?
You guys sure love to overthink!
Really, how hard can it be
to just keep your mouth shut?
After all, Taru-sama's
passionate kiss is what I'm here for!
Honmaru.
Ah? Sister Ria?
I'll prepare special magical obstacles
for Taru and the other magicians.
Alright! That's settled, then.
The rule is to make a circle around the park
while passing several obstacles.
Now, who is going to be the winner?
Iyona-chan...
I'll win this, whatever it takes.
And then, your...
I'll take your passionate kiss as my prize...
Let's do it!
Yeah! Honmaru, I'll do my best too!
When Maru-sensei's passionate kiss is at stake,
I won't stop at nothing, going through fire and water!
Oh! Matsu-san on fire too!
I won't lose!
What a bunch of happy-go-lucky brats.
Taru-chan, Honmaru, stay strong!
If you're a man, you can only return with the first prize!
As a winner, Honmaru, Taru!
Young Master! I'm looking closely at your performance!
Let's start!
Ready!
That must be obstacle number one!
Like a walk in the park!
If I...
Fall here...
No good, sir!
Don't mind me!
Taru! That's unfair!
Nannosho's Children's Association Obstacle Race
We first!
A pitfall course this time?
Oh! I can overfly!
Taru-sama!
Dammit! Taru, you jerk.
I'll never lose! Not to you! Taru!
Dammit! Those magician upstarts again!
Hey, Sister Ria!
Taru-sama, be careful.
Ah! Sister going to obstruct us?
I suppose. I can't just let you pass for free, after all.
With all due respect to Taru-sama's sister,
I'll pass though here no matter what!
Ah...
Me going too!
Don't forget about me!
Taru-Taru-Taru-Taru.
Taru! Mimora! Rival!
Don't mind me!
Sister!
That's cowardly, Taru!
Now's my chance!
Ta... Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta... Takoyaki!
Conjure!
Takoyaki!
It'll be a long while before
you can beat me in a magical duel, Taru.
Even if I won't win,
I get to eat takoyaki! I'm happy!
Taru-sama!
Leaving me behind like that... how cruel!
Takoyaki! Takoyaki!
You... you... you nasty thing!
This means there are no
longer any obstacles in the way!
I'm happy!
Taru-sama?
Crap! I'll show you now, Taru!
The one who'll get Mimora-chan's kiss will be me...
Dammit! And we're supposed to be
just two obstacles away from the finish line!
This is a bit of a pickle...
Such a thing wouldn't even slow me down!
Don't mind me!
Hey! Be careful, Rival!
Incorpore-re-real!
Smell you later!
Ugh! Ya think some lousy dog
will make me quake in my boots?
How can this stop Harako Tsutomu,
when Iyona-san's lips are at stake?
Think I'll lose? Like hell!
Wait...
This is the final one!
I'm coming for my victory!
This is no obstacle at all!
Just as I said, the victory is mine for sure!
Ray!
Mimora-chan!
Mimora-chan...
Even if I say I need this victory,
Mimora-chan is still Mimora-chan.
I can't do anything terrible to Mimora-chan.
With enough guts, no concrete wall can stop you!
I've let myself be overtaken...
Still, Mimora-chan...
Damn it! This is not the time to be hesitating!
Ah?
We do a little cheating! There!
Finish
Honmaru-kun!
Suddenly, Honmaru and Matsugoro appear!
They are the main candidates for victory now!
Yeah! Honmaru!
Alright! That's the way!
Just a little more, Honmaru!
You gotta do your best too, Matsugoro-san!
Honmaru, I ain't holding back, you hear?!
I know that!
I won't tolerate anyone
getting in the way of my victory!
Ray-Ray-Ray-Ray-Ray! Ray!
Honmaru!
Stop!
Run away, both of you!
That's it! That's right! I'm working hard in life!
When will the new album be released?
What's going on?!
© Hisashi Eguchi
You think I can afford stepping off now?!
Even a second's advantage is crucial for victory!
Here!
Ray!
Rival!
That's it! That's right! I'm working hard in life!
When will the new album be released?
What's going on?!
© Hisashi Eguchi
Ray! Ray-Ray-Ray-Ray!
Now, which one of the two was able to reach the goal?
The winner is...
By only a measly margin, the winner is Edojo Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Hang on, Honmaru-kun!
Are you okay, Matsugoro-san?
Done bad...
Honmaru and Matsu-san
will feel better from drinking Power Upple Juice!
Rival! Will you ever part
with that twisted personality of yours?!
It seems your training at my place
is still far from completion!
And so, we'll now proceed
to holding the award ceremony
for the victor of the Nannosho
obstacle race, Edojo Honmaru!
Honmaru, your guts got the better of me this time.
Matsu-san!
Now, Honmaru-kun.
Announce the name of the person you want to kiss.
In other words, who is
your most favorite person here?
Yeah! Honmaru great!
I sure do envy that sucker!
It's preordained now.
Well, that was a magnificent victory.
Now say it loud and clear like a man, Honmaru!
Hurry up and decide. Who will it be, Honmaru-kun?
That's right. I must say it boldly like a man.
I worked myself to the bone
for the one person I love the most.
Honmaru!
Say it without hesitation.
Honmaru-kun...
My... My most favorite person here...
Iyon—
Honmaru loves me the most.
He decided to kiss me. Me happy!
What a truly beautiful
story of friendship indeed.
This concludes the award ceremony.
So that's how it is!
Honmaru's most favorite person has been Taru!
Good for you, Honmaru.
Well done, Taru!
It can't be...
I don't agree with what just happened!
Taru, why'd you do such a thing to me?!
Don't be embarrassed, Honmaru.
I love Honmaru the most too.
But it was a wonderful kiss, Honmaru-kun, Taru-chan.
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
There, I set it off!
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius
Thank you for bearing with us through these 87 episodes + 3 movies of mid!
Yours truly, LonelyDildo. '2023-24
Taru's love is you
Love is you!