Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Through the use of a magical item - Professtick
of Literature, Dr. Into-Book-Putter, me and Taruruuto
were put inside a book that dad wrote!
However, the Great King Dowahaha, who imprisoned the Goddess of Light and descended the world into darkness,
snatched Professtick from us.
The Great King's subordinates,
Eland and Count Rakula, attacked us on the way.
But with the hero Doberk, the protagonist,
we managed to fend them off.
Taru! Defeating the Great King Dowahaha should be
our first priority, if we're ever to return to our usual world!
Yeah!
You can do it, Honmaru!
Episode 34
This is Your End! Great King Dowahaha
To our new hero Taruruuto-sama! Hooray!
Hooray!
That's the way, Taruruuto-sama!
Yeah! Together, we'll make away with Great King Dowahaha!
Will we, though?
The path is still riddled with mighty enemies...
This time, even I'm worried.
Since someone's that fat.
Sorry, Honmaru.
It was so yummy, I couldn't help overeating.
Honmaru-sama.
Ah?
Mayoi-chan?
What is it?
In my family, this pendant has been handed down
for generations. Let it protect you.
Receiving something so important...
Kinda makes me feel obliged to you.
I don't want you to die.
Taruruuto-sama did this to you,
so I figured it's some special greeting from your world.
I'm so sorry!
Our village!
Ah? The village!
In a sea of fire!
Danger! Danger, danger, danger!
Another one of the Big Four!
Beautiful Beast Gabella!
No way! The one defending the final bastion
of Dowahaha's army...
The strongest and the most dreaded monster...
What is he doing here?!
Mayoi-chan!
Danger, danger, danger!
I can't move my feet!
This whole forest is alive!
We're done for!
We strayed right into the Delusive Forest!
What did you say?
Who the hell is this guy?
Can't you tell by listening to his laugh?
This here is King Dowahaha himself!
You bastards!
You'll pay for the misery of my precious underlings.
They've been reduced to this!
Bats! Bats! Bats! Bats!
Hiccup!
Ah! Sorry, I can't help laughing.
Your offenses against the two of them
will now return to you tenfold.
You assholes!
My entire royal army is now on the move,
to thoroughly rough up every single villager!
What'd you say?!
I summon thee, Pack Leader Pachulas!
Eh?!
Pachulas, start by gobbling up the fat magician!
This is dangerous!
You're supposed to defeat those one by one,
between training sessions with the Mountain Wizard!
You don't just come straight
to the strongest one of the Big Four, Pachulas!
This ain't nothing like my story!
Taru, watch out!
Oh! You finally decided to do something yourself?
Doberk, now I see you're a real man!
Doberk... Wink, wink...
Don't, Doberk!
This technique is supposed to be your ultimate technique
for finishing off Dowahaha!
You lack the training.
You can't use it with your current power!
My sacred sword!
I knew it - that technique is way out of his league.
This tree won't save you from being torn to pieces!
A giant hand is flying our way!
It's nothing to be happy about!
Wanna play rock paper scissors?
What a dense one! Prepare to get gobbled up!
Rock, paper...
Taru!
Scissors!
Eh?
Ehehe?!
No way!
It hurts so much, papa!
Did he...
somehow find out
that Pachulas' weakness is in his eyes?
My eyes! Eyes!
Attaway, Taru!
Honmaru! I won by throwing scissors!
Ya alright there?
Taru! If you have the time to show pity for the enemies,
you better go save the village!
Village in trouble!
Can't move at all!
Momo?
Ah? Momomo, please check my bag
for something we could use right about now.
Momo!
Oh? Inflatable Muscles-kun!
What's that thing?
When you use this guy, your muscles swell up outta thin air
and you become a powerful machoman!
Sounds great!
Stick it on my belly.
Open the lid.
Hey, Taru! This one is letting the air out!
Are you sure it's Inflatable Muscles-kun?
No... This - Exhaustable Listless-kun!
What?!
You use Exhaustable Listless-kun
to exhaust your body completely listless!
Taru! You're shrinking at an alarming rate!
Listless-kun made my size perfect again!
Well done, Taru!
You bastards! Gabeila,
make that shrimp into a nice little charcoal!
Gabeila! Go for a ramming attack next!
Make that damn shrimp into a pancake!
Taru!
Taru...
Whoever dares to defy me, the great King Dowahaha,
will soon meet their untimely demise!
No enemy has yet been able to withstand a charge
from Gabeila, our army's strongest warrior!
Taru...
Good, Gabeila. Now just do away with the others,
flattening them just as well!
Eh?
What is it, Gabeila?
Ah... The Great King, sir! This empty head of mine
is leaking something out with a hiss.
What did you say?!
It feels like the power is somehow seeping out of my body!
Good job, Taru!
You stuck Exhaustable Listless-kun on Gabeila's head!
Damn it, I'll make that shrimp pay for sure!
Now I'm really goddamn mad! I'll teach that shrimp a lesson
by frying every single one of the villagers together with him!
Oh?
Uh-oh?
Fire!
Nice weather you have around these places...
That's what you get for burning down our village!
Ah! No... Stop! No! Ouch-ouch-ouch!
If we don't put out the village soon,
everyone that's still in there will be burned alive!
Raincloud Taro!
Here, dear!
How about we put out this village?
I'd gladly do it for you!
You impudent brats!
But not after the Delusive Forest
strangles you all to death!
Let Honmaru go! If you don't let him go, I'll prune you,
and make you into houses!
Oh! Taru! You're alive, after all!
Yeah! Power-Upple Juice restored my liveliness!
Time's out!
Making houses!
I beg your forgiveness! And mercy...
You swine! Your crocodile tears won't make our houses
arise from the ashes! Isn't that obvious?
Houses... fell from the sky.
You rogues! How dare you dunk on
my great army one after another?!
Great King Dowahaha!
We're the ones here who've been offended first!
Give back Professtick of Literature,
Dr. Into-Book-Putter!
Without him, we can't return to our usual lives!
And let the Goddess of Light go!
Let the light into this world!
Silence, you pestering bugs!
He vanished...
Dowahaha big!
Don't tell me this is the Great King Dowahaha's true form...
Bastards! You made me come
to pass a death penalty on your three myself.
However... If you show me the way
to get to the world that you've come from...
I will consider letting him live.
Professtick!
Now, what do I do to find a way to your world, huh?
If you make a wish while holding that stick...
The hell?! Taru, why are you telling him?
Then, I'll stop.
I see, much obliged for the guidance.
Time for me to head to your world
so I can bring it down to knees as well!
Huh?! They're letting the Great King invade our world, too?
It's a disaster, Honmaru! Find a way to stop it!
If we let the King set a foot in our world,
it'll be beyond saving.
Dad, mom...
Iyona-chan, everyone...
Everyone would be at the King's mercy!
Crap...
I'll fight him! I, myself! I'll fight and beat him,
saving this world and protecting ours!
Yeah!
Still, Honmaru, you shouldn't forget
that the Goddess of Light is still being held hostage.
Our quest is not to beat him, but to free the Goddess of Light!
That's true...
But then, where did he imprison the Goddess of Light, Doberk?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
Aren't you the protagonist here?!
There are things even the protagonist doesn't know!
You cretin! How can this be a story of saving her,
if you don't really even know?
Shut it! The plot went completely sideways
ever since you two showed up!
Their friendship went sour!
Whaddya say?
You dare say this
even after we helped your ass out of it?
Who ever asked you to come? I would've completed
the journey in my own place and be all hunky-dory!
Goddess of Light!
Oh?
Honmaru!
Goddess of Light!
Taru! That's plain cheating!
You were supposed to solve the riddle of her location
with clues you find on the way!
Goddess of Light!
Please help us bring the light back to this world!
We need your help!
I'm grateful to you for saving me.
I can now proceed with fulfilling my destiny.
Shining Radiance...
Hooray!
The light was brought back to our world!
Glory be!
You pests! Now you've done it!
He used his ultimate trump already, the Eye Rays!
The Great King Dowahaha must be really, really mad!
Taru! To the side! Run to the side!
Okay!
This way!
Taru! Up!
Okay!
Can't do this anymore... Nothing helps...
Taru! Fly towards the tip of Dowahaha's nose!
Taru! Now make a sharp turn!
You did it! The Great King blew up his own nose!
Me did, Honmaru!
Bite, gulp...
Eaten...
Eh? Taru got swallowed!
My gastric juice will dissolve anything!
Must fly out of here!
Oh no!
Search-search. Search-search! Anything at all!
What would I redirect?
What to do?
Help me someone!
Bendpost!
Ah... That's right! If I give a "Bendpost" command,
Bendpost redirects arrow and goes the other way!
Bendpost... Bendpost... Bendpost again!
What's that?
Uh? Where's here?
Oh! I'm relieved to see you here.
Professtick Into-Book-Putter!
Ugh! How dare you come all the way here,
into the control room!?
Who you?
Before you, the operator of the Giant Dowahaha Robot,
the one and only, true Great King Dowahaha!
Great King Dowahaha?
How do you know that?!
How can I not? You said it yourself out loud just now.
I won't let anyone who finds out
about this secret out of here alive!
Numerous were your misdeeds, Great King Dowahaha!
En garde!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I won't ever commit any more bad thing!
Please grant me mercy!
I'll do anything.
Anything for your forgiveness!
Alright! You're forgiven!
I see. So it was a robot all along?
You got any idea what we had to go through?!
But it was... It was because nobody
wanted to make friends with us!
What the hell is that pretext?!
Get this!
It hurts! Hurts!
I feel sorry for Dowahaha-san...
Mayoi-chan, it's as though you borrowed your kindliness
straight from Iyona-chan...
I'm so sorry!
Alright... Wait a minute, good folk of the village!
Good folk!
Why don't you pardon him already?
Already?
If Taruruuto-sama requests it,
we have to abide...
I'm so infinitely grateful!
I swear I won't do anything like that ever again!
Is it time for you to return already?
Yes. Our family is probably getting worried.
Make sure to come visit us again one day, will you?
Feel free to come play around together.
Sure!
I should say, although I thought you were a bungler and a coward when we first met,
I wouldn't wanna question your courage now!
Farewell.
And now, it's where Honmaru safely returns home.
Taru, Honmaru, you did we—
Taru, what did you do this for?
Me very liked this giant robot!
Dowahaha also let me have it!
Incorpore-re-real!
Let's see how it operates!
Ah-movin', Taruru, swingin' Taru... Like this.
You've gotta be kidding, Taruruuto!
Honmaru, I wanna eat takoyaki!
Not happening! My allowance is long gone.
But hear this: Wanna eat, wanna eat, takoyaki, takoyaki,
wanna fly, tako-tako-high!
Oh, come on... Why won't you try
to figure something out yourself, Taru?
Oh, idea!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Takoyakinfection to Conquer the World!
City's flooded with takoyaki, me so happy!
Episode 35
Takoyakinfection to Conquer the World
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius