Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru!
Hey, Taruruuto!
Hey, Taru!
I bought us some takoyaki!
Takoyaki?
Look!
Episode 9
Takoyaki of Friendship!
Takoyaki! Takoyaki!
That was my last pocket money this month.
After this, we're not eating takoyaki any time soon.
That's why
we should savor every last one of them.
Let's have a good meal!
Damn swindler!
You gobbled my share, too?!
Give back my takoyaki!
You're so nasty!
I wanted to try them, too!
Takoyaki! Takoyaki!
I wanted to try them too, takoyaki...
Sorry, Honmaru.
I know, Taru! Make takoyaki with magic.
Consider that a compensation!
Okay...
Why didn't I come up
with that brilliant idea sooner?
With Taru's magic,
we can even live on a takoyaki diet!
Ta-ta-ta-ta-takoyaki I summon!
It worked!
Not as much takoyaki as yakitako.
Didn't you mix something up?
I err'd...
But this time, I'll do it right, Honmaru.
Takoyaki, hey, appear!
Did it!
Finally... This time, it's a real takoyaki.
Knew you'd manage, Taruruuto!
What's that?
Take-o-ya-kite! Kite!
Taruruuto-kun, do you find it that amusing
to be pulling my leg?
Give back my real takoyaki!
Me... Me is not that good at summoning magic!
Takoyaki offense is grave!
If I buy takoyaki, I make up with Honmaru.
Takoyaki!
Need takoyaki!
Welcome!
You again?
I sure hope you came with money today.
Money... haven't.
No money means no takoyaki.
Just window-shopping again?
Money, where do I get it?
You get money from the bank!
Then I go to the bank.
Off you go, already. Off you go!
Nobody here can waste time playing with kids!
I have business to run. A business!
That's where everybody get money from.
Mo-mo-mo-mo-money appear!
Me is not good at summoning magic, after all.
I know!
Hey, little one... This machine
isn't just some toy. Get it?
Taruru!
Listen, this machine is not...
Yo! Looking for something?
What the heck, what the heck, what the heck?!
Summon me some money.
Got a cash card or a passbook?
No and no.
Then, I can't help you.
Please...
Look, it's beyond my power.
It's here.
I'm sorry, dear customer,
but we don't yet have machines speaking on their own.
Look! That machine!
It's now even sweating heavily!
I don't suppose we have a roof leak again?
Kid, what is it you're playing with,
in a place like that?
What are you doing? Let me go!
Nobody move!
Hands in the air.
Let me go! You hear me?
Hey! You there! Freeze, too!
Quit it with that noise!
Now, get the stuff.
Conjure me some cash.
Okay.
Quit fumbling with it. Hurry up!
Money!
Found my fellow mages!
I told everyone to stay put!
Conjure me money.
You dare mess with us, damn brat?!
Stingy!
What's going on?
Board Pen Magic-kun
becomes a cannon.
Magic of rose binding.
You picked the wrong guys
to show off your sleight of hand to!
For this alone, you have to die! Damn brat!
Kid, watch out!
Be careful what you wish for.
Well, that was one notable feat, son.
In all that fuss you caused,
before I knew it, both culprits somehow got cuffed.
Still though, a blowout at a moment that fortunate...
Must be the doing of some god from the machine.
Either way, I feel we should reward you in some way.
Anything you want?
Takoyaki!
Thank you, son!
I must have been working too much lately...
Where did you get all these?
I went to the bank and they bought me takoyaki.
Also said "Thank you!"
Where do you find a bank
that buys takoyaki for you?
Many takoyaki.
Make Honmaru happy!
Yummy!
Want to eat takoyaki.
No, you can't, Taruruuto. Gotta share it at home,
with my friend Honmaru. Patience, patience!
Me and takoyaki are almost home
where I can eat them.
Together with Honmaru...
Can't wait to eat! Alright.
Just gonna make sure they're all in place.
All takoyaki in place!
Patience, patience.
Patience. Patience.
Out of patience!
Me full...
Where could he have gone off to?
I swear, Taru...
Maybe I went too hard on him?
Sorry, Honmaru.
Me in trouble.
Me in trouble!
Could be that someone
lost a takoyaki around here?
Huh?
Whatcha doing?
Role-playing koala!
Me a baby koala!
Oh? Daddy koala fell from tree.
What's going on?
What was that sound?
Honmaru's teacher!
Good evening.
What am I seeing?
Taru-chan deciding to keep me company?
Teacher, what are you doing?
I was just about to get in the hot bath.
Join me if you'd like,
would you, Taru-chan?
Bath!
I love bath!
Well, isn't Taru-chan cute?
Taru!
The time for supper came and went,
but you never showed up, Taru.
Taru! Where did you fly off to?
Taru-chan, you like it?
Now it's my turn to clean teacher's back!
Thank you. Then, please do.
Taru!
Teacher has very pure skin!
Whoa, there! Even a child
should be careful with such compliments.
I love teacher!
Hey...
I'll be damned!
That should have been me, not that kid!
It's a lovely song. Very soothing to the mind.
A song that arranges your soul back in order.
This - what mama sang to me, magical song.
Mama.
Who's there?!
You scum! A panty thief, aren't you? Disgraceful!
Superb, teacher!
When my favorite set of underwear disappeared the other day,
you were behind that as well, weren't you?
Take off that helmet
and show me your face!
I ain't showing you my face,
but you can still have my name!
Under my belt,
20 years of panty theft experience.
A vagabond panty-stealing rider,
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer!
Venereal Self-Pleasurer or whatever it is,
your sorry ass helmet is already dead.
What?
Weird face.
Well, sorry I such a weird face, boy,
but I never let those who had truly seen it live!
Lookin' cool, Venerealable Self-Pleasurer!
Watch out!
Block... Block!
What the heck?
It's not even a real pistol, is it?
I'm a noble panty thief.
Hurting people is against my rules! I'm off.
Farewell!
Wait!
Taru-chan, you stay here
and look after the house, okay?
Game of tag?
Let me partake too!
No way!
Wait, you!
Tag game!
Taru-chan? When did you...
Impressive, teacher!
Caught up with him already!
Did you see it just now?
A pretty woman riding in nothing but a bathrobe!
Lucky!
After her!
Nice!
So many wanna partake in tag game!
Try to overtake us, people!
Taru-chan!
I can't drive if you twitch so violently on my chest.
Sorry. But it's feels so warm and good down here.
Hold on tight, Taru-chan.
Oh wow, you caught up with me after all?
But Venerealable Self-Pleasurer
has nothing to fear.
Secret weapon: Pachinko Ball Attack!
You asked for it, baby!
This is not nearly enough to down me!
Teacher!
Taru-chan, stop twitching!
Sorry.
Next attack, then!
Deploying Fireworks Attack!
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer! Very cool!
You're well into your adult years,
yet you're sticking to childish gimmicks!
Neck Chop!
That's what my battery-shock glove is for!
Lightning Attack!
Teache-e-ehr?!
How do you like it?
Lightning Attack sure is refreshing!
Teacher, what's with you?
Bad!
Me not good in driving!
Tarururuu!
Bike-chan, chase the Venerealable Self-Pleasurer.
We're playing tag!
Alright, got you covered!
I'll catch him in no time! Let's go!
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer sets out to prowl the city at night,
looking for yet another prey!
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer
gets pleasure tonight!
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer!
We're getting to you!
The hell?!
That kid's steering it by himself?
Alright...
Lightning Attack!
Tag! Big bro is now "it!"
Don't miss me!
I touched you.
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer is now "it."
Should I touch him by the torso to make it count?
Taruruuto, don't give up!
Alright...
Touching once again, by the torso!
Venerealable Self-Pleasurer is now "it!"
Venereal pleasure - venerable measure...
What the?!
I can't, can't, can't fly!
Good grief...
Teacher. Teacher!
When it was Venerealable Self-Pleasurer's turn
to be "it," he tried to run away.
It's against rules, so I made him feel "it."
Oh, my?
Was it really you who caught him?
That kid again?
Having a busy day, it seems.
Now he is the next "it."
That was a notable feat, Taru-chan.
And besides, I must thank you for saving me.
Is there anything you want in return?
Me tako—
Shucks! I forgot takoyaki!
Teacher bought me takoyaki!
Going to teacher's house was good idea, after all.
Me so smart!
Smell so good.
Just a block or two more.
Takoyaki, watch out!
Taru!
Taru?
Where have you been all this time?
I went out looking for you!
Honmaru, I... I... I...
Sorry I flew off the handle back then.
I'm not mad anymore.
Look!
I bought it with my allowance
for rubbing dad's shoulders.
I thought I can only eat them
together with Taru.
I was so excited,
I even passed on my own supper.
I swear, if you had dawdled any longer,
it would've gone completely cold!
Honmaru! My friend! Friend.
Cut it out, Taruruuto!
Come on, come on.
Let's just get to eating it sooner.
Yummy.
Why did you gobble them all up yourself again?!
Oopsie. My bad, my bad.
What kind of friend are you?
Taru! Give me back my toil!
Sorry, Honmaru.
I'll eat this instead!
Taruru!
Oh God, why am I that unlucky?!
My life is a chain of misfortunes!
Can't you do something, Taruruuto?
Then, Honmaru, you should try-ry-ry this on.
What's that thing?
Are you messing with me, Taru?!
Taruruuto cannot tell lies.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Conscientious Use of Oppoositer.
Episode 10
Conscientious Use of Oppoositer
Wait for it, fairu-ru folk!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume