Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
At last, Honmaru defeated Nezo.
However, Honmaru lost his own life in the fight.
Not even Ria's magic was able
to breathe life back into Honmaru.
No!
Episode 60
Magical World
Did I really die?
Light... An exit?
Somehow, I feel much better now!
Ngh!
What is this place?
So warm... A wonderfully pleasant place!
Edojo Honmaru
Mama...
HONMARU!
Honmaru!
Honey!
Honmaru! Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Mama...
Honmaru! Honmaru!
Honmaru... Why... Why did you die?!
Taru, isn't it about time
we returned to the Magic Realm?
If you go back, you might be able to see Honmaru again.
Eh?
After all, the Magic Realm exists in the world
where people go after they die here.
Eh?!
Oh, I see now!
Alright! Let's hurry home to see Honmaru again!
Okay, let's return then.
Yeah!
Taru, what's wrong?
If I return, I won't be seeing everyone anymore.
Perhaps...
I gotta resurrect Honmaru after all!
Then we'll all live together!
Sister, don't you really know some magic for resurrecting?
I don't.
Really don't know?
Sorry, Taru. I really don't know of any.
However, if Honmaru is in the Spirit World now,
we can bring him to the Magic Realm.
Then, if we ask our mama, she might agree to resurrect him.
Oh?
Spirit World
Magic Realm
I'm leaving for the Spirit World!
Where is the spirit world?
How do I get there?
Taru, these two worlds are governed by unbending laws.
Sister?
Honmaru...
Honmaru!
Sister, where spirit world?
Sister!
Sister...
The spell for going to the spirit world is the spell
for returning to the Magic Realm that you already know.
When you use it to go home,
you'll pass through the Spirit World on the way.
I see! Alright, let's go!
Good day! Nice to meet you...
Hold it! I'm not done talking.
Once you reach the Spirit World, you'll need to take Honmaru
to the Magic Realm without anyone noticing.
If someone spots you,
grab Honmaru and make a run for it!
If you get caught... It's not just that Honmaru won't be resurrected. Taru, you'll be punished too!
Sister, let's go togetheru-ru-ru.
I can't do that.
Why?
You're supposed to know that as well.
Only magicians who came to this world
upon being summoned by humans
can go to the Spirit World to be judged
on whether or not they have properly trained in this world.
I only came to this world
as moral support for you.
Once you disappear from this world,
I'll get sucked away into the Magic Realm immediately.
I get it. I gotta go alone to resurrect Honmaru.
And then, me, Honmaru, and everyone
would live together again!
Forget it!
Even if Honmaru comes back to life,
you won't be able to live in this world.
Because once you return to the Magic Realm,
until someone summons you again,
you won't have any way of reappearing in this world.
Honmaru will re-summon me
after I resurrect him!
Did you forget?
After you say the spell for returning to the Magic Realm,
everyone will immediately forget all about you.
Forget about me?
Hey, Sister, please teach me some magic
for living with everyone in this world ever after!
I don't know of any convenient magic like that.
Tama-chan, please teach me. Tama-chan!
I'm sorry, Taru-chan. I don't know either.
So I was thinking...
Since Honmaru is there, in the other world,
why don't we live together over there -
the three of us and mama. Why not?
If Honmaru resurrected,
Me forever apart from Honmaru
in the Magic Realm.
If Honmaru dies, me live together with Honmaru!
Alright! Me live together with Honmaru!
Now! Let's go home!
Good day...
Honmaru!
Honmaru...
Ah?
Mama...
He died...
But without everyone... don't wanna!
Mama, Iyona, papa, Rui,
Teacher, Jabao, Korekiyo, Matsu-san, everyone... Everyone!
Goodbye!
What in the world is this place?
No one's here. What should I do?
Honmaru...
There are people!
Hey there! Hey!
Honmaru...
Honmaru!
Taru!
If someone spots you,
grab Honmaru and make a run for it.
Ah!
Hey! We're here!
Don't do that, Honmaru!
What are you saying, Taru?
Weren't those people calling me...
Run away quickly!
Please wait!
Taru, they're coming after us!
If you get caught,
Honmaru won't be able to come back to life.
If me ask my mom, Honmaru will come back to life,
and me forever apart with Honmaru.
But Honmaru's mama, papa,
Iyona, Rui - everyone will be happy.
I'll be happy too.
Honmaru!
Wait a minute!
Taru, what's going on?
Honmaru died. This is afterlife.
Then... I won't see Iyona-chan ever again?
Huh?
Honmaru, we have to hurry!
Honmaru, move it!
Me bring Honmaru back to life!
Really, Taru?
Great!
But if people chasing us catch up and catch us,
I can't bring you back to life!
Honmaru!
Gotta run!
Iyona-chan!
I can fly too?
In this world, you can have any power you can think of.
Whoa! This feels pretty darn nice!
Huh? What's that?
It's fine. There's the entrance to the Magic Realm.
It's me, Taruruuto! This is my friend, Honmaru!
Ooooh?
Glad to see you've come.
What's this, Taru?
This tunnel leads to the Magic Realm.
Those chasing us can't enter.
Honmaru!
Wait a minute...
They're here!
Ah! Gotta hurry up!
Taru!
It worked! Seems like we shook them off.
We'll be in the Magic Realm soon enough.
I'm falling! Do something, Taru! Taru!
Taru-chan, Honmaru-kun,
you both can fly on your own, remember?
Oh, right.
There!
Is this the Magic Realm?
Don't relax your guard just yet!
The spirits from earlier can still catch up with you.
First, let's fly towards that high mountain.
Yay! Will see my mama again!
Taru's mama is there?
My mama is the Great Magician.
With my mama's magic, Honmaru can be resurrected.
That's it! I'll get to see Iyona-chan in no time!
Head towards that ball of water, surrounded by clouds from all sides.
The next would be the third island from the left.
The Magic Realm sure is vast.
This place is close to our home.
Soon enough, our home...
Mama.
Taru...
Come to think of it, he's been away from his mama
ever since I summoned him.
No wonder he misses her greatly...
Taru's mama, then? I wonder what kind of person she is.
My mama very gentle!
Oh? How did you understand what I was thinking?
In Magic Realm, what you think is what you say.
Kinda like telepathy?
Gotta keep my mind away from thinking lewd things.
Yeah! Me not thinking lewd things!
Oh no!
Let's have a duel, Taruruuto!
What do you want to compete at?
Eeeeck!
Eecking, then?
Oh! Taru!
Taru!
Why, you! How dare you fry Taru unprovoked?!
Oh? You wanna go at it too?
I'm in luck today.
I'll get two prey at once.
Why did you... Why did you do this to Taru?!
Honmaru Punch!
He's too tough for me!
Stop fooling around and decide what we'll compete at!
In the end, I'd rather not!
When he turns his back,
I'll kick him then and there!
What?!
How cowardly!
Crap! He knows immediately everything I'm thinking!
Can't be helped! Let's duel!
Alright! What will we compete at?
Alright! Let's have a duel in rock, paper, scissors!
I mean, we can do that, right?
Okay! Let's have a duel in rock, paper, scissors.
Lucky! This way, I'll at least have a chance too!
You idiot, you can easily win in rock, paper, scissors
if you can read the opponent's mind.
That said, which one should I choose?
Would it be rock, scissors or paper?
If I had to choose, rock or paper?
What's the matter?
Decide already!
If I throw paper, it may be a mistake...
Enough! We're starting!
Hold up, I've not decided yet!
Rock!
Ah! I've not decided yet.
Paper!
Ah! I don't understand his thoughts!
Scissors!
Oh? Seems like I won.
Shit, I lost!
It's as easy as that!
Then, I'll be taking that...
Scroll!
Trunsform!
Yes, like this.
Hey! Give Taru back!
Taru, you're alive!
Taru!
Look, after defeating you,
I've collected ten stamps already!
Now, it's your turn!
You beat me at rock, paper, scissors, remember?
Here, Honmaru, you can use this.
It's still brand new.
Huh?
Honmaru, you need to produce a spell of youru-ru-ru own!
Spell of my own?
Honmaru-ru-ru!
Something like that?
Great!
And like that...
When you win a duel in Magic Realm,
you make a stamp of your opponent and press it on a scroll.
If you collect a lot of stamps, you can return the scroll
and exchange them for magical items.
Everyone here duels a lot.
This is also magical training.
Uhm. Taru-chan, if you don't hurry,
the spirits will find and catch you two!
That's right!
I completely forgot! Let's hurry, Taru!
Yeah!
Our home!
Made! We made! We made it, made it, made it, made it!
Brought Honmaru to our home!
Is that what you call home?
Yeah!
It's mama!
Taru-chan,
I've been waiting.
Mama, I'm coming home!
Mama!
Even Taru's mama can't bring me back to life?!
Taru, what do I do now?
Don't cry, Honmaru. The Colored Sky Hermit
on Ice Spirit Mountain can still help you.
That's it! Soon enough, dad, mom, Iyona-chan,
Iyona-chan, Iyona-chan, Iyona-chan, just you wait for me!
Honmaru, do your best!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Operation Resurrection.
Everyone, come back to life with us!
Episode 61
Operation Resurrection
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
TLC by Aurelius
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)