Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
How about this, Taru?
This is what they call a motor show!
Amazing, amazing!
I would love to drive along the coast at sunset
with Taru-sama in a car like this.
Okay! I'll take care of that.
Niruru, look closely.
Hey, Taru! You can't...
Hey, Taru!
Wait, you!
Taruruuto!
Episode 65
Rival's Unrequited Love
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama, isn't this wonderful?
How dare you, Taruruuto?!
How dare you have such a good time while I'm suffering here and doing all the housework for Mari-sensei?!
At this rate, Mimora-chan
will become his love slave!
Unacceptable!
Have you finished cleaning the bathroom yet?
No, um... You see...
No.
Oh? Isn't that Taru-chan and Mimora-chan?
Ah! Looks like they're having fun. Lovely!
What's the matter?
No, nothing at all, alright?
But it does look really fun!
Rival-chan, do you happen
to be in love with this girl?
Ick!
No, actually... No idea whatchu talking about.
Ah! Taru-chan is making a move on Mimora-chan...
What?! You're going to regret it, Taruruuto...
Just kidding.
Relax already.
Trying to hide it won't get you anywhere.
You have a crush for Mimora-chan.
However, Mimora-chan has a crush for Taru-chan.
"That's it, Taruruuto!
You'll pay for this!"
"Whatever it takes,
I gotta steal Mimora-chan's heart!"
"Alright! I'll make sure Taruruuto's bad side
is exposed to Mimora-chan!"
Teacher!
It's been such a hard time! For me!
No matter what I try,
it just doesn't seem to work!
Even when I assumed Taruruuto's appearance,
I made a mistake and hurt Mimora-chan!
Teacher!
Okay, okay, Rival.
I understand how you feel.
It must've been painful.
Yeah! It was so crippling, in fact,
I couldn't even clean the bathroom!
I see. Very well. Okay, okay.
Success. This way, I'm not getting scolded. Lucky!
If you really thought I'd pamper you that much,
you're dead wrong!
If you can't think of a better way to steal a girl's heart
than disparaging your rival, you're an excuse of a man!
If you're a man, act like one
and use your manly back to captivate women!
My back?
Yes.
Wonderful...
My back, you say...
Not that!
Then, what did you mean...
It's sports!
Huh?
Beautiful sweat appearing after an intense training.
Eyes sparkling bright.
Even now, it's still overwhelming my chest -
the hot and sour taste of youth!
That's the kind of men
women fall in love with.
Then, if I show Mimora-chan my sporting side,
Mimora-chan will fall in love with me?
Only if you give it every ounce of your strength!
Yeah.
Play with all seriousness.
Yeah!
Her heart will belong to you, once and for all!
Yes! Yay!
It's settled!
Teacher...
Rival...
Now, everyone!
Today's gym class will be a beach volleyball match.
Taruruuto.
Today, I'm beating you decisively in sports!
And then, with my glistening manly sweat,
I'll seize Mimora-chan's heart as well!
What the heck is beach volleyball?
Like dancing in the sea?
Da-da-dancing?
You don't even know about beach volleyball?
What a dunce!
What?!
Quiet, everyone!
What we call beach volleyball is a volleyball game
played on the sand in teams of two.
Just look... there!
For this day specifically,
I reequipped our sandbox as a volleyball court.
Looks like so much fun!
That's our Teach for you!
You never know what to expect from her!
Very true, Jabao-san.
Teacher, should we play it so suddenly,
without any practice?
In any discipline,
nothing beats learning on the job, Kawai-san.
Alright.
Well, first, let's hold a match between magicians.
Here it comes!
A-team:
Taruruuto-kun.
Yeah!
Do your best!
B-team.
Rival-kun.
Alright!
Rival, yes!
Unimpressed...
Now then, who should we pair them up with?
Teacher!
I guess I'm the only one
who can form a pair with Taru.
Honmaru!
Together with Honmaru-sama again... I'm getting more and more apprehensive about these two!
Then, if we have Honmaru-kun
and Taru-chan as the first pair,
one more person...
Harako-kun?
Teacher,
it would appear that as the World Junior Beach Volleyball Champion, I have no choice but to make an appearance.
Long title again.
But he'll probably lose anyway.
Okay, sounds good.
Then, B-team is Harako-kun and Rival.
1, 2, Taruru.
2, 2, Taruru.
This should be a duel between Taru and me.
If you can, try not to stand in the way.
Shut up!
That's my line!
Taru! Let's do our best!
Yeah! We won't lose.
Taru-sama, good luck.
Mimora-chan, watch them closely.
Huh?
Okay...
You need to try hard
to make the sweat appear, Rival.
If you do that, I'm sure, all your dark,
simmering jealousy will be purged at once.
Whether you win or lose, a refreshing
manly friendship with Taru-chan will be born from this.
Let the match begin!
Mimora-chan, watch closely
at my cool performance!
Let's go!
Alright!
Fire!
What?!
Hey! Watch out, Taruruuto!
I'll be fine. I got Bendpost.
Volleyball!
Raincloud Taro!
Here!
Looking good.
Here, Honmaru!
Alright, Taru! Attack now! There.
Okay! Huh?
Oh! Here-here-here it comes!
Alright, give me a good toss!
Harako Tsutomu's special...
Huh?
Die, Taruruuto! Roar!
What?!
No! Taru-sama!
Now's my chance!
Explosive Goro!
Explosion!
It huru-rts...
How was it, Taruruuto?
This guy's completely ignoring the rules.
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama! Hang on, Taru-sama!
Yeah...
Me fine.
Do you see now?
Mimora-chan, my sweat is stunningly beautiful!
Can you see it?
Rival...
Yes?
You... You're...
disgusting!
Teacher!
Mimora-chan said she hates me!
Of course she did!
If you use magic, it's the only outcome.
You need to play honestly
and tenaciously, without magic.
If you do that...
If I do that...
Rival-sama!
Rival🖤Mimora
Mimora-chan...
Will definitely love me!
Teacher! I, Rival, solemnly vow to fight honestly and tenaciously, without magic, starting now!
Alright!
That's the spirit, Rival!
Go there and fight like a man!
Okay!
Mimora-chan, I won't be using any more magic.
Just you watch.
Harako Tsutomu's
Atomic Thunder Serve!
Taru!
Honmaru!
Nice! Good position! There!
Not so fast!
I'll show you what Mari-sensei
taught me every day!
Give me a good toss, Harako!
My deadly...
Ri...?
Special Atomic...
Thunder...
Punch!
I'll catch the ball that Honmaru received!
Taru!
Nice, Taru!
Be sure to pass it to me, Rival!
Taru, it's coming!
Okay!
It's my chance! Die, Taruruuto!
Watch out!
Thank you! Honmaru!
Okay!
Attack!
Didn't I tell you to pass it to me?!
Shut up!
This is a duel between me and Taru!
So what of that?!
I must absolutely hit the next one!
Shut up!
Here!
Alright, Taru!
There!
Yeah!
It's mine! Give it to me!
It's mine!
Taru!
Okay! Honmaru!
Good!
There!
Leave this one to me!
Never!
It's mine!
Go die in a ditch!
Atomic Kick
You! Out of my way!
Silence!
I'll hit!
You bastard...
On you, Honmaru!
Alright! Ready, Taru!
Piss off, Rival!
In your dream!
We'll get more points if I hit!
Attack!
Beautiful sweat scattering...
Eyes sparkling bright!
Radiating the heat of his heart,
the man's back!
That's right!
This is what makes
a girl's heart throb violently!
Game set!
With 15 to 13 points,
B-team, Rival-Harako team wins!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru-kun...
I did it! I won!
When you're teamed up with me, the World Junior Beach Volleyball Champion, losing is not an option.
It was a good match.
It was wonderful!
Honmaru-kun, Taru-chan,
Rival-kun, and Harako-kun too.
Rival and Harako also worked pretty hard, didn't they?
Very much so, Jabao-san.
Well done, Rival-kun.
You did wonderfully.
Mimora-chan!
I won without using magic!
You've seen it, didn't you?
It was wonderful!
I got to witness the glowing sweat of men!
Mimora-chan! You finally understand, Mimora-chan?
I was moved deeply!
Thank you, Mimora-chan!
You're the best!
Thank you!
Mimora-chan...
My wonderful boy!
Slip
Huh?
Taru-sama, I finally realized! There's only the manly friendship between you and Honmaru-sama!
Yeah!
Oh my, I'm embarrassed.
Really! You two were so cool!
Yeah...
Teacher!
Why... Why?!
Did I err?
Shit! Shit!
Teacher, you really are one big disappointment!
I'm going to run.
Even covered in bruises, with a growling stomach,
drowsy from exhaustion...
Why do I want to run?
I believe in the path on the other side.
Honmaru, you really just wanna look good before Iyona!
Bull's eye!
That's why I can't afford losing to Harako!
Yeah!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Mad Marathon.
Episode 66
Mad Marathon
Honmaru, will your belly hold out?
No way, it hurts!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) &
Translation checking by Aurelius