Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru-sama! Taru-sama...
Taru-sama, I appreciate that you invited me
to come with you.
Yeah! Mimora like mountains too?
Me love mountains!
If it lets me spend time with Taru-sama like this,
I absolutely
lo-AUGHHHHHHH-ve mountain climbing!
So refreshing!
Right, Iyona-chan?
You're right. The air is so clean.
Really, it feels good to be one with nature.
I'm glad we've come, Korekiyo.
Rightly so, Jabao-san.
Yahoo!
Interesting!
Anything you say bounces back at you!
That's called a mountain echo.
Mountain Echo must be awfully busy all the time!
So admirable.
You know, Taru-chan, what we call a mountain echo...
It's when you make a sound here,
and then it bounces off the mountains back at you.
In other words, Mountain Echo-san
doesn't need to answer to every single sound.
Hey! Mountain Echo, answer me!
See? Taru's voice returned.
Mountain Echo's an idiot!
Answer me if you disagree!
I'm not an idiot!
See? He's right there.
It's only natural.
Episode 54
Friends with Mountain Echo
Hey, everyone! For how much longer will we have to go?
It's almost lunchtime!
Huh?
Oh? It's lunch time already?
Oh! Honmaru, we're eating bento?
Yeah, let's do just that.
Hey-hey-hey, do you suggest we eat
in the middle of this road?
Bear with it for a little longer.
Yay! Bento, bento!
Everyone, if we walk for a little longer,
we'll arrive to a beautiful lake.
Let's have lunch there.
Yay! Bento! Bento! Bento!
Hey-hey-hey, yo-yo-yo.
If that's where we're having it, let's hurry up!
That's right, let's hurry up.
Yay! Bento! Bento!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
...Bento! By the lake!
Me and Honmaru are having a bento! We'll eat a ben...
Taru-sama, this is highly improper of you.
Wonderful!
Isn't it?
Taru-sama!
Now, what about that meal...?
Let's eat already!
Taru-sama, is something wrong?
Lake looks sad.
Taru! Come eat bento with us!
Bento!
Taru-sama, you're such a...
Now that's luxurious!
Thanks for the meal!
I hope everyone finds it to their taste.
Iyona-chan, it's absolutely delicious!
Honmaru, Honmaru!
Actually,
I made them.
Ah, is that so?
Well, then, I wonder what Iyona-chan's taste like.
Listen, you! What the hell do you mean by that?
Taru-sama, please try the bento I made too.
Taru-sama?
Taru-sama!
It was delicious, Iyona!
You goddamn bet it was!
Why the hell did you gobble it all up?!
What are we supposed to do now?!
It's alright. Look, I got more of it here.
Would've been better if you said so earlier!
Taru-sama.
Taru-sama, you wouldn't give my bento
so much as a glance!
Why...
Why?!
Mimora...
That was the final straw!
Huh? What happened to Taruruuto?
Mimora-chan, where's Taruruuto?
Who?
I'm sure Mimora-chan got mad
and sent him away!
So even you can't stand Taruruuto sometimes, Mimora-chan?
By my word, I will never forgive Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan, if you don't mind,
could you please share with us the bento you made?
Let's eat it together.
Sure! Most certainly.
Ouch-ouch-ouch. Mimora suddenly goes mad,
me don't understand why.
You, what are you doing?
You!
Me?
I'm not an idiot!
You were making a fool of me earlier!
Me was making a fool of you?
Making a fool! Making a fool! Making a fool!
That guy is amazing!
Me join you too!
Mosesu-su-su!
Yay! He's gathering empty cans!
A good guy. I like that guy!
Mimora-chan.
For how long do you plan to hide Taru-chan from us?
Don't you think it'd be better for him to show up soon?
That's a good point.
But for sure, you do seem to eat a lot.
My body is still growing, that's all!
Um, I think, I'll go with Mimora-chan and look for Taru.
Then, I'll join you too.
No way!
No, I mean... There's no need, you can just wait here.
Now, Mimora-chan...
No, I said! I'm still not done with my meal...
Quick!
Mimora-chan, how far did you send Taru flying?
I haven't finished eating yet.
But if we don't find him soon,
everyone will get suspicious!
That reminds me.
Perhaps, it's about time I forgave him?
Please do it in an inconspicuous way.
That, I understand.
Taru-sama!
I missed you so much!
Here, Taru-sama, say "aah."
They've made up that soon?
Honmaru-kun, here, say "aah."
I wish Iyona-chan would do something like that for me too...
Impossible.
With this idiot in the way, there's not a chance of it happening.
It'd sure be nice if he disappeared off somewhere!
What is it, Honmaru?
Is there something on my face?
No, nothing.
Alright, then.
You're a weird fella.
Ah, boy am I thirsty!
Ah, time to empty one more.
Boy, the juice you drink in the mountains is the best!
It was tasty!
Ah! Jabao threw away a can.
Threw away!
What was that?
You got a problem with me?
I said this because I do have a problem with you!
She's telling you not to litter in the nature.
I'm not buying that childish crap!
That's what everyone else does!
Who did that?! It hurts!
You can't throw away empty cans here!
You again!
What the hell are you?
Are you...!
What's your problem, you ass?!
What's your problem, you ass!
You ass!
Stop mimicking me!
Stop mimicking me...!
Mimicking me!
Me - Taruruuto!
Nice to meet you, I'm Mimora!
Hey! I'm Mountain Echo Taro.
Taro! Taro!
So you're the mountain echo who said "I'm not an idiot?"
I'm not an idiot!
You're idiots!
What did you say? I'm not an idiot!
Well, Honmaru being an idiot is a confirmed fact.
But you were mistaken on my account.
Same for me.
No I wasn't! You're all idiots!
Throwing cans away!
I didn't throw away a thing!
That guy is the one who did!
What? You also littered here earlier!
That's right. I've seen it too.
What the hell? When did I...
We're sorry.
We'll take our litter home, so forgive us, okay?
We have no business apologizing to him!
We're not the only ones who come here
to litter away!
You idiots!
Get back here!
Yahoo
Iyona-chan got turned into a crystal ball!
Interesting!
Taru-sama, this must be voice magic.
Impressive, Mountain Echo Taro!
Return them to normal!
Iyona-chan apologized, didn't she?
Don't care. Not listening to what idiots say.
You prick...
Mountain Echo Taro, amazing!
Amazing indeed.
Stop admiring him! Do something about him!
Yeah! Mountain Echo Taro used voice magic.
I can use voice magic too!
Wa
You showed him!
Yay! Showed him!
Showed him!
Wa
Taru!
About time I dealt with you as well!
Yahoo
What now, you can just dodge it?
Taru! Help me!
It'll chase you forever!
Such a nice weather.
Right, I get it now!
Your weakness is this!
There!
No-no-no-no, stop it please!
If you want me to stop,
return everyone back to normal.
Never...
What?
Then, how about now?
Honmaru!
Taru, Mimora-chan?
Honmaru, stop the bullying.
Me like Mountain Echo Taro!
Mountain Echo Taro can't stand the sound of empty cans.
Me get rid of empty cans -
become friends with Mountain Echo Taro!
Friends?
Yeah!
You... I sent you flying, you not mad at me?
No.
You good guy!
Hey, there! You're getting a little too close, you two!
Really, Taru-sama!
Litter of the mountain!
Was there really this much litter,
even on a mountain that looked so clean?
Amazing!
But Taru, how do you intend to bring it with us?
It's fine, I'm the Great Magician.
I'll use Sword-Pen Magic-kun.
Return to the city!
Thanks for your trouble.
I'll return everyone back to normal.
Thank god!
But I was wondering if I could ask for one more favor...
What is it? Speak your wish.
Thing is, it's about...
I wonder what just happened to all of us.
I still feel some emptiness in my head.
It was just a dream. A dream. You were seeing a dream.
Were we really?
Honmaru-kun?
Huh? Where's Taru and Mimora-chan?
Ah, right. They returned home already.
Ah! A giant monster!
I do like me a trip to civilization every now and then!
Aren't you glad, Mountain Echo Taro?
Yes.
Ah! Taru-sama, the ten minutes are almost up!
I forgot!
I forgot...
Honmaru? Honmaru, what happened?
Ah, Taru.
I wanna take Iyona-chan out on a date in the park,
amidst the falling leaves!
Honmaru always so troublesome.
Alright, I'll help in any way I can!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Date on an Autumn Day.
Now, Honmaru, let's head to the park!
Episode 55
Date on an Autumn Day
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius