Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama! Wait for me!
I love you.
Why am I seeing those ridiculous
bullshit dreams again?
As long as Mimora-chan stays in the human world,
I'll keep seeing these dreams over and over again!
Taruruuto, you jerk! Once again, you're the only one
getting to taste the best parts of life!
Unforgivable!
Unforgivable, Taruruuto!
Episode 35
Takoyakinfection to Conquer the World
Honmaru.
I wanna eat takoyaki.
Ain't happening.
My allowance for this month is long spent.
Besides, you just had your mid-afternoon snack, dincha?
Ah... Japan's best takoyaki from Matsu-san...
I wanna eat takoyaki, you hear?!
Takoyaki!
Suppa-yum!
Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Oh, give me tako-yaki, tu-tturu-ru-ru.
I wanna eat takoyaki!
Hey, Taru, what was that over-the-top solo performance?
Um, takoyaki...
Taru-sama, is takoyaki the foodstuff of your craving?
Oh? Mimora, you know how to make it?
What I know about takoyaki...
It has this very spherical shape...
Wow! Mimora so knowledgeable.
Then comes the sauce, green seaweed,
and chips of dried bonito on the top!
Yeah, yeah!
And then, you put an octopus inside!
Oh?
With an octopus inside!
I think, takoyaki...
IS THE MOST DISGUSTING!
How come you didn't know that?
Didn't know...
For me, the very thought of takoyaki is hair-raising!
I know, Taru!
Why doncha try to make something with your own magic?
You're the Great Magician, after all!
Yeah! Honmaru smart in the head.
Me the Great Magician!
Hm... A method to get full on Matsu-san's takoyaki...
Taru?
Don't fall asleep!
You're supposed to produce a ton of takoyaki now!
Ah, you right...
These are your own words:
I suddenly have this irresistible craving for takoyaki!
Yeah!
When in doubt, ask Tama-chan for advice.
Tama-chan, howdy?
I'm doing well, Taru-chan!
Please teach me the magic to get full on Matsu-san's takoyaki!
You'll have to think about it on your own!
I thought about it, but I can't understand.
Please tell me, Tama-chan!
Just think about it yourself, will you?
Ta... Tama-chan, you're also especially
bright and shiny today. You're beautiful!
My...
Look, you're sparkling! Rub... Rub-rub-rub.
Oh... You... You think so?
Yeah!
Hm... So let me get this straight:
you want to eat a lot of Matsu-san's takoyaki?
Yeah!
Then, the Takoyakinfection magic should do.
It's described on page 35
of Mimora-chan's Magic Book.
Great!
Thanks a lot, Tama-chan!
Mimora, lend me that Magic Book of yours!
I refuse. I can't stomach seeing that darn takoyaki.
Oh, then we can simply eat it somewhere
where you can't see us. So, is that fine by you?
I refuse.
Mimora...
Can I have it, please?
Mimora!
Rub, rub, rub.
But... well...
Taru-sama, it's at your disposal!
Find anything, Taru?
Alright! Honmaru, we're going on a foray for ingredients.
Yeah!
First - Matsu-san's Takoyaki.
Matsu-san!
Oh! Ain't that Honmaru and Taru in flesh?
Aye, business goin'?
Not at all, got in a slump.
Needja to donate one takoyaki
for it to be top-knotch again.
Just one to make it good?
Aight, here comes your top-knotch!
Matsu-san, much obliged!
What's next?
A lizard's tail!
Lizard's... tail?
Alright, let's get that, Taru!
Matsu-san, thank you!
Next - freshly squeezed breast milk.
I beg your pardon...
Next - miracle-working water of Mt. Fuji.
Looks done to me.
Ah!
We're in trouble, Honmaru!
I forgot the final ingredient!
Eh? What is it?
Must be really unobtainable, isn't it, Taru?
Tears of a kind-hearted woman.
Is this unobtainable?
That's difficult for sure.
First of all, we need a kind-hearted woman that'd fit...
And then we need to find a way to make her cry.
Honmaru, I'll ask Mimora for a bit of cooperu-ru-ruiton.
Guess we'll have to approach Iyona-chan, after all...
You'll make Mimora-chan cry?
Wait, Taru!
Wa-wa-wait a minute!
Hey! Wait! Wait, I said!
There's gotta be a better way to this!
Ah! Hey, Honmaru, Taru-chan!
My, that smells good! Are you two cooking something?
Yeah! All Matsu-san's takoyaki we'll ever need!
Oh, is that so? I hope you manage to handle it well.
That's it, Taru!
That's how we'll get mom to cry!
Mom! We need you to chop up this onion!
Honmaru, good thinking.
We got mama's tears out with an onion.
Heh! With this, it should be ready now!
Yeah! Now, just to cast a spell.
It worked! It worked!
They're multiplying! It's amazing!
Let's try it!
Yeah.
Yummy!
They totally taste like Matsu-san's!
Just what are those children really up to?
I think they said something about making takoyaki today.
I swear, those two manage to be rowdy in anything they do.
I'm chock-full already.
I'm chock-full too...
That went awfully well, Taru!
Yeah!
Takoyaki are overflowing the room, Taru!
I can gobble more yet!
Taru! Do something to stop it!
First time I used that magic.
Don't know a way to stop it yet.
What?!
Oh?
Eh?! Takoyaki!
The hell?
What are those children doing, really?
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Takoyaki are flooding the Greater Tokyo area!
The Self-Defense Forces are being dispatched as we speak,
and the dangerous rescue mission is underway!
This critical situation
seems to only deteriorate furthermore!
What do we do, Taru?!
Me gobbling as hard as I can!
Huh?
Oh, that's right! Your magic wears off safely after ten minutes!
Yeah!
Honmaru.
Dad...
It's lunchtime.
You can't be playing forever!
Got it!
Huh?
Oh? What could these things be?
Tako-tako yaki-yaki! Tako-tako yaki-yaki!
Wow! Takoyaki are talking!
Ain't they cute?
Yeah. So cute I wanna eat them.
Thanks for the meal!
Whoa there! Taru!
Wait a minute! This guy is a living being!
You'd eat that?
You're right. Because he's alive, I'll ask him.
Can I eat you?
Eat, eat! I'm the mouthwatering Yaki-san, after all!
He said I can eat him.
But still, Taru...
Let's eat!
What's going on, Taru?
Taru!
Yummy! So yummy, Honmaru! Insanely yummy!
Is it really that good?
The best ever!
You don't mind me eating you, either?
Eat! Eat!
Me is a Tako-chan, pleasant to the mouth!
Oh, is that so? Maybe I should take a bite, after all...
Let's eat!
Amazing!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Soooo amazing!
It's amazing, Taru!
It's at least 30 times better than Matsu-san's takoyaki!
It's that yummy!
Yummy, yummy!
That yummy!
Yaki-yaki!
Yaki!
Tako-chan!
Tako!
Tako-tako, yaki-yaki!
Eh! Tako-tako!
You've become a takoyaki yourself!
Yaki-yaki!
Honmaru, you too.
Tako! Tako... Tako!
Tako! Tako!
What do we do now, Taruruuto?
Yay!
I became takoyaki!
What are you so happy about?
Hurry up and make us normal again!
Okay!
Me don't know how to make normal.
Tako!
I wouldn't have eaten it if I knew it'd make me like this.
But it was so yummy!
Tako!
Mimora-chan's Magic Book
might have something about this!
Yaki!
Hm. The children sure are taking their time.
That's true. I wonder what happened.
Tako! Tako-tako!
Yaki!
Mimora-chan, we need help!
Help us become normal again!
No!
Takoyaki are talking!
Tako! Tako!
What the hell is going on?
No!
Papa-sama! Help me!
You two! What the hell are you?
Tako! Tako!
It's me, dad!
I am Taru.
I've no time for hoity-toity monsters messing with me!
What's all that "tako-tako" bullshit?
Yaki-yaki!
That's strange!
Seems like the words we say don't get across to them!
What do we do, Honmaru?
Tako! Tako! Tako!
You're goddamn noisy!
I swear by my name of Edojo Shogunosuke
to deliver judgment upon you!
Eh? Tako-tako!
Stop, you monsters!
By Lord, we're the ones most boisterous here!
Tako! Tako! Tako! Tako!
Yaki! Yaki! Yaki!
Tako-tako! Tako!
Tako! Tako! Tako! Tako!
Yaki! Yaki! Yaki!
What's that?
What's unclear here? Those are some monsters.
Come to think of it, they were probably the one
behind the whole takoyaki panic earlier today!
That must be so!
I ain't letting that crap slide!
Taru, do something about it!
Racing is fun!
Tako!
Get 'em!
Stop, you monsters!
Ah! We've run into a dead end!
It's fine, I'll cast a spell for slipping though things.
Incorpore-re-real!
My magic won't listen.
Taru...
The monsters are cornered!
Tako! Tako!
Stop, please!
Such destructive force in this hand!
You did it, Honmaru!
Yaki-yaki!
Tako-tako!
Taru, we need to break through the enemy lines!
Yeah!
Tako-tako!
Yaki!
Too weak! I can see your movements from a mile away!
Shogun Punch!
Hey, Taru!
Look at what we've become now!
You did it!
Serves them right!
Taruruuto, you fool!
Once the Takoyakinfection was dispelled, I caught you off-guard spectacularly with the Takotakoyakiyaki Curse!
Now then, time for the finishing touches!
Starvation Ray!
I'm straight-up starving all of a sudden!
Why don't we slake it with those takoyaki?
They sure look appetizing.
It's probably alright.
When I'm that hungry,
I don't need you to tell me if it's alright or not!
Will we end up just being gobbled up?
But everyone says we look delicious!
I'm a bit flattered.
They're not kidding!
Soon, Taruruuto will be dealt with,
making Mimora-chan mine! All mine!
Rival...
Ria-san...
I want you to leave them alone at that.
My perfect chance...
For a child's prank, this is going too far.
Okay! I'll revert it to normal this instant!
Thanks for the meal!
Uwah! I'm about to get eaten!
Ri—
Honmaru? Taru?
Eh? Where's takoyaki?
So you were those takoyaki monsters all along?
I apologize to both of you, Honmaru and Taru.
Dad!
Papa...
Whatever you do, getting full on mere snacks
before dining properly is a no-go, Honmaru.
Okay! We get it, dad!
Mama's cooking tasty.
My, thank you, Taru-chan.
Taru-sama, this is the actual food
you can put your trust in.
You taste the food well while eating.
That makes the food happy as well.
Yeah! You eat it with gratitude.
That's right.
A refill, please.
Sure!
Refill!
My! Sure, sure!
I've not given up, Taruruuto!
Oh! Ah! It's good to be a girl!
For someone like Ijigawa, it's enough
to break into tears to gain everyone's sympathy!
In turn,
a man's life is the one full of hardships!
Okay, Honmaru, use this!
Magical Taruruuto-kun: I'm a Man, Ijigawa Rui!
Episode 36
I'm a Man, Ijigawa Rui
I'll have my fun now, Ijigawa!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius