Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
There!
To me!
Episode 71
Fresh Otoko
If I don't run, I'll be late again!
Honmaru, I'm faster than you!
Magical Ostrich Ru-ru-run!
Oh? But I won't lose!
Edojo-kun, let's duel and see who can pass through the school gate first!
I know I've won already!
What?! I don't know who you are,
but I ain't losing, dammit!
Me won't lose either!
Hey, Honmaru, and you, the other one!
The victory is mine, alright?
Dammit, Taru!
Dammit!
Hey, Taru!
Pain, fly away!
Taru, are you okay?
I'm al—
pig!
I won this duel, oink-oink-oink!
Wait, Taru!
Alright!
I ain't gonna lose!
That's what I'm supposed to say!
Dammit...
Alright...
Honmaru's victory!
I lost?!
Still, you were amazing,
Edojo Honmaru-kun of Class 1.
No wonder you beat Zakenja Nezo
from Class 2 so wonderfully.
It was a good duel.
Yeah...
He was so discouraged just a moment ago,
and now he's suddenly so fresh...!
Who the hell are you?
Handshake, handshake, handshake!
Honmaru-kun, good morning.
Ah! Good morning, Iyona-chan.
Otoko-san!
Hey! Iyona-chan, good morning.
So that's what your name is - Otoko?
You're always so energetic.
You're attending Class 3 now, right?
Yeah.
What the hell, Iyona-chan?!
Acting so familiar with him...!
Honmaru! We can have rub-rub too! There...
Moreover, Iyona-chan just called him
"Otoko-san." "San", goddammit!
Even I only get a "Honmaru-kun" from her!
But this guy deserves a full "San"?!
Could it be that Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, what's the matter?
At least pretend to listen
when I'm talking to you!
Otoko-san!
Good morning, Otoko-san!
Yo, sup.
Let's hurry up and leave our bags in class
so we can go play some games!
Otoko, come sooner!
This guy...
He's super popular with the girls from Class 3.
Iyona-chan, how exactly do you know Otoko?
Well, during the third and fourth years,
we went to the same class.
Is something wrong, Honmaru-kun?
I see!
So you just were classmates once?
That's all?
I see!
This nitwit Honmaru is suspecting some chemistry
between Iyona-chan and Otoko-san?
Even so, ain't Otoko trying to be too fresh and cool?
I really love Otoko-san.
What?
Iyona just said she loves Otoko?
Me love Otoko too! My type!
I quite love them too!
Right, Iyona-chan?
Because Honmaru doesn't know a thing about it,
he's in complete shock! What a dunce!
Hey, Otoko, let's start playing soon! There!
Oh, Teacher?
Teacher, good morning.
Yes, good morning.
Isn't Class 3 lucky?
Waseda-sensei is playing with them all the time.
Iyona, Class 1 has me to play with.
Had Iyona-chan actually been dating Otoko for a while already...?
That's right! That's why he
challenged me to a duel today!
Oh, Kawai, Edojo, Taruruuto! Good morning.
Good morning to you as well!
Otoko, who's dating Iyona-chan, doesn't see me as anything more than a nuisance!
Edojo!
This bastard Otoko...
He challenged me so as to sever me
from his girlfriend, Iyona-chan!
So that's how it is?!
Teacher, using this should help.
What a wicked bastard!
Good morning!
Good morning!!
Good... morning...
Damn, you startled me!
They're laughing at me! The class 3 bastards!
Iyona-chan and Taru too! Even Ijigawa!
And Otoko!
Shit! No way in hell I'll lose to someone like you!
I don't care if you're the one dating Iyona-chan now,
I'll do my damnest to take Iyona-chan back!
What was the point of all these hardships, even?!
You jerk!
Alright...
Otoko, I'll give you a duel you want!
I accept it!
I won't lose!
I see. Honmaru partaking too?
What do you mean?
What else?
A milk drinking competition, of course!
I'm quite certain I've heard you saying
"I won't lose" just now, yessir.
Having learned what you signed up for,
do you wish to chicken out already, Honmaru?
What? It was time for lunch already?
Honmaru spent whole morning thinking hard.
Iyona-chan is watching.
Fine! I'll show her my cool side!
Now, Jabao, Harako!
I'll show you two that you're no match for me!
Way to go, Honmaru!
Alright.
Prepare to behold the strength of Harako Tsutomu-sama, the World Junior Speedy Milk Drinking Champion.
You won't be able to beat me,
not in your life, Honmaru!
Ready...
Go!
Stop!
5.23 seconds!
What?!
The victory is mine this time, Honmaru-kun.
Otoko? Why are you here?
Well, that was really one legendary match.
Thanks, everyone!
See you!
That little...
So fresh!
Isn't Otoko-san cool?
Ah... So dreamy!
Hey, hey, introduce us next time, okay?
How can one even be so popular with girls?!
Harako!
How come even you swallowed it?!
Say something at least!
I can't compete with Otoko.
Hey, Iyona-chan.
Isn't Otoko-san really nice and wonderful?
That's right, wonderful.
What?!
So I was thinking this...
If Iyona-chan wore her wedding dress,
and Otoko-san donned a tuxedo...
Wouldn't you two look as a great pair together?
Oh no!
Rui-chan, what are you saying?
Iyona-chan's beaming with joy
just thinking about it...
This is a disaster!
As soon as I swore to never lose to Otoko in anything,
I'm suddenly losing to him, even in milk drinking contests!
At this rate, Otoko will keep
imposing his pace upon me!
For some reason I can't get even close
to winning Iyona-chan over!
Honmaru, you won't lose!
I'll give you special training!
That's it! All I need to beat him
is special training!
Alright! Let's do it, Taru!
Yeah!
What's going on with Honmaru-kun?
He's acting somewhat strange today.
Just leave him alone, Iyona-chan!
Please, Niruru!
Niruru, take a good look.
Alright!
Special training for the milk drinking contest!
Let's drink!
Do your best, Honmaru!
Drink it up, Honmaru!
Honmaru, you can do it!
I can deal with him easily now!
I'll beat Otoko!
Honmaru can't beat Otoko.
Why is that, even after such a
strenuous special training?!
Honmaru can drink faster.
But Otoko would look fresh.
And Honmaru would look lame.
Otoko's victory.
It can't be!
What was this training for, then?!
It's just as Taru said.
His greatest weapon is his freshness!
To counter that freshness...
I know!
I just need to become fresh too!
Taru, isn't there some good magic
that'd make me a fresh man?
Fresh...
Yeah!
Pointurner that I borrowed from Mimora!
Shiny-shiny beautiful eyes!
Only the eyes?
Hm! I do feel fresher somehow, though!
No!
Honmaru pervert.
No magic can make Honmaru fresh.
But hey, Taru, I'm not the only lewd guy around!
Most men are.
Wait, though...
That guy Otoko is a man, just like me!
I won't believe there exists a man in this world
so perfectly fresh and cool as Otoko!
Alright. I'll become a girl myself
and expose this bastard Otoko for what he really is!
And when I do, Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan, help!
I was wrong on your account, Otoko-san!
Honmaru-kun is miles nicer than you!
Iyona-chan...
Taru, gimme Hormonger!
Okay!
Drink, Honmaru.
Yeah!
Refreshing!
Let's go, shall we?
Here he comes, Taru.
Please bring Iyona-chan
to the venue we've agreed upon.
Okay.
Later!
Otoko-san.
It's you! Marue-chan, right?
How do you know me?
You played in that volleyball match back in the day.
That was one truly spectacular match!
See? Just as I thought,
he's already trying to pick me up.
Iyona... huh?
Iyona not here.
I can read your thoughts like an open book.
You'll try to make a move on me as soon as we're alone!
In the end, my judgment was entirely correct.
Marue-chan!
There it comes!
Your true nature is showing through, Otoko!
Now's the time, Taru!
Hurry up and bring Iyona-chan here!
Iyona!
I also love sports, so I think you
and I would get along really well.
Get along, you say?
I'll never hang out with someone like you!
I'm sure the two of us will become great friends.
Come on, Taru! What's taking you so long?
Hey, next time, how about we do sports together?
What's wrong, Marue-chan?
You've gotta be kidding me!
I may have a woman's body, but I'm still a man!
If I get kissed or something, I'll throw up!
Oh!
If it isn't the pretty gal I met one day?
I...
Very well. I will gladly listen to your confession.
Um...
Don't get in my way, you prick!
Your smile - dazzling whenever I look at it.
There's no need to be shy.
Harako-kun, what are you doing to Marue-chan?
Otoko,
if you keep being too nosy,
you'll end up in trouble.
Alright. If you say so,
I'll accept the risk.
Are you out of your mind, Otoko? Harako is a World Junior Champion of all and every martial art!
He's even ready to face him
just to defend me?
What's gotten into me?
I guess I lost, Otoko.
What? Harako resigned before even trying?
Is Otoko really that insanely strong?
Ah, this is bad!
Looks like you're injured.
Well, let's go, Marue-chan.
Nurse's office
There, you'll be fine now, Marue-chan.
Thank you.
Marue-chan.
Stop it, Otoko!
See you, Marue-chan. Take care!
Otoko...
Honmaru.
Sorry. Couldn't find Iyona.
Forget it.
What do you mean, Honmaru?
Honmaru crying?
Taru, it's no wonder
Iyona-chan fell in love with that guy.
Otoko really is the nicest guy ever!
And yet, all I've done
was being unreasonably suspicious of him,
going as far as becoming a woman
to estrange him from Iyona-chan!
What an idiot I am!
Honmaru don't cry!
When Honmaru cries, me sad too!
Iyona-chan would definitely
be happier with a man like him!
Honmaru, cheer up. Iyona only loves Honmaru.
That's what I believe!
There's no need already, Taru...
Let's go, Honmaru!
We'll find Iyona and make sure!
Taru!
Found Iyona!
They look so happy, walking side by side.
What?!
Women's restroom
Otoko, you hack!
He entered the women's restroom with Iyona-chan!
What is he scheming?
I thought better of you, you sick bastard!
How far are you willing to take it with Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan, stay away from that man!
How cruel of you to slap me, Iyona-chan!
Did you go cuckoo these days, Honmaru?
Honmaru?
Honmaru, in ten minutes magic wore off.
Honmaru-kun, you're the worst!
This is the girls' restroom!
Why are you alright with Otoko being here,
but I'm suddenly the worst, Iyona-chan?!
No matter how close you two are,
you can't be that partial towards him!
But... But Otoko-san is a girl!
What?!
Surname's Otoko, and name's Onna.
That said, I'm still a girl, though.
A... girl...
I see. Edojo mistook Otoko for an actual boy?
What's more, he was jealous because Otoko-san and Iyona-chan are on such good terms!
What a cretin!
Is it true you've been jealous, Honmaru-kun?
No, I wouldn't say...
Really, the reason Harako didn't fight Otoko
was because she's a girl!
Sensei, as their homeroom teacher,
please see to it that the girls in your class look girly!
What's wrong with it, Edojo?
Why should we force anyone to look girly?
That's right, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru! Why dontcha be the change you wanna see
and start becoming manlier yourself?
"So cruel, Iyona-chan."
Who was it yelling like that just now? Hearing that almost made me vomit!
Come to think of it, Honmaru-kun...
That was a joke. Just a joke, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun, let's do our best
from now on as well.
Yeah...
Me also like Otoko very much!
Please shake my hand too!
My regards, Taruru.
Oh! So fresh!
I can freshen you up too!
Otoko Onna, you jerk!
Despite being a woman,
you're cooler and fresher than me, a man!
So frustrating!
In life, there are ups and downs.
But at times, you also have to get involved
in a once-in-a-lifetime grand showdown.
However. However...
Why does my life consist
of nothing but such showdowns?!
Also, that Otoko—what's her deal now?!
Let me think...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Duel with Otoko!
Episode 72
Isn't Matsu-san's takoyaki delicious?
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius