Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 85
Ijigawa's Sibling Duty
You lost this one.
Please wait just a moment...
I've been waiting for 18 minutes already.
If I move to here, my rook...
Where can it walk?
Just go ahead and admit defeat with grace.
Think of it—saying "Ijigawa Rui-sama
is beautiful" 100 times isn't that hard.
You gotta stick to the promises you made, remember?
Losing to this kind of person is a disgrace
for any Great Magician. Really, what do I...
Sis, sis!
Give me some pocket money!
I was gonna go buy burgers with my friends.
What am I hearing, Bui? For the last
time, it's not "sis." It's "Dear Big Sister!"
Dear Big Sister, Dear Big Sister, Dear Big Sister!
See? I said it.
Give me pocket money.
My favorite overcoat!
Don't touch me with your dirty hands! Jeez...
Because you're so boorish, it's stained now!
Why get so snappy over that?
Just wash it and it'll be alright!
Ah! Come to think of it, Bui, give back
my stereo headphones I lent you the other day.
I... lent it to a friend.
Hold it, Bui. What are you hiding there? Let me see!
It's broken... You cretin!
I'll never lend anything to you again!
Suit yourself!
I'll never ask you to lend me anything again!
Just give me the pocket money already!
Think I'll give you any in your lifetime?
Stingy and ugly! Vulgar broad!
What are you saying to your beautiful sister?!
Get away from me, I said!
Crap, just as I already won!
Oh my, just as I came up with a
comeback plan that'd bring me the victory...
Such a shame!
Saved by the bell.
This is also your fault!
You started this by not giving me my pocket money!
I'm home.
Mama!
You fought again?
It's Rui!
Rui, you're the older sister, remember?
Why'd you bring your little brother to tears?
But it was Bui who broke my headphones!
You should bear with it.
You're the older sister, after all!
Jeez... I don't need no little brother!
In any conflict, the parents take his side!
At times like this,
I wish I had a nice big brother.
He'd comfort me and look after me.
If I had a choice, I'd wish for a kind big brother,
looking cool just like this.
Why are you just sitting there, gaping?
I just thought...
That's it!
Hey, Mimora-chan.
What is it?
You don't happen to know some magic
for getting a wonderful big brother?
Oh? Just as I thought. You don't know it, do you?
Even if Mimora-chan calls herself a magician,
she's still a baby. There's no way she could wield such magic.
But I know such magic!
Oh? I wonder if we could ever find out if it's true.
Look at this...
And... It's this!
It's called Spudibling.
People who eat this spud together become siblings!
Rui-chan, with this, you can
make anyone your beloved big brother.
No way! It just can't be!
You let the person who is to become
your big brother eat a piece first.
Then you eat yours, to become a little sister.
And then, before long, the person you chose
becomes your big brother, to your great joy!
I can hardly believe it...
Why are you still being so distrustful?
Then, how about you try it yourself and see? Here.
Even if you say so, should I really try it?
Fell for it again!
Keeping a magician at home sure is convenient!
Oh? Ryoguchiya's scent...
Korekiyo, bushes!
Ah! As expected of Jabao-san.
I couldn't hide from your well honed
sense of smell that befits a true predator!
Well, well. There's a reason they call me
Nannosho's number one "kick the can" seeker.
There!
What?
You did it, Honmaru!
Taru, let's run!
Okay!
Tsk. What a chump.
Harako's scent...
Jabao needs to train way more to catch us.
Honmaru! Hey, Honmaru!
Want some sweet potato?
It's freshly baked and delicious!
Here.
What happened, Ijigawa?
Since when are you giving me stuff?
It's too big for me to eat it all myself.
Besides, I figured Honmaru must be hungry now,
so I decided to bless you with it just this once.
Tsk. Always have a reply ready, huh?
It really is steaming hot!
We'll get found there.
Here, Taru.
Okay!
Wait, wouldn't Taru prefer this?
Oh, takoyaki?
Ah, this sweet potato is great!
Great takoyaki!
Me don't need sweet potato.
He's eating it!
Dammit, I can't find Taru and Honmaru anywhere!
Where could they be hiding?
I'm hungry.
Let's go home already, Korekiyo.
Good call. Let's do that, then.
I quit!
This game is done!
Oh? Jabao is leaving.
Can't be helped.
Let's go home and play something else now.
Okay, Taru?
Yeah! Go home.
See you, Ijigawa.
The sweet potato was good.
Ah! Wait a moment...
Rui, we're going home!
We're home!
I wonder what's for dinner today.
Dinner today...
The magic worked!
Taru-sama!
Hey, Mimora!
It worked!
Honmaru-sama became Rui-chan's sibling,
so they moved together!
Which means I'll also get
to live with Taru-sama now!
Brother, let's go play soccer!
Sure. Just what you need before dinner.
Here!
Get this!
Bui also calls Honmaru a brother.
I see!
Because Honmaru and I became siblings,
my little brother Bui also became Honmaru's sibling.
Mimora-chan's magic affected Bui as well!
Rui, you wanna play too?
Do it, do it!
Yeah! I'm in, Honmaru!
Did you say "Honmaru"?
That's no way to address your big brother!
I'm sorry.
Then...
B-Big brother.
That's right.
Don't you call me anything else ever again!
Really, now?
He already adopted "big brother" mannerisms.
He's usually so obtuse!
Let's go, Rui.
Okay!
There!
There, big bro!
You're getting quite good at it, Rui!
There!
Okay!
Big brother, huh?
Everyone, come to eat!
Delicious!
Papa isn't coming home to eat tonight.
So help yourselves to papa's portion as well.
Mama is under the spell too!
A beauty...
And a cooking expert!
That's our mom for you!
Why did it feel like you just called me mom
for the first time ever?
Ah, never mind that.
Oh? You ain't eating that?
Don't mind if I do!
You snatched my fried shrimp...
Huh? What is it?
I thought you didn't want it
since you left it behind.
That's because I have a habit of saving the
most delicious part for the end. My fried shrimp...
Ah, sorry for that.
Then, take my potato as compensation.
I don't want your potato!
Give back my fried shrimp...!
Can't you see there's nothing
I can do about it since I ate it already?
Aren't you one bit ashamed
of snatching food from others?
You're a monster!
I hope you get sent straight to hell.
Rui-chan, you shouldn't say things like that.
Honmaru apologized.
You have to forgive him.
That's right, Rui. You need to be respectful when talking to your big brother.
That's right! You're the one at fault here.
But come on, mom!
My fried shrimp...
Show some humility.
You're a little sister, after all.
It was delicious!
What was that?
Everyone says I should just swallow it!
Not fun at all!
Say what you want, it ain't fun at all.
Despite having a big brother,
everything's the same as before!
Smack!
Ouch!
Rui! That was vulgar of you as a girl!
What's your problem, you jerk?
Who taught you to call your big brother a jerk?!
Hmph! Drop that intimidating stance!
I was the one who made you my big brother!
One way or another,
you threw a fit over just a single shrimp!
That was also improper of a woman,
you bow-legged thing!
Your whole personality is utterly twisted!
No sane man would ever want to take you as a wife!
Lecturing me on this and that...
Aren't you supposed to be more condescending,
as befits a big brother?
I'm saying this all for your own sake!
Shut up!
I was an idiot for choosing you as my big brother.
I don't need a big brother that's so nagging!
Honmaru, you cretin!
Hey, where are you going? Rui!
What an unruly little sister!
Little sister?
Little... sister?
Honmaru?
Nothing good came out of
Honmaru becoming my big brother!
That's because the original Honmaru hated me,
and making him my big brother with magic can't change that!
Honmaru and everybody else just hates me!
After all, I threw a fit over just a single shrimp,
so he called me a vulgar woman,
with bowed legs and a twisted personality...
A waste of a woman!
Honmaru, you absolute imbecile!
Honmaru, you idiot...
Hey, little lady!
Wouldn't you like to play with us?
So? Don't you fancy it?
Are you okay? Hey!
You little babies!
You wench...
Get back here!
Whatever. I'm Ijigawa Rui!
Screw your decency!
Screw it!
You stupid brat!
Don't you know it's dangerous?
I don't care what becomes of me!
Everyone would hate me anyway.
No one has a bit of concern for me!
I don't care anymore!
Hey... It's dangerous, little lady.
What I'm doing is none of your business!
Thanks for your concern, though, mister!
Don't complain when you fall down!
Everyone's pretending to care.
They think they know what's better for me.
Everyone is like that!
Taru!
Honmaru.
Not anywhere this way.
Not this way either.
I wonder where she went.
You literally can't get your
eyes off her for a minute!
Okay, we're going to my place next!
I can't find the exit! Give me a break!
Am I going to just die here like this?
Freezing and stinking?
I wish someone would come to save me...
I'm a fool.
Taru, are you sure about that?
Yeah. This - Oh my lost child.
A very useful hard hat.
Honmaru, hurry up and say the spell.
Okay...
Ijigawa Rui,
Oh my God!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to bother you!
And I didn't mean to break into your wall! Now, farewell!
Hold it, Taru! I can't go there!
Dying in a place like this... So lame!
What's that?!
This is no good.
I won't last here for much longer...
Whoever it may be,
hurry up and come save me!
Please!
Hey!
Are you alive? Answer me!
Honmaru!
How did you know I was in a place like that?
Thanks to this. Oh my lost child, Taru's magic item.
You say the name of the lost child and say a prayer,
"Oh my God," and it'll direct you towards the lost person.
Are you okay?
Eh! This is just a scratch! It's nothing!
I'm relieved to know you haven't lost your temper,
but try not to worry me like that anymore.
Sorry,
big brother.
Well then, see you at school tomorrow!
Bye!
Ah? Where are you going? We live here!
My magic wears off in thirty minutes.
Eh? Wears off in thirty minutes?
Then...
Then, he did it...
when the magic of Spudibling
was already long gone.
Well, I'm still a magician in training.
So before long, I'm sure
I could make it last for a whole day or so.
That means, even with the magic dispelled,
the one who cared about me...
Honmaru…
It was you!
Mama! Rui is back!
I was very worried, Rui.
You're so dirty, sister!
Where in the world have you been?
Shut up! Stop questioning me like some street girl.
What's your problem?
Can't you simply tell me where you've been to?
Now, now, hurry up into the bath, both of you.
Okay, mama!
Rui, let's use shampoo
that makes a lot of bubbles!
Just do whatever!
Wassup!
Honmaru, are you already here?
Big brother, it doesn't hurt, does it?
No, it doesn't hurt.
Iyona, once we're done with this,
let's play doctors next.
Honmaru fed to Iyona the Spudibling
he borrowed from Mimora.
Honmaru and Iyona siblings.
Honmaru, you dirty bastard...
In the end, isn't it the best, Taru?
If you want a little sister, having the one
of Iyona's type is the best you could get!
Best you could get!
It tickles. It tickles, dammit!
Iyona-chan, what's this?
Are we playing doctors already?
I'll teach you your sibling duty!
This way now!
My doctor is a little too violent!
I can even stretch like that? I had no idea!
Well, whatever.
Honmaru twisting funny!
Iyona, try to go a little easier on me, won't you...
Now dance...
Scum like you deserve way worse than this!
You're weird, big brother...
Taru, it's been a while since we met, hasn't it?
Yeah.
And I've grown up a lot, haven't I?
You've grown big?
Yes. That's right. I've been
through various special trainings too.
I wonder what things like this are called. Maybe
"personal virtues"? People also started liking me a lot more.
Fine, we'll investigate Honmaru's personal virtues
with Personal Flovirtue-kun.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Special Training with Personal Flovirtue-kun.
Episode 86
Special Training with Personal Flovirtue-kun
Honmaru's Personal Flovirtue-kun is withered.
Hey there, Honmaru here!
Take it easy, please.
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius