Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru and his buddies are mimicking
the boxing match they saw on TV the other day.
They seem pretty earnest about it.
Right... Keep it up, Taru!
Now you're screwed!
Episode 11
Unyielding Boxing
Sorry. Sorry there.
You swine...
Special Prize of the World's Male Models Carnival
and World Beauty Junior Branch Grand Prix winner,
Honorary Dreamboat League Unrivaled President
just had his face brutally scarred!
Did you really hope to get away with it scot-free?
Watch out!
Harako-kun, what's the big idea
behind this sucker punch?
If you allow me to explain.
While I was studying earnestly, sitting here,
this guy boldly attacked my face with a mechanical pencil.
Before I realized,
the juvenile reflex took over.
Is that so, Honmaru-kun?
I always rely on Taru's magic
to rescue me from jams like that.
Should I apologize to cover Taru up just today?
However, getting roughed up before Iyona-chan's eyes,
then toeing Harako's line immediately after...
Gosh, I'm in a predicament!
What's the matter, Honmaru?
Play dumb all you want,
I'm not buying an ounce of it.
Wouldn't that be awfully clichéd to always frame me
as a villain, while you usurp the "good boy" role?
Cut the crap!
I did exactly what I intended to!
Your face has long been
a bone up everyone's throat!
With a bunch of toadies bootlicking you,
of course you've no blithering idea!
Toad...
Where'd you see the toadies?
Hit the sore spot, did I, Harako?
Jabao-san, it seems Honmaru
is now straight-up picking a fight with Harako!
From the outside, it's as though Honmaru is a tough nut.
But for fighting, he's as good as a sandbag.
Stop it, you both!
We're in the middle of class!
For fighting, any other time is just as good!
Actually,
I don't think any time is good for that.
Teacher!
What is it, Ijigawa-san?
Be it even in the middle of the class,
just looking at Harako-kun's face can get anyone nauseated!
What?!
Don't blame me for this constant
"I have the reddest comb in this coop" look on your face!
I am Harako Tsutomu!
I will never condescend to listening to ridicules
from your ilk, the commoners!
Yet you did to hitting me!
That's exactly what nauseates everyone about you!
What did you just...
International kindergarteners' Style Contest
and "The Rosiest Newborn" Grand Prix victor,
unblemished and uncontested
Junior Best Dresser honorable award holder,
I will not tolerate such rubbish on my account!
What do you know about honor
after hitting a girl?
If it itches you to throw fists around,
I'm always up for it!
Jabao-san, look!
Now this smells like some whopping fun.
Such escapade is certain to precipitate a rain of blood.
Come on!
Bring it on if you dare!
You prick!
Why'd you do that?!
What a doofus! You don't know
I'm the World Spitting Contest champion, either!
Jabao-san...
Forget the rain of blood,
it's raining spit now.
Like it, huh?
Huh?
Like it?
I can too!
Taru-chan!
Taruruuto wins!
This damn shrimp again!
Alright, I see it now!
If you wanna fight that bad,
then let's settle it your way...
With boxing!
In the bygone days of Japan's boxing,
five concurrent World Champions emerged from it.
We were in the golden age.
However, the title matches of recent years
suggest nothing but stagnation.
It wouldn't be an exaggeration to say,
no fraction of our former glory can be seen in those.
The time is ripe for you, young cream of the nation,
to remold Japan's boxing with your own hands!
Honmaru-kun, will you?
Of course he will, teacher!
Isn't that so? So? Honmaru-kun?
Yeah...
Damn right!
What about Harako-kun?
Time to show the swine its place once and for all.
Who're you calling a swine,
you Dino-mugged Grandpa?!
Asshole! I'll shove it back
down your bloody throat!
Break!
You'll have your match in one week from now.
See it as a productive way
to diversify your PE class. Deal?
Now this sounds hella lot of fun!
I know, right?
C'est la vie, Honmaru.
Even though you're destined to lose,
I'll still be rooting for you.
I'll do just fine with no rooting from the likes of you!
Ah! How ungrateful!
Honmaru-kun...
Together with Iyona,
roo-rooting for Honmaru!
Taru-chan... But I...
Alright! Iyona-chan rooting for me
is worth a hundred people's rooting!
Why, then, did you give me the brush-off
when I said you can have my cheering?
'Cause I couldn't care less for yours!
He's clueless about me holding the World's
Junior Boxing Champion title for five years straight.
Pesky little imbecile.
Still, though, can never be too sure.
Hi, Mack!
Hi! Tsutomu!
While training in Hawaii, World Heavyweight Champion
Mack Tynso announced a sudden change of plans.
In order to take the position of a personal trainer
for the heir of Harako Conglomerate, Harako Tsutomu,
he had already arrived to Japan.
Very-very good!
You have nice boxing sense!
Thank you, Mack!
Oh, no...
Mr. Tynso seems to be profoundly moved
by Harako-kun's devotion.
He aims to teach his new trainee
all of his own boxing techniques.
Their enthusiasm is on everyone's lips.
Iyona, Harako boxing maven.
I'm told he's the Junior World Champion.
Boxing will not bring anything to conclusion,
but if we talk to him, I'm sure we'll come to terms.
What'll you do, Honmaru?
You can't even defeat Jabao in a fair fight.
Better apologize to Harako sooner.
Wouldn't it be better if the match is called off now?
Shut your trap!
Can't know if I win or lose before I try!
Spare me your nagging!
Don't you know what concern means?
Instead of giving me your concern,
wouldn't you rather wanna butter up Harako with it?
My!
Now I see you don't deserve my concern!
Out we go, Iyona-chan!
Rui-chan...
Iyona, have no worries!
But say,
Iyona-chan, didn't that make you reconsider
taking Honmaru's side?
Still...
Don't let it bother you, Iyona-chan!
Let's say he loses - doesn't mean he'll die.
Honmaru, let me handle this.
I have magic even for the most desperate times.
Honmaru, you got headache?
Dad used to tell me this:
"The candid showdown between the men -
that's what boxing is."
I'll show Iyona-chan
what a man's candid showdown truly means!
And then, with my own power and resolve,
I'm gonna defeat Harako!
Honmaru on fire!
And that's why I have something to ask of you.
That is...
Ask anything you want!
Grant me...
A special magical training!
Taru, can I ask you to not go too hard on me?
Just trust me!
Now, commence special training.
First strength building.
For that, make Honmaru small.
Trunsform!
Then, make Attractor big.
Grow like mushroo-roo-rooms!
With Attractor, I'll ground Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Get up, Honmaru.
Exercise there - grow much stronger.
Easy for you to say,
but the ball's pulling me in as it gets bigger...
Honmaru, no resolve in you.
If only I could...
Huh?
Is it getting warmer here?
HOT!
Honmaru, moving swifter already.
What kind of training is this?
Didn't I ask you not to go too hard on me?
Fine footwork, Honmaru.
Dad!
For special boxing training,
you should let me be the coach.
Honmaru, take this stance.
Wrong! Elbows to torso.
Okay!
Taru, what about his sparring partner?
Flame-kun will do.
Flame-kun?
Ayo!
Need help with anything?
Please become Honmaru's partner.
Ayo! Won't let him slack off!
Taru, gimme just a moment.
With this, Flame-kun
will be much more ardent!
Ayo! I'm fired up!
Honmaru-kun, I'm going in!
That sparring partner sure is one-of-a-kind.
Even minor flaws in your defense
will be burnt into your memory with Flame-kun's punches.
To avoid it, you have to dodge every single one
of Flame-kun's punches like your life depends on it.
Even dad wants to go to such extremes?!
Hey! Don't let go of your fighting pose!
Yeah!
That's it. That is a swayback!
Now try to dodge everything by swinging your torso sideways!
That's it. That is ducking!
Lookin' good, Honmaru!
Flame-kun, don't hold back!
Ayo!
Not going easy on you any longer!
Honmaru, don't give up!
Yeah!
Grow as big as you want,
your clumsy punches are just as easy to dodge!
Now come, Flame-kun!
Honmaru really on fire!
Burned out already...
Just keep doing this every day,
then your footwork and defense would be OK.
But next is punch practice!
Please, no more...
Honmaru! What is that unseemly spinelessness?
Honmaru, don't give up.
If you drink this Power-Upple Juice,
it will give you a power-up!
It really did!
Suddenly, I'm determined again!
Is this...
Use it, Honmaru.
Those gloves are soaked up
in the blood and sweat of my own youth!
Dad!
Great gift, Honmaru!
Taru! As for now, you might think
dad is just a fameless picture book author,
but during his high school years,
he excelled at each and every sort of martial arts.
Including boxing!
He was even prominent at the interschool level!
And now, dad's precious gloves...
Try them on, Honmaru.
When I wear them,
I feel like I'm becoming as strong as dad!
Great. Then your opponent will be your dad himself.
Attack from wherever you wish!
Alright...
Start trying harder!
Such punches stand no chance against me!
Do they?!
Honmaru, don't let down the gloves
of dad youth's blood and sweat.
Long time no see!
Been waiting for years to see some action again!
What's that?
Get this!
Dad, I'm sorry!
Your gloves wouldn't obey me...
The years took a heavy toll on Shogunosuke.
Can't even dodge a green punch like that!
Honmaru, let us two teach you some good old boxing!
Gotta find a guy looking mighty
and do sparring!
Here we go, Honmaru!
Honmaru, fight!
Pay attention!
Memorize it with your body, Honmaru!
Honmaru, I hope you find someone strong enough soon.
How can you be so carefree saying this?
Locating prey dead ahead!
After the sparring,
he might end up simply dead!
Hold it! He's a high-school student!
Ain't nothing we can't handle! Go get him!
Taru!
You there!
Is it a ballsack on your head,
or just your stupid face?
What?!
We're screwed!
First, a barrage of jabs from the left!
Give him no breather, keep hitting! Hitting!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
The hell?! He's in elementary school!
This way, the opponent's offense is suppressed!
And you have full control of distance!
I'm sorry!
Apologizing while bombarding me with punches?!
Now's our chance!
Wait till there's enough an opening, then exploit it!
Ha! Here's a right straight for you!
A weakling.
Too weak after all.
Quit acting tough if you don't live up to it!
Made it through, Honmaru!
Let's look for someone with more guts!
Maybe this way?
Sure thing!
Those look like a somewhat sturdier bunch!
At least show some discretion
against guys like that!
Oh, just lemme do my thing!
Bald one! I'll fight you next!
The heck this punk just say?!
This is...
Right jab!
Left hook!
And finally, my uppercut!
Damn brat, now you're dead!
Honmaru, watch out!
Did it!
Left straight!
Are you really just...
Just in elementary school...
Looking good, Honmaru!
Honmaru, that was one bloody good head slip.
Flame-kun's and dad's lessons in defense
are finally starting to pay off.
Did you just now wake up to it?
Alright, let's find another one! Another!
'Kay, lessgo!
Looking for it yourself now?
Gotta pick a fight with some real bruiser now!
Aye! There's no stopping me!
Honmaru is picking a fight!
Someone drop it for him to pick!
He'll be happy to!
We're raided by another dojo!
Honmaru, special training
comes morning, too. Wake up!
Let me have just a smidgen more of sleep, Taru.
Would you look at this loafer!
For how long are you planning to sleep?
Come on, we got practice to go through!
Honmaru is now totally
on the same page as Glove-kuns!
Superb. Superb!
Tomorrow, we'll finally get to see
the match between those two.
I wonder if Honmaru will make it out in one piece
after foolhardily giving the guy a mouthful.
Omura Boxing Gym
Recruiting trainees
This is where we make sure
the special training has been fruitful.
Aight, let's go!
Ain't that Honmaru?
Secret weapon - Cross-counter!
Jose...
The three are perfectly combined!
Coach! This kid is unbelievable!
He made short work of a former World Champion!
Jabao-san, heard it just now?
Can it really be Honmaru?
Honmaru, need to apply some finishing touches
to your special training.
Sure! Just point at the opponent!
Finishing touch!
Which elementary school are you from?
No... This wasn't me, the glove did it...
A glove that gropes people...
Where'd you seen that?!
Just as you'd think he took up practicing earnestly,
Honmaru reminds you that he is still Honmaru.
Maybe this shout earlier was actually just
"this kid is unbelievably short!"
So it seems.
Honmaru, a warrior never lets his guard down.
Need to work on that, too.
I can't wait for tomorrow's match!
Honmaru!
Eat a takoyaki on your way home
to re-restore stamina.
Nice! Nice punch, Tsutomu!
Edojo Honmaru,
prepare to share this wretched fate!
Harako Tsutomu vs Edojo Honmaru
Thank you, fellow fans!
Greetings to all 24 million boxing fans nationwide.
Today we're broadcasting
from Harako Conglomerate special ring,
where a bout between Edojo Honmaru
and Harako Tsutomu is taking place.
Honmaru, do your best!
Bring it on, Honmaru!
I'll make sure you get a good taste of how dreadful I can be.
Magical Taruruuto-kun: Honmaru's KO Punch.
Episode 12
Honmaru's KO Punch
Honmaru, go for it!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius