Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 50
Gritty Endurance Contest
So hot...
Fine!
Fine.
Hot!
Is that...
Shaved ice?
I sure would like some!
Shaved ice is better than takoyaki?
But... of course is it!
On a hot day, shaved ice is what the doctor ordered!
Yeah, I want too...
Fine...
Money...
I don't have any...
Wait! I do. Maybe...
Is it money?
One-time Five-pointed Pleaseal.
Five-pointed Pleaseal?
You stick this seal on your head and make a wish.
It'll make just one wish come true.
Really?
Alright, let's give it a try!
Yeah!
I stick this on your head...
Is this where I make a wish?
Oh, good God, good Buddha!
Please let us eat some shaved ice!
Hey!
Honmaru, Taru!
Grandpa!
Honmaru's grandpa!
I was just about to come see you at your home.
Well...
But let me tell you, it sure is hot.
Is this just a coincidence?
Or perhaps an illusion?
So hot.
Maybe I should get some shaved ice?
That's it! Shaved ice, shaved ice, shaved ice!
Hey there, welcome!
Hello.
Ma'am, you got any shaved ice?
There, take your time.
Cold shaved ice is the best on a hot day!
This - shaved ice?
The sauce doesn't seem to cover it.
Is that okay?
Listen, takoyaki and shaved ice
are two totally different things.
Eh? Different?
Try this!
Cold!
Alright...
Thanks for the meal!
Eek! Ouch-ouch!
It's because you ate in a hurry.
What do you think? Tasty, isn't it?
Yes! Delicious!
Cold and nice!
I like takoyaki very much,
but shaved ice I love!
Oh! Here it is again...
Fine, fine, eat until you're full.
Okay! Ma'am, a refill!
Father! Please be more careful.
We're in the season when it's the easiest
to overburden one's stomach.
Ah, my bad, my bad.
My stomach hurts so much!
Hurts...
You're a pitiful sight, Honmaru.
That's what you get for sneaking outside
and buying street food!
As a punishment, you're not getting
any more shaved ice this summer!
No pocket money!
We won't have any more shaved ice this summer!
Won't have...
Damn, it's hot.
Hot...
Honmaru, let's eat shaved ice!
Not gonna work, Taru.
I'm strapped for pocket money.
Not gonna work, no more Five-pointed Pleaseal.
But...
Wanna eat, wanna eat, wanna eat!
Shaved ice, wanna eat!
Wanna eat, wanna eat!
Eat at the same shop, very good there!
But won't eat anymore!
Hey, Taru!
Throwing a fit will only warm you up even more!
And then, you'll crave
shaved ice even more!
It's just as Honmaru says... Still...
Oh no, I still want some shaved ice!
Shaved ice, shaved ice, shaved ice!
Shaved ice...
Shaved ice.
Shaved ice!
It was just a mirage...
Oh, Honmaru!
What is it, Taru? Another illusion?
Honmaru, Honmaru!
Shaved ice, shaved ice!
What?
All-you-can-eat shaved ice?!
Hey, take a look!
The endurance contest winner will go to Hawaii,
and will get all-you-can-eat shaved ice!
All-you-can-eat?
It means you can eat as much as you can fit!
This is a gift from heaven!
I love all-you-can-eat!
Hey, it's all-you-can-eat.
All-you-can-eat...
I sure love shaved ice!
Nannosho's endurance contest is already in its middle stage.
Good things come to those who endure!
Now, dear participants! Let's do our best!
The rules are pretty simple.
The one who exits this kiln, loses.
And the current temperature is...
Oh! It's 58!
Now, there are only seven participants remaining!
It's hot, so hot! It's unbearable!
Shit... Won't the rest of you give up already?
But damn it, how come everyone is so determined? Shit...
You're about to see Jabao
going on a winning trip to Hawaii.
I'll do my best, mom.
Oh, is that so?
I would also kill to eat some shaved ice.
I won't stop at anything!
Shaved ice, shaved ice...
Hey, why did Iyona-chan decide to partake?
Eh? Well, Rui-chan invited me.
Because that's just the diet you need!
You've gained some weight recently, you know.
Eh, really?
Then, I gotta endure it for a little longer.
So you didn't even enter to get the prize?!
I'm here because I really need shaved ice! Shaved ice...
Honmaru!
What?
Honmaru, don't you think it's about time you go down?
After all, I'm the only world endurance champion here.
Honmaru, I won't ever lose to you!
And this clown also entered the endurance contest
simply to duel me!
Gosh, you're annoying!
Someone like you can easily afford shaved ice!
Stop getting in my way over such petty stuff!
Not bad! That's it, fight, fight!
Ah, teacher?
Well, if it ain't me dear Mari-sensei?
One's endurance is a matter of guts!
With enough guts, you can't lose to anyone!
Please leave it up to Nanigoro, the gutsy man,
to demonstrate it!
Even Matsu-san is here?
Mari Sensei...
I thought I should give her a bonus
in the form of some present.
Bonus
But with this damned heat,
the business dried out completely!
That was exactly when I spotted the poster of this endurance contest, with a trip to Hawaii as the main prize.
Moreover, it's a trip for two!
That instant, I vowed solemnly
to present Mari-sensei with that trip.
Oh, Matsu-san! Make sure to endure with us, then!
Hey, Taru!
Matsu-san is our rival, remember?
Yeah! Rival for shaved ice Matsu-san.
You'd be better off leaving right now, Honmaru.
'Cuz Matsugoro will make it through with his guts alone!
Honmaru, there will only be one winner - Harako Tsutomu!
I think you've lost 500 grams already, Iyona-chan.
Really? Let's make sure
we get to our goal of two kilograms, Rui-chan.
Mom, just wait for me, will you?
Shit... You're all so obnoxious!
Wow now, isn't that tremendous?
Great tensions are arising between the competitors!
Fight!
Can anyone predict who among them
will leave with the prize?!
Now, everyone, thank you for waiting.
Finally, it's time to serve nabeyaki udon!
Alright, coming!
Bon appétit, and do your best!
And now it's nabeyaki udon?
Now, we'll ask our chef to pepper it lavishly!
Lavishly! Right!
This is just absurd!
I'm just getting started, this is nothing!
More! Bring it on!
Now look at yourself,
wrinkling in agony, Honmaru!
You're so noisy, Harako!
Oops. I shouldn't get mad,
lest I heat up even more.
Only now you get it?
Oh, you don't seem to have an easy time either, bud.
Sorry, but I'm leaving with the prize today.
Are you kidding me?
That man hasn't even started to sweat yet!
Well, ain't it natural?
No matter how hot it gets,
I have to keep selling takoyaki.
I can't have even a drop of sweat fall on it!
It's easy! But only for someone who's a true takoyaki pro.
How about this?
Crap! I won't...
Matsu-san doin' his best.
Matsu-san may be an even more
formidable enemy than Harako!
Taru, we need to eat this to get shaved ice later!
Yeah!
Dammit...
My head is splitting apart!
I can't take it! I can't!
Iyona-chan, isn't nabeyaki udon rich in calories?
You're right, and I'm on a diet...
Eating hot udon while it's hot...
That's how Naniwa's ancestors always ate it!
Can I get a refill?
I never doubted you, Matsugoro-san!
How can this stop me?!
Shit... I won't lose!
Ah! I can't take it anymore!
Me too...
Hot!
Ah, so chilly!
And we've achieved our goal of losing two kilograms!
Yes, the diet was successful.
Oh, two beauties just dropped out!
And the next challenge is...
A hot bottle!
Hot!
And now, let's move on to Indian curry,
which is 100 times spicier!
Can you even eat this?
Spicy!
This curry terribly spicy!
Spicy...
This curry...
Curry devil... Why, you...
Now, everyone, next we have...
What'll it be this time?
Be it a cactus or a puffer fish​, bring whatever!
And now, some juice service for you!
Those who'd like some, it's here!
Here!
What kind of service is this?
If you go out to drink it, you'll drop out!
That'd be nice...
No-no, it's dangerous!
I'm boiling! Can't take it! Goodbye!
That's it, Jabao-san is disqualified!
Mom?
Scary!
But I did my best...
I was trying my best, mom!
Madam!
Now, the next challenge is the lens!
Shaved ice, shaved ice, shaved ice,
wanna eat shaved ice sooner!
Honmaru, you're about to witness the true power
of the World Junior Endurance Champion!
One last push until the ticket to Hawaii is mine.
Now, it's the final hurdle for the remaining four!
Hell from below!
Wow! Isn't that harsh?
It's terribly intensive!
Do your best, everyone!
Eh?! Are you serious?
Yay! Fried egg, fried egg!
And it's yummy!
After making it this far...
When sitting on this red-hot frying pan,
I can understand truly well how it feels to be a takoyaki...
My body is as hot as the fire itself!
But why isn't the fire hot?
Ice will melt if you put it in a fire.
But if you add more fire to the fire, it's perfectly alright.
It's dangerous for me to enter
the women's changing room as man.
Eh?
Ouch...
However, if I use Hormonger and enter it as a woman,
I can get away with anything.
I see! The fire fears not joining another fire,
because it's just as hot!
I've ascended!
The current room temperature is 89 degrees!
Alright, I'll turn into a fire myself!
This way, I couldn't care less for the heat!
I am the fire! Heart of fire!
Nah, it's still hopeless...
Hot...
Taru, how can you be so goddamn carefree?!
This - I drank the Fire Element.
Drinking this makes your body as hot as fire.
This way, you don't mind the heat at all.
My hands are hot like fire too.
Why didn't you show it to me sooner?
Honmaru, winning with magic is no fun.
It's fine. It's all alright.
If that'd let me eat shaved ice, anything would do.
Honmaru drank the whole bottle...
Now I couldn't care less for the heat!
I'm fired up!
Honmaru, you're actually burning!
Hot-hot-hot-hot! I lost!
That's impressive! Two more stepped off!
Amazing, Honmaru-kun!
Did it, did it, did it!
Shaved ice, shaved ice, shaved ice is mine!
Matsugoro, the man of infinite guts,
won't yield an inch, for Mari-sensei's sake,
Honmaru!
Shaved ice!
A trip to Hawaii for two...
Honmaru burns with magic,
and Matsu-san burns with love.
Please evacuate!
I lost?
Well, looks like the contest is finally concluded.
Let's see if there are any other survivors.
Oh! Someone is still inside!
It's none other than Matsugoro-san,
the man of infinite guts!
Aye.
Mari-sensei, I did it!
Everyone, only the concluding part of our event remains!
Here, your trip to Hawaii for two.
I did it! I got them!
Mari-sensei, did you see me doing it?
Matsu-san! I lost, Matsu-san.
Honmaru, that was one fine bout!
Matsu-san!
Honmaru!
My present for Mari-sensei just went up-up-up-up in flames!
Matsu-san!
You bastard! Why did you do that,
you numbskull Honmaru?!
No! I'm sorry, Matsu-san!
My trip to Hawaii that I risked my life for!
What should I do about it now, you ass?! Get back here!
Honmaru! I got shaved ice as participation award!
Eh? Shaved ice?
What?
Shaved ice... Shaved ice!
Thanks for the meal!
My shaved ice...
Sukeban Deka
Is that all you got?
©Toei Entertainment
Sukeban Deka
Is that all you got?
©Toei Entertainment
Shaved ice... I wanted shaved ice!
Lovely trip to Hawaii!
Honmaru overdrunk Fire Element, so he's still burning.
And Matsu-san is burning with sadness!
Eh? My shaved ice...
Trip to Hawaii...
Crap! I haven't done a piece of homework
during the summer vacation!
What should I do, Taru?
The teacher will have my butt tattered!
Hey Taru! Wake up, come on!
Me been playing with Honmaru day after day,
completely exhausted.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Doing Homework With Magic?
Wake up, I'm begging you!
Episode 51
Doing Homework With Magic?
Uh? I've not done any either! What do we do?
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius