Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Spring is here to stay, Taru!
Here, Honmaru.
And I feel so buoyant for some reason!
Reason!
Maybe something good will happen to me.
Maybe...
Alright, let's race to school, Taru!
Yeah, race with Honmaru!
Iyona-chan!
Iyona!
Good morning, Honmaru-kun.
Episode 82
I Love Everyone🤍
Good morning, Iyona-chan.
Sup, Iyona.
Sup, Taru-chan.
Isn't it great?
The cherry blossom season is here.
So gently and indecisively warm...
It feels like I move weightlessly through the air.
Perhaps I'd even be able
to climb all the way to the sky...
And sometimes this breeze blows
and makes me feel so relaxed...
I absolutely love this.
Iyona-chan...
Why is Iyona-chan always so lovely?
She really lives up to her name of Kawai Iyona!
Honmaru drooling.
Oh no! What is it?
Did I say something strange?
You see, I've been taking
ballet courses recently...
I don't like this look.
Is there something on my face, Honmaru-kun?
No, it's just that I was thinking
how wonderful you are...
Oh no, Honmaru-kun!
Dodged it! Up until now, Iyona-chan
has always inevitably blasted me away!
Oh no, Honmaru-kun!
It hurts...
Could it be that I've finally become a man
worthy of Iyona-chan?
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan...
Taru!
No, Honmaru-kun!
!nuk-uramnoH ,oN
Oh no!
Honmaru, Iyona.
Sorry, Taru!
I forgot I was carrying you on my shoulder!
Sorry, Taru-chan.
Okay, Power Upple Juice it is.
Yeah! Me fine already!
I'm so glad.
Sorry, Taru-chan, Honmaru-kun.
I'll be careful not do something like that ever again.
Don't worry, Iyona.
That's also a part of yourself.
Maybe he's right.
I already learned to dodge it,
so feel free to even do that daily.
And so, every day,
I'll get to do this to Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun...
Come on, Taru!
No... It was but banter,
Iyona-chan. Banter!
Well, if we get held up
in the street like this, we'll be late.
Let's go now!
Yes. That's true.
Wait, Honmaru!
Hey, Harako, Jabao.
Don't talk like nothing happened, you rogue!
Eh?
What is it you're doing to Iyona-chan
so early in the morning?
That's right, Honmaru!
So you saw what happened, huh?
Have some decency, you!
Jealousy is unbecoming of a man.
Right, Taru?
I wanna eat jelly sauce too!
No, it's not that.
Honmaru! You've been getting
on my nerves recently!
Dontcha get your nose in the air
just cause you got kenpo and Taru's magic!
A tall tree catches the most wind!
What was that?!
You heard it!
What, huh?
Yay! Looks interesting.
Stop it, everyone! Don't forget,
we're all friends, so let's get along!
Iyona-chan...
With all due respect, Iyona-san, I don't remember
ever becoming friends with Honmaru's kind!
Neither do I!
Same here.
Please, everyone! Let's calm down
and remember that you're friends with Honmaru-kun.
I don't remember any such thing!
Harako, this Rememberawer.
Helps you remember anything you forgot.
Harako! Honmaru and Harako are friends.
Rememberawer!
Honmaru...
You were my only true friend.
No one around could understand my feelings.
No one could stand up and face me.
That is... Except you!
You alone!
See, Harako-kun?
I remembered it too, Harako.
How could I...
Forget about something so important?!
Honmaru!
Harako!
Friends are bound by fate
to also be rivals!
Forgive me.
I hereby swear to never forget my friendship with you!
Harako!
Jabao also needs to remember
that he and Honmaru are friends!
That's right. Fighting is bad.
Yes. Let's get along.
I'm sorry, Jabao-san.
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun.
That's how it was!
I can't believe I forgot something so important!
Honmaru!
Jabao!
It was my fault.
Sorry for being so rude time after time!
Jabao!
How could I forget something so important?!
Honmaru!
I remembered it too!
Our passionate friendship!
Korekiyo...
Oh? But I haven't even put
the Rememberawer on Korekiyo yet.
This is called playing by ear, yessir.
Rememberawer!
How about this?
As expected of Jabao-san! Spectacular.
Jabao is so insufferable!
He's been getting in my hair since long ago!
Right, Honmaru-san?
You didn't have to say that.
Korekiyo!
You're getting carried away
with your chameleon agenda!
Give it a rest already!
You didn't need to remind us of that!
I understand, so calm down already.
There's no need for tears, everyone.
Thank you, it's all thanks to you, Taru-chan.
Yay! Me praised by Iyona!
Iyona always so kind to everyone. Me won't forget.
Well, let's be on our way, Taru, Iyona-chan.
Yeah!
Man, I sure love spring!
Is it really better this way?
No, it feels better, but it kinda isn't...
I feel like the wool has been pulled over my eyes.
Scratch that, I can't accept it!
Just think about it -
beautiful and clearheaded Iyona-san
is smiling and having fun
with that problematic kid, Honmaru!
Realistically, this isn't acceptable!
This miracle has only been
made possible by Taru's magic.
If this continues, we risk losing Iyona-chan
to Honmaru's influence, Jabao-san.
But there's a hitch - trying to beat Honmaru
with physical strength is a nonstarter.
After all, even Harako
is struggling to go about doing that now.
It is true that numerous duels up to now
ended in Honmaru's victory.
And I willingly admit
that each one had been a tough match.
However, we're yet to hold
an actual duel in love.
I still have my chance!
For Harako Tsutomu,
the "Unprecedented Technique" Award Winner
of the World Junior Feeling Couples 5v5 Championship,
giving up on Iyona-san's heart
without even trying to win it fairly is unacceptable!
Both Honmaru's kenpo and Taru's magic
would not prove enough for this!
Yeah! Even I flared up with enthusiasm!
Same here, Jabao-san.
Harako sure had plenty of confidence about it,
but what is he really going to do?
Speak of the devil and it shall appear, Jabao-san.
Hey, Taruruuto-kun! How are you?
Harako need something?
A bird, wink-wink...
Oh my, what's gotten into me?
What's going on? Hey?
Beats me...
Well, I thought maybe I should
give this to you, Taruruuto-kun.
No need to be shy.
Takoyaki!
Better not rush yourself!
By the way, Taruruuto-kun,
you and Honmaru-kun are friends, right?
Yeah. Honmaru and me friends.
Then, if I'm also friends with Honmaru-kun,
that makes me friends with Taruruuto-kun as well.
Isn't that right?
Yeah! Friend of friend - everyone friends!
Raise your friends on your hands...
Oops, I did it again!
Ice-cold.
Wanna go get an ice crusher, Ryoguchiya?
Harako...
...weird.
That's right. There's this one favor
I'd like to ask for, as a friend.
Say anything. I'll hear.
So you'll hear me out?
Then...
Hold up.
No matter how naive and easygoing Taru is,
if I ask for magic that'll make
Iyona-san fall in love with me,
would he really follow up on such a specific request?
Hm. Should I turn it into yet another clever joke here?
What?
Harako, that jerk! Always so boastful of his own persona, and now he plans to employ Taru's magic himself, Jabao-san!
What happened to winning it "fairly?!"
Oh my! You've been listening, huh?
That was unnecessary.
Completely unnecessary, you hear?
I'll have my leave! Later!
Harako, use this!
Eh?
This - Yahook up with me-kun.
You shoot this arrow at Iyona's heart
and Iyona starts loving Harako.
As expected of a good friend!
Thank you, Taruruuto-kun!
Yeah! We friends.
I never thought it'd be this easy.
I'll show you now, Honmaru!
What's that?
I wonder.
Taru! Where are you?
And like that, you aim for the heart.
I see.
Cute thing!
What are you doing, Taru? Stop it!
Eh? Honmaru?
Honmaru mad?
Of course I am!
You don't understand what you're doing!
With Yahook up with me-kun making
Iyona love Harako, Honmaru is mad...
Ah! Harako, sorry.
Stop using my magic.
It's too late now!
With this, Iyona-san's heart... It's mine!
Stop it, Harako!
Harako!
I'm not stopping!
Harako, you scum! Stop it!
Like we'll let you have it all to yourself!
Exactly!
Give that to me!
Where did you come from...
Ah! Hey!
We were right here!
Let go!
Hey! This arrow is mine!
Let go, go! It's not yours, Harako!
Pierced!
What?
It's so hot today.
What are you doing, Iyona-chan?
Iyona-san...
Harako-kun...
Those eyes are staring
so intently at Harako! This is bad!
I did it! Yay, you finally realized it, Honmaru?
There's no need to be shy, Iyona-san.
Please hurry up and jump right on my chest!
Iyona-san!
Huh?
Jabao-kun.
Yes?
Yes, I did it!
I had a better grip on the arrow than Harako!
I'm finally reunited with my beloved Iyona-chan!
Iyona-san!
Oh?
Korekiyo-kun.
What's going on?
Good things come to those who wait.
Yay! While Jabao-san and Harako
were just wrestling for the arrow,
who do you think took the trouble to aim
it at Iyona-san's heart? It was Ryoguchiya Korekiyo!
Indeed, fortunes are made where others fight,
like the suddenly falling fruits!
Iyona-san!
Huh?
Honmaru...
You three are all wonderful!
Huh?!
What in the world happened to you, Iyona-chan?
Taru's magic for making people fall in love!
All three of them used the Yahook up with me-kun
at once, so Iyona-chan fell in love with them all!
Yeah. Still have one more
Yahook up with me-kun.
Rui wanna use it too?
Really now? How many times
did you use this magic on me, then?!
Don't be stupid!
Why would I ever use it on you?
Yeah. Not used it even once on Rui.
Never used?
Can this really be?
Then... then... why am I this much...
Rui kinda weird.
Iyona-chan!
Get your hands off her, you scum!
Iyona-san only belongs to me!
Who was it who tricked Taru
into using magic on her?
You've been the scum all along!
Looks to me like you're two sides of the same coin!
Only Ryoguchiya Korekiyo can be trusted with her!
Stop!
It hurts...
Sorry, Iyona-chan!
Iyona!
Are you o—
Are you okay, everyone?
Are you hurt?
Honmaru-kun, why...
Why did you have to push
everyone out of the way? So cruel!
Iyona-chan, please don't give me that kind of look...
I'm okay now, Iyona-san.
Really? I'm so glad everyone is unharmed.
How about this, Honmaru?
Iyona-san wouldn't give you a jot of her concern!
All she's worried about is me!
Move it! It's not just you, Harako!
Same goes for me!
Move it! Well, since there's also me,
why don't we consider it a victory of all three?
Listen, Iyona-chan!
Your love for Harako and other others
is a product of Taru's magic!
They used Yahook up with me-kun
to make you fall in love with them!
Why would you tell
such an obvious lie, Honmaru-kun?
Stop trying to disparage others!
They are all wonderful people, that's why I...
Which part of them is wonderful?!
Come to your senses, Iyona-chan!
Well, Iyona-san. Let's forget about
this fraud and go play elsewhere.
That's right, Iyona-chan.
Let's go.
I suppose...
Wait!
Iyona-chan...
Ah, here! Here!
I'll catch you first!
Ah, I can do that too!
Iyona-chan, why did you
fall in love with guys like them?
Taru, can't you do something?
It's okay, Honmaru. Just wait for ten
minutes and the magic will wear off.
If only you
I see! That's right!
hadn't showed up
It's only ten minutes!
I need to endure it for ten minutes!
My life
Still...
wouldn't have changed
When I see you,
In these ten minutes, I'll surely engrave on Iyona-san's
heart her eternal love for me deeply and irrevocably.
And when I don't,
It's bizarre, even, how much I care about you
Wait!
I wanna say that awkward line,
But for now, the two of us are just friends (Sorry)
I'm not asking for any extravagance!
Even ten minutes is enough!
I'm sorry.
I'm impatient to know for how long it'll last
My heart throbs and I can't stop asking questions!
Iyona-chan!
It could as well be a dream...
Everyone is happy and laughing!
Let's go play with them too!
What are you saying at a time like this, Taru?
Ah! Is it not over yet?
How can ten minutes last for so long?
Those ten minutes are so goddamn long! Shit!
Okay, Honmaru!
Hurry up and use this.
That's right, that's right, that's right!
I can use Yahook up with me-kun too!
Iyona-chan's heart...
What do you want now?
You're at it again!
How much of a happy-go-lucky idiot can you be?!
What is it? Trying to screw me up again?
Out of the way, Ijigawa!
What do you intend to do
with that arrow, Honmaru?
Using things like that to toy with woman's heart...
Don't you see how cowardly it is?
Why would you even think of using
something like that? Answer me, you!
You're truly pathetic!
Are Iyona-chan's feelings
really that worthless for you?!
Ijigawa...
If you can't even conquer a woman's
heart without resorting to magic...
If that's the kind of man you've always been,
you're the worst ever, Honmaru!
The worst ever...
Thank you, Ijigawa.
I don't need it, Taru.
Honmaru?
It's as Ijigawa said.
Not... Not with magic, but with my true self,
I'll make Iyona-chan fall in love with me!
Iyona-chan...
I will...
To your heart...
I'll send my own heart,
that treasures you more than anything.
I'm sure, with my telepathy,
I'll be able to get through to Iyona-chan's heart!
My love... My love for Iyona-chan!
I love everything about you!
Of course, that means I love you even now,
when you're in love with someone else!
Iyona-chan's heart...
When it meets my heart,
they find a wonderful harmony!
If it's for Iyona-chan,
I'm prepared to go through fire and water!
I'm sure I'll become the man
who can make Iyona-chan happy!
Even decades from now...
Even centuries from now...
Now, Iyona-chan.
Turn to me!
Notice my passionate gaze!
You come join us too, Rui-chan, Taru-chan!
Huh?
Yeah! Me play too!
That's not what I meant, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru, ten minutes ran out already.
Huh?
Oh?
That's right, the magic is supposed
to wear off in ten minutes.
But if Iyona-chan is still with Harako and others...
Could it be that she ended up
falling in love with them for real?
You...
What's the matter?
Wasn't Iyona-chan petting you before?
Iyona-chan...
It tickles!
I guess this guy understands it too.
Iyona-chan is kind to everyone.
I'm a little jealous, though.
I see! That's it!
With or without magic,
Iyona-chan has always been the wonderfully
kind girl who loves everything in this world!
I was such an idiot!
But I guess getting jealous was kinda unavoidable.
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
You should come play with us too!
Sure!
You're the best, Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan!
That's right, I also gotta be kind to everyone.
Without that, I can never make Iyona-chan happy!
Everyone, Honmaru-kun is "it" in the next round!
Ah?
Honmaru-kun, hurry up and try to catch me!
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan!
Ah, Iyona-chan!
How cute can you really be?
Splashing sweat, shining eyes, long, slender legs!
I'm mesmerized by your athletic omnipotence!
Mesmerized!
Honmaru, you're drooling!
Alright! Let's renew the special training
aimed at winning the championship!
Wow! Honmaru burning! Boom...
Boom!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Fateful Volleyball Battle.
Episode 83
Fateful Volleyball Battle
Iyona and Marue, do your best!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius