Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 36
I'm a Man, Ijigawa Rui!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, hello?
You... Why, you... Shit...
Honmaru!
You died...
I made it so far in this run...
Hey, hey, Honmaru-kun!
Lemme try to tell your future fortune.
You crook! Why did you need to distract me
for such meaningless bullshit?!
Ah! A nosebleed!
You broad...
Just 'cos you're a girl,
you think I'll swallow everything?!
Wait, I said! You broad!
The hell do you want?
A man is supposed to be more enduring than that!
Look who's talking!
A woman is supposed to be more refined than that!
Don't say nonsense!
Men and women have equal rights these days!
You can't discriminate against me
just 'cause I'm a woman!
What'd you say?!
Really? Talking equality now?
I can do that, too!
Have a taste of my equality!
What happened?
Ow! Ouch!
Honmaru-kun abused his manly superior strength
to smack me with a shoe!
But... I... But...
What?! He did what? He did what?!
Huh? What was it? Speak up!
It seems, Honmaru hit Ijigawa
with all his strength!
What?!
But I adjusted my hand...
Right, Taruruuto?
Huh? Taru? Taru! Taru!
Honmaru, me here!
Me not seen anything. Heard nothing.
Taru...
Honmaru-kun...
A misunderstanding!
It's a misunderstanding, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun...
You ought to know that girls are very delicate.
Be more careful.
I'm gonna expose you for what you really are!
Just you watch!
You wench...
Dammit...
Honmaru just groped my bust!
I'm not supposed to let anyone touch it!
My maiden's chastity!
What's wrong with you?!
You took it upon yourself
to ensure that this would happen!
How brutal!
Iyona-chan, Honmaru is harassing me!
Rui-chan...
Harassing!
You wretch! Who in the world
would willingly grope your bust?
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan...
GOD DAMMIT!
Not only did he raise his hand against a helpless woman,
he's now brazenly boasting his impunity before everyone!
You won't be excusing yourself any longer, Honmaru!
Yes! Precisely!
But I never...
Shit! Screw you, Ijigawa!
As a girl, she gets away with anything!
Ah, this is so riling!
What's all that equal rights garbage?
Women win from it, but men only lose!
Isn't that right, Taru?
Yeah, Honmaru! In that case,
might as well ask Tama-chan for advice.
Tama-chan, please help.
Always Captivating Tama-chan!
If it's Tama-chan, she can understand my feelings for sure!
Tama-chan, please! Tama-chan...
Ah, how can one reject you?
If so, how about putting to use
Nature Switch Juice Hormonger from Taru-chan's bag?
I see! That'll reverse our respective social standings!
Honmaru woman, Ijigawa man - sounds fun!
'Aight, that's what we'll do!
Really, that teacher is asking for too much!
And I'm starving!
Ijigawa!
It's as though someone just called me.
Ijigawa, here!
Sorry about this morning...
What now, Wet-maru again?
Here - the sign of my repentance.
Pentance!
Hm? Trying to barter for my favor?
Ah, so be it. You're lucky I'm parched right now.
I ain't turning it down!
Men's restroom
That's it, Ijigawa. As soon as you turn into a man,
the ordeal of manhood will hit you with full force!
While I myself will be reaping the fruits of womanhood.
Well, Taru-chan, let's be on our way.
Okay!
You seen it?
Friggin' weird!
Definitely a girl...
Women's changing room
You're right, you've lost a little weight!
It's seriously cute! Where did you buy that?
Rui-chan.
Uh? What is it?
Rui-chan, you seem to have gained some muscle lately...
Oh? You think so?
I feel this strange crawling in my chest.
Gone!
What's the matter?
It's nothing!
The heck?!
Rui-chan...
Ah, no-no. It's... It's nothing, really.
Oh my, Rui-chan!
Feeling unwell somewhere?
Ah! Marue-chan!
Ah! Been a while!
Oh?
Rui-chan has such a boyish physique!
So muscular.
Also, your crotch is protruding.
No boobs either!
Boobs melted...
Get off me!
Come to think of it, Rui-chan...
You don't suppose she could be a boy?
No... No way...
Don't give me that crappo!
Look! She even talks like a boy now!
Let's try and see for sure if she's a boy.
You can't do that!
I can do that!
You can't! Can't!
Rui, let us see!
You stop right there! Stop it!
Stop it, I said!
You prick!
Piss off!
Goddamn pest!
Ah! How scary!
I'm scared!
Iyona-chan, help me!
Rui-chan... It can't be...
Exactly! Rui-chan has always been a boy!
B-O-Y...
Impossible!
Oh, whatever! It can't be helped,
since it leaked out already!
Seems like I've actually been a boy for my whole life!
If it comes to this, I ain't got no choice...
But to keep on living...
As a boy.
Adios!
Rui-chan...
It can't be...
Did we go a bit overboard?
Then, I'll face you!
Really? Wanna do it?
Oh, come on, boys!
Get to the cleaning already!
Haven't you had enough?!
You twat!
Cleaning's bullshit - why should a man do it?
Yeah! It's just as Ijigawa says!
Though I never saw him as anything special at first,
after finding out Ijigawa was actually a man,
in him, I found my closest pal!
Remind me, when did I allow
your stupid ass to call me "pal?"
My bad, Ijigawa-kun...
'Aight! Let's go play outside now!
Yeah!
Stop right there, you!
Ah? It's you pestering me again?
It's unfair to say you don't have to clean
just 'cause you're a boy!
Equal rights and stuff, remember?
Quit saying nonsense!
We, men, are superior to you in every aspect!
We leave it to women to do womanly things
like being refined and all!
This rogue Ijigawa switched
to a completely opposite view!
You don't wait on us,
we trust you to handle the cleaning!
We trust you, you hear?
Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey!
We trust you!
Smell ya later!
Adios!
I swear, boys can be so selfish sometimes!
Alright! I got this one in the bag!
In the end, some folk are just hopeless.
Hm! This fragrance is magnificent.
To think that I'd find a boyish cutie gal like you
right here in my school!
Umph! Why does my heart break into a gallop
when someone like Harako looks at me?
I guess, from a woman's point of view,
I see Harako as super-chic.
By the way, m'lady, if you'd like to see
the Fukien china I recently imported...
Iyona, me doing my best!
My, as expected of Taru-chan!
Oh no-no-no...
If Iyona-san notices me doing this...
"He who runs after two hares will catch neither!"
Or should I risk it for the biscuit?
Oh, but it's also so hard to give up on this boyish gal!
Apparently, this prick Harako is weighing Iyona against me!
Now I'm also somehow terrified to realize
I have to outrival Iyona-chan!
Things are anything but simple between women...
On that note, m'lady...
Very playful of you!
I'll see you again soon enough!
Hey-hey, Iyona-chan, isn't that unfair?
Cleaning is fun!
As soon as Ijigawa-kun had realized he's a boy,
he neglected cleaning altogether!
I suppose so.
You agree? Agree? That's just so vexing.
Isn't that one more to the downsides of being a woman?
However, I don't find it vexing.
In fact, I like to do the cleaning.
After all, doesn't it feel good to see things turn clean?
Oh, I see...
Tsk. That's kinda hard to pick up.
When you look at her as a fellow girl, Iyona-chan is just way too dazzling, making you feel a complete underdog.
In every single thing that a woman does, she is perfect.
I really feel like I'll never be in the same league as her.
A!
Eh! When I became a woman, my butt also grew in size!
Here, use this.
My sewing kit.
No, keep it. I don't know the first thing
about sewing anyhow.
Eh?
If so, just let me sew it for you!
Iyona-chan, thank you...
Iyona-chan is just so caring...
I see! Iyona-chan is caring towards girls as well.
You're good at it.
Thank you.
Even as a girl, I end up relying on Iyona-chan's kindness.
Iyona-chan, I'm sure you'll make a great wife.
And a good mom, too!
Really? I'm so glad!
Here.
Thank you!
Marue-chan, when I grow up,
my dream is to become someone's wife.
Wearing a pristine white wedding dress,
marrying a caring and wonderful man.
Actually, Marue-chan, which boy do you like?
Eh?!
I mean, you also yearn
to become someone's wife later, don't you?
Asking which boy I like? Becoming a wife?
I could answer whatever, but I'm still a man inside!
I am... a man...
That's right! I'm a man.
Which means I could also be the one who makes
Kawai Iyona-chan, the most caring girl in the world, his wife!
Iyona.
Honmaru.
Marue-chan?
Ah! That's right! I forgot I've got
an important business elsewhere.
See you, Iyona-chan. And thank you!
Me... Me come, too!
Did you hear that, Taru?
This ain't the time to be posing as a woman!
It could be better spent becoming
a wonderful and caring person of Iyona-chan's dreams!
Yeah!
And then, I'll be the one standing next to Iyona-chan,
gowned in a beautiful wedding dress!
Yeah...
HI, SWEETHEART!
Sorry I kept you waiting!
Yeah! Marue breaks ahead!
OH, MY BABY! POWERFUL...
We're back!
Ah! That voice...
Ah, it's goddamn chilly here.
This fella sure is handy!
Being able to do it while standing is not half bad.
Lemme tell you this,
a man's life is friggin' easygoing!
He's a guy for sure.
As much as a guy can be.
Ijigawa-san, please let us be your adjutants
from now on and forever.
'Aight. You have my permission!
Okay.
Shit... This bastard Ijigawa is undermining my authority
even with his willy! Let's laugh!
Ah! Stop! Stop looking!
Ah! Ah! Ah! Make it stop! Uh!
My magic wore off.
Ijigawa...
In the end, being a girl fits me best!
For starters, leaving these looks to a man is a terrible waste!
Eh! She came out of it completely unaffected!
Surely it was some medical condition, that's all.
So? I bet, my little magic trick had y'all freaked out.
You really friggin' believed I was a man!
Rui-chan, it was a magic trick?
The hell! Don't freak us out like that!
I'm so glad, so glad...
"Glad" doesn't do it justice, Jabao-san.
There!
Honmaru!
Ouch!
It's my...
You wench...
That's right. A man of Iyona-chan's dreams.
As a caring and wonderful gentleman,
I can't afford getting mad at that.
That was a feat of your agility, Ijigawa!
Why aren't you mad at me?
Honmaru, that's weird. Hella weird!
You doofus!
You wench...
Such petty stuff isn't enough to affect a man's composure.
Not even this?
Wow, looks interesting! Lemme, too.
And how about this much?
Uh! What a creep!
Honmaru-kun is... weird.
Iyona-chan...
I'm working my way to you as best I can!
Damn it all and this blood-sucker Harako!
If I lose a game of dodgeball to him,
he made me promise not to talk to Iyona-chan
for the rest of my life! Oh no, oh no, oh no...
Honmaru, haste makes waste.
Taru, I need your special training more than ever now!
Okay!
Magical Taruruuto-kun: Midday Dodgeball.
Episode 37
Midday Dodgeball
But... What's dodgeball?
Eh? Hello?
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius