Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Mom?
Mom!
Episode 53
Birthday All Alone
Now, then. Let's all make cards for those
who celebrate their birthdays this month.
It'd be a nice present.
Okay!
Zakenja Neyo also has her birthday this month.
Huh? It's today, actually!
Is that true? Show me, show me!
I wonder what everyone else wrote.
Let me see too!
Happy birthday! Please get along with others.
Try to be a little more honest, you!
I'm the heir to the Harako Conglomerate, Harako Tsutomu.
Listen, you seem promising,
so I could make you my henchman.
As expected of Jabao-san!
Seems like no one was holding back.
Honmaru, what you write? Write?
Let's see, maybe I...
Alright!
Hey, Neyo. Happy birthday.
Please teach me to play kendama one of these days.
- Honmaru
Me write too!
Hey, are you sure, Taru?
Me learned the characters recently. To write my name.
Taruru~
Taru! These characters are backwards!
Neyo is reading the card!
What? Is she really?
Where, where?
Oh?
Exciting. Exciting!
Zakenja-kun.
Wait a minute!
Why did you throw away the card
everyone wrote for you?
See now, Iyona-san? I'm the agent of justice.
Atomic Man Harako!
What's her deal?
That's decisively unforgivable!
Really! She's the worst!
Zakenja-san...
Ignored altogether...
The World Junior Agent of Justice, the Honorable Champion
of Atomic Man contest, I... got ignored altogether!
Neyo, why aren't you happy on your birthday?
Beats me.
Somehow lonely...
Alright! I'll take it on myself to make Neyo happy!
Yeah! You can do it, Taru!
That's a dead end. She'll remain as the "Displeased Neyo",
no matter what you guys try.
Give up.
And I'll make Neyo happy!
Hey! Taru!
You're so caring. Good luck, Taru-chan.
Taru, how do we go about doing this?
This - Tickleflies.
This to make Neyo delighted!
What?
Tickleflies! Body-tickling butterflies!
Did it! Neyo happy!
Nicely done, Taru!
Still, something feels wrong about this.
Happy birthday, Neyo!
Kid, did you do something to me?
Yeah! I did!
Are you kidding me?!
Neyo, wait for me!
This time, I'll make you happy with this Babanger!
Taru! Are you sure about this?
Yeah!
Neyo! Happy birthday!
Are you kidding me?!
I'm still a little dizzy from this bang.
Neyo not happy.
Me in trouble.
Me not give up!
Will make Neyo happy at any cost!
Taru, she's almost here!
Okay!
What is it this time, Taru?
This - seeds of Congratonus.
You spread them on the ground.
Then you water them with this Congratuwatering Can.
And in a blink of an eye, it bears the fruit of Congratonus!
Because tonus is another word for pumpkin.
Here she is, Taru!
Congratonus-san, counting on you!
Sure! Olive it to me!
Everyone, get radish, will you?
Get radish!
Happy birthday! Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
You two are at it again?!
How many more times do I have to say it?
Are you kidding me?! I swear to god...!
Honmaru, full steam ahead!
What's your next plan?
Kendama! Conjure!
Hey, Taru! What on earth do you need this for?
Neyo! Neyo!
Neyo! This for you! Birthday present!
Uh?
She's gone real mad...
That goes beyond mad...
What would make Neyo happy?
What does Neyo want?
Hey-hey, what should I do? Honmaru!
Let me think...
At times like this, it'd be nice to have some detective magic
that can solve any riddle.
Alright. I got this for such cases!
This - Detective Holmestick!
Famous for solving the most perplexing of cases.
Yes. I'm a detective, alright. Itchy-itchy.
Tell us, Holmestick-san.
What present would make Neyo happy?
First, you gotta conduct a background check.
You start by trailing her.
Can you really not know even that? Itchy-itchy.
What a disagreeable guy.
Yeah! Let's do tailing!
Neyo, wait for me!
Neyo!
Stop!
When tailing, you do it in a surreptitious way, you dimwit.
The best first step for that
would be becoming transparent, itchy-itchy.
Okay!
Great! We're becoming invisible people with Magic-kun?
Yeah! Sword-Pen Magic-kun, eraser version
can erase all sorts of things!
Erase, erase, erase.
Me Invisibletective!
Better be quiet now, itchy-itchy.
Zakenja really lives in a place like this?
Big house!
Let's hurry, Taru!
Okay!
Yay! Yay! Elevator!
Apartment 506
Zakenja Neyo
Zakenja Nezo
Oh? She lives all alone with Nezo?
Is that you, Neyo?
It's our birthday today, right?
So what of that?
Mom would probably congratulate us if she were still alive.
What now? A birthday?
It's just a sign that you're one step closer to death.
Brainless nonsense!
I suppose...
Zakenja...
Oh! Try to investigate what's in her heart
with Hearer. Itchy-itchy.
Okay!
Can we really do something like that?
Mom...
I told you! The old man's not coming!
It's not "old man," it's "daddy," Nezo-chan.
Well, let's have some fun, it's our birthday after all.
Very true! Now, Nezo-chan, you cheer up too.
Cheers.
Cheers, alright!
Happy birthday!
Nezo, happy birthday!
Neyo, happy birthday, alright!
Our kind mother...
Mom...
Happy birthday
- Dad
What the hell is this cake?!
Mom... Why did you have to die?
Leave us two behind? Why? Why...?
Taru-chan, goodbye.
Mama...
If my mom died... I... I...
Honmaru, stay strong!
That would be too much for me...
But Neyo has been living with this for a long time...
Compared to her, we definitely are
like some spoiled brats!
I'll go change.
She's been used to living without her mom for eternity while still attending elementary school. You're astounding, Neyo!
Her dad also barely ever shows up at home!
That also doesn't make
the family environment one bit simpler.
In comparison, you could almost say I'm blessed!
You're so amazing!
You assholes! When did you get here?!
Taru! I can see you!
Honmaru! Magic wore off!
What's the matter, Neyo?!
They sneaked into my room without me noticing!
What?!
Aw-aw-aw...
Aw-aw-aw-aw!
What is that "aw-aw-aw?"
Exactly!
Get lost!
Taru...
Honmaru...
Christ, what human trash!
So disgusting.
Do I have to teach you this lesson again?!
What?
Nezo! Neyo!
Mom?
Are you doing fine?
My, how big the two of you have grown! I'm so happy!
What is this thing?
Nezo-chan, Neyo-chan, happy birthday!
I see you're doing fine,
so I'm relieved now!
Mom?
This is a lie!
What on earth is this heart TV?
Are you kidding me?!
Mom,
you're still alive, even now?
Is this a dream, huh?
Mom, where are you now?
People call it the afterlife.
A pretty fun place, if I do say so myself.
It's a lie, a lie! It's a dream, a dream, a dream, a dream!
I'm watching over you two closely from here,
so don't worry.
Really, mom?
You're watching over us?
Now, the longer we talk,
the harder it is for me.
Mom...
She's been watching over us...
It's the best birthday ever.
Thank you, mom.
Good evening! Delivery service here!
Enjoy!
The same shit as always has arrived.
Then, it's getting my accustomed treatment this year as well.
Why did you stop me?
Enough already.
Stop.
Hooray! Neyo happy!
I'm so glad! It's all thanks
to Spiritual TV-phone Hello-hello Itako-chan!
The mountains are nice, after all!
Besides, Iyona-chan's bento is the best ever!
Yay! Bento, bento, bento!
Taru, who is this guy?
This - Yamabiko Taro, an interesting magician.
I like this guy a great deal!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Friends with Mountain Echo.
If I help Yamabiko, we can make the mountain clean!
Episode 54
Friends with Mountain Echo
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius