Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 33
The Grand Adventure in a Picture Book
Get back here!
It burns!
"It burns, it burns!" - our hero Doberk was bravely skedaddling away, making lots of noise.
Well, isn't this protagonist a dumb one?
Honmaru!
Whatcha reading?
It's another book that dad wrote.
And this main character Doberk sure is a bungler type of guy!
How can you be that spineless?
Come on, show some more courage!
Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Relax, I'll let you read it too.
But really, where could you find a guy that worthless?
Honmaru, do you really believe that main character
to be entirely stupid and gutless?
No, I never...
I would have fought with more courage than him!
I'd be fighting with way more courage!
Meaning you wouldn't be running away,
if you find yourself in his shoes?
No! Me - never!
Me too, me too!
Oh?
Sounds promising.
Well then.
Allow me to introduce:
Professtick of Literature, Dr. Into-Book-Putter.
A-hem!
You need but to ask Professtick.
He can put you inside any book of your choice.
Oh, that sounds handy.
Get in now, Honmaru!
Get in and show us all
the courage you bragged so much about!
Alright!
We're going in, Taru!
Okay!
Even if it gets that dangerous,
all I have to do is just to return to our usual world.
A-hem!
Ow-ow-ow.
Look where you're going!
Get off me already!
Okay.
Hey, hey! Handling me with such indiscretion is unacceptable!
What's your deal?!
What?
My mission is to defeat the Great King Dowahaha,
who wants to plunge the world into darkness.
Also, to save the Goddess of Light
and let the light rush into this world again. I'm a hero!
Doberk?
Yes! That's me.
Who'd think I'm that famous already?
That stupid yellow protagonist!
Not at all!
Something interesting, yay!
What's this?
Those who dare to defy me, the Great King,
never make it out of here alive!
What the...
Eugh!
Behold, it is me - one of the Big Four
of the Great King Dowahha: Eland-sama!
Stop running away, you cowardly prick!
You're the one who's the coward here!
You're the one who's the coward,
despite calling himself a hero!
But you're obviously way more of a coward than I am!
There, see? You ran away 50 centimeters further than me.
If you're running away,
isn't it all the same if it's 50 cm or 50 mm further?!
Hell no!
What?!
Whahaha!
Oh, you!
How about that? Watch and learn, Doberk.
It's my buddy who didn't run away,
but is laughing at it right in its face instead!
You fool! What's this naive nonsense?
Eland's main weapon is that beam coming out of his eyes!
Whoever gets showered in it
just keeps laughing out loud until he dies!
What?!
Come on! Oh, come on!
Taru...
Honmaru, rescue me!
Oh, I can't take this... Oh...
Hey! What should we do to defeat hm?
Dunno.
What the hell? Aren't you a hero?
Well, I don't like making a big deal out of it.
Hero Doberk
Here, my autograph.
Screw this!
Taru! Help is on the way!
Stop! You thief!
Give it back! Back!
That's it, that's it! Laugh more!
Keep laughing and laughing, until you explode!
If I dash recklessly at him,
I'm definitely getting showered with that beam!
Oucha-ha! Very funny! Funny!
Rats! How should I deal with it?
Hey... Give back my sword already.
His distinctive feature is his single eye.
Single eye...
I know!
Come on! Come on...
Laugh hard, laugh like mad,
laugh until you're dead!
Single eye comes with the drawback
of being completely exposed from the flanks!
Ow-ouch!
Taru! Redirect the beam back at him with a Bendpost!
Okay! Bendpost!
I'm not about to let you do that!
Good, do it now!
Taru, you idiot!
You got yourself caught again!
What'll we do now, Taru?!
Laughin'!
Bendpost won't work if you don't know the name
of the thing you want to bend.
Oh, I see, Tama-chan!
Except we have no idea what the name of his beam's is!
His beam is called Uwahaha Beam!
Thank you, Doberk!
Alright, Taru! It's Uwahaha Beam!
Uwahaha... Lemme... Uwa... Uwahaha... Oh... Uwahaha... I can't, I can't...
It's useless! Anyone showered in the Uwahaha Beam
forgets every other language!
Away!
Good thinking, Taru!
You can't use your mouth for talking while laughing,
but Hearer can do it with no problem!
Uwahaha Beam!
Taru! You aimed it at the wrong person!
My hand is shaking hard from laughing!
Oh no...
Taru! What the...
Come on, Taru!
Aight... Will take good aim this time...
We got him, Taru!
Did it! Did it!
Nicely done, Taru!
We did it!
How about that, monstrous ilk?
Giving up already?
We beat him pretty hard, didn't we? Hm?
Well, so be it. The monster is beaten, after all.
Taru, get ready to return to our usual world soon.
Yeah!
What's up?
I've lost Professtick of Literature,
Dr. Into-Book-Putter that sister gave me.
Wh-wh-wh-wh-what?!
That was Great King Dowahaha's pet,
the Bat-Dragon!
What now?!
That's why I told you
not to handle me with such indiscretion!
Help me, someone!
Imbecile!
You can't return to our world without it!
According to this map, the path to the Great King's castle
lies through a fight with his numerous minions.
I wonder if we can manage to bypass
at least some of them without a fight...
What's wrong with just fighting all of them?
You're so cowardly.
Cowardly! Cowardly!
I despise unnecessary violence, that's all!
Coward. Coward!
I'm not, ya hear?!
What's a "coward," Honmaru?
Perarenka Village
That coat of arms!
Ah! It's a ghoul!
Good folk of the village!
The legendary hero has materialized!
The one destined to defeat
the Great King Dowahaha, Doberk the Hero!
Please, deliver our world from those misfortunes!
Welcome!! Doberk the Hero and his entourage
Pass your judgment on Great King Dowahaha!
Doberk! Doberk!
Don't hesitate to let our brave hero Doberk
take care of everything!
So cowardly before monsters, so bold before others!
And these two here are my loyal servants -
the Wizard Taruruuto and Honmaru!
What now? Since when am I suddenly your servant?!
Honmaru-san!
Oh my! Amazing!
Yeah!
Our dear hero, may I possibly have a word with you?
Iyona-chan!
My name is Mayoi.
And this here is Momomo.
Momomomo!
The matter is...
Ever since our world started its descent into darkness
at the hands of Great King Dowahaha,
Count Rakula was also gaining power...
Count Rakula?!
That's right.
Count Rakula obliged our village
to yield one young maiden to him monthly.
What a vile bastard! Right, Taru?
Yeah!
So far, Rakula has already imprisoned
40 of the village maidens in his castle.
I beg you, my hero! Rescue our maidens!
Hey! What'll you achieve by running away?
You only say that because you've no idea
how dreadful the Count is!
Not everyone commands one hundred and eight
blood-sucking bats! He's a great magician, mind you!
Bats! Bats!
He used to be vulnerable to sunlight, but ever since
the world descended into darkness, he's become invincible!
My good hero...
Iyona... No, Mayoi-chan.
Doberk! You're nothing but an excuse for a hero!
Hey, everyone! Let it be known
that I'm the one and only real hero here!
Real here!
Honmaru-sama!
This job ain't half-bad so far!
Your village was saved the moment I showed up!
Hooray!
My dear hero, I'm sure the Mountain Wizard Pororon
will gladly teach you a way to bring about the Count's demise.
Ah, and also, you might want to bring this child along.
When a peril is drawing near,
he'll let you know by skipping around.
Momomo-mo!
I won't need such a thing!
Yeah!
Hey you, stupid Count! Hey you, stupid Great King!
Come face me, Honmaru-sama!
Yeah!
I'll bring you down in an instant!
Wait a minute! I'm not done! People, hey!
What's this?
Ill-wisher! Ill-wisher!
What the damnation are you?!
One of the Big Four
of Great King Dowahaha, Count Rakula.
Please show me how you'll bring me down in an instant.
Cretin! If you don't visit the Mountain Wizard first,
you won't last a minute in a fight!
Do it, my blood-sucking swarm.
Help me!
Seems like enough.
I don't feel so good with my blood sucked out...
Taru, at least do something...
Honmaru, I got whipped, too... No strength left...
Should've went to see the Mountain Wizard, after all...
Is that all you got? How disappointing.
Hand Power!
Thanks, grandpa!
We're saved!
Much obliged, Mountain Wizard!
It appears that some wandering heroes wound up at my place!
All that could have been avoided
if you would have come to train with me for a month first!
Beard! Beard! Beard.
Ah! Whoa, whoa!
This girl's blood is getting better with every sip.
Don't you think so, too?
Oh, dear count! If you play with me tonight,
it would be oh so lovely!
You're trembling so hard now.
But once you imbibe some of my blood, you'll be
just as fascinated with me as any one of my other girls.
No!
What is it?
Sorry to interrupt!
You bastards! You survived our previous meeting?!
Let Mayoi-chan go!
How impudent!
My blood-sucking family!
Wah!
Nicely done, Taru!
His bats are able to catch the reflected ultrasound
that they emit with their own cords.
Their hearing is superb, because they use it
to find their way around obstacles in the dark.
You'll neutralize the blood-sucking swarm
if you shout at them real loud!
Wah!
Ka!
Ka!  Wah!
He's strong!
The Count has his weak point as well.
The key to defeating him
is to make him imbibe his own blood.
Taru! We need a blood sample!
Okay!
You little... Once More Hand Power!
You've learned some new moves!
That's the way, Taru!
Fell for it! This time for sure, Hand Power!
Taru!
I've had enough of your meddling, you shrimp!
This time, I'm making sure you're done
by drinking every drop of your blood!
Once the Count's fangs sink into him,
he'll be beyond saving!
Taru!
This - Self-Projector-kun.
You project a copy of yourself
to anywhere you direct its light at!
We did it!
The count is sipping his own blood!
That's... Such nonsense... Did I... Did I just lose?
Argh! Unforgivable! Next time, we attack all at once!
Get this!
Don't let your guard down, Honmaru.
Soon you'll get a taste of the true power of Dowahaha's army!
Damn! Great King Dowahaha!
Give back Professtick of Literature, Dr. Into-Book-Putter!
We'll never be able to return to our usual world without it!
To me, this world is fun too!
Honmaru, will you be heroing here for the rest of your life?
What are you saying, Taru?
I've had more than enough of this world!
But Honmaru, you seem to very enjoy it
being together with Mayoi here.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
This is Your End! Great King Dowahaha.
Episode 34
This is Your End! Great King Dowahaha
Don't miss it, people!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius