Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Honmaru!
One, two...
There!
Episode 49
Down the River with Kappa
What's wrong, Honmaru?
My eyes hurt!
Oh! Deep red!
Honmaru didn't wash eyes thoroughly after the pool.
That's only natural!
It's their fault for pouring so much chemicals into the pool!
Honmaru, if you don't like the pool,
let's swim in the river.
Don't say such nonsense!
Swimming in a filthy river like this
is a surefire way to get yourself sick!
River dirty... Poor river.
Come to think of it, grandpa told me once...
When grandpa was a kid himself,
he could swim in this river himself.
And he used to fish here.
Who was it that polluted the river?!
Who?
Taru!
What's that thing?
I'll go check it out!
Hey, Taru, wait for me!
This must be a kappa doll.
Kappa?
Kappa!
It moved!
Power-Upple Juice to cheer you up.
Taru, could that guy actually be...
Kappa!
Kappa kappa!
I knew it! It's a real kappa!
Me Taruruuto. You who?
Me is kappa Kotaro. Kapa-kapa.
Thanks a bunch for aiding me out!
Kotaro, what are you doing here?
Kotaro?
What's wrong?
I don't know this place!
I wanna go home, Kappapa...
What do we do, Taru?
Help Kotaro return home!
Ah, right... That's right.
Hey, Kotaro, we'll bring you home,
so stop crying, okay?
Seriously?
Yeah.
Me happy, so happy Kappapa!
So, where exactly is your home?
I don't know, don't know anything, Kappapa!
Kappa-pa...
Good grief...
It makes sense that he washed up here from upstream.
But if that's the case,
there must be some place he calls home
in the upper reaches.
Kappa...
But how should we even go about doing this?
I got you covered.
We'll ride the Fish-All-Around to there.
Fish-All-Around?
Yeah! An amazing ship parked in my secret base.
Are you serious, Taru?
Alright. Time for an emergency deployment of Fish-All-Around!
Yeah!
Kappa!
So you're a kappa, huh?
That'd be Kotaro the kappa.
And that'd be Mimora.
I always thought kappas were extremely stylish!
Stylish?
That's right!
Search-search, found!
This - Pointurner.
You point it at something and that something
is turned into whatever you'd like.
Kappa!
Kappa! Kappapa! Kappapa!
How about this, Taru-sama?
Mimora stylish!
Now, let's get him home!
Home, home!
Trunsform.
Wait, Taru-sama!
Flying in! Flying in!
Is this the entrance to your secret base?
Yeah. Come in, everu-ru-ryone.
This - the way to secret base.
Everyone, follow right after me!
Alright, coming in!
Kappa!
Kappa-fun!
Taru, isn't this...
Taking off!
Someone please help!
Fish
I-I didn't plan on getting eaten today, sir!
That was just the lid closing.
That's a cool one, Taru!
Yeah! This - Fish-All-Around.
Perfect for swimming smoothly through the water!
Alright! Is it my turn to see some action?
Fish-All-Around, takeoff!
Forward                         Back
Kappa!
My head is spinning!
Kappapa! This is scary!
Taru, there's the exit!
Taru! Don't just stare idly, do something already!
We can make Fish-All-Around eat this Telepotato.
Eating this teleports you to the place of your choice.
Thanks for the meal!
Taru! Hurry up!
To where Kotaro the kappa was lying exhausted, let's go!
Faster!
Oh! It brought us to that river!
That's impressive, alright!
Power
Alright. Next step is eating this Power Potato.
This one is even cooler than telepotato,
gives you enormous power!
Fish-All-Around! Now you can easily
swim the river upstream!
Heck yeah!
Power Up!
Kappapa!
Taru-sama's magic is always a little crude.
What the?
It's alright. We just got caught in a garbage bag.
Fish-All-Around, be more caru-ru-reful!
Will do!
Yahoo!
There's still fish!
It's fish, sir! It's fish!
That's quite some way we've come, Taru.
About where are we now, Taru-sama?
Fish-All-Around, show us the scenery outside!
Heck yeah!
It's so peaceful here...
Eugh!
Why do they have to look so stuck-up?
That'd be near where our house is, sir!
Really?
They'd be my friends, sir.
Aren't you glad?
That'd be there!
That'd be my home, past that big cliff, sir!
Kappapa!
Planned golf course construction site
Our house... Our house, sir... Kappapa!
Taru, you gotta do something!
Okay.
President!
Once this golf course is completed,
we'll be making even more green!
I see.
The reason Kotaro got swept away
was because they ruined Kotaro's home!
Kotaro!
Kotaro, ahoy!
Kappapa!
Kotaro?
Sister!
My sister's there!
Kotaro, hurry up to meet her!
Gro-ro-ro-row!
Kotaro!
Sister!
Kotaro...
Kotaro!
Sister!
I'm so glad!
Sister?
It can't be!
Kotaro...
Kotaro!
Taru-sama, please, please hurry up to save them!
Okay!
Kotaro, run away, now!
Not without you...
Ko... Ko...
Kotaro!
Taru-sama, I'm leaving Kotaro's family to you!
Taru! Rush to save Kotaro!
Okay.
What is it?
President, we're in trouble!
The workers believe that kappas live around here.
And now they refuse to disturb them any further,
saying the place is haunted!
What?
Kappas are haunting them?
Do you think you can make any money
when you're scared of such bull?!
Stop the construction!
Restore the river to its natural state!
It's a kappa!
I said stop the construction this instant!
What's that nonsense?
I'll catch a monster such as you
with a snap of my fingers!
You said I'm a monster?
That was the final straw!
Stop the construction.
Silence! Nobody tells me what to do!
Hey! Wake up!
Get the police! No... the Self-Defense Forces!
Okay!
My! I've said it so much times,
but you still won't listen?
On my land, I have every liberty to use it however!
What liberty are you talking about?
If you destroy all the nature,
kappas would also go extinct!
What's it to me?
Kappas should apply to live in a zoo or something.
Actually...
If I build a kappa center,
I'll make even more profits from commercializing them!
What was that?
That's it! You're getting no mercy!
Kappa!
The hell?!
It's that kappa!
Hey, looks like a real kappa!
Alright, let's catch it!
You're wrong! It's me! Me!
The real kappas are over there!
This kappa thinks it can trick us humans!
Well, how does it feel now?
Construction canceled
*Repurposed for agriculture
Your turn, Kotaro.
There!
Kappapa!
In the end, rivers are the best for swimming!
Yeah!
I'm happy for you, Kotaro!
Nannosho's big endurance contest
This hot summer, on August 18th
Your body will get even hotter!!
Prize: trip to Hawaii for two
Supplementary prize: shaved ice (all you can eat!!)
Delicious!
It's so tasty, Taru...
It's tasty, Honmaru.
At times like this, cold shaved ice
is what the doctor ordered!
Wanna eat! But we also don't have money.
Ah! Leave that to me!
If we win the endurance tournament,
we'll get all-you-can-eat shaved ice!
Alright, I'll do my best!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Gritty Endurance Contest.
Episode 50
Gritty Endurance Contest
It's delicious to even look at...
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius