Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 8
Magic Ball Baseball!!
The teacher looks like she's about to scold us again.
Baseball
Baseball!
My blood boils for it.
The king of sports!
Baseball
In this ball...
A romance.
A dream.
A sensation!
A magnificent youth!
So today...
we divide the class in two
to play a match against each other.
Your team is your 8 classmates
sitting in the same row.
Lucky! I'm in the same team as Iyona-chan!
Honmaru, looking happy.
Once more, Taru's magic will be the game changer.
With me hitting a home run!
Honmaru-kun, nice!
And a strikeout when throwing!
Honmaru-kun is cool...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru!
Taru!
What's he thinking? Let's hear it.
Taru.
My team's gonna win, hands down!
With such a solemn pledge of victory,
you must have some confidence to boot.
How did you find out?
We winners!
Taru?
I used Hearer
to put things from inside your mind into voice.
Well, so be it.
Yes, teacher! As long as our team has me and Taruruuto in it,
we're not letting the victory slip away!
The smallest dog barks the loudest.
Well, not for long.
For I was reared by the American Junior Major League,
where I'd always pitch for the entire game.
Naturally, you're clueless about my professional average
of 70% batted balls, you cocky mongrel.
Just you wait and see.
Just like the king of all beasts, the lion
won't stop at anything within his power to crush the rabbit.
Thanks for the meal!
Taruruuto, let's practice for the match!
And the winner is...
The closest one to the hallway, my row.
Alright, catcher! Are you all ready?
Wait a minute, Honmaru.
I use Attractor-kun.
Incorpora-ra-rate!
Can throw, Honmaru.
I'm going in!
Each ball like the last one!
Ball!
Amazing, Taru!
With this, we'll have nothing but strikes!
Honmaru, good pitch!
And mine's pitch isn't that harmonious.
What is it, Taru?
Toilet!
Even Magicians can't do without a toilet.
Neither can I...
It seems the drug is starting to take effect.
I added a dose of laxatives
to your and Taru's school lunch.
What? You... You friggin did it...
When the name of Harako Conglomerate is on the line,
losing to the likes of you is absolutely out of question!
It's unhealthy to be holding it for too long.
Honmaru-kun, what's the matter?
We need to hurry,
they're starting soon.
Iyona-chan, I...
Pledged to win, right?
Without a doubt!
Iyona-chan, let me help.
Thanks.
Harako Atoms
Big Edo Magicals
Play ball!
Catch!
Safe!
No outs and all bases are loaded!
Honmaru-kun...
What has Taruruuto been doing this entire time?
We can't afford
going to the toilet at the same time...
Crap...
The next batter is Harako!
Damn it...
No way I'll ever let myself lose to you!
Still, my body and soul are at their breaking point.
Honmaru, I didn't forget to wash hands!
Sorry, teacher.
I will be the catcher.
Taru?
Took you long enough, damn it!
Sorry, Honmaru.
Now throw!
One shrimp more or less
won't make any difference!
Watch the white ball disappear into the blue sky!
He just pledged a home run!
Taru, I'm counting on you!
My soul is leaving my body...
Yet I can't leave the game!
Not even a ball that's bound to fall
deserves any sympathy! Hey!
This is the swing of the Major League!
Ball!
What?!
Strike!
Enough ball.
The ball sped up while it was on the way!
Is that really Honmaru's pitch?
A miracle ball!
Honmaru-kun!
I just need to wrap this up quickly.
Then I'm hitting the toilet!
I bungled the throw!
A wild pitch won't help you.
Ball!
Another miracle ball?
Strike two!
He pitched two miracle balls in a row?
Honmaru, you scum!
Yet I can't lose either!
If it passes through the strike zone,
I will hit it!
You won't hit a single one of my pitches!
Ball!
Impossible...
I flew right in, even without the throw...
Strike! Batter out!
Honmaru, nice!
You did it!
Gonna strikeout the rest of them as well!
Batter out!
One strike!
Two strike!
Batter out!
Harako Atoms
A heavenly relief...
What's that?
Impressive!
Is he really in elementary school?
A little trick from the Major League.
A 180-kilo blazing fastball.
Nobody has been able to hit it yet.
Harako!
What was that for?
Got nothing better to answer?
Oh well, I guess our defeat is established.
We don't lose!
We winners for sure!
Taru, you got some useful magic for that, too?
Got!
Power-Upple Juice!
Power-Upple Juice?
Drinking this apple-ies
an incredible power-up on you!
Thanks for the good stuff!
That helped! Somehow, I feel like
my body's overflowing with power!
It's your turn, Rui!
Is it just me, or had Rui-chan
grown somewhat bigger lately?
Must be just due to her acting more confident.
You there! Harako!
Show me that rookie ball of yours!
Even if you're a woman,
you're not getting any mercy!
kyaaa
I see it!
Upple Juice power-ups eyesight as well.
Caaaatch!
What?!
Ground ball to the first base!
Safe!
What are you waiting for?
A corpse would react quicker than that!
Next is Iyona's turn.
Give me your bat.
Taru!
What are you trying to do,
drawing a face on the bat?
You'll see.
You drew a face on the bat for me?
Iyona hit with this.
Taruru!
Do your best, Bat-Taro-kun.
Doin' my bestest!
She hit my knuckler with her eyes closed...
Looking good!
Taru!
Alright, alright! Taru!
I need you to make me even more herculean than that!
The guy who does what nobody else can.
Surely, there's magic for that?
Attractor-kun?
I will incorpora-ra-rate him into the bat.
Damn you... My pitching is flawless!
It's the fielders who are all thumbs!
Die, Honmaru!
Ball!
This ball is not a hitting back material!
The ball?
Taru!
Field!
Limpy-kun will manipulate Honmaru's body
to make him look the most herculean!
Taru!
The hell!?
Safe!
Amazing! To do a head-slider
all the way from the batter box...
Easy-peasy!
But consider steering less extremely, Taru.
Crap... Those three are in the field already.
The next batter will be your terminal point!
What?
Harako! Throw already!
That pesky brat!
Nobody messes with me!
I am unbeatable!
Wah
You scared the life out of me!
Lemme have a good aim.
Taru!
Taru! It's a hit! Run!
I run!
You thickhead!!
If they touch the home base, it's an out!
Safe!
You absolute morons!
Out him on the first base!
Huh?
Honmaru, let me ru-ru-run ahead!
No way! If you overtake me,
you'll be scored with an out!
Bunch of blockheads!
Sandwich them between 1 and 2!
Tarururu
Cheer
This fine by you, Honmaru?
Iyona-chan!
IYONA!
Stop sabotaging me!
Out them on the third base!
Kick!
Kya!
Like this?
This is super-fine by me, Taru...
Out them in the home already!
I'm coming to cover you too!
Taruruuuu!
Bobo-kick.
Bang!
Home-in!
A running home run!
Alright, me too!
Then, I will, too.
Don't touch her breast!
Spare us your filth, Harako!
Three out! Change!
Teacher, why so?
A player that touches the home base
before the previous runner does, is outed.
And then, Iyona-chan was also touch-outed.
Ouch!
So, the overall gain is just one point for Ijigawa-san.
I see. So it's him.
If I just drive the imp away from here,
Honmaru's team...
Anything I can provide for you, Young Master?
I need a favor of utmost urgency.
Yes. Will do right away.
Move it!
Got it!
Taru!
Hey! Where are you going, Taru?!
Someone lost a takoyaki here! Got you!
And lost here, too! Got you!
And here too, here too!
Right, right, right.
This is sure to lure him out.
We just need to keep the bizarre boy
tied up here for long enough.
Sorry.
Hey, kid.
Have you heard already?
Today is Takoyaki Day!
Takoyaki Day!
You can eat takoyaki to your heart's content.
Aren't you hungry?
Takoyaki Day! Takoyaki feast!
Yummy!
That's the spirit...
Keep your jaw busy until the match ends.
This way, no one stands in the way
of Young Master's victory!
Make more!
Make even more to keep it coming!
Taruruuto, where are you?
Just where the heck did Taru run off to?
It's no use getting mad, Honmaru-kun.
My victory is already inevitable!
But it's Taruruuto's turn at bat!
Besides, we have two outs already.
And the runner is only on the first base!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
This Harako schmuck avenged his grudge
by throwing straight at me!
This is our last chance to turn the tables!
Honmaru.
Taruruuto!
Honmaru!
How did your body become like that?
Takoyaki burp...
Taru-chan, you've grown so big!
Just where have you been all this time?
Today is Takoyaki Day.
Can eat all the takoyaki you want.
First time I'm hearing of this.
Just get to work!
It's okay, I'll hit.
What is it?
Our guilt is grave, Young Master.
After feeding him all 23,000 takoyaki,
we had no other means to pin him down!
We are all terribly sorry!
Well, whatever.
This outta be enough to curb his movements.
The sufficient effect was achieved.
Bat unwieldy this way...
Laughable escapade!
Someone has to give this kid
a rough side of the tongue!
Good idea! Taruru!
Don't you make fool out of me!
Don't let us down, Taruruuto!
Taru-chan...
My tongue can do it!
He hit it with his tongue?!
That's it! Home run!
Great, Taru-chan!
Ball-blast!
The fireworks that went off with a fiery bang!
Today is Takoyaki Day.
Celebrate with fireworks.
Damn it! If we catch all the fragments,
we can still out him, you dimwits!
You'll be safe with me, Iyona-chan.
Home-in!
Taruru!
A winner!
I am unbeatable!
Hey, Taruruuto! I bought us some takoyaki!
Thanks for the meal!
Taruruuto! Why did you eat them all yourself?
Our friendship is over!
Honmaru scrooge, scrooge, scrooge!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Takoyaki of Friendship.
Food ones are grave offenses.
Episode 9
Takoyaki of Friendship!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume