Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Girls' restroom
Why is it fine for Otoko,
but I'm suddenly the worst?
Iyona-chan, you can't favor him that much
just cause you're dating!
Well... Well, that's because Otoko-san is a girl.
Surname's Otoko, and first name is Onna.
That said, I'm biologically a girl, though.
Episode 72
Duel with Otoko!
Hey, Taru! Let's go grab a bite of takoyaki.
Yay! Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Even if I leave you, soon enough...
Matsu-san, we're here!
Oh! If it ain't Taru and Honmaru!
Matsu-san, bake some sooner!
Alright! It'll be ready this instant!
Very well. Let's have a takoyaki duel today, Honmaru-kun.
Uh... Otoko Onna?!
Me duel too!
Well then, five takoyaki boxes for everyone.
Let's see who'll be the first to finish them.
'Aight, coming right in!
15 takoyaki boxes for three clients!
I'll put in all my guts while baking these!
Let's do it, Honmaru-kun.
When it comes to takoyaki speed eating,
you stand no chance in a duel against us!
Yeah! Me fast!
Ready?
Startin'!
Yay!
Already gobbled them all!
Me number one!
We have a winner!
As expected of the Nannosho
Takoyaki Speed Eating Champion, Taruruuteya!
Your prowess is fabulous!
I lost this one.
That was a spectacular victory, Taruru-kun.
It was a good match, Honmaru-kun.
Yeah...
Finally, sir. I may have lost the duel, but at the same time, I'm glad I could eat your delicious takoyaki. Thank you.
It's my honor...
So fresh...
If my guts serve me well,
that's one fine man, I say.
Honmaru has a gift for making friends
who are all sorts of fine men.
Matsu-san, Otoko is not a man.
Ah... What I mean is... Otoko is a woman.
I ain't buying me none of that metropolitan claptrap, Honmaru.
Men had always been men, and women had been women,
that's how it was since the beginning of times!
Eh... What I mean is... Otoko is actually a woman,
even if her name is Otoko...
Honmaru, me go play together with Otoko.
Hey, Otoko!
Um... Matsu-san, I'll give you the details
some other time, alright?
Wait for me, Taru!
Hey! Can't you hear me, Taru?
A man is not a woman, but a man... Um...
Man, these elementary students sure have
all sorts of stuff in their heads.
Tsk...
I'm almost out of pocket money, thanks to Otoko...
Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan, cram school's good and all,
but you gotta take a break every now and then.
Iyona, come play tag with us!
Sounds good.
Then, maybe we stay for a bit
and have some fun, Rui-chan?
Sure. When Otoko-san is inviting,
turning her down is not an option.
Hey, Honmaru-kun!
Come join us too!
Come duel with me
in a game of tag this time!
Honmaru, come! Come!
Tsk. What's the point of holding a duel in a game of tag?
Before, I used to just play along passively. But now
I understand - Otoko and I have nothing to compete for.
I mistakenly thought Otoko was Iyona-chan's lover,
so I convinced myself that I can—by no means—lose to her.
But having learned she's actually a woman,
I'm relieved now.
So I no longer need to prove anything with a duel.
Honmaru-kun, come along!
Okay!
Rock-paper-scissors!
How about once more?
Me the "it"!
Honmaru-kun, once either of us
becomes "it", the duel is on.
Whoever catches everyone first, wins.
Now, run away!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
Ijigawa, touch!
Whoa! Already?
Iyona touch too!
Iyona-chan, leave this to me.
Try to get us, Taru!
Keep it up, Otoko-san, Iyona-chan!
Otoko-san!
Don't worry, Iyona-chan!
Otoko, you rogue!
Carrying Iyona-chan away...
Iyona-chan also looks so happy in her hands!
It doesn't matter if Otoko is a girl or not,
I'm still jealous!
Touch!
Did it! Caught two at once!
Seems like I lost to you, Taruru.
But if it wasn't for Otoko-san saving me,
I'd be in Taru-chan's prison long ago!
When I hang out with Otoko-san,
I forget the passage of time completely!
That freshness!
Despite being a girl, she's both manlier
and cooler than me, a man! It's unacceptable!
You sneaky bastard...
Honmaru touch!
Alright, that makes everyone caught!
As expected of Honmaru-kun!
He kept trying his best until the bitter end.
So admirable!
Don't you laugh at me with that fresh laughter...
Honmaru! We've no time to eat the meal as usual!
Yeah!
These days, every class has to scramble
for a court in the yard.
It went down the wrong pipe...
What are you doing, Taru?
Stre-re-re-retch!
Thank you, Taru.
And I'm done!
Stop taking your time, Honmaru! Let's go!
Come on, dodgeball is waiting!
Hurry up, Honmaru!
Me coming too. Wait for me!
Dammit! I gotta make it there fast!
Let's have a duel, Honmaru-kun!
Our Class 3 will be the first
to grab a dodgeball court!
This girl sure loves to duel, doesn't she?
I'll do it, Honmaru-kun!
Stop sticking so closely to me!
Hey, Honmaru!
Dammit! We've been beaten to the punch?
All the courts are already taken!
Honmaru, there's still one over theru-ru-ru!
Oh! Well done, Taru!
Think I'll lose?!
First one to get there wins!
Honmaru, it's our victory!
Let's draw the field togetheru-ru-ru!
This way is faster!
Thank you, Taru!
What the... What is this?!
Honmaru-kun, I was the first to grab a court.
It's my win.
That's Otoko-san for you!
Okay, let's play dodgeball now!
Hey, Honmaru! You grabbed a court?
Sorry...
What?! You dumb slowpoke!
What did you say?
What have you been doing yourself?
Don't act as if you're any better!
Honmaru-kun, did you get a court?
About that...
That klutz is no use to anyone!
It was foolish to rely on someone like Honmaru in the first place.
I was so looking forward to it!
This is what you get for counting your chickens
before they hatch, Jabao-san.
Accept responsibility, Honmaru!
Don't you feel bad blaming this on Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru-kun.
If you want, we could use our court to hold a match between your Class 1 and our Class 3.
Sounds interesting!
Alright, let's do it! Do it!
Yahoo! We'll get to play dodgeball, after all!
Thank you, Otoko-san.
It's a duel between us two, Honmaru-kun.
Yeah!
Whenever and wherever she's doing something,
it feels fresh and too cool!
Alright, since it came to this,
we gotta settle it for good.
With a true man's pride at stake,
I'll make sure to show everyone my amazing side!
Watch closely, Iyona-chan!
Everyone, let's show Class 3 what's what!
Yeah!
We won't lose either!
Our teamwork is honed to perfection!
Yeah!
Otoko, I'll destroy someone like you—
I, Jabao-sama, will teach your class of snowflakes
why dodgeball is a sport to be reckoned with!
It falls upon me, Harako Tsutomu,
the World Junior Dodgeball Championship Grand Prize Winner to show you my Super Play—
Hey! My name is Ryoguchiya Korekiyo, remember?
You idiots! Stop blabbering around already
and get into your positions!
This class is completely disorganized.
Now, who wants to fight for the jump ball?
As for the ball, we trust your class
to find a good use for it.
Harako, don't decide for everyone!
Against a class this amateurish,
it'd be more than enough to have me alone on the field.
Therefore, at least some sort of handicap feels fair.
Such great confidence!
Harako, one wouldn't wish to find an enemy in you,
but having you on our side is reassuring!
In this case, I won't be holding back with this ball.
Here it goes!
Otoko-san is so cool!
No matter how cool you try to look,
I'll receive a ball from a woman with my eyes closed!
I'll do you the favor of catching it!
Damn it! My ball...
It was my ball!
Harako, stop kidding around! It's not volleyball!
Come here, pretty ball.
I see! You were planning to catch the ball
after weakening its power.
Yay! Me catch it!
Hey! This is my ball.
What?!
Harako-kun, you're out.
That's it! One got self-destructed by his lack of teamplay!
Taru! That was your fault!
Why did you do it?!
Sorry, Harako.
To think that I would be the first to get outed...
To think that I...
To think that Harako Tsutomu-sama would be...
Come on, come on, come on! Get the ball rolling!
Hurry up and pass it to me! You obtuse imbecile! I hate you!
Harako, one would be terrified to find an enemy in you,
but having you on our side is embarrassing...
Okay, let's resume the match!
Alright! I'm going in, Otoko!
You can do it!
You can't stand up to the power I forged
in the mountain retreat!
I'll show you the power of a true man!
Behold and dread!
Amazing, Honmaru-kun!
As expected of Honmaru-kun!
You're burning with passion already.
She caught it like it's nothing...
It's my turn now!
Stay out of the way, everyone!
Taru! It's dangerous, get down!
Okay! I'll deflect the ball with Repeller. Dodgeball!
Jabao got outed next!
What the hell, Taru?!
Jabao.
You bastards, now you're obliged to revive me!
Come on, come on! Get the ball rolling!
I was the first! Pass the ball to me!
Alright, Harako, Jabao, I'll roll the ball!
Taru, you need to throw it hard!
It's fine, I'll throw with my tongue.
Not bad, Taruru.
Alright! Good job, everyone.
Jabao-kun, Harako-kun!
What?!
Otoko amazing!
Class 5-3 is close-knit.
Our teamwork is impeccable.
We're not about to let you have the ball.
Otoko-san, fight!
Do it, Otoko!
Dammit! For our Class 1 to have a chance of winning,
we need to take out Otoko first!
What's that? A pass?
Throw it if you have the balls!
Catching a girl's throw is easy as pie!
Man, this cute longhair!
I did it!
Why the hell are you a man
with that kind of face?!
You have a girl who looks like a boy,
and a boy looking like a girl!
Why is nothing what it seems
to be in Class 3?!
We're sorry for your loss, Honmaru-kun.
Shut up! There's still no way you could beat us!
I'll definitely get revived so I can come back and get you! Along with the match!
Hey! Toss the ball to here sooner!
Give me a pass!
Give the ball to me!
I'm your key to victory!
What was that?! Why, you...
My turn is the first!
Alright! I'll do my best with magic.
Taru-chan, this is a match.
Magic is cheating, so it's unacceptable.
I don't mind, Iyona-chan.
Taruru's magic is a marvelous power
that he developed on his own.
It's not cheating.
Really? Well, if Otoko-san says so...
You're nice even to your enemy, Otoko-san!
Dammit, Otoko can even afford
saying things like this...!
If the opponent says it's alright,
use whatever magic is necessary, Taruruuto!
Don't be picky with your methods!
Just send me the ball!
Alright. First, I'll take the ball with Attractor.
Dodgeball!
Ah, what the?!
Got that...
Come on, come on, come on, come on! Pass me the ball, Taru!
Will use Fangust-kun to neutralize the enemy ball.
Hurry up and pass the ball!
Stay strong, Taru!
What are you doing?!
If only I was still in the game...
Hey! Pass it here already!
Don't worry about anything!
I have a lot of magic yet to try!
Bendpost!
TVkinesis-kun!
Huh?
There!
Limpimpy!
Ah! No! Stop it! Ah, not here!
How about this?
Scared already, Otoko?
Idiot! Idiot!
Taru, you bastard...
Our defeat is inevitable at this point!
It's all your fault!
Taru...
Taru-chan is the only one left! Hang on!
What an utter fool I had been!
Oh? Nobody but me left?
Alright. I'll beat the entire Class 3 with one ball!
Seems like the victory is ours, Class 3!
It was a good fight!
We lost...
Throw and gro-ro-row!
Hooray! I've beaten everyone in Class 3!
Otoko-kun, it was a good fight.
Because of Taru, the match turned
into a ruckus again...
But it was your victory, Otoko.
Honmaru-kun.
In order to not lose to you, a woman,
I must also grow manlier, cooler than ever before!
Though I'm a little jealous,
you're wonderful, both of you.
Taru...
Didn't everyone have fun playing dodgeball?
What are you talking about?!
Rival, Rival!
Hey, Rival!
Honmaru, Rival is acting a bit strange.
Seems like he's been pretty depressed for a while now.
Rival, what's the matter?
Eh? Did you say it's because Mimora-chan hates you?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Diary of Rival's Pure Love.
Rival, keep doing your best for Mimora!
Episode 73
Diary of Rival's Pure Love
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius