Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru!
What is it, Taru?
Honmaru, me learned a great thing.
Eh? What? What is it, Taru?
Want me to tell you?
I do want you to tell me!
It already sounds like some mighty useful magic!
Please! Tell me.
Taru?
I will tell you...
Well, I'd be awfully obliged, Taruru-sama!
Look, Honmaru.
Okay!
We take one straight stick
Is it a leaf?
It's not a leaf, it's a frog now
It's not a frog, it's a duck now
On the sixth of sixth month, it rained
Crack the triangle ruler in two
Please give me two sweets buns to wear
Please give me three beans as buttons
Please give me two bread buns to hear better
Ah! Before you know it, you got a cute cook-san!
Episode 75
Taruru! Cook-san
So?
That was all?
Impressive, isn't it?
What is?
Me can sing and draw at the same time!
Every kid knows a drawing rhyme like that!
Me was the only one who didn't know?
Yes.
I was the only one who didn't know...
Taru?
Look, you shouldn't be that dispirited.
That's right!
We're practicing cooking
in home economics today.
I'll be sure to treat you to some delicious miso soup!
That's a deal, okay? So cheer up now!
Okay! Me cheered up!
Listen, Taru.
When cooking miso soup,
what do you think determines the broth's taste?
First, we soak the kelp in water and heat it.
That's where the most important part starts.
The trick is to remove the kelp before it boils.
Once this is done,
it's time to add dried bonito.
Let's sprinkle it like this...
Once it comes to a boiling point, turn off the heat.
Now, you do this: filter it through the cloth,
and your broth is ready!
It takes time and effort,
but that's how you prepare the best broth.
Honmaru amazing!
Not there yet.
It's time to complete the dish.
When cooking it with tofu,
do not let the broth boil, keep the heat low.
When it's already in the pot,
rock the tofu back and forth a little.
And start adding the miso through the sieve.
The important thing here
is that the miso absolutely mustn't boil.
Once the miso is pasted in,
it's ready to serve!
Honmaru prepared miso soup!
Thanks for the meal!
Honmaru's miso soup is fantastic!
Why wouldn't it be?
It's my mom who taught me how to cook it!
Oh, he's right!
This miso soup is actually good.
Isn't it true what they say,
don't judge a book by its cover?
You've actually done it, Honmaru!
True! It's delicious, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru.
No matter how good you say it is,
it's still just miso soup.
Nothing to be proud of.
What's your problem, Harako?
Yes, Young Master?
One serving of the Harako Special Atomic
Delicious Soup that I made for everyone.
Yes, in a moment.
We've had our computers analyze
gourmet reports from around the world
to recreate the flavors of the planet's top chefs.
That's not nearly all.
It is the ultimate soup that has been carefully calculated
to be healthy, not to mention low caloric!
For what his bragging is worth,
Harako's soup is awesome!
Yeah! Harako delicious!
My superb culinary abilities were once rewarded with the
World Junior Scientific Cooking Contest Special Cook Award.
Naturally, comparing it to Honmaru's miso soup,
is like comparing the moon to sixpence.
But hear this. Somehow, eating Honmaru's miso soup
makes you wanna keep eating it every day.
Yes. I guess you could say there's a certain
nostalgic feel to this taste, Jabao-san.
That's true. It feels like Honmaru's soup ever so slightly
warms me all the way to the heart.
Iyona-chan...
You've grown in my eyes, Honmaru.
I'd like a refill.
Honmaru, give me refill too.
Me too!
I'll have a refill too.
How about this, Harako?
Fine!
Let's have a cooking duel, Honmaru!
Bring it on, Harako!
It was a mere trial run today.
In a serious competition, you won't stand a chance!
This Sunday, we'll settle it once and for all
whose cooking abilities stand supreme!
Oh!
As Nannosho's first gourmand,
Jabao-sama will gladly provide his judging expertise!
Sounds interesting!
I'd like to attend too.
A cooking duel? Must be fun!
Right, Honmaru-kun?
Yeah!
Um, wait... Wait a minute!
Wanna chicken out, Honmaru?!
That's not it!
It's just that even if we call it a cooking duel...
I can only cook miso soup!
What?
You're just trying to make us laugh, right?
This idiot, who can only cook miso soup, seriously
considered dueling Harako Tsutomu—the genius cook!
Tsk. And I already thought I'd get to see
another engaging duel.
Can't be helped. If only Honmaru knew how to cook
anything other than miso soup.
Listen, you!
Instead of Honmaru,
compete against my magic's cooking.
Taru...
Deal?
Oh? Against magic?
Very well. I accept it.
Scientific cooking versus magical cooking?
Now this spells some real fun!
Harako, let's do our best.
Make sure your hand is steady, Taru.
In all the duels up to now,
Taru's magic was the prime source of my humiliation.
However! If I beat his magic now, fair and square,
I'll restore my reputation all at once!
Once again, Harako Tsutomu
will reign supreme over the whole world.
Tsutomu Fight.
Say, Taru, are you sure
you should've signed up for that?
For starters, do you know any cooking at all?
I don't.
You don't...
And you're zero in conjuring magic as well...
Yeah!
It'll be fine. Don't worry, Honmaru. Let's go!
Gramps,
I can't, by no means, afford to lose this duel.
I understand.
Commence the preparations at once!
Taruruuto's Magical Cooking VS Harako's Scientific Cooking
Well, everyone, thank you for waiting!
Here, in the hall of the Harako Sports Building,
at last, the time for the onset
of the cooking duel is approaching!
Please note: as a special judge today,
the renowned connoisseur or the cuisines of the world,
picture book author
Edojo Shogunosuke-sensei is also attending!
I'm honored.
Also here, known for being picky with how her lunch tastes since at least her elementary school days, Oaya Mari-sensei.
Other than that, some other members
of Class 5-1 who volunteered to judge.
Even dad came, dressed to the nines!
Hey, Honmaru's papa!
You're playing dirty, Harako!
Why did you only furnish
your own kitchen with cool gizmos?
Don't chide in, Honmaru.
This is a duel between Taruruuto and me.
If he wants those,
he's free to conjure some with magic.
Yeah! Duel of me and Harako!
With that, the full course cooking duel
between Taruruuto and Harako begins now!
The ultimate ingredients
collected from all over the world, just for today...
Also, created with the use of a computer analysis
of the world's five star restaurants' best dishes:
the best menu of all time,
never having been experienced by anybody ever!
The masterpieces I'm going to make will awe everyone...
Behold! The brilliant kitchen knife handling technique
I learned from France's top chief!
Wow! Look at Harako!
His knife handling is like that of a pro...
No! It's way above that!
Moreover, calculated into perfection,
high-tech cooking!
Indeed, he's a terrifying young chef with a terrifying scientific cuisine approach!
As expected of Harako!
Always able to live up to his claims,
thanks to his abilities!
On the other hand,
the magic dish chosen by Taruruuto is...
Oh! My name is Taruruuto! I'm dueling Harako!
Taru!
This is not the time to be playing around!
Taru, do you even have any plan
for your magical cooking?
Yeah!
I should be alright wearing this.
Ah! A True Storing?
You're gonna say that you won,
and you'll really win, right?
We take one straight stick...
Taru, what are you doing at a time like this?
What on earth is Taruruuto
planning to do with this stick?
Is it a leaf?
It's not a leaf,
it's a frog now!
It's not a frog, it's a duck now
On the sixth of sixth month, it rained
Crack the triangle ruler in two
Please give me two sweets buns to wear
Please give me three beans as buttons
Please give me two bread buns to better hear
Ah! Before you know it, you got a cute Cook-san!
What is that thing?
Cute Cook-san,
please treat everyone to some delicious food.
Will do right away, croak.
Taru...
Quack-quack, quack-croak. Quack-quack, quack-croak.
Oh, he's actually doing it?
Yeah! He's great!
That creepy cook is a power to be reckoned with.
Now then—the first dish of the day,
hors d'oeuvres, seems ready!
The three major delicacies of the world—caviar, truffles, and foie gras—were used extensively in this Harako special...
Hot patties under Perigord-style sauce!
Oh?
Let's start by trying Harako's dish first.
Delicious!
I see.
The three delicacies are blended harmoniously
to create a luxurious and elegant taste.
Indeed, it's as though...
this rich flavor melts in your mouth!
It's a work of art!
Now then, what will Taruruuto's response be
to Harako's wonderful hors d'oeuvre?
A croquette?!
The outcome is predefined already.
There's no way I can lose to someone like that.
Taru!
Everyone try it sooner!
I never thought croquettes could taste this good!
Overflowing in the crispy fried batter,
this creamy flavor melts in your mouth!
It's an unpretentious dish, but the one with a
really deep flavor that shows the chef's attention to detail.
An enchantingly gentle and multifaceted taste.
Truly wonderful! I'm so glad to be alive!
Hurry up and serve us the next dish already!
Just a moment, croak.
Taru, it seems like he's better received than Harako.
Yeah! Good luck, Cute Cook-san.
What is this Cute Cook-san bullshit?
Alright! Let's have a duel
of the main dishes!
This is an important duel
that will serve to restore my reputation.
I absolutely cannot lose this!
Gramps!
Yes, Young Master.
Please trust me to take care of everything.
Uh?
Huh?
Taru! Our water's been cut!
Cook-san!
Have no worries, croak.
What should we do now?
What?!
Such clean water.
This water is natural rainwater.
Young Master...
We're out of potato starch!
Well, whatever. We can just croak this.
What's that?
It's the natural starch, croak.
What?! Natural starch instead of potato starch?
I consume the sunlight with my leaf lips
to perform photosynthesis to produce starch.
Gramps!
Yes! Roger, I'll take care of it right away...
Come on! Are you ever gonna serve me the dish
that I entered the jury for?!
Hey!
Over there!
If this continues, we may have to start deducting points.
Come on!
Taru, this ain't looking good!
Leave it to me, will you, croak?
Eh?
Impressive.
Impressive!
Since it came down to this...
Harako Special Quantitative Strategy!
Petit sautéed beef with Bordelaise Sauce!
Dobojo-style lobster stew!
Gastronome-style beef pillow!
How about this?!
As you'd expect of Harako!
He came to this duel with an assortment of main dishes
that boasts luxury both in terms of quality and quantity!
Now this is what I call a main dish!
I never had any idea
such an abundance of foods exists on earth!
Do I even deserve such luxury?
I got this duel in the bag.
Congratulations, Young Master.
That said, what is the Cute Cook-san's dish?
I can't call it particularly luxurious...
But why is it so good?
You can feel the heart of the person who
prepared the dish, and it makes you feel so elated!
Thank you, Cute Cook-san.
Harako-kun, you can use up all the ingredients on Earth and have the computer calculate everything,
but it still won't be on par
with food that has soul in it!
Indeed, the magic cooking
is the one brimming with soul.
Cute Cook-san, this is your victory.
Impossible...!
Cute Cook-san's cooking
makes you wanna taste more and more of it!
I wanna try your bread!
Jabao, don't be so selfish!
Bread, croak?
Scary!
Please eat this, croak.
No way! Without ears, Cook-san will become deaf!
That's right!
I still have my left ear so it's fine.
Why is he going that far...
Hey you, creepy-faced frog!
Is that how you're planning to win the duel?
I'm not cooking because I want to win the duel, croak.
I keep doing my best because I like seeing the smiles
on everyone's faces when they are happy with the food I make, croak.
Cute Cook-san...
"Because you want to make everyone happy?"
I see!
Cute Cook-san...
My magic wears off in ten minutes...
The Cute Cook-san left us...
However, we're still due for a dessert round
in the cooking duel!
No matter how hard we try,
we can't compete with Harako.
It's your win, Young Master.
Accept my congratulations.
Honmaru.
Taru.
Harako?
I lost this one.
Ten minutes is enough.
However, today, I didn't lose to you two.
I lost to that Cute Cook-san.
Yay! Cute Cook-san wins!
Harako...
Cute Cook-san...
Thank you!
I'll never forget your cooking.
It was so good!
Thank you, Cute Cook-san.
Take one straight stick
Is it a leaf?
It's not a leaf,
it's a frog now
It's not a frog, it's a duck now
On the sixth of sixth month, it rained
Crack the triangle ruler in two
Please give me two sweets buns...
When Neyo opened her heart to me,
she was warm like the sunset itself.
Honmaru, Neyo is getting beaten!
What a bunch of bastards!
Even though she's a girl...!
Neyo covered in bruises.
Neyo is actually a very kind girl!
Honmaru!
What's wrong, Neyo?!
Gonna lose all your spirits so soon?
Something strange with Honmaru and Neyo.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Special Training for Neyo!
Episode 76
Honmaru!
Taru, I'm serious this time.
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius