Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 68
Heated Skating
Good, 6 o'clock exactly. After that mountain training,
I always wake up at the exact same time.
Wake up, wake up!
Wake up this instant!
Wake up I said!
Off I go. Time for morning training.
What?
What's that? You're still sleeping?
That's dangerous.
Don't drive while you're asleep.
Honmaru, I'm going too, on my
Three-Wheeled Attack-Type Combat Vehicle Tricycle-kun.
Taru, don't force yourself.
It's still too early.
Me and Honmaru friends. Always suppo-po-po-port...
Taru...
Say, Taru...
Yes?
Do you think I've become a man that's suitable for Iyona-chan?
Have become!
And then, Iyona-chan said she loves me, didn't she?
Yeah!
Well, as for me, I also love Iyona-chan
more than anything in the world!
Yeah.
Which means this feeling is mutual!
Listen to me till the end, Taru!
I'm just getting to the best part!
Iyona's smell!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun, Taru-chan, good morning.
Sup, Iyona!
Iyona, are you also training this morning?
Yes. A volleyball match is coming up.
Iyona-chan's sweat is glistening beautifully.
Good luck, Iyona-chan. I'll be rooting for you.
Thank you. You keep up
the good work too, Honmaru-kun.
Sure.
More than anything in the world,
I loved Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru-kun, what is it you're working towards now?
What I'm working on...?
Well, that should be obvious by now.
Why does Iyona-chan even need to ask?
I'm doing my best to be fit for her.
Because Iyona-chan said
she wants to become the wife of a wonderful man.
Marue-chan, when I grow up,
my dream is to become a wife
To wear a pure white wedding dress,
and live with a kind and wonderful man.
And have... Five or six children.
That's why I'm working hard to become a wonderful man,
one that's able to protect and comfort Iyona-chan.
You're so cute, Iyona-chan!
Looking at me so intently with your big eyes...!
Iyona-chan, I love you!
I've been into you for an eternity.
Oh? This doesn't feel right.
Hey! Since when have you been listening?
Taru, did you put Hearer on me again?!
Yeah! 'Cause I'm doing my best for Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan heard everything I was thinking...
This is bad. Very bad!
No! I mean... That was...
Iyona-chan, you heard him, right? Well...
What do I do? What to do? I'm so screwed! Shit...
Enough already! I'll say it!
I love you! Let's get married!
Married!
I'm so done!
Iyona-chan didn't actually love me?
I see! It's because Iyona-chan
is such a kind-hearted girl,
that it didn't matter who from the class dies,
she'd say the same thing...
Even if Harako died...
I actually loved Harako-kun!
Even if Jabao died!
I actually loved Jabao-kun!
Even if Korekiyo died!
I actually loved Korekiyo-kun.
She'd definitely say the very same thing!
Ah, how could I... How could I be such a naive fool?
I was so conceited,
jumping to the wrong conclusions!
But now that I've said all sorts of weird things,
she'll hate me!
Hate you...
Honmaru, let's run after Iyona.
It's no use following her.
She came to hate me already.
Wrong. Iyona loves Honmaru.
Ah, really?
Me understand Iyona's feelings.
I can do without you comforting me, Taru.
Rival! We'll rectify your obnoxious habits
with an early morning marathon!
Now, follow right after me!
Fight!
I ended up with a woman who's off her rocker!
Taruruuto!
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama! Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
You woke up so early to go for a jog?
That's very admirable!
Mimora...
A good morning kiss for good boys.
Mimora-chan, what are you...?
Taru-sama, I love you!
Ain't they lucky? Children are so innocent.
Why are you staring so suspiciously at me?
No, I just thought about
how you're always full of energy.
Why shouldn't I be?
It's all thanks to my great love for Taru-sama.
Whatever happens, I must be cheerful for him.
Whatever happens?
Then, even if Taru came to hate you...?
Yes. Even if that dark day of history ever comes,
I would still love Taru-sama until the end of times!
My love is not so uncertain
as to be shaken by something like that.
I see!
I'm sure you would do the same for me, Taru-sama.
Yeah! Me love Mimora.
Oh, you're so not getting away with it, Taruruuto!
Hey! Why are you slacking off here?
Yes, ma'am!
Then get going! Off you go!
Okay!
I understand, Mimora-chan!
Even if Iyona-chan came to hate me,
I'll still love her!
Alright, we'll chase after her!
Taru!
What a rather primitive fella.
Alright, Honmaru.
Iyona!
Taru-chan's magic again?
Pulled Iyona back with Attractor.
Iyona-chan...
Well...
Do you remember this?
Raser?
Raser had seen his share of misfortunes.
So he ended up looking like this.
I got him from you once.
And I've cherished it ever since,
always keeping it close to heart.
In times of joy, or in times of grief, whenever I see Raser,
I seem to always regain my motivation, somehow.
Therefore, even if you come to hate me, I... I... I...
I would still love you.
Honmaru-kun...
Nice mood!
Mimora, get your Limpy-kun out too!
Yes, at once.
Sorry, Honmaru-kun.
It's just that it happened so suddenly...
Honmaru-kun, are you free tomorrow?
Would you like to go skating together?
Eh?! For real?
Honmaru, mood is great!
Time to give Iyona a kiss!
Yes, Taru-sama.
No! Honmaru-kun, you pervert, pervert, pervert!
Ouch...
You try to slack off as soon
as I turn my eyes away!
A healthy mind comes from a healthy body!
So keep fighting!
Okay!
Damn you, Taruruuto! I'll remember this!
Taru, why did you do that?
Iyona-chan was so upset about it,
for real this time!
Sorry, Honmaru.
I'm sorry, Honmaru, dear.
It was your fault.
Sorry, Honmaru.
Honmaru, you've got a call!
Who is it?
It's from Iyona-chan.
Hello? Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan, you've nothing to apologize for.
I should be the one to...
Honmaru and Iyona made up!
Good for you, Honmaru!
Yes, I'd be happy to.
At 10 o'clock?
Honmaru, what happened?
Me wanna know too.
Oh?
Oh, I do that a lot too!
I can't wait to meet Iyona in person,
not over the phone!
Huh?
Again?
Come on, Taru!
No, it was nothing.
Alright! Honmaru...
If you use Promptelephone,
you can see her in person right now.
I've been learning figure skating since kindergarten.
Oh?
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
Hello?
What? What? What is this?
This - my magic.
With Promptelephone you can fit yourself
into the phone mouthpiece.
Then you send yourself to the other end
via the telephone wires.
Nicely done! That's one useful magic!
Um... The phone is getting very heavy, though...
Hey Taru, how do we get out now?
It's fine. We'll get out in no time.
Huh?
Two cannot fit through it at once, no sir.
Are you telling me I'll stay like this forever?
Don't worry, Honmaru.
In ten minutes, my magic will wear off.
You want me to wait ten minutes?!
No! It's heavy!
I'm sorry, Taru-chan, Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru got a date today!
Yeah! That's what happened!
Honmaru looks happy.
Yeah...
Still happy?
Yeah!
Yeah...
I got a date!
Honmaru really happy!
Me happy too!
Is that clear, Rival?
After you finish cleaning, laundry, and shopping,
don't forget to do 100 push-ups and sit-ups.
Yes, teacher!
Come bleh-ack soon...
It's as if I had the time to work now!
I need to exact my revenge on Taruruuto!
Nannosho Ice Arena
Good morning, Honmaru-kun.
Hey, Iyona-chan!
Taru-sama!
Oh, Mimora!
This makes it a double date, doesn't it?
You're right!
Okay, let's go!
Mother, why do I have to wear something like this?
It's really embarrassing...
My!
You're going skating with Honmaru-kun?
I can't go?
For a daughter of the Kawai family,
just skating would never suffice.
Iyona,
wherever you go, you must skate
with grace and splendor.
This is the only outfit that would avail you to do that.
You aren't allowed to go unless you wear this!
With this, the gentlemen's hearts would be yours!
Better already!
You sure are taking your time, Iyona-chan.
Oh! Iyona's here.
A staggering outfit, Iyona-chan!
Iyona looking cool!
Ugh! Taru-sama too!
An outfit like that is a shortcut to catching a cold!
Amazing! Her white and clean skin is all out...
Honmaru drooling!
Please don't stare at me, Honmaru-kun.
No!
Sorry, Iyona-chan!
I do wonder why she chose
that outfit in the first place.
Women are so inscrutable!
Everyone is staring.
I knew it would be embarrassing, mother!
Those looks are so scrutinizing!
Amazing, Iyona-chan!
Just skating around
in these clothes is embarrassing indeed.
But if you take that chance to show off your skating techniques, the awe would displace embarrassment.
I'll do my best, mother!
Great, great!
Bravo!
Well done, Iyona-chan!
So cool, Iyona!
Just a couple of cheap tricks.
Okay, I'll skate too.
Did you see that guy?
He'd find a thousand and one ways to fall!
Sli-li-li-lip!
This is fun! Everyone sli-li-li-lips!
Come on, Taru!
You can't play tricks on people here!
I slipped, so everyone should sli-li-li-lip.
In skating, falling is a foul.
Uh, actually.
Taru, isn't there some magic
for skating well without falling?
I'm a complete zero in skating, you see...
Taru-sama!
Please drink this.
With this Balansolution, you'll be able to hold your balance perfectly and without falling.
Can I have some too?
It's a little sour.
Taru!
Me skating!
Look how well I can skate, Honmaru!
Yeah! I feel like I can't fall at all!
This is great!
Iyona-chan... I'm here!
Honmaru-kun, you're so good at this!
Taruruuto!
Having all this fun with Mimora-chan...!
Unacceptable!
Alright! Time to turn it around
with the Transformation Belt!
I'll turn invisible and send him flying from behind!
Transformation!
Make me an invisible man!
That's it!
You'll fall flat before Mimora-chan's eyes!
I'll expose your most miserable side to her, Taruruuto!
There!
Taru-sama...
Eat this, you parasite!
Whoa! That was fun!
All thanks to Balansolution!
As expected of Taru-sama!
With spectacular midair turns!
I just fell even deeper in love with you!
You scum!
I'll destroy you this time!
Even more spectacular this time, Taru-sama!
Iyona-chan!
Are you okay, Iyona-chan?
Thank you, Honmaru-kun.
Lucky! Thanks to the Balansolution,
I even saved Iyona-chan!
Damn you, Honmaru!
I'll make you pay for my humiliation as well, you ass!
Taru-sama! Look, look!
Rival, care to explain why you're here?
And the work I tasked you with
was abandoned, I assume?
No, you see...
Just as I thought, your nasty habits...
cannot be rectified by any other means!
I didn't mean to... Ow! It hurts!
That's enough! Ah, Sensei! Forgive me!
Honmaru, skating is fun!
That's right! It's the best ever!
Iyona-chan, as long as I'm with you,
you'll always be safe.
Right... But Honmaru-kun,
would you mind putting me down already?
Oh, you don't need to be shy!
You're not actually one bit heavy, Iyona-chan!
That's not the problem...
Oh? But I like it this way!
Achoo!
What the hell is this haircut?!
Hey, Taruruuto!
It's your doing, isn't it?!
Oh! Honmaru, looking cool!
So brushy-brushy and nice!
No! It's spiky-spiky and cold!
That's how my head is now!
I can't go to a New Year's party like that!
Do something!
Okay...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
The Greatest New Year Ever!
This better?
Episode 69
The Best New Year Ever!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius