Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Happy New Year!
Everyone!
We wish you...
A happy New Year!
This year as well...
Thank you for your continued support!
Why Honmaru not bowing properly?
Taru! Do you ever consider others' feelings?
What?
Don't you remember what you did to me on New Year's Eve, Taru?
On New Year's Eve?
I forgot everything that happened last year.
Daily rip-off-a-page calendar
What? A barber?
Your hair has grown quite long indeed, Honmaru.
Right! After all, it's best to enter the New Year
with a spruced up head!
Me spruced up too!
Are you done cleaning your room?
Sure thing!
The bath?
Shining clean!
Alright, I get it! You can go now, guys.
Thank you, dad!
However!
Make sure you end up looking as manly as you can.
Okay!
Episode 69
The Best New Year Ever!
I'm excited visiting a barber for the first time!
Thank you, come again next year!
Next client, please take your seat.
Taru, you can go get a haircut first.
You don't mind? Thank you, Honmaru.
Hm, that's impressive hair you got.
How would you like it cut?
Any cut is fine as long as it's spruced up.
A bowl cut would do!
Yes, that's good.
Okay, understood.
Cut-cut-cut-cut.
The barber's is a funny guy!
There, it's done.
How about this, Honmaru?
Looks pretty good on you!
Except it's hella weird!
Yay!
Alright! I'll take care of Honmaru's cut!
Taru!
There's no need...
Next client, please.
Okay!
Don't be shy, Honmaru!
Stop it, Taru!
I wanna do Honmaru's head!
You can't be serious!
I don't need my head turned
into a nightmare come true!
Please, Honmaru!
Never!
Understood.
Jeez!
Barber-san looking happy.
Alright!
I'll stop the time and do it myself!
If I do it right, no one will notice.
Okay, everyone stopped.
Let's cut some hairu-ru-ru!
I'm actually good at this.
Cut some from the front too. Cut-cut.
Oh! Honmaru looking manly!
I've a gift for being a barber!
Now, where was it...
Will do the back with the buzzer!
Oops, it slipped.
Oh, looking like a nice road!
Alright, let's build an intersection!
Will ride to the front too!
So much fun!
Forgot...
I played on Honmaru's head...
So cool!
Yay! When magic wears off,
it'll be lots of fun!
Huh? My scissors?
This...
How could I do something like that
without even realizing?!
If the word gets out
that I did such a thing to the client's head...
I gotta do something.
Alright! This kid's gonna hate it,
but I'm gonna have to shave it all off!
Why are you cutting more?
That cut is already top grade!
Ah! What the hell is that cut?!
If someone sees me with a haircut like that...
Eh! Weirdo cut!
Honmaru-kun, what is this hairstyle?
Honmaru-kun is weird.
Honmaru is a weirdo in everything!
My life is over!
So sorry! I don't know how this happened...
Honmaru, why you don't like that look?
It's totally cool!
Now I see... Taru, it was your work!
Taru!
It was fun!
Wait, you!
I'm so sorry! Of course, I'll give you a refund...
Please don't apologize.
Since it can't be helped now,
please just make everything short.
If that's what you wish...
Thank you as always!
Phew, he let me off the hook.
Honmaru.
Hey, Honmaru! Looking cool!
Right, right! Just super!
Honmaru, I'll do something with magic!
You'd better!
This - Helpflute-kun. You can use it for various things.
So what?
I'm sorry, Honmaru.
And the tune for growing hair is... Found it!
That's good! It's coming out, Taru!
You did it! As expected of a great magician!
I'm so glad! Honmaru is smiling again.
It grew!
I'm not Nobita, I'm Honmaru!
And this is really not something to laugh at!
Sorry.
Taru!
You two!
Dad!
Why the hell do I suddenly have
this excuse of a haircut?!
Did you have a hand in this?!
Everyone who hears this flute gets the same haircut!
Taru!
It's fine, my magic wears off in ten minutes.
Until then, just wear these earplugs.
What? Ten minutes?
Gonna have to bear with it for ten minutes.
I suppose.
That's right, man! Taru's magic wears off in ten minutes!
Yeah!
That flute seems interesting!
Let's play with more different hairstyles!
Yeah! Leave this to me, Honmaru!
I forgot again.
Taru's magic wears off in ten minutes, after all.
Sorry, Honmaru.
What do we do now, Taru?
I can't show up in town with a head like this!
It's fine! With a hairdo like that,
nobody would recognize you.
That doesn't make any sense!
Ah... How can I waltz in there and say hello
to Oaya-sensei and everyone like nothing happened?
Sorry, Honmaru.
Perhaps, I should try to help you?
Sister Ria!
You want a hairdo that looks
like the one you had before, correct?
Can you do that?
Ke-Ke-Keruru!
What?
Keruru, keruru!
Oh, Keruru?
Keruru?
Keruru is buddy of Niruru.
It can transform into whatever hairstyle you want!
Which means...
Honmaru's hairstyle!
Honmaru!
That's it! With this, I won't be made
into a laughing stock!
I'm so glad, Honmaru!
You'll have to make do with this
until your hair grows back.
But be careful.
Keruru and Niruru are very alike,
so if it sneezes, it'll go back to normal too.
Okay! I'll be careful!
Keruru, seems like we'll be stuck together for a while.
That's really delicious, Honmaru!
Yeah! It's the rice cake soup cooked by mom!
It's the best New Year's day ever!
There's still some rice cakes left.
Then, can I have a refill?
Me too, me too!
Wait for your turn!
Then, wait just a minute.
That's right, Honmaru.
Some New Year's cards arrived.
Eh? What's in them?
Ah! This one is from Iyona-chan!
That's a great New Year already!
Iyona-chan! I love you!
What's wrong, Honmaru? Read it sooner.
I know, alright!
Let's see...
Happy New Year!
Thank you for taking care of me last year.
Honmaru-kun, girls don't like it
when you stare at them lewdly.
Take care.
Let's remain good friends forever. Iyona.
Iyona-chan doesn't think of me
as of anything more than a friend!
Worst New Year ever...
Don't lose heart, Honmaru.
It'll get better one of these days.
I wish...
Excuse me!
Ah! Grandpa!
What?
Father, I apologize.
In truth, we should've visited your place instead.
Hey now, let's not say something so trite
first thing in the New Year.
Grandpa, happy New Year!
Counting on you this year as well.
Right, happy New Year.
Isn't that a nice way to greet an elder?
It feels like this year I got myself three grandchildren at once!
Now...
Here.
I'm glad to be able to give you New Year gifts like that.
Ah? For me as well?
Hooray! It's the best New Year already!
Thank you, grandpa!
Oh! Honmaru, look, ten pieces in mine!
Whoa! A whole stack in here!
It's the best New Year ever!
Oh! Sister got a lot too!
I hope I put enough in there.
If it's not enough, just let me know.
I hear kids these days have a lot of expenses!
Father!
An amount like that
is too much for the children!
That's right, Father. We build our upbringing
on austerity and simpleness.
"Father?"
"Upbringing?"
When it comes to upbringing...
What do you know about upbringing?!
You delinquent mongrel!
Who do you think you are to talk about upbringing?!
This'll teach you some!
Stop it, father!
It's New Year's Eve!
Hey, Matsu-san!
What's tha'?
Congru-rutulations!
Oh? Congratulations.
Counting on you this way as well.
Yeah! You can count on me.
With this, I'll feed myself to death with takoyaki!
Oh? That's quite some buck you got.
The New Year's gift I got from grandpa.
Sure you wanna spend it all at once?
It's okay!
Taru, that'd be a mistake to do.
What?
They say that Tokyoites are used
to living paycheck to paycheck.
They don't mind spending all the dough
the same day they receive it.
But in Osaka, those who spend themselves to death
are called buffoons.
You either invest it or save it. Thanks to that, I never
have any trouble when Boss comes to collect his pay.
Money is important stuff.
You gotta make the most of it.
Exactly. Matsu-san is talking pure wisdom!
It's the best New Year ever!
So I'll save my money.
I understand, Matsu-san.
I wanna eat Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Me love takoyaki! I'll make the most of my money
by getting Matsu-san's business goin'.
Matsu-san always kind to us,
so I won't regret it!
Oh, really?
Much obliged, Taru!
Taru, just admit it - you didn't really understand anything!
What are you talking about?
Well, so be it.
Honmaru-kun?
Iyona-chan is terrific in her long-sleeved kimono!
This is the best New Year ever!
Congra-ra-ratulations!
Congratulations!
Accept my congratulations.
Congratulations.
Honmaru-kun, I was looking for you.
You promised to come
to Oaya-sensei's house today, remember?
Huh? Is it that time already?
But did you come all the way here just to pick me up?
Yes...
Honmaru-kun, here...
What? New Year's card? But why?
Well... For some reason,
I just ended up writing another one...
Besides, I sent out the previous one a long time ago.
Please take care of me next year as well!
But in the end... Isn't it silly?
I couldn't even find the words to write.
I look forward to hanging out
with you this year.
This is mutual, Iyona-chan!
This is the best New Year ever!
Now, shall we go?
I think everyone else gathered together already.
Sure.
Right, when everyone sees you in a long-sleeved kimono,
I hope they don't swoon right away!
Long-sleeved...
Honmaru, Taru?
Oh!
What do you think?
I donned a long-sleeved kimono too.
Pretty!
Looks absolutely stunningly, Sister Ria!
Best New Year ever!
Geez, Honmaru-kun...
Yes!
And here!
Oh, Honmaru! Ah, Iyona-chan!
Wow, beautiful!
Ria is not too far behind either...
Teacher! Happy New Year!
Congratulations. Glad you could come.
Iyona-chan is beautiful!
Yeah, like champ and cheese,
compared to someone here.
I think you meant to say chalk and cheese!
What's that supposed to mean?
No fighting!
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama, I wish you a Happy New Year!
And... Thank you very much
for looking after me throughout the last year.
I look forward to your continued guidance
and support in the coming year as well!
And... In addition, everyone wished...
Good health and...
What was it?
Mimora, I'd be happy to look after you again this year!
Taru-sama!
She actually practiced a lot for this!
Really?
Mimora-chan!
Be quiet!
Rival, I'm sure something good
will happen to you this year. Don't lose hope.
You think so?
Yo! Happy New Year!
Oh, Harako!
So much for a peaceful party.
Oh, is that... Neyo, how come?
Now that's rare!
See? That's why I didn't wanna come!
Have no worries, everyone!
For Harako Tsutomu, #1 winner of the World Junior Street Corner Pick-Up Contest,
hooking up with any girl is not a problem!
What's that hooking up bullshit?
You just pulled me here by force!
You just can't stop lying!
What was that?!
Then, who was it that kept skulking around,
too embarrassed to come in?!
You promised not to tell...
Why can't you be more honest?!
Are you kidding me?!
You wanna fight?!
Stop!
It's nice that you're so full of energy
on New Year's Day.
Now, how about everyone
sits down where there's empty...
That's what I would've liked to say,
but my place is rather cramped.
Teacher, how about we hold
a badminton tournament outside?
Oh, yeah, I like it!
Forgive me for the inconvenience.
There!
Okay!
Wow, did it!
Honmaru!
What the hell are you doing?
What is the meaning of this, Honmaru-kun?
You don't seem to understand your position yourself!
Thanks to you, we'll have our faces
pitch-black on the New Year,
which is preposterous and unprecedented,
because ill weeds grow apace indeed!
Is that clear to you?!
Oh, why am I getting the shaft alone?
Worst New Year ever!
In badminton, much like in martial arts,
you need to hit with all your might.
The men's team is nothing to worry about
as long as I'm here!
Wearing long sleeves for badminton was a bad idea,
I can barely move... Do your best, Rui-chan!
I'm glad I came in plain clothes, knowing that
something like this might happen! Right, Zakenja?
Oh my? I wonder who was it that made a giant stain
on her long-sleeved kimono right before the new year?
You take that back!
Why should I?
Let's go!
Alright!
Here!
Honmaru!
Sorry, Honmaru-kun.
I'm so worried about my wig coming off,
I can't move well at all!
Do your best and cling tight to me, will you?
Yay, paint me more! Pitch-black! Pith-pitch black!
Alright, Taru! That's when magic should come handy!
Yeah! I'll do something.
Hey! I heard "magic!" That's unfair!
Well, isn't it fine?
We'll forgive them on the occasion of New Year!
There!
Leave this to me, Honmaru!
No!
The best New Year ever!
A sublime sight to start the New Year!
See? Good pigs happen when you wrist expect!
"Good things, when you least expect."
Nicely done, Taruruuto!
Alright, go for another one, Taru!
Okay!
Honmaru-kun, you...
If that's how they wanna play...
What's this?
It tickles!
Oh, Honmaru, that's Butterfluster!
It makes you laugh even more than Itch-Itchocolate!
Ah! We learned the lesson, make it stop now!
But that looks fun to me too!
Oh no, not you!
Achoo!
What the hell is that haircut, Honmaru? Look at yourself!
What's that crap?
Come to think of it, Honmaru-kun is weird...
Looks interesting!
Yo, Ikkyuu-san!
Why did it come to this, Taru?
Leave this to me, people!
Butterfluster, fly away!
Wow, everyone looks so happy!
What's a better way to celebrate?
It really is the best New Year ever!
It sure is delicious! Being able to eat anything
is a proof of good health!
Chocolate, shortcake, crepe, marshmallow!
Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Sweet roll, cream bun, peanut bread!
Takoyaki!
Ah!
It hurts! My tooth hurts!
Honmaru, you eat too many sweets!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Throbbing Caries Bacteria!
Eating takoyaki will cure you!
Episode 70
Throbbing Tooth Bugs Infection!!
It won't...
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius