Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru-sama, "aaah!"
Finally, you grew to accept my love humbly,
and yet you're still being so unaffectedly kind to me!
That's exactly why
I fell so madly in love back then!
Taru-sama...
Damn you!
I will never forgive Taruruuto!
He and my beloved Mimora-chan
have even started living together!
I'm so jealous!
Episode 18
Rival Strikes Back
Taru-sama...
I'm so happy!
Ah! Honmaru!
Y-y-you little...
My, this pains, pains, pains!
I can't listen to it anymore!
What's wrong, Honmaru?
As if anything has ever been right!
It's not even noon yet,
but you're being lovey-dovey already!
Not a hint of concern for me!
Ah! Iyona-chan...
Honmaru can do lovey-dovey with me!
It's this man...
This man is the root of all!
The reason for Taru-sama's lingering in this world -
is this vile man named Honmaru,
who had seemingly seduced him!
Fine, fine!
We'll see about that,
when I turn your face into a pig's.
That'll help Taru-sama perceive the truth,
he'll return home with me in no time!
Mimora-chan, what is it?
Pork-Bonk.
If this hits you, it'll turn your face
into the most disgusting pig's mug.
Wait!
Taru-sama! Filthy man is turned into a pig,
so you can't play with him.
How about playing with me, instead?
Mah... Oink! Oink.
Honmaru looking so funny!
Oink...
You'll be fine.
Mimora's magic wears out in 30 minutes.
Oink! Oink! Oink!
Honmaru, Mimora let's go play outside!
If it's Taru-sama's wish...
Taru-sama!
Oink!
It was because I followed Taruruuto into this world,
that Mimora-chan also arrived into this world, following me.
Whatever I try,
I just end up serving him a foil!
Just like back then in our world!
Rival!
Fly, fly! Fly! Damn it...
Magic-free Zone
↙Magic❌
No way!
Magic invalidated
No use of magic here!
Magic❌
Magic invalidated?
And what can this line be?
No use of magic
⬅(on this side)
Rival!
It would take more
to stop The Great Magician, Rival-sama!
I got it, alright?
No use of magic past here!
Mimora-chan!
With this, Mimora-chan...
will realize the extent of my feelings!
I found it, the Engagement Grass!
Legend has it that
if a woman receives this as a proposal gift,
she and the man she marries
are bound to become the happiest couple ever.
The ultimate manifestation of love -
the Engagement Grass.
Got it!
The flower... is unharmed.
Unlike me.
It hurts. It hurts so much!
Mimora-chan...
She's here. Here! Mimora-chan is here!
This one moment...
I don't know how long I've been waiting for it!
Here!
Mimora-chan!
Huh?
Kyaaa
Ran by?!
Did someone call me just now?
Taru-sama!
My! Taru-sama, isn't that the Engagement Grass?
If you gift this flower...
If you gift it to me...
Taru-sama, that would mean you love me
more than anything!
Taru-sama, even though you always
put on an act of indifference,
making it look as though my love is unrequited,
in reality, you also
always had a soft spot for me!
I'm so glad!
Our love is mutual!
I am honored to receive this flower
from Taruruuto-sama.
Take this, take this, take this!
Taruruuto, you rogue!
Here again, Rival?
No way I'll let you spoil a moment of perfect harmony
between me and Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan, you're misled!
It was actually me!
This guy Rival...
is disgusting!
Are you kidding me?
I'll never forgive you, Taruruuto!
The very recollection of it is nauseating!
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama! Taru-sama!
This way, this way!
Wait!
Taru-sama!
No oink!
I won't forgive you, Taruruuto!
Never!
You stupid prick!
There, there, this will teach you some!
This, and this, and this, and this!
And this! And this!
Taru-sama!
Did something grip you, Taru-sama?
Tummy pains!
This! And this!
Your agony merely starts, Taruruuto!
Tummy pains!
Pains so much!
Can't take it...
Tummy pains... Tummy pains!
Taru-sama!
Hold it together!
Pains! Tummy pains!
Tummy pains so much!
Taru-sama.
I'll try curing it with my special massage!
Rub-rub here. Rub-rub there.
Belly pains...
Rub-rub. Rub-rub.
Better already?
Maybe doing it with my tongue
will help you even more?
Let me take them off...
Have no worries, Taru-sama.
I won't give up
until your tummy is fully healed.
Stop it at once!
You're still too little for this!
There. Happy now?
No reason for it to hurt anymore!
Me tummy hurts no more.
What a relief!
This must be also
the power of my love, Taru-sama!
Tummy healed!
Taru-sama, my love did it!
Taru-sama!
Ugh! One way or another -
everything I do
only ends up serving him a foil!
Mimora-chan's tongue
is for nobody else but me!
Mimora-chan!
ON
And I have just the tool for that!
By impersonating Taruruuto,
I can get Mimora-chan to lick me instead!
Turn
Turning with the Transformation Belt!
Transformation!
Turning Taruruuto!
This guy is indistinguishable from Taruruuto!
Except for those long legs
and functioning brains.
Taru-sama!
Mimora, let's play together with Honmaru.
Not with his kind!
Mimora my friend, Honmaru my friend.
Mimora and Honmaru friends.
Oh, but me and Taru-sama
are much more than just friends.
Mimora, play together with Honmaru?
Well? Well? Well?
Well?
Well, if Taru-sama wants it so bad...
Play, let's play! Honmaru!
Taru-sama!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, where're you?
Wait for me, Taru-sama!
Flip-flip, flip-flip the hatch
replaced with Rival's perfect match!
This bastard Taru is head over heels
for some strange victual of this world, called takoyaki.
How about this?
Honmaru!
Takoyaki!
That's more like it.
Taru-sama!
Caught you!
Mimora-chan's pretty face is so close!
What's wrong, Taru-sama?
Crap! Need to calm down.
Calm down, Rival.
Now, come on. "Tum-tum hurts.
Lick on my tum-tum, I really need it!"
Be-belly. Hu-hurts aga-gain.
Taru-sama, what in the world happened to you?
Your face is suddenly only shades of red!
Mimora-chan gave me a pat!
For some reason,
it is also growing hot now!
How can I bear this delight?
Is this something Taruruuto gets
on a regular basis?
You rogue, I'll never forgive you!
Taru-sama is scary...
That's right, I'm Taruruuto now...
Actually...
Now that I'm already disguised as Taruruuto,
if I demonize him in Mimora-chan's eyes...
Mimora-chan will start despising Taruruuto!
You snub-nosed thing! Shrimp!
Still wetting your bed, are you?
Taru-sama...
Come on, start despising Taruruuto!
Idiot! Not even your ugly mom likes you!
Now you've crossed it!
I wonder what Taruruuto is up to.
Hanging out with Mimora somewhere, maybe?
Taru-sama's stupid stupid stupid
stupid stupid stupid stupid stupid!
Mimo...
Mimora-chan!
What? Taru suddenly started calling you names?
It seems Taru-sama had changed too much
in the time we've been away.
Him being so vile towards me...
Mimora-chan, calling girls names
sounds nothing like Taruruuto.
You grew up with Taru,
so you should know him better than I do.
Still...
You're getting something wrong here,
I'm sure of it.
Taruruuto-sama!
If it's me. If it's me...
Then I'm the one getting it wrong!
Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan!
I'm so sorry! I failed to see
through Taru-sama's solicitude!
You had every right to say
"Mimora is a short-sighted fool!"
Taru-sama was merely aiming to mold a better person
out of me, hence he warned me of my shortcomings.
I finally realized that.
But that also means I've mistreated so cruelly
the one friend that's been the most attentive to me!
You were right about everything.
Taru-sama, you meant nothing but the benefit for me,
when reprimanding me so openly.
And yet, I repaid your solicitude
in the most violent way!
Will you ever forgive me?
Sure!
Ah! This infinitely generous heart
makes me fall in love over and over again!
Taru-sama...
Seems like you sorted this out already.
But I can't believe you did this all
just as a demonstration for me! Jeez...
Yeah, Honmaru!
Mimora, let's have fun in the park with Honmaru!
Sure, Taru-sama.
Taru-sama!
Well, whatever.
'Kay, let's go!
Why does this keep happening to me
time after time?!
Mimora-chan, you're returning
to the Magic Realm by yourself?
Yes. After meeting Taru-sama again, I know for sure -
his love for me has not changed a tad bit,
and that's all I need to know!
But if I wander away from home for too long,
my parents would get uneasy.
Mimora, say hello to my mama, too.
Sure, I'll make sure to pass it along.
Alright!
Well then, Taru-sama.
Keep your chin up.
Goodbye!
Mimora-chan, good luck to you, too!
Bye-bye!
Come play with us again sometime!
Goodbye!
Mimora!
Rival!
Taru, don't let your guard down.
With Mimora-chan out of the picture,
nothing stands in the way of me making away with you!
Prepare yourself, Taruruuto!
Rival! If you mistreat my Taru-sama,
I will be very mad!
Rival! Return with me, or I'll be sooo mad!
Fine, Mimora-chan!
Well then, let's call it here once more.
Taru-sama, take care!
Just gotta say, you're one lucky fellow
to have chemistry with a girl that cute, Taruruuto.
Goodbye, Mimora-chan!
I have chemistry with Honmaru, too!
What, again? Stop it already! Hey, hey...
Taru-sama, if you cheat on me,
you'll reap my wrath!
My bad...
Unforgivable! Absolutely unforgivable, dad!
Even though it's your wedding anniversary,
you're dating another woman!
Somehow, this repulsing.
Isn't it? Isn't it?
Alright, Taruruuto!
We'll punish him with magic for cheating on mom!
Yeah!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Papa's Punishment!
If we punish him,
think he'll wake up to his wrongdoing, Honmaru?
Episode 19
Papa's Punishment!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius