Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 64
Combination! Ijigawa, Mimora
Welcome back, Taru-chan.
Mama is also happy to see you again.
Me happy too, Honmaru's mama!
Niruru returned as well, so I guess we've a full party now.
Taru, I brought this to celebrate the reunion.
This - Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Don't hold back and eat to your heart's content.
Good for you, Taru.
Thanks for the meal!
Thank you, Honmaru's papa. Me delighted!
You don't say your thanks while eating, Taru.
Sorry, Honmaru's papa.
Really! Both now have takoyaki all over their faces.
If she saw this, Mimora-chan, who hates takoyaki so much,
would probably make a fuss.
Come to think of it, Mimora-chan
moved to Ijigawa's house to freeload there.
I wonder if those two are getting along...
I won't stand for it!
Hey, please keep it low, will you?
It'd be dangerous if someone notices.
Listen. I'm letting you freeload at our house,
but in secret from my family, okay?
They'll make a big deal of it if they find out
we're living with a magician.
We come from a totally normal, serious family,
unlike that of Honmaru.
However, to say I won't even get my own room!?
That was the final straw!
You're a freeloader, remember?
So stop being so extravagant, you silly girl.
Silly girl?
Ah, too bad you're the one being silly here.
Pork-Bonk!
Look! Isn't that a silly face?
Don't you like your new look?
That's damn noisy!
You're so noisy, Rui!
Do you have a guest over?
Rui became a pig!
Yes, it's true! I'm not lying!
Just go there and look at it yourself!
My magic will wear off in 30 minutes. Please be patient until then.
Gosh, you're noisy.
What was that?
Let's try this.
I understand! I'll let you use this room however you please!
So please return my face back to normal!
You should've just said so in the first place.
Oh, alright! I'll go there to recheck just once!
I know, I know. Let me use this.
This is called Pointurner. Anything you point it at
can be turned into whatever you command it to be.
For a demonstration,
how about turning that cushion into a monster?
I understand.
Rui!
What now? How many times do I have to tell you
to knock before entering?
Rui, your pig face...
Huh?
What's this nonsense you're talking about?
How can you call your sister's elegant face a pig's?
Look closely.
Sister.
Maybe you should use some face serum?
I liked her more when she was a pig!
What'd you say?!
I'd have preferred to be a pig's little brother!
Gosh! I thought it'd be good to keep a magician in the house,
but I made a huge mistake in my calculations.
Oh? Isn't that because you didn't speak your wish earlier?
Oh, shut up, you! My wish...
I know exactly. I'll tell you my wish now.
Just make me a magician myself!
Such a wish...
Oh? Don't tell me, you can't grant it?
That'd be pretty embarrassing, wouldn't it?
Well...
What now? Is there something you can't do?
Aren't you one bi-i-i-i-ig
liar?!
You said it loud and clear before -
you can make any one thing come true.
That's a bare minimum for being a magician!
If you can't even do that, stop being so bossy!
Better yet, you shouldn't have said it in the first place!
Despite being an inexperienced mess, you think you can go ahead and promise me you'd do anything?
What's that you want to tell me?
What? An earthquake?
What's that?
Could it be Mimora?
Taru-sama.
Looks like it's settled down already.
I understand. Just as you said,
I'm an inexperienced mess.
It's been a short time,
but thank you for your care. Goodbye.
I'd rather ask Honmaru-sama to accept me
than live in such a woman's custody.
Moreover, I'll be living with Taru-sama this way!
It's no use trying to trick your way into Honmaru's house.
Honmaru's family isn't rich enough
to afford two freeloaders.
Besides, if he finds out you're just an excuse of a magician,
who can't grant even a single wish,
something tells me,
Taruruuto wouldn't be too happy with that.
He might actually run out of patience for you.
It can't be! To think that Taru-sama
might ever come to dislike me...
No, I've thought it through, actually.
Think I'll let you run off?
If you were to ever run away from our home,
I'd wager no amount of excuses would be enough.
Really?
But you don't need to worry for now.
Mimora-chan, it's very easy to avoid.
Until I come up with another wholesome wish,
all you have to do is stay quiet and listen to me.
Don't you think that'd be the best thing to do
so as to bring you and Taru closer?
Perhaps.
Please take good care of me, Rui-chan-sama.
It's great that you understand!
I'm counting on you from now on.
The morning's here!
I'll see Iyona-chan again today!
Taru-sama!
Oh, Mimora-chan?
Good morning to you,
Taru-sama, Honmaru-sama, and Niruru-chan.
Good morning.
Ning.
Ah, ever so polite, our Mimora-chan!
Oh, I wouldn't go that far...
Yo, Honmaru, Taruruuto!
What now, Ijigawa again?
Taru-sama!
Why can't you just say hello properly,
even though you're clearly old enough?
Just follow the little one's example.
Gosh, you're annoying!
Don't go around teaching everyone how to live!
Nobody likes bastards who are too stiff.
Doncha feel like you've been getting
stuck up lately, Honmaru?
What now?!
Doncha start acting all so important
just 'cause you died once, you dimwit!
Ahem!
"Only death can cure an idiot," that's what they say,
but you managed to remain an idiot even after death!
What a nasty girl!
Honmaru-kun, Rui-chan,
good morning.
Hey, Iyona-chan!
Good morning!
What's with your face today?
Please never mind that.
Good morning, Iyona-chan.
Good morning to you!
To you!
Good morning.
Man, Iyona-chan sure is elegant and beautiful,
so unlike any other woman around here!
Iyona-chan, you're looking even more dazzling today!
Oh no! Honmaru-kun, don't.
Taru-sama, will you let me accompany you to school?
Yeah!
Shall we go together too, Iyona-chan?
Huh?
Let's go!
Hear this, I've seen it with my own eyes!
His whole body is completely white!
Very fun, I'd say!
Tsk. Not one bit fun.
Time to move on.
Hey, you...
You're one cute thing.
You can understand humans' feelings, right?
Hey! That tickles.
What's going on?
Whatcha trying here, giving me that look?
Oh? I feel like I've seen you somewhere.
Hey, Niruru!
Niruru?
Niruru - my friend.
When you squeeze its tail,
it turns into whatever it's looking at.
Wait for me, Taru-sama!
Which means...
Oh my! Who might this lovely girl be?
Such a neat style
and a cute slanting on the eyes!
I see! This is actually Niruru disguised as me!
That's right.
I just had a brilliant idea!
I can use Niruru to play pranks on Honmaru!
Sounds fun!
Very much so, Taru-sama.
Hey, Taru! Where are you?
Hey, let's go play outside, Taru!
Okay, Honma—
Quiet, you!
I wonder where Taru might be.
Ah! Jabao!
Now!
That's it! Honmaru acquired -
first part is done!
Time to commence the operation!
Iyona-chan!
Rui-chan?
This is bad! Come, come.
What? What happened?
Honmaru-kun... Honmaru-kun...!
What happened to Honmaru-kun?
He took away my bra!
Why would Honmaru-kun
do something like that...
Look!
See? I wasn't kidding. Moreover, I've just bought it.
And it's brand new too!
Honmaru-kun, what are you doing?
Please return it to Rui-chan!
Honmaru-kun...
See?
Those are his true colors.
Why would you be doing something like this?
Honmaru-kun, answer me seriously!
Niruru amazing! Complete perv.
A complete perv, just like the original!
Hey, Taru!
Hey, Honmaru!
What now, so that's where you've been?
This is bad! The real one is coming!
Hey, you! Use your magic to turn Honmaru
into a chair or something!
I refuse! I'm not your servant or something!
I don't like being bossed around!
Oh? I wonder whose house you're freeloading at.
To your ultimate benefactor, who even agreed to take this inexperienced magician under her wing,
you think it's an acceptable thing to say?
I can throw your sorry ass out anytime!
Honmaru-kun, why are you like that...
Huh?
That voice...
What's wrong, Iyona-chan?
Cha-a-a-air!
Wow! What's this?!
That's strange... Just now, I saw Honmaru-kun behind you...
What are you talking about?
You just imagined it!
That's right!
You need to stop, Honmaru-kun!
Mimora used Pointurner
to make Honmaru a chair! Funny!
I see! I got turned into a chair by Mimora-chan's magic!
Huh? Hey, it's not me!
What kind of weird things is he doing to Iyona?
Give it to me!
Iyona-chan is angry!
I see! That "Honmaru" is actually Niruru!
Get your act together, Honmaru-k—
What?
What the hell?!
Honmaru-kun, stop it!
Really! Well, isn't our Honmaru a pervert?
This was another one of Ijigawa's tricks!
Man, this is serious! Help me, Taru!
Yay! Funny! Playing pull or push!
Tsk! Easy for you to stay cheerful
when you don't know how others feel!
Hey, Mimora-chan.
How may I help?
I wonder if there's some magic
to control Niruru as I want.
This selfish woman keeps making too many requests!
You can go to the streets anytime.
Limpimpy!
With this, you can control freely
the movements of anyone you're pointing your finger at.
Okay! Lend it to me.
Ah! What is she going to do?!
Like this?
This sounds fun already!
What is that weird posture?
Honmaru-kun, stop it!
Alright!
Ah! Stop it, Ijigawa!
Yay! Niruru funny!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun, you...
Oh? This is getting really interesting!
Damn it! Rattle-rattle-rattle!
Shut your rattle-rattle right now!
Stop it, Honmaru! You sick scum!
Stop it, someone!
You're the devil of a woman, Ijigawa!
Hey, Honmaru-kun, tell me what's gotten into you?
I want you to return to your usual self!
Please! Honmaru-kun would never do something like that!
Honmaru-kun wouldn't...
Iyona-chan...
Actually, it was your fault to begin with, Honmaru!
Can't be helped. Should I leave it at that?
But using this thing can be quite addictive...
Oh?
Back then... He used this magic on me!
Hey! You were the one who played around with my body!
Oh no!
Alright! I'll pay you back in your own coin!
Ah! No! Stop it!
Honmaru-kun!
Oh, Rui, what's that? Limpimpy?
Oh no!
First, let's go for "squeeze-squeeze," is that how it goes?
You can't be serious!
I wanna play too! Me too!
Don't get in the way, Taru!
Get lost, I said!
My! How dare you do such things to my Taru-sama!
Alright. Honmaru-sama!
Hey! Ijigawa!
Ah? You're back already?
Oh no! It's happening again!
Honmaru-kun, you...
That's not me!
Iyona-chan!
Oh?
No!
Ugh!
Honmaru!
I'll pull you up slowly! Stay still!
Honmaru, you just...
You did all that to save me! It was you!
Oh no, my hair is all frizzy.
Are you okay, Ijigawa?
Does it hurt anywhere?
'Course I'm not okay, you freak!
Hey! Can't I even get a "thank you" for saving you?
Shut up! You did that just so that you could
peek into under my skirt all you want!
Why are you like that?!
Honmaru...
Iyona-chan! Where are you?
Iyona!
I no longer understand anything!
Why'd Honmaru do such a thing?
Mimora!
Again...
Iyona-chan!
Why are you all alone up here?
Come on. Rui-chan, you saw it too.
What Honmaru-kun did to my clothes...
Huh? It's not torn.
Did I really dress up like that to school today?
Iyona-chan, weren't you just seeing
a bad dream or something?
Did I really?
Right. I probably did.
Honmaru-kun would never do something like that.
'Course he wouldn't, silly girl!
I guess I'm the weird one here.
That's right! It was a dream! A dream.
A dream, you say?
Here's what really happened!
You! Stop time with your magic!
Mimama! Time, stop!
Alright! Now make a beeline for Iyona-chan's house
and get her some new clothes!
Okay!
I brought it.
Then change her clothes quickly!
Alright! Unfreeze the time!
Mimama!
Really! That woman is a natural-born taskmaster!
That's one weird dream you saw!
I suppose.
She made it right with Mimora's magic.
Rui really a good person!
Are you sure about that?
But I'm glad all the same.
Honmaru-kun!
Because of this very weird dream I saw,
I made wrong conclusions about you.
I'm sorry!
It's alright, alright! Don't worry one bit!
After all, I can forgive anything to Iyona-chan.
You're so kind, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan...
Thank you, Ijigawa. You're a good person.
You're the one who really saved me!
Honmaru-kun.
Yes, Iyona-chan?
Remember that I'll never turn my back on you!
Iyona-chan, wanna come home together?
Iyona-chan, hey!
Huh?
Why, Iyona-chan?
It's been a while since I went home with Taru-chan.
But Honmaru and Niruru not here.
Let's just hurry home!
If that woman comes,
there goes our peaceful life!
But I wonder where Honmaru-kun could have gone...
Iyona-chan...
I don't understand!
Such strength in a girl...
A girl's heart works in mysterious ways...
Isn't it fun, Honmaru?
Honmaru, barefoot! Barefoot seems fun!
I'll take my boots off too!
Of course, Taru! Playing beach volleyball in the middle of winter is what the doctor ordered!
Look. Teacher and Rival are mysteriously excited today.
This might as well be happening in a spokon manga!
Honmaru, children belong to the wind!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Rival's Unrequited Love.
Oh! Mimora is rooting for us too.
I'll do my best!
Episode 65
Rival's Unrequited Love
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius