Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru wants to make a wish
to be brought back to life.
With Taruruuto in tow,
he headed towards the Colored Sky Hermit.
However, to do that, he'd first need to collect 70 stamps.
Because the only way to reach him
is with this magical item, Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo.
Be it Mahalapa, Papparapa or whatever else,
I'm not here to lose!
Episode 62
Farewell, Honmaru
Still wanna duel for more, boy?
Dammit. Alright, let's settle the duel
with rock-paper-scissors this time!
Settle!
If we play rock-paper-scissors several times,
I might win at least once.
With just one win, we'd gather enough stamps
to qualify for the Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo!
Customarily, the previous winner
gets to choose to the next duel's competition.
But it's all the same to me.
Go ahead, let's wrap this duel up already.
Alright! Rock, paper, scissors!
Ow... I lost!
Honmaru getting turned to stamp again!
Papparapa!
Here, let's stamp you here.
I won again.
Let's have another round!
Rock, paper, scissors!
And another one! Looks like I won again! Too bad.
Let's have another duel!
Go, Honmaru!
Rock, paper, scissors!
My win again!
Damn it...
Why, why, why, why?!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Lost again.
But for real, are you even trying?
Yeah! I'll try again and again until I win!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Scissors
Paper
Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock
Honmaru, Honmaru!
Why am I so unlucky?
Honmaru, you've been a stamp so many times
your face is now completely flattened!
Really?
238 matches, 0 wins, 238 losses?
And I've not collected a single one yet!
Mahalapa strong.
But why is it that I can't win even a single one?
You'd better give up, young man!
Mahalapa-sama's magic
is on a completely different level from yours!
Dammit.
Taru, don't you have some magic
that could defeat Mahalapa?
I can't take it anymore.
We can't ever collect that many stamps...
Iyona-chan...
I'm already...
Honmaru-kun, do your best.
Iyona-chan.
Oh! I got an idea!
Mahalapa pervert.
Same as Honmaru!
What now? Isn't that Nature Switch Juice Hormonger?
Ah, I see! That might actually work!
Hey, Taruruuto.
Please bring out Stylish Champion of Taste.
Okay!
Here!
Bonjour! Stylish Champion of Taste Garçon here.
I can tail any clothes according to your order, right!
Taste Champion, please tail me some sexy clothes
that'll win me the heart of that sleeping Mahalapa.
Oui! Easy as one-two-three, right.
Forget it.
Mahalapa, wake up!
Ah, forget it...
Come on! I'm asking you to wake up, you hear?
What is it?
I'm Emoto Marue. Nice to meet you.
Woohoo! Pound-pound-pound!
Alright! Do it now, Taru-chan!
Okay!
Alright. Here it comes!
What's this?
I used "Waaah!-Scared-the-daylights-out-of-me!
My-heart-jumped-out-of-my-chest-then-you-
potato-sliced-out-of-it-a-stamp!" to defeat Mahalapa!
Including the previous one, we collected 81 stamp!
Which means we have enough for the Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo now!
We'll head right now to the hermit
so that he can resurrect me with his magic!
Iyona-chan, I'm coming to see you!
Marue, my love,
will you become my 756th wife?
You're a fool, Mahalapa!
I'm actually a boy!
I know that! A man would do as well! Please be my wife!
What do you say?
Taru, run!
It felt like I loved you for the last 100 years!
Dumped again...
We've collected 81 stamps!
Please exchange them for a Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo!
Good job collecting those.
Here, Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo.
We did it, Taru-chan!
We can meet the hermit now.
Cli-li-li-limbing!
Easy!
Oh? Returned so soon?
Yeah. 'Course we did!
Alright, that's where we use Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo.
Jump-oh! Shampoo! Now, bare your heads please.
Okay!
Jump, jump!
Now please wash your heads.
Okay, jump now.
There!
We did it!
It's jump-o-clock!
Did I lose?
Feels good too!
We're finally here!
Now where could hermit be?
I don't see no entrance.
If you climb on top of this rock, you'll meet him there.
I see. Thank you Tama-chan.
There!
The shampoo bubbles are getting smaller!
Gotta cli-li-limb faster!
Taru, I'll be alright.
I can more or less climb from here.
Trunsform!
Huh... There nothing's in here, and we're alone.
Hermit-sama!
Hermit-sama...
I'm right here!
Where?
Here!
Enoru-ru-rmous!
Young man, do you need something from me?
Hermit-sama, please bring me back to life!
You're asking me to bring you back to life?
You fool!
You bugs come to me like a bolt from the blue
and just casually ask for favors?
Ain't you some impertinent fellows?
We apologize!
Sorry, Hermit-sama.
Did you think I'd snap my fingers
and fulfill the wishes of just anyone passing by?
Some spoiled and foolish youngsters you are!
Sir, please read this.
Letter from my mama!
I'm begging you!
Hermit-sama...
I beg you-yu-yu!
Why is it that you want to come back to life so bad, kid?
If I don't come back,
I won't get to see Iyona-chan ever again!
Again!
So a woman, huh?
Do you really love that woman?
Yes. I do love her. Very much!
But at times, Honmaru is a bit of a pervert.
What? A pervert?
So you want to come back
just to continue your perverted way of life?
No! It's... wrong! It's wrong.
Why'd you say something like that, Taruruuto?
But it's the truth that Honmaru is a pervert!
The truth is that I love her!
I love Iyona-chan!
Although being lewd
is my occasional guilty pleasure...
Called it! Honmaru - a perv.
Ah! Crap!
Honmaru trying to hide his guilt!
We're in a bath!
No, it's a hot spring.
Ain't it pleasant, Taru?
Yeah...
But it feels like I'm forgetting something...
Ah, whatever.
Someone else is coming.
Honmaru-kun.
Yay! Iyona!
Iyona-chan?! Why are you here?
You don't mind if I join you?
Yeah!
B-Be my guest...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru blushy-blushy!
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
You're bright red!
And bloody-bloody in the nose.
Honmaru-kun, would you like me to rub your back?
Honmaru nosebleeds
Thank you!
Honmaru-kun, your back is so broad and sturdy...
Iyona-chan.
Honmaru-kun?
What's the matter, Honmaru-kun?
This isn't right.
You broad! You're no Iyona-chan!
What are you saying, Honmaru-kun?
Of course it's me.
Something isn't right.
But I can't quite put my finger on it...
Where? Where?
Can you put your finger on
what is wrong with this body?
Honmaru!
You can touch me all you want, Honmaru-kun.
Do you dislike me?
No...
Why refuse if so?
We could stay here forever,
in the warm embrace of safety.
I'm all yours to do whatever you want with.
Well done, Honmaru!
Can do anything you want with Iyona!
Yeah...
Whatever I want, huh...?
Then, can I kiss you?
Yes.
It would be my delight.
Delight! Yay!
Iyona-chan...
This is all wrong! She's not Iyona-chan!
I remember now.
I can't afford the luxury
of doing this here and now!
Yeah!
Hermit-sama!
Please bring me back to life!
Please bring me back to life
and let me meet the real Iyona-chan!
Please!
Huh?
Well said, Honmaru.
Hermit-sama!
I'll bring you back to life.
Hooray!
I'm happy for you, Honmaru!
Honmaru, Taruruuto.
I found you.
This is bad!
It's an angel from heaven!
Help me, Hermit-sama!
If an angel catches me,
I won't be able to come back to life!
Too bad.
Not even I can meddle in the work
of the heavenly angels ordained by God.
My bad.
Forgive me, Honmaru.
Hermit-sama...
Sama...
Honmaru.
You're...
Mom's mom!
Honmaru's grandma!
Long time no see.
So grandma was the one following us?
That's right.
But you just wouldn't wait even if I told you to.
Such an unruly child, really.
You should've told me sooner that you were the angel from heaven!
Yeah! Resurrect Honmaru!
I'm sorry.
I don't have that power.
Should one go back to earth
or stay in heaven - it's for the God to decide.
What is this place?
Edojo Honmaru-san.
Thou shall hereby face the divine judgment.
One's destiny cannot be changed on a whim.
But worry naught.
The earthly life is but a momentary journey
within the great process which is the rectification of thy soul.
Thy loved ones shall soon conclude their journeys
and follow thou to here.
So I'll have to just die in the end?
Honmaru can't be resurrected.
...thus I would pronounce ordinarily.
Edojo Honmaru-san,
the stars signify thou weren't destined to pass away that day.
Which means...
Please come back to life.
Hooray!
She said it! Honmaru, you'll come back to life!
Thank you. Thank you, Taru!
Aren't you glad?
Yes! Who'd ever think, Taru!
Honmaru!
Per every human soul, there is a mission
thou is to accomplish within your earthly life.
Thou cannot die until thy mission is fulfilled.
Mission?
What exactly is that?
Honmaru, I'm so happy!
Honmaru, I'm so glad!
Thy lifelong goal which thou had set thy mind upon
long before thou have been born as Edojo Honmaru.
Come back to life and make the most of it.
Please fulfill thy mission.
Okay!
The good God only gave you one body.
Please make sure to value it well.
Alright!
Hooray! Hooray!
Honmaru will return to how he used to be!
Hooray...
I came back to life!
Peace!
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan.
Honmaru-kun...
I...
Dad, mom!
Honmaru!
Ijigawa.
I can make you the butt of my jokes again!
Harako.
I'd say you've bested me,
the World Playing Dead Contest Winner.
Jabao!
Stupid Honmaru!
Neyo.
Are you kidding me?
Korekiyo.
Only death can cure an idiot!
Everyone...
Thank you!
Right, hear me out! I do remember having been somewhere, in the other world, and...
Huh?
Did you say the other world?
Sure you weren't seeing a dream?
On the matters of afterlife, you should ask me, the champion
of the "Let's play with Angel-chan" contest for children.
Are you kidding me?
Something...
is missing.
What is this sense
of emptiness in my chest?
Good for you, Honmaru.
Can live happily with everyone...
Honmaru...
Once Honmaru returned to life,
any and all memories of Taruruuto
have been effaced from his and his friends' hearts.
This was another one of the intransigent laws of the Magic Realm.
Ah! I wonder if I really did die and meet God?
What do you think, Taru?
Hey, Taruruuto? Where are you?
Oh? That's strange.
Though you were put under a spell that makes you forget
all about magicians, how come Honmaru remembers?
I recalled it, Taru.
We're friends, remember?
Yeah! Friends!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Episode 63
Overcrowded with Magicians
Overcrowded with Magicians!
Mimora and others also returned, Honmaru!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius