Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
I love Mimora-chan!
How can I... How can I make Mimora-chan
fall in love with me?
For conveying your feelings
to your beloved ones - "Love Message!"
Give her a marvelous present to win her heart over!
I see. A present?
Wham
A present to win Mimora-chan's heart over...
Episode 73
Diary of Rival's Pure Love
Ugh! It's so chilly!
Let's hurry up inside the greenhouse.
Yeah!
We hurry-ru-ru inside!
So warm in here!
Warm!
It's like spring has come.
Isn't it wonderful? So many different flowers!
Wait, Taru-sama!
It's good to be carefree like Taru.
I should've brought Iyona-chan along too.
Mimora!
Taru-sama!
Alright. Time to find out what Mimora-chan wants!
Caught you!
I am so sorry.
Taru-sama? Are you okay?
Me okay.
I'm glad.
Damn you, Taru!
Always so clingy and flirty with Mimora-chan...!
I won't let it slide!
Rival! The thing with girls is,
you need to enamor them using your own power.
Screwing over your rival in love
will get you nowhere.
If fact, doing so is very cowardly.
I'm no coward!
I'll use my own power to wrest
Mimora-chan's heart out of his claws!
Taru-sama! Aren't the flowers beautiful?
Oh my!
Cute!
Flowers are friends.
Let's sing togetheru-ru-ru!
I love you!
And you love everyone!
Everyone also loves me!
Let's go around and tell everyone!
How can you be that childish?
What's all this crap about being "friends with flowers"?
Together, together!
You're just a sissy, Taruruuto!
Isn't Taru-sama's magic wonderful?
I'm mesmerized!
I love flowers so much!
I see! Mimora-chan loves flowers.
Alright. My present will be this.
What's wrong? Did someone hurt you?!
There's a bug!
What now, just some bug? Don't scare me like that!
Come.
Bugs are friends too.
Not for me. I... I think, bugs are...
Everyone friends.
No!
Friends!
Taru-sama, take it away!
Mimora-chan, I'll save you!
Wait! Don't you bully Mimora-chan!
Mimora-chan has me to protect her!
Taru-sama!
Rival... Sneakily attacking Taru-sama like that...
That was the final straw!
That was the final one for sure!
Why did she do that!?
What can I do to make Mimora-chan happy?
This flower ate the bug!
Amazing! This flower is amazing!
Mimora-chan loves flowers.
And Mimora-chan hates bugs.
A flower that eats insects!
This is it!
This flower must become my present!
I wonder what kind of flower this is.
A beautiful one!
Mimora-chan!
Seems like Rival hasn't had enough.
What is it he's carrying?
Look at this flower!
Hey, where did you get it from?
What in the world is this flower?
Here. See this?
Right? Ain't it disgusting?
But that disgusting insect...
This thing is impressive!
See? Ain't it amazing?
This flower eats insects that Mimora hates!
This is my present to Mimora-chan!
Keep it.
I don't feel so well!
And don't come near me!
Why...?
You can't expect a girl to be into this kind of flower.
Dammit!
Sniffle...
Easy, easy. This isn't your fault.
Let's return you to where you came from.
I don't understand, I don't!
Rival, if there's something you can't understand,
read a book and conduct research.
Right! If I consult a book, I'll be fine!
Things that girls want...
Big plush toys and sleek cars...
Good, good!
Special presents catalogue!
I see. A trip, a cake...
A set of diamond colliers...
Oh, I see!
Dear customer?
Alright! This would be perfect!
Dear customer!
I gotta hurry and get the presents!
Hey you! Wait!
It was a pretty interesting exhibit, Taru.
Yeah!
I'm happy that I got to see so many beautiful flowers!
Me happy too.
It sure is good to be getting along.
Mimora-chan!
Here's your present!
Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan, everything you see here
is my present to you!
Aren't you amazed?
Are you alright, Taru-sama?
Rival, what are you doing?
This... Everything for Mimora-chan, my pre...
Keep it.
Let's go home, Taru-sama.
Sorry about that, Rival.
See you!
Thief!
Give my car back!
You can't take it without paying!
That's just mean!
Hey you, thief!
Give it back!
Shut up!
Rival!
Sensei...
Where'd you get the idea
that stealing is okay?!
Show some remorse!
But... this is...
Sensei...
Let's apologize to everyone together, okay?
Spirit, technique, strength​
I can see what the general situation is.
However, even doing it for Mimora-chan
can't be a justification for stealing, Rival.
Yes...
I apologize.
As for the present for Mimora-chan...
On your path to conquering the heart
of the woman you love, you'll make countless mistakes.
But losing your heart
over each such mistake is a no-go.
Sensei...
If you correct your behaviour,
use your head, and put in your every effort,
your dreams will come true someday.
Fight on, Rival.
Okay!
I won't give up!
Alright.
The transformation belt should help!
Transformation!
Turning Honmaru!
With this, I can learn what Mimora likes,
straight from the horse's mouth!
Hey, Mimora-chan!
Oh? Honmaru-sama?
What in the world happened?
No, I...
Mimora-chan, what do you like?
What's this question, all of a sudden?
I was wondering, just for kicks.
You're so naughty, Honmaru-sama!
Unfortunately for you,
Taru-sama is already the love of my life.
That little shit...
Little... Oh, little star,
how I wonder what you are...
It's a popular song these days.
Honmaru-sama is weird.
Mimora-chan. I wasn't asking who you love.
Look, I wanna know what things you like.
Well, I like summer a great deal.
That's not what I meant!
What about things? Things you like?
Let me think...
I also like sunflowers quite a lot.
I see. A sunflower, then?
Alright! A sunflower it is!
What was that?
I'll give Mimora-chan the best present!
One sunflower, please!
Welcome!
Did you say a sunflower?
Yes!
I wonder if we have any by now.
Manager, do we have any sunflowers?
Eh? What? Sunflowers in the win—
Ah! It's you! Back at it already?!
No!
"Sunflowers in the winter," my butt!
Don't you dare come back again!
Ouch!
That's right. Sunflowers only grow in the summer.
Alright! In that case, I'll search far and wide
to bring you some sunflowers!
Sunflowers, sunflowers... Where are you?
Found them! The sunflowers!
Taru-sama, it's so cold outside these days.
Oh it's snowing!
Oh my! It's snowing indeed.
Freezing!
So beautiful...
Yay! Snowing, snowing!
Taru-sama, that's so like you!
I did it!
This will delight Mimora-chan to no end!
So cold...
I gotta present it soon!
Alright...
Ah! It's no good.
Flying through the sky makes it scatter!
I gotta hurry. Mimora-chan!
Please wait.
She went out to play?
Goddammit! It's that Taru again...
Sunflower, will you hang on?
Mimora-chan, where are you?
Stop it, Taru-sama!
Hey, Taru! Let's have a snowball fight.
Honmaru-sama.
Okay!
You two can join forces.
Let's do it.
Fine by me.
Alright. Commence the battle!
Oh? Unfair!
That was sly, Honmaru-sama.
Speed is the essence of battle!
Honmaru wide open!
Oh no! You missed!
Ow-ow-ow! Oh no... It's cold.
Dammit...
Taru-sama so cool!
Watch out, Mimora!
I'm not done yet!
Mimora-chan!
Mimora-chan...
Where are you?
No... My sunflower!
Thank god...
You're safe.
Let's hurry up and find Mimora-chan.
You're so good at it, Taru-sama! Here.
Why, you!
You wanna play serious?!
Come and get it!
There, there, there, there, there!
Taru, come!
Mimora-chan!
Sorry, Rival.
Mimora-chan.
What's up with you, Rival?
Here. A present for Mimora-chan.
And...
What is it?
A sunflower.
This is...
Mimora-chan's favorite, the sunflower!
That's one tattered sunflower.
Why'd you do such a cruel thing to it, Rival?
Sunflowers cannot live in the cold!
Return it to where you found it at once!
Huh?
You can't be serious...
But it's a present...
I feel kinda sorry for Rival.
He went to all the trouble of bringing it here.
Mimora, accept the sunflower.
Oh my! Taru-sama is always so considerate!
I understand.
If Taru-sama says so, I accept it.
Good for you, Rival.
But don't do anything this wicked ever again!
Rival, let's have a snowball fight!
Everyone friends.
Rival!
I'll never be friends with your kind!
Are you kidding me?!
You fools!
Oh, so he actually went the extra mile.
Rival-kun worked really hard to get me.
He was sure I'd delight Mimora-chan.
He put in his every effort to bring here.
Is that so?
Rival can be a nice guy too.
Rival friends.
I was an idiot...
Rival? What happened?
Mimora-chan came, saying she wants to see you.
I refuse!
Are you sure, Rival?
Rival, I'm sorry.
Sunflower-san told me everything.
Please, come out to meet me.
Looks like it's to no avail, after all.
Alright. With his wisdom,
Honmaru-sama will come in clutch.
Can you really?
Yes I can!
Mimora-chan!
Now, wake up, Rival.
It's jogging time.
But it's snowing outside.
Running in the snow is the best
for training your stamina.
Oh?
Can't we skip just today?
Rival! Come see this.
Uh?
Come on, hurry!
You need to see this.
What is it?
You did it, Rival.
I'm sorry, Rival🖤
Thanks for the sunflower!
A message from Mimora-chan.
"I'm sorry, Rival...
Thanks for the sunflower...
Mimora-chan."
Aren't you glad, Rival?
Yes, sensei!
Behold, myself - the Great Magician Ria Kinakamo.
I'll make your one wish come true.
This is a story from a long time ago.
Though it started from a coincidence for Ria and Gosuke,
fueled by genuine kindness,
the love became real.
I'm sure you will...
You'll find someone wonderful.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Ria's Love Story.
Episode 74
Ria's Love Story
I'll send you a warm heart.
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius