Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Well then, we're finally having a marathon tomorrow.
Everyone, do your best, will you?
Okay!
The course is as follows.
Starting from the school,
all students will make one circle around town
before arriving back at the school.
The first to return back to school wins the prize?
Right. Isn't that easy?
Alright! I'll do my best and win first prize!
Alright, so will I!
This year for sure, I'm taking
that "#1 in school" title home!
Taru-chan, I'm not planning to lose either.
Yeah! Iyona will do her best too?
Iyona-chan, if you follow after me,
you have a chance to come second.
Hey, Honmaru!
Iyona-chan was #1 among the girls last year.
On the other hand, at what place
did your sorry ass finish last year?!
Shut up! Humans have a potential
for improving daily. Don't talk about last year!
For now, I'll let him make whatever claims he'd like.
But the ultimate victory will be mine this year.
This time, I started preparing in advance
and have been working on it for a month already.
It's perfect! This secret
magic countermeasure strategy I've prepared.
You bastards! Taru in particular,
no matter what magic you'll try to use...
I'll squash it all like that, with a pop!
The victory will be mine.
Episode 66
Mad Marathon
Sponsored by Harako Conglomerate
35th Marathon
I'm extremely honored to be able
to run alongside Taru-sama!
Shit... This bastard Taru
is with Mimora-chan again!
I'll show you soon!
Marathon is the very special of my specialities.
Just today, my truly amazing side
is going to shine for you as never before.
Ready!
Make way, make way, make way!
Harako!
Dashing like that right off the bat?
Heh! That's just stupid.
You'll wear yourself out right away.
You snail-paced lowlifes!
Nobody is able to keep up with me, the Super Sprinter!
Harako fast. But me won't lose.
Me no snail-paced lowlife!
Taru!
Isn't it amazing? Harako-kun and Taru-chan
are both full of energy!
I bet Honmaru can't pull anything of the kind!
Seriously?
It's easy!
Honmaru came too!
Yeah! I'll do my best!
Riding your idiotic drive?
That'll use up all of your energy here and now.
You're wonderful, Taru-sama!
Damn, I can do that too!
What do you think, Mimora-chan?
You've seen my fantastic dash just now, didn't you?
Taruruuto!
How dare you run right over me?!
I swear by my name of...
One-two, one-two...
I hate the marathons!
Midway point
Sponsored by Harako Conglomerate
Taru, let's knock the pace down a bit.
At this speed, I'm wearing myself out real fast.
Me still a-okay.
Do your best for a little more!
Really? Do my best?
Ah! There's water!
Thanks!
Ah! That was tasty!
Idiot. You drank it?
Honmaru, your defeat is now predestined!
Honmaru, what's wrong?
My stomach suddenly twisted around!
Dammit! It was Harako again!
He mixed something into the water I just drank!
Honmaru!
Are you okay?
I... can't... I can't take it anymore!
Just a little more to the bathroom!
Out of service
You can't be serious...
Honmaru!
Honmaru, here! Here!
Temporary bathroom
Lucky! I'm saved!
Honmaru!
At this rate, he won't get out until we reach Osaka.
Young Master's victory is certain.
Huh?
Honmaru, come out quick!
That bathroom is moving!
You should've said so sooner!
It ain't that easy, though!
Honmaru!
Harako, you dick!
This really is a hit below the belt!
You're not getting away with it!
It's a special laxative for turning Honmaru
into a Shitstormaru in a blink of an eye.
Honmaru, with this Helpflute,
I'll make all of it come out at once!
Whoever hears this sound, gets a diaru-rurhea!
Honmaru, did it come out?
Hurry up outside, then!
That's right, hurry up!
That curry's coming out!
Honmaru!
Taru, my strength is drained by excessive shitting...
Just vacate the cabin already!
Honmaru, you alright now?
Oh no! Everyone heard the sound of Deflutecator.
It's not my fault!
Nobody has a clue that the bike
leading the way is also pulling me.
Harako cheating.
Dammit!
That's cowardly, Harako!
Honmaru I just had a good idea!
What is it, Taru-kun?
This - Fangust-kun.
If I fan with this, I can make great winds gust.
Why'd you do that?
Honmaru, by riding the wind,
you can catch up with Harako! There!
I see!
Honmaru can ride the wind easy
thanks to becoming so light!
We'll catch up in no time!
There!
This idea isn't half-bad!
I'm winning easily and by a huge margin.
You're too slow, Harako!
Don't mind me!
What?!
How can I ever be slower than Honmaru?!
There!
Damn it... He found a way
to use Taruuruto's magic, after all?
Gramps, prepare the measures
we previously discussed.
I wonder how far ahead
Honmaru-kun and the others are.
We've lost sight of them completely.
Obviously, he collapsed from exhaustion
somewhere up the road!
Oh, that Taru-sama!
Leaving me behind like that!
That was the final straw! Umph!
This is the product of the combined scientific efforts
of the entire Harako Conglomerate.
ZX50, sir.
Leveraging the power of electricity, they create
a magnetic field, allowing for super high-speed running.
Good.
Right...
Also, in order to be able to keep up
with the high operating speed of the shoes,
we'll administer the muscle-strengthening agent.
However, Young Master,
going this far just to get good results in a marathon...
Gramps! The only thing I hate more than losing is relying on luck!
Hurry up and turn on the switch!
Okay!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, start!
This one is honestly good!
I'm like a wild goat!
Honmaru! Taru!
You're too slow, Honmaru-kun!
What?
Tama-chan, why is Harako so fast?
Harako-kun used a muscle-strengthening agent.
Plus, it seems he's using
some shoes that run on their own.
This jerk Harako! He decided not to be picky
when choosing the means of victory, huh?
If that's how you wanna play, we'll play too!
Taru!
Yeah! We'll use Godspeed Slippers, right?
Been a while, Honmaru!
You just leave this to us, alright?
Okay!
Counting on you!
Let's go!
Nannosho Elementary marathon course
⬅Regular route
With this, the only person who'll be #1 in Nannosho
is the World Junior Marathon Championship winner, me!
Harako!
What's the matter, Harako-kun?
Why so slow?
What?!
Slow!
How dare you!
With all the Harako Conglomerate's scientific advantage
on my side, there's no way I'll lose!
Gramps. Gramps!
Yes?
Proceed with the plan.
Very well.
Honmaru! Harako is far behind by now!
What do we do next?
Next - just follow the course and we'll be fine.
Oh, that one?
Nannosho Elementary marathon course
⬅Regular route
Let's go!
Much obliged.
Sir!
Oh?
Wha-a-a? Honmaru!
I'm alright!
For the Godspeed Slippers,
even this slope is a cakewalk!
Still, this must mean we've turned the wrong way somewhere.
Let's retrace our steps, Honmaru!
Yeah!
I'm the best in everything!
Good for you, Young Master.
At last, the long-craved
victory over Edojo Honmaru is...
Harako!
As expected, to be frank.
He caught up already.
Thankfully, we came prepared
for this kind of situation!
I'm sleepy.
Honmaru!
What's wrong, Honmaru?
Wake up, Honmaru!
A remote-delivery tranquilizer.
Honmaru, wake up-up!
Smell you later!
If I attach this Waking Up Straw, Sleepiness Cleaner,
it'll suck out your sleepiness.
Harako!
Let's suck out more sleepiness!
So that Taru-kun is the problem again?
Activate plan T.
Hey!
Today's Takoyaki Day again!
You get to eat some for free
for getting this far!
It's this way!
Takoyaki!
Make haste to wake Young Master up!
Young Master. Young Master! Get yourself together!
Wake up please!
Honmaru, wake up! Wake up, you idiot.
Taru-sama!
I'm so delighted!
You were concerned for me, so you've returned!
Taru-sama?
That damned takoyaki again...
That was the final straw!
What?! The batteries are dead?
My sincerest apologies.
What useless shoes!
In this case, I just have to finish this on my own.
I won't lose to Honmaru no matter what!
This is bad!
Hey, Godspeed Slippers-kun!
Hurry up after Harako!
That's right, Taru's magic wears off in ten minutes.
Whatever! Against someone like Harako, I need no magic except my own strength!
Faster! There's no way I'll lose to Harako!
There he is!
Harako!
Honmaru...
Not so fast!
Shit...
You'll never overtake me at that speed.
Honmaru, don't give up!
Damn it! Harako is almost at the finish line!
I'll never lose!
I won!
I did it! I'm first!
Think again, Honmaru. You ain't first.
Which means... I'm first!
As expected.
Right. Harako is #1.
That's it!
...From the end.
Me? From the end?
That can't be!
Apologies. No matter how much we shook you,
your majesty just wouldn't wake up.
What?! Then, everyone ran by while I was sleeping?
I'm... the last?
But then, that red ribbon...
That was a closing ribbon of the marathon.
Shit...
Despite all the technological advancements
of Harako Conglomerate,
Taruruuto's magic snatched the victory off of me?
Marathon...
Marathons are the worst thing ever!
Oh! This delicious smell is from Matsu-san's takoyaki!
I love takoyaki!
Grow like mushroo-rooms!
Hey, business goin'?
Taru! You're trampling over Matsu-san!
Sorry, Honmaru!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Taru's Takoyaki Shop.
Alright, the business will get going after I take over!
Episode 67
Taru's Takoyaki Shop
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius