Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Here!
Okay!
We did it!
Yeah!
That's right, they did it!
Nobody expected anything less!
Nannosho has secured a slot
in the finals for themselves!
Hooray, hooray!
Episode 83
Fateful Volleyball Battle
9th National Volleyball Tournament Smong Elementary Schools
Prefectural Tournament Women's Semifinals
Iyona-chan! This year, you'll win
with a comfortable margin for sure!
Win for sure!
We won't.
Huh?
I've never heard you talk so dejectedly, Iyona-chan.
Look there. Another semi-final match is about to start.
Fight!
Yeah!
Those are the three Kusuda
sisters from Higashinosho!
Since last year, they've grown taller...
And now, they're 2 meters and 3 centimeters tall.
Eriko, Emiko, Eiko—the triplets.
They're the big brick wall,
standing in the way of our Nannosho school.
That's right, there are also these guys.
Same pattern as last year, huh?
Get this!
Die!
Got it!
Get this!
Okay!
Rui-chan!
Ijigawa-san!
Ah! The final, seventh player has been outed for Nannosho!
There are no more spare
players on Nannosho's sidelines!
This makes the situation extremely perilous!
Is this how Higashinosho's victory will be finalized?
Wait!
Please... Please let me play!
No country for amateurs!
Let's do it, everyone!
Okay!
Got it!
Here!
There!
Get this!
Marue-chan, please!
Okay!
Out!
Too bad, Nannosho team!
They fought to the best of their ability,
and still got trounced!
So frustrating!
Besides...
The bullet spikes of the three Kusuda sisters
are even more powerful than last year.
What is that we're seeing?
All three are moving in a strange pattern!
Eh! They're jumping together!
Kusuda Triple Attack!
And they scored!
The opposing team didn't even get a chance to react!
Did you see which one hit just now?
And the ball, too...
Kawai-san, look closely.
It's our newest deadly technique.
Better not be too...
...Surprised, because it seems, we're...
...Winning it this year!
Stop laughing and serve already!
This is bad, Iyona-chan! What should we do?
What to do-do?
I'm looking forward
to next week's match, Kusuda sisters.
Oh! As expected of Iyona-chan!
After seeing it just once, you've already figured out
a way to overcome that deadly technique?
No.
The Kusuda Triple Attack is not something
you'd be able to overcome, Kawai-san.
Jesus Christ! Enough laughing already!
Are you gonna serve today or not?!
Iyona-chan is determined!
Honmaru, that ball is awful heavy.
Yeah. It's filled with lead inside.
Iyona-chan has been taking
this special training all by herself!
I can't just sit back
and watch her go to such lengths!
We're having special training, Iyona!
Honmaru-kun?
It's not Honmaru-kun. Call me Coach!
Coach?
Then, we'll have special training like last year?
I mean... Would you please give it to me, Coach?
Yeah. We lost last year,
but we'll prevail this year, Iyona.
Prevail, Iyona.
Okay! Please take care of me, Coach.
This smile is irresistible!
Listen. First of all, you need to grow accustomed
to the Kusuda triplets' indiscernible bullet attack.
Okay.
Taru, please give me an item
that allows me to move super-fast.
Okay.
This - Hurrice.
Eating this makes you incredibly fast.
Right, thank you, Taru.
Alright, we're starting!
Okay, Coach!
Iyona-chan, I'll put in every effort to help you win!
There!
Amazing! I can see neither
Coach's hands nor the ball!
Iyona, what are you waiting for?
Stand up! You need to be in position!
Okay!
Let's go!
There!
This speed...
And this!
It's the same as the Kusuda Triple Attack.
I just can't receive this ball!
There! There! There!
It's impeccable, just like
the one from the Kusuda triplets!
And this!
What's the matter? Stand up!
Don't give up, Iyona-chan.
Iyona, don't give up!
Okay!
Ready or not, I'm starting!
Come!
Rui-chan!
I won't let Iyona-chan go through this alone!
Or else I'm not a regular at volleyball club!
Well said, Ijigawa.
Let's go!
And there!
It hurts! Coach's hands are too strong!
Running away, Ijigawa?
But come on, I'm just one weak girl!
Iyona is the same girl as you!
Look!
And there!
There! There! There!
Got it!
Still too slow!
Iyona learned to receive it!
Take this!
I'm getting used to this speed!
That's amazing, Iyona-chan!
Forgetting about everything, you just do your best
while your eyes glitter as you try to receive every ball I send!
It's your supreme form!
There! There! There!
Those two are so good.
I wish I could also receive this special training,
but the ball's just too tough.
Here! Rui, drink this.
What's that?
This - Hormonger. Women that drink it become men
and men become women.
I see! As a man, I might be able
to receive a serve that strong.
I remembered!
Taru!
Were you the one who made me go through fire
and brimstone by letting me drink this a while ago?!
Taruruuto...
Wait, you!
Wait, though...
If a woman becomes a man,
and a man becomes a woman,
Honmaru turned into Marue-chan by drinking it!
Good, Iyona! Keep it up!
Okay, Coach!
Another one coming!
Get this!
Okay!
There!
Honmaru, let me help too.
Sure. Take this!
I'm going, Iyona!
Hey, Iyona! Sorry, you okay?
Sorry, Iyona.
It's alright, Taru-chan. Nothing happened.
Taru-chan, you used this to serve, huh?
Yeah. I really liked
this boing-boing, so I picked it up.
I wish I could also serve spikes
as strong as this spring.
Yeah!
Here.
What is it? Why are you giving me a rice cake?
This - Cakemotion.
Iyona, eat this.
Eh?
Eat this and you'll understand
how spring feels. Eat, eat.
Okay.
Iyona-chan?
Now I know what it feels like to be a spring!
Nicely done! Iyona feels like a spring.
Rui-chan, serve me the ball.
Sure.
And... Get this!
Iyona amazing!
She really is like a spring!
Here!
Impressive!
Wow! That's a fearsome spike!
With this, even defeating
Higashinosho will be possible!
Rui-chan!
What's wrong, Rui-chan?
Are you unwell?
Okay, resume special training!
I'm going in, you two!
Okay, Coach!
There!
Okay!
Get this!
And this!
Ow!
Okay!
Taru!
9th National Volleyball Tournament Among Elementary Schools
Prefectural Tournament Women's Semifinals
Well, the time has finally come for the
women's finals of the Prefectural Volleyball Tournament!
Last year's winner, the Higashinosho
team, will face Nannosho team!
The match will start any minute now!
Okay!
I can't see it!
The movements of the Kusuda triplets!
Kusuda Triple Attack!
I can see it! Thanks to the special training!
Oh! Iyona saw it!
Good, Iyona-chan!
Oh-ho! The Kusuda Triple Attack
plowed right into player Kawai!
Ah! Iyona-chan...
If Iyona could see the ball, why...
Iyona-chan!
I'm alright.
Kawai-san, you did well keeping up with our speed.
You deserve some praise for that.
But you know...
That's not enough to handle the Kusuda Triple Attack.
Damn it! So arrogant!
Thank you, Kusuda triplets.
I'm profoundly happy to be able to face you all,
who wield such a fearsome technique.
"Happy," you say?
Yes. Because your serve just now let me understand
the mechanism behind the Kusuda Triple Attack.
What did you say?
Behind an illusion of all three hitting the ball at once,
only one of you actually hits it.
But because you have to change the order every time,
this attack messes up your timings!
Exactly so!
However, even having understood the mechanism...
...This attack is not something...
...You'll be able to receive!
There!
This is incredible!
The naked eye is completely unable
to keep up with the movement of the Kusuda triplets!
Attack!
I don't understand. I was sure...
You can’t tell who’ll be hit next, can you?
It doesn't matter who you'll hit next.
Just watching the ball closely should be enough.
Think you'll handle it that easily?
Attack!
It'll never be that easy...
...To receive!
Kusuda Triple Attack!
Attack!
There! There! There!
Gotta receive it. I gotta receive it,
lest they'll incapacitate everyone again.
Attack!
Nannosho's fatal seventh down!
Nannosho no longer have anyone else to put on the field!
Ah! It's like last year all over again!
Continuing this way is too dangerous, isn't it?
Oh my, it's over already?
Such a disappointing match!
Last year, with the appearance of an unexpected backer,
they made it through a tight spot.
But what are they going to do about it this year?
Alright!
Taru, give me the Hormonger.
Okay...
Faster, Taru!
Honmaru!
Now, enter Marue!
Yeah!
Wait...
Magic is no longer a secret to anyone, right?
If I disappear from the cheering seats now,
concurrently with Marue's appearance,
everyone might figure out I'm actually Marue!
And then...
That thing...
And this thing...
Even things like that!
And that thing too...
Everyone will know!
What a sick person you are, Honmaru-kun!
No way! I can't step in as Marue!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, look!
Iyona-chan is crying with frustration.
Crying because she's unable to fight until the very end...
Let's go, Taru!
Yeah!
It's alright.
I don't care if the secret of Marue is uncovered
and everyone calls me a pervert...
As long as Iyona-chan can fight until the very end!
Teacher!
I'll come out on the count!
You showed up, after all, Emoto-san!
We've been waiting.
Marue-chan, thank you!
I'm so glad to see you here!
Thank you, Marue-chan!
Alright! Everyone, let's put our backs into it!
Yeah!
Just having Marue-chan here, right by my side,
is somehow reassuring already.
That's right...
Volleyball is played by a team of six.
But up until now, I've been so focused on myself
that I haven't looked around at all.
Get this!
It's coming, Iyona-chan.
Yes!
Kusuda Triple Attack!
I saw it!
Okay!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
What?!
Did it, Iyona!
Iyona-chan!
In a serious mood
Nice toss, Marue-chan!
Iyona Spring Attack!
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
What is this shrimp trick?
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Kusuda Block!
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
Oh! Even without magic,
Iyona understood how volleyball feels!
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
You did it!
You managed to handle the Kusuda Triple Attack!
Marue-chan...
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
Alright, let's keep this up!
Everyone,
fight!
I made up my mind,
Yeah!
I'm not playing around
Triple Attack!
Okay!
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Here!
Though it's private,
Triple Attack!
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
There!
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
Iyona Special Spring Attack!
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Hooray!
Great, Nannosho!
They did it at last!
I'm so glad, Iyona-chan.
Thank you, Marue-chan.
Thank you!
Thank you, Honmaru-kun.
For coaching, for always being by my side,
for giving me strength.
Marue-chan.
Thank you, Marue-chan.
Uh-huh.
Thank god.
Seems like it never occurred
to anyone who Marue really is.
Thank you, Honmaru.
Iyona, Rui, Honmaru.
I'm glad you could win.
Everyone, what do you do
when you feel low and depressed?
Well, actually, I got 0 points on the test.
Take one straight stick!
Taru-kun, you're always so cheerful!
And the secret to that is...
Yeah! When I'm feeling low,
this Maddemboldening Samurai emboldens me.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Maddemboldening Samurai! I choose you!!
Episode 84
Going that far?!
Everyone is emboldened!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius