Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru-sama!
Episode 31
In Spring, Love is in the Air
Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
Who's there?
Hey, Taru-sama!
Taru-sama?
Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
Taru-sama!
Where are you hiding?! Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
Taru-sama's not here!
Mimora-chan, I think Taruruuto said he was going to the park.
Speaking of which, I was about to join him.
Taru-sama is favoring Honmaru-sama again,
leaving me out as the third wheel...
I'm in trouble... We've barely finished rebuilding the house,
and she's about to break into tears again!
That was the final straw!
It's not like that! It's not! Taru wanted me
to invite you there with him! Not to go there instead of you!
For real?
Without a doubt.
I never doubted it. My Taru-sama would never be so careless
as to leave his precious betrothed behind.
Give me just a minute, Taru-sama.
I'll join you in no time.
Right a-wa-wa-way!
Oh? A flying broom?
I could use a ride, too!
Like that!
I always wanted to try riding it once.
Take-off!
If you don't hold on to it real tight,
you might hurt yourself!
Ah! The woods!
Come on!
Warming softly, good feeling...
Taru-sama!
Oh, Mimora.
How are you, Mimora-chan?
You'd better get your slimy hands
off my Taru-sama!
Haven't you learned yet,
that Taru-sama is my betrothed?
And Taru-sama also knows that he is mine!
As long as he has a woman such as me,
why would he ever need a woman
so small-eyed, and an old hag to boot!
Apologies, Iyona-chan. Children as they are,
those two have some grown-up ongoings.
Perhaps I really was
encroaching on Taru-chan in someone's eyes.
Taru-sama...
They're a couple...
I'm jealous.
"I'm jealous..."
Iyona-chan,
could you be yearning for a partner?
Right?
It's that time of the year...
Iyona-chan's partner...
If only Iyona-chan would want me as her partner!
A pipe dream, huh?
Get out of the ring!
Hey, hey! Hey-hey! Hey.
Is there any way for me to become Iyona-chan's partner?
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Hey!
I see, you're of no help to me.
Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out! Get out!
That's it!
If we hitch Honmaru-sama up with Iyona, there will no longer
be anyone to get in the way of my love for Taru-sama!
Honmaru-sama!
You let me handle this for you, please!
Mimora-chan, are you serious?
When I say I'll handle it, I mean it!
Mimora-chan, a thousand thanks!
Those classes are such a bore.
Now, then!
And Iyona is...
Found her! She's right there.
Let's go!
Hey, Rui-chan, next time you're going shopping
for the new spring sweater, bring me along, will you?
Yeah, sure.
The flowered collection must be copious this year.
I sure hope...
Uh-oh!
If it's the fashion you're after,
I am at your service.
By bringing along the champion
of the World Junior Fashion Coordination Competition,
you could always count
on my educated and precise advice.
Iyona is the local celebrity, I should think.
Falling for old hags
with eyes drooping down to their knees -
bad tasted must be the new epidemic nowadays!
Ahem! I just couldn't help noting, Iyona-san,
you could use the help of someone overwhelmingly versed in dressing up smartly, only wearing trendy British suits.
Ahem! Only after you consult me.
The combination I put together through scrupulous picking
from the great pile of garbs,
was so good, it's now set in my calendar permanently.
What you're saying is simply called trendy coordination.
So what?
Aren't you just making an excuse
for wearing one and the same thing all year round?
What, now?
Iyona, no getting along with people other than Honmaru!
Iyona-san, please ignore these hindrances
and let me guide you through the spring-summer collection.
Well, you can still have me...
Don't you know when to stop fooling around, you two?
What's the meaning of this?!
Whoa!
What do you mean?
Iyona-san!
Iyona-san...
Eh... What are those guys up to?
Iyona-san!
Let me, the World Champion
in barrier-breaching demonstrate—
Iyona ate a Cheese-Me-Alone.
Did you make her?
Not me, probably Mimora.
If you eat Cheese-Me-Alone, you become unapproachable.
Mimora, then?
But how is that supposed to facilitate us becoming partners?!
It's not what we settled on!
Right? Taruruuto! Hey! She is your girlfriend, isn't she?
Don't you worry about anything, Honmaru-sama.
You just need to don this.
What?
Trunsform!
Oh? What's this thing?
With this on your head,
Iyona would be inseparable from you!
You're the best, Mimora-chan!
Iyona-chan's smell is so cheasant!
Honmaru! What is your sorry ass trying with Iyona-san?!
Piss off!
Right, right!
You prick...
But why...
Serves you right!
Honmaru-kun, could you please let go of me?
I really wish I could stay here for a little longer, but oh well.
Eh?!
Honmaru-kun, what are you doing?
It'squeak... Nosqueak... Squeak, squeak...
Eh?! I've unlearned to speak!
And I can't get away either!
It's not funny anymore!
I wasn't trying to be funny, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Eh? I'm in trouble. What is this irresistible urge
to sink my teeth into Iyona-chan?
No!
Stop it!
Not again!
Well then. I may have bungled it the last time,
but I'll make up for it during this break!
Let's go!
Yeah! Me help, too.
We make Iyona Honmaru's partner.
You're making me so happy, Taru-sama!
I beg you, don't fail me this time, Mimora-chan!
I got it!
This time, I'll use the Ventrueloquitor.
We'll start by inquiring into Iyona's tastes in men.
Yeah!
Hey, hey, by the way, which of the boys do you like?
Red, then?
I was thinking of a sweater with a flowered pattern.
Hm... Are there any with red flowers?
Hey, hey, by the way, which of the boys do you like?
It worked, worked! The triumph of magic!
Mimora, you're good, good!
Whoa! That was unexpected.
You don't usually bring up topics like that.
Eh? I wonder what just made me say such a thing...
Well, it's spring, after all.
Spring?
Come on! I don't need you sayin' anything!
Mimora not get mad, not get mad.
I know how you feel - it's probably nice
to spend time with a funny guy.
Show me one person who asked for your opinion!
That's right, funny people are usually good.
Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
You need to remember this! Okay? Okay?
Yeah. Funny guy.
But then, it's also important that he is caring.
That's right. To be caring is important.
You get it now?
Taru-sama, it's because you're so caring!
But say, even if he's caring enough,
it's a no-go if he's a gloomy type.
This is also true.
So I guess, he must have a bright personality.
She said it!
Wow! So bright!
So, overall: handsome,
and with eyes that are big enough and shiny.
Probably, yes.
Guys with beautiful eyes are great.
And with long legs... A cool guy.
That's right.
With legs as graceful as those of a wild doe.
He, with big and shiny eyes!
But also with doe's legs?
You get it now? Only one such great person.
Right, that'd be great...
Come on! Iyona-chan, you've only been saying
that "that" or "this" is right.
You should voice your own opinion sometimes, too!
That's right...
Then stop saying "that's right" already!
My ideal type is someone with a flaming passion in their heart.
With a flaming passion in their heart.
Well, then, Honmaru-sama!
You two will go home together.
Invite Iyona now!
Are you sure?
Then, on your way home, when you two are all alone,
we'll make sure she is fascinated by your prowess.
Alright!
Oh, Honmaru-kun?
Let's go home together!
I'm sorry for what happened today...
And well... Uh...
Oh, Honmaru-kun?
Let's go home together.
Iyona-chan...
What a beautiful dandelion field!
Whe-ehell done, Mimora-chan!
And now, the first in the list...
To demonstrate his caring side.
Taru-sama!
Got it!
Snow Cloud Taro!
Hey! Snow Cloud Taro here.
What's going on? A blizzard amidst the spring!
And... Found!
I'll let this Pointurner handle the rest.
A coat!
Now then, offer this coat to Iyona!
Ah! I see.
Honmaru-kun?
You won't feel cold if you wear this.
Thank you.
Attaway, Mimora-chan! The mood is ideal!
Alright, and now, for some shiny eyes.
Honmaru-kun...
Still, where did you get that coat from?
Oh, I figured it might still get colder.
Honmaru-kun, do you love me?
Honmaru-kun, do you love...
me?
Iyona-chan!
I do.
I love you.
This is it! The supreme mood!
Yeah!
And for the finishing touch, the next magic is...
Here. The legs.
I...
Honmaru-kun, I also...
What... the hell... is this?!
Oh, come on, Mimora-chan!
We bungled this? Not the doe legs? Ah, oh, wait, wait...
Alright, the flaming heart!
It burns, burns, burns!
Mimora, stop, you're getting in my way!
And now... Now...
Big eyes!
It burns! It burns, it burns so bad!
Honmaru-kun!
Wrong! You're doing it all wrong, Taru-sama! Let me!
Let's see... Iyona loves a bright man.
I command you to become the brightest ever,
the dazzling Honmaru-sama!
What's this?
Honmaru-kun! Honmaru-kun, what's going on with you?
Mimora, quit getting in the way! I can do it ru-right!
It's here, here. Here. Funny guy.
Iyona loves a funny guy! High-level magic:
Funny Face!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan?
Hang on, Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan!
Stop this!
Iyona-chan... I'm sorry, Iyona-chan!
Ah, Honmaru-sama!
I admire the depth of Honmaru-sama's love for Iyona!
And it helped me realize
how much I love my Taru-sama, too!
This way, I won't ever have to worry
about others stealing Taru-sama away from me.
Peck!
Taru-sama!
You pests!
I've had enough!
I'll get you two out, like it or not!
You two...
Get back here, you walking mince!
Sorry, Honmaru!
Get back, get back, get back, get back, get back!
I said I'll kill you pests, didn't I?
Wow, Honmaru! I drew a picture of Honmaru.
What did you mean by that?
Oh, that the picture Honmaru drew?
Oh-ho! This powerful picture! I like Honmaru's drawing.
No wonder! Try to beat it!
Alright, we'll have Honmaru's picture fight my picture!
Come-tru-ru-rue!
Magical Taruruuto-kun: Come Alive, Giant Monster!
We're in trouble!
The whole class is scared to death!
Episode 32
Come Alive, Giant Monster
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius