Magical★Taruruuto-kun
Love-Love🖤 Takoyaki!
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Famous Osakan Takoyaki
Yahoo!
Hurry!
Matsu-san, we'll have one box.
Business goin'?
Doin' a buck here 'n there!
Matsu-san, we'll have the usual!
Gotcha! Will get you served in no time!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Ride of the Takolkyries technique!
No matter how much of them there are!
Here, sorry for the delay!
Matsu-san's technique is amazing every time I see it!
Okay, now look at my technique!
Okay-okay-okay-okay!
Taru's Scattered Technique!
How was it?
Why did you do that to everyone's share?!
Me...
Sorry, I only wanted to use a little bit of it...
Well, it ain't no big deal, right?
No way!
No deal?
Matsu-san, me guilty,
me no good magician, no good magician...
Settled! It's positively impossible
to refuse the little one in such a pain!
Why don't I cook up another box for you?
Me love Matsu-san!
Don't you know it tickles?
Thank you, Matsu-san!
It's nothin'!
Hold it, boys and girls!
Harako!
Iyona-san, victuals for the masses,
such as takoyaki, don't befit you.
Better leave that stuff to Honmaru's kind
and let me take you to a cafe.
What?
Oh? But I really like takoyaki.
Besides, the ones that Matsugoro-san
makes are not just delicious...
They're also filled with genuine happiness.
Happiness?
Yay! Get cold-shouldered!
Happiness, she said?
How's that...
How's that?
Oh?
My takoyaki's filled with happiness, huh?
Well, I guess I can't help it!
Would you like another box?
Thank you, Matsu-san!
Ain't no need to be scared.
You too wanna eat one of those, huh?
A little treat from me!
Taru-sama?
Mimora, me here in little house!
Taru-sama, I'm coming!
Ah! Takoyaki, takoyaki! Takoyaki!
I'll never be able to eat that kind of stuff!
Takoyaki really yummy, just try this!
It really is, Mimora!
Mimora, you'll see when you try it!
I hate takoyaki the most!
Mimora! Oh... Huh?
If Mimora hates takoyaki, I'll eat.
Taru-sama!
This kindness is what I love the most in you!
You rescued me by eating it yourself!
Taru-sama...
I'm happy to have you.
But I'd also be just as happy
if we didn't have any takoyaki between us.
Happy?
If Matsugoro is unable to make takoyaki,
Taruruuto will be depressed.
But Mimora-chan will be delighted instead!
And then...
Rival!
Thank you for getting rid of the takoyaki for us!
Kiss!
She'll be happy!
Alright... Ray!
Set out, Wucondor!
Condor!
Go and steal Matsugoro's takoyaki soul!
Soul
Huh...?
Tako.
Matsu-san! What happened, Matsu-san?
Taru-chan, there's trouble!
What is it?
Come here, Taruruuto!
Something's wrong with Matsu-san...
Matsugoro-san's takoyaki soul got stolen.
Huh? Takoyaki soul?
A takoyaki soul is a spiritual container
for Matsugoro-san's love for takoyaki.
Matsugoro's takoyaki soul is mine!
Rival?
It's above, Taru!
Yeah!
Ah! Taru-sama!
Come on...
If we don't get the takoyaki soul back by sunset,
Matsugoro-san will never be the same!
Then, if we don't return it by tonight...
Matsu-san will remain forever this way?
Matsugoro-san, try this. It's takoyaki.
You'll feel better.
Matsugoro-san...
This way, Matsugoro won't be able
to make takoyaki for the rest of his life!
Eat this, Taruruuto!
Matsu-san...
Come and take it back, if you wanna!
I'll take it back!
Matsu-san's takoyaki soul!
Think I'll give it up so easily?!
Taru's Attractor!
Taru!
Jeez, Taru-sama...
Takoyaki!
Hey, business goin'?
The mouse spoke!
That's because it swallowed the takoyaki soul.
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
Well, ain't I grateful? Big time!
Ah, no! Not today!
My name is Chugoro.
Nice to meetja!
Oops.
What's this inexplicable drive to bake takoyaki all o'sudden?
Hurry up!
You can extract his takoyaki soul with Achooweed!
Okay!
Think I'll let you help him, Taruruuto?!
Taru!
What's there to be so agitated about?
Why do they even care if the takoyaki
and the takoyaki cook are gone?
Dammit, where are they now?
Here?
Oops!
Leap!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru, I can't hold on any longer!
Taru!
Hm! Serves you right!
Ouch!
Are you okay?
Iyona-chan!
Thank you!
Taru, any idea what to do now?
Yeah! Use Gakigugego!
Who's there?
I don't suppose you mind getting help from me?
What?
Trunsform!
Gakigugego, emergency start!
Landing successful!
Phew.
Ah, it stinks!
Can't be helped. We're in the sewers, after all.
Yeah! I'll ask where we should look for Chugoro.
Tama-chan, Tama-chan!
Always captivating Tama-chan, please tell us!
Huh?
Oh!
Harako-kun?
Rival too!
Damn it! Why did they do that?
Yay! Rival and Harako became small too!
Wait up, Harako!
Wait for us!
He sure is heavy, Jabao-san...
You've only been complaining, Korekiyo-kun!
Oh?
It's you guys!
Oh, Oaya-sensei!
Isn't that admirable?
Taking care of the elderly like that!
We're not!
There, see?
Hello.
Matsugoro-san!
Crap! I lost sight of Harako!
Taru-chan, Chugoro has left the sewers.
He's in the supermarket on the surface.
Okay, let's hurry!
Yeah!
We heard it.
Tako-tako, yaki-yaki!
Come close!
I'm gonna be baking some of the most
appetizing takoyaki in no time!
Squeak!
Oh?
Fried balls!
Ah!
Chugoro-san!
Chugoro! Please give back Matsu-san's takoyaki soul!
Oh, you stubborn clowns!
Ah, there!
Wait!
Wait! Chugoro!
Now!
Ray!
Evacuate!
Who did it?
Taruruuto! I'm not letting you catch that mouse, ever!
Ray!
That's what I like to see!
Those stupid humans started a feud between each other!
Oh?
Iyona-chan!
Keep going!
What a cute lass they got!
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan, are you okay?
Iyona-chan's so close and soft!
Oh?
Huh?
Not there!
Iyona-chan,
it's getting dangerous now!
Trust me and Taruruuto to take care of Chugoro!
But...
It's okay. Don't worry.
We're not coming back
without Matsu-san's takoyaki soul.
Okay.
Alright! Let's roll up our sleeves, Taru!
Yeah!
Charge!
Be careful.
Isn't that Chugoro's cart?
Yay! Huge octopus! Octopus!
That means he's also somewhere nearby!
This way?
A dead end...
There!
What's that sound?
What's that?
What?
Prepare yourself, Taruruuto!
Serves you right, you scum!
Huh?
Iyona-san! You're...
You're getting in the way!
Ray!
Iyona-san!
Hey! Harako, hurry up and plug in the machine!
What? Nobody gives me orders!
Taruruuto!
Honmaru! I cast a spell!
Everyone, please-please help us!
What the...?!
Help me!
Help, someone!
Why is...
This happening to us?
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun! Honmaru-kun!
And... down!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun! Honmaru-kun!
Damn you, you swine!
Iyona-chan!
Oh?
Crap...!
The sun is almost setting, Jabao-san.
All we can do is twiddle our thumbs nervously...
Ah, a beautiful sunset...
Come on! Come get a taste
of my scrumptious takoyaki!
Don't be shy, eat as much as you can!
Iyona-chan's share too!
Eh?
Mine?
Delicious!
Are you serious?
Alright! Everything's on the house today!
Hey! Give back Iyona-chan!
Don't you go around
pretending to be a real takoyaki chef, you fraud!
Honmaru-kun!
Give back Iyona-chan!
You little...!
My takoyaki!
That's for getting distracted in a fight!
You're mistaken, Honmaru-kun.
Ah! Iyona-chan!
You're mistaken!
Honmaru-kun!
Chugoro-sama never hurt me. He only treated me to takoyaki!
Huh? Takoyaki?
Chugoro-sama just wanted me to try his takoyaki too.
My lady...
Please forgive us.
But I have one urgent request!
Request?
Chugoro, need a favor, big time!
Give back Matsu-san takoyaki soul!
Whatcha doin', you creepy kid?!
Chugoro-san, please!
Please give us back his takoyaki soul!
Please! Please give back his takoyaki soul!
Honmaru-kun!
Takoyaki soul, you say?
Takoyaki soul resides in Chugoro's body now.
If we don't get it back to Matsu-san before sunset,
we'll be in big trouble!
Chugoro understands too.
Matsu-san is a kind and nice guy.
He also always treats us to takoyaki!
Treats you to takoyaki...?
You also wanna try one of those, right?
That's on the house.
That guy?
I'm a man too! When it's
for such a good cause, I can't refuse!
Thank you!
Thank you, Chugoro-san!
This - Achooweed.
Makes you sneeze when it tickles your nose.
Achooweed. Rub-rub-rub.
Matsu-san! Matsu-san!
Matsu-san's takoyaki soul!
Ah! Matsugoro-san!
Matsu-san smells of his own takoyaki!
Chugoro-san...
Chugoro...
Thank you!
Chugoro-san!
Faster, Taru! The sun is setting!
Okay!
I can see it already!
Matsu-san's house!
Taru, are you okay?
Is Matsu-san okay?
You're not making it
to Matsugoro's place, Taruruuto!
Ah! And we're almost at Matsu-san's house!
This is your end, Taruruuto!
Who did it?!
How dare you bully Taru-sama!
That was the final... The final...
Mimora-chan...
I just...
That was the final straw!
Alright, Taruruuto!
This is our chance to deliver the takoyaki soul!
Yeah!
There you go-go-go, Taru!
I'll make it in time!
Matsu-san!
Matsu-san! Matsu-san!
Taru-sama!
You wanted to see me...
No! Takoyaki!
Ah! Mimora, don't!
What do I do now?!
The sun is about to set!
Matsu-san!
That mouse...
Oh!
It's him!
Matsu-san!
Huh? Matsu-san!
We didn't make it in time, after all!
He died!
Yeah!
Matsu-san!
Open your eyes, Matsu-san!
Open your eyes!
Boy, I slept so well!
Matsu-san!
Real Matsu-san!
Yeah.
What's with everyone gathering here?
Huh?
Real Matsu-san!
What was that?
Business goin'?!
Doin' a buck here n' there!
He's the real one! Matsu-san!
Matsu-san!
Our good old Matsu-san!
What was that?
Well, aren't you guys weird?
Matsu-san!
Me happy!
Gotta say, I feel jolly myself!
But I have this feeling, dunno why,
that I wanna bake takoyaki for free!
Dunno why, I wanna eat them for free!
Tromp-tromp, I'm running straight ahead
Sniff-sniff, the smell is calling me!
My heart is doing throb-throb, why? Why?
That's the power of takoyaki magic!
Matsu-san's takoyaki is the best in the world, hm!
If you eat it, you'll feel happy instantly!
Honmaru and Iyona are feeling great too
The magic of takoyaki is amazing!
I'm sure it'll reach you too
Everyone is happy and loves each other!
With the help of takoyaki magic, even the earth
Can turn into a huge takoyaki!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius