Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Autumn is the season of love!
Episode 55
Date on an Autumn Day🖤
Honmaru!
Iyona
Iyona-chan...
An outstanding athlete and an exemplary student.
Moreover, a lady of noble descent.
And above all, so pure-hearted and kind.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru...
Honmaru?
What are you thinking about?
Argh, I wanna go on a date with Iyona-chan so bad!
I wanna, wanna!
I so wanna go on a date...
The torments of love, right?
Honmaru is that age, after all.
Alright.
Ouch! Hey! That hurt!
Honmaru, Honmaru!
You got it, you got a Five-pointed Pleaseal!
Eh? Five-pointed Pleaseal?
A Five-pointed Pleaseal that'd make only one wish come true?
But do take care, Honmaru.
Should you abuse the wish to offend or hurt others,
it'll catch up to you later.
Try to use that wish for peace and happiness then, alright?
I understand, Sister Ria.
Honmaru, hurry up and speak your wish!
Okay!
O Lord, o Great Buddha!
I love Iyona-chan more than anything!
Let us have a date in the park today. Please!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, hurry up to the park.
Thank you, Sister Ria!
Taruruuto! We're going out!
Okay!
Let's go!
Taruruuto, I need a favor.
Try to create the right mood for me and Iyona-chan today!
Leave that to me!
Central Park
Alright!
Alright.
Still, did Iyona-chan really come here?
...Here.
Iyona-chan!
Taru! Taruruuto, as agreed!
Yeah, as agreed!
Alright!
Come on, Ninomaru.
Iyona-chan!
Oh? Honmaru-kun.
Good morning.
Wishing you a wonderful morning.
Today, Iyona-chan is cuter than ever!
Ah, were you busy with something?
Yes, I was reading a book.
I thought to myself, "What a pleasant day".
Then, somehow, before I knew it, my feet took me here...
So it worked?
Never mind.
Mind if I sit here?
Sure, feel free.
Pardon me.
Well, isn't Ria's magic amazing?
Say, where is Taru-chan?
Taruruuto is on a date with Mimora-chan.
Me here. But be hush about it.
Is that so?
Aren't Taru-chan and Mimora-chan lucky
to be getting along so well?
Even her laugh is beyond cute!
Somehow,
it feels like the spring's warmth is arriving again,
but only around us two.
Good, good, Honmaru. Right atmosphere.
Hey Iyona-chan, what book are you reading?
This? A book called Earth's Ecosystem.
Ecosystem?
Never expected less from you!
Great books you're reading there...
Though I sure wonder what kind of stuff is written in it.
I'm still just a kid, so I don't really understand.
Makes sense.
This book is about the trees, grass, and flowers
that surround us from all sides.
Huh?
For example, trees bathe in sunlight
and perform photosynthesis.
They breathe in carbon dioxide,
then exhale oxygen.
As for us, we breathe in that oxygen
and exhale carbon dioxide.
Which, in turn, is consumed by trees again.
Nurtured and blessed by the sun, the trees and grass
grow big enough. And then, animals eat them.
But before long, those animals would also die.
Those animals return to the earth,
from which vegetation is born anew.
On our planet, this cycle comes full circle,
goes on around and around, spreading life all-round.
This harmonious flow of living organisms is the circle of life,
which constitutes the essence of our world.
Ah, I get it now!
Since it goes on around and around, it forms a circular cycle!
How peculiar!
That text was so difficult, I didn't understand a word of it!
What's more, if you ponder seriously on the carbon cycle...
Hey, hey!
Oh! Honmaru mouth-flaps, trying to say something.
Hm? Forehead hurts?
Ah! Head! It's head!
"Bright."
"Ma!"
"Gic."
Oh! Head, bright, ma, gic.
Got it! Magic for making you bright-headed.
This - Turbohead-kun.
Helps increase the speed at which your head operates.
So the thing is...
What's this? Taruruuto's magic?
What kind of book should I...
I see. So that's the kind of books you're into?
Admittedly, our human species has been hitherto single-minded in our pursuit of self-preservation.
And yet, little heed
did we spare to the ecosystem as a whole.
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan seems stupefied by my words.
Ergo the cataclysmic crisis we had to face as of recently;
that is, each and every organic system
collapsing all around our Blue Planet.
Mood is perfect between Honmaru and Iyona.
But I gotta try even harder.
All life forms are afflicted by that rapacious, wanton slaughter,
not to mention the wars waged amongst humanity.
And of course, pollution and radioactive contamination.
To contend post-haste with those challenges, we need
to advocate for our coexistence with the flora and fauna.
This - Overhead Falleaves.
Would help boost the mood even more.
This is a world for just the two of them.
Mood is excellent.
A success! Iyona-chan is completely entranced by my words!
In other words, we need to find our unison with the universe,
and reach for it in our heart of hearts.
That may well be our fated mission, as humans.
Even this tiny fallen leaf
is a part of the process that supports our big earth.
Thank you.
Honmaru-kun, you're truly amazing.
It's as if you're knowledgeable about everything...
Uh, I wouldn't go that far...
I was enthralled listening to you.
Overhead Falleaves fall-fall, fall there, fall here.
Oh, dragonfly. Red dragonfly!
Iyona-chan! Iyona-chan, are you okay?
I wonder what had just happened.
A mystery indeed...
Ah! Actually, Iyona-chan...
Yes?
Iyona-chan, would you like to ride a boat?
With pleasure.
Okay, let's go then.
Okay.
Hey, Taru! You're overdoing it!
Me overdid.
This - Mood-upping Gramophone.
Creates romantic atmosphere between two.
So far so good, Honmaru.
Alright, now we'll make Iyona stick to you.
Wind
This - Fangust-kun.
Can cause all kinds of wind to rise.
Gro-ro-ro-row!
Wind
Now...
Must be Taru's doing again.
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Ah! Lucky!
You'll be alright, Iyona-chan.
Ah, Iyona-chan's skin is so soft!
And such a sweet smell when she's close!
Honmaru-kun!
Don't worry, Iyona-chan.
Iyona and Honmaru hugging tight!
It's alright now. The storm has settled, Iyona-chan.
Were you scared?
I'm sorry, I lost my composure.
No...
No, coming from a girl, that was rather cute.
Said it! My head is still turbocharged!
That's Turbohead-kun for you!
Whenever you're scared,
don't hesitate to jump on my chest.
I just keep those killer lines coming!
That line sounds a bit precocious for your age,
Honmaru-kun.
Nah...
I look at you and they roll off the tongue naturally.
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru doing well so far.
This time, I'll be helping you from invisibility.
With this!
Erase, erase, erase, erase.
"The long sobs of the violins of autumn
Wound my heart with a monotonous languor."
That poem by Verlaine is sublime.
Honmaru-kun, you're much more than meets the eye.
You're actually quite the romanticist.
Is that so?
Ah, Iyona-chan, what a cute smile you have!
Ninomaru?
Huh?
Me find myself in trouble...
Hey, don't come near! Shoo! Shoo! Oh, you...
Ninomaru? Ninomaru!
I wonder what happened.
Alright, let's muster up the courage and go for it!
Ninomaru!
Oh? What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
Ah! That doggie is getting in the way. Getting in the way!
Honmaru-kun, let me deal with it!
Huh? What's the matter?
Era-ra-ra-rase!
Ninomaru?
Oh, that's more getting in the way!
Not romantic at all!
I'll deal with that too!
One-two, one-two, one-two...
Era-ra-ra-ra-ra-rase!
That's better. Much, much better.
Oh my...
How about some candy?
Would you like some candy?
Candy! Anyone want to have some candy?
Oh no, this park is full of noisy people!
You'll be getting in the way! I'll erase everyone!
Already, it's autumn...
It looks ominously empty today.
So it would seem, Jabao-san.
You're in the way!
What? In the way?
Huh? Jabao-san, where did you go?
Korekiyo, where did you go yourself?
Where are you, Korekiyo?!
Right here!
What do you mean, "here"?!
Help me!
Pitcher swings at the third pitch!
Did he decide on a forkball?
Let's see!
Strike! Batter out!
Honmaru doing well.
Alright, time for some more closeness with Iyona.
Gro-ro-ro-row!
I’m sorry...
Keep it this way.
Looking good, Honmaru.
Time for finishing touches.
I'll use this - Yahook up with me-kun.
When this arrow pierces someone's heart,
they fall in love with the person in the photo.
I can't take any chances with this,
so I'll shoot them all at once.
Oh! Takoyaki stall!
Oh no!
Iyona-chan, I brought yours too.
Here.
Thank you.
Love!
I love more!
What?
My, you're so handsome!
You all think you love me?
Yes!
I see. How about...
Serious.
Thoughtful.
Careless.
Well, girls, you're so troublesome!
Really? You think so?
Ah... Ah, Honmaru!
Honmaru, Iyona is walking away!
What to do, what to do, what to do?
Everyone, can you hear it?
The voice of autumn
Huh?
What in the world happened to me?
What's with this kid?
None of the arrows pierced the heart.
That's why the magic wore off in no time.
How can we appreciate this big blue sky?
Why don't we stare into this blue yonder together?
Who do you think you are to be hitting on our women? Huh?
What do you mean?
We're not kidding, you brat!
You little!
Next time, don't get even close to our women!
Honmaru!
Taru...
Honmaru, Honmaru, are you okay?
But why...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun, don't get up! Really...
My little idiot.
Iyona-chan...
Thank you, Iyona-chan.
Thank you, Taru.
Autumn day, autumn sky, autumn wind.
Iyona's laps as a pillow.
Honmaru oh-so happy!
Honmaru, what's the matter?
Another special training?
Yeah. I'm going to the mountains with my dad.
Alright, I'm coming too.
Trust me with this!
No, this time I want to try out my own strength.
So just wait at home, Taru.
Oh? Honmaru, you don't want to bring me along?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Honmaru, a Tearful Decision.
Honmaru, come back soon!
Episode 56
Honmaru, a Tearful Decision
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius