Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Attempting to bring Honmaru back to life,
Taruruuto headed with him to the Magic Realm,
where his mama lives.
Episode 61
Operation Resurrection
Welcome back...
Welcome back!
Welcome back.
Mama... Mama!
Taru-chan...
Mama!
...Taru-chan!
Mama...
Welcome home.
Mama!
Taru-chan!
It tickles!
I'm so glad for you, Taru.
You got to meet your mama.
Mama... Mama...
Taru-chan...
There, there.
She sure is a wonderful mama...
Mama, huh?
Good for you, Taru.
There, there.
Honmaru-chan.
It's alright.
Mama!
The Magic Realm is the world of souls.
If your thoughts are honest,
anything can come true.
Here, you're not bound by either fleshly or material ties. This is a world of freedom.
Anything you can think of...
Everything in your heart...
What was death in the previous world
is life in the next world.
Honmaru-chan...
We have no sway over the matters
of human life and death.
Forget it all and sweet be your sleep.
Soon enough, an angel from heaven will come for you.
Honmaru-chan...
I don't want it!
I don't wanna die!
I don't!
Taru's mama!
I want to come back to life!
Please use your magic to bring me back to life!
Please!
Mama?
I can't do that.
Anything but that!
Please don't make me go through this!
I wanna live...
In my world!
The one I loved the most in this world...
was Honmaru-kun!
...With Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan...
Iyona.
Iyona...
Iyona-chan!
Don't tear your heart apart so much.
Very well.
You'll come back to life, Honmaru-chan.
Taru?
Honmaru!
That's it! I'm coming back to life!
Coming back to li-li-life!
We did it, Taru!
I'm going back, Taru!
But I'm so sorry.
I don't have the power to return Honmaru-chan back to life.
In the Magic Realm, everyone knows
what you're thinking of, remember?
It's impossible to tell lies.
Mama!
Then, how should I go about coming back to life?
Listen carefully.
In the heart of this Magic Realm,
there lies the Ice Spirit Mountain.
The Colored Sky Hermit lives there.
And it's said that he has the power
over human life and death.
Ice Spirit Mountain?
Colored Sky Hermit?
Yes.
I'll write him a letter of request right now.
Thank you, Taru's Mama!
We can do it, Honmaru!
Yeah.
However...
You'll have to rely on your own strength
to meet the Hermit.
And climbing Ice Spirit Mountain is awfully difficult.
We'll be alright!
Nothing is impossible for Honmaru-sama!
That's the spirit, Honmaru!
The path to meeting Colored Sky Hermit
is fraught with trials and hurdles.
It's a tall order as it is to meet the hermit
before an angel from heaven catches up to you.
Maybe it's better to give up now while you still can.
Honmaru has achieved all sorts of things,
doing his best up until now!
Don't worry, Taru's Mama.
It's because I know you very well.
You can make it happen.
Your soul can make it through.
I'll definitely meet the hermit,
I'll definitely come back to life and see Iyona-chan again!
Just you wait, Iyona-chan!
It's damn cold, Taru!
Honmaru, you're naked.
That's why it's cold.
I see.
Taru,
please conjure something for me to wear.
Honmaru, just think about yourself getting dressed.
Then you'll get dressed.
In Magic Realm, what you think about
takes shape in the world.
When you thought about flying in the sky, you flew in the sky.
I see.
When I took off into the sky,
that was with my own power too.
Alright!
Warm clothes...
Honmaru, you're natural!
Piece of cake!
Impressive!
You alright there, Taru?
Achoo-achoo-achooweed!
Honmaru invented interesting game!
Now, it's your turn. Do it, do it!
Taru.
I'm really not trying to play around here!
It's cold even with clothes on.
Why is it so cold even with clothes on, Taru?
This mountain likes cold.
Honmaru's desire to be warm is defeated
by this mountain's desire to be cold.
That's why Honmaru is cold.
You kids!
How can you hope to climb me, if one frosty gust is enough to discourage you?
What's the cold treatment and mockery for?
Why not go easy on us, pretty please?
Spirit Mountain-sama.
Someone too gutless and too weak to climb me
has no business meeting the Colored Sky Hermit!
Better reconsider now!
Bleeeh!
You jerk... Pretending to be humble,
but you're actually just a selfish, stuck-up mountain!
Why, you... I'll make you take that back!
Ah? Honmaru, you're wrong!
Mountain-sama actually is stuck way higher than us!
Who do you think you are?!
I can be that great too!
I'll climb you up easily!
In this world, heart is all that matters!
That why I can't lose either!
I have enough guts so I'll win!
Hey, Mountain! What about now?!
Who do you think...
Who do you think you are?!
Damn it all!
Honmaru!
Can't hold on...
Honmaru. Honmaru!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Honmaru? Honmaru!
Honmaru, stay strong, Honmaru! Honmaru...
Honmaru...
Honmaru, I'll try to do something with magic.
I should have something...
Something... Must be something...
My magic is no match for the power of Mountain-sama.
What?
What's this?
Bonjour!
My name is Stylish Champion of Taste Garçon.
Can you help?
Oui! I can tailor any clothes exactly according to your order!
Really?
I want some clothes that'd make me
completely immune to any low temperature!
Oui.
Me too!
Oui! It's as simple as one, two, three...
I'm starting!
I'm the best tailor in all of Magic Realm.
This sure feels warmer than before!
Oui!
Warmer!
How are you finding my design? Like it?
Yeah!
It's the best!
Oui...
Alright, Taru, let's start!
Okay!
It's nothing, nothing!
I did it!
How about this, Mountain?
We climbed you!
As expected of Taru's magic!
This wasn't even my magic.
Well, good job climbing! Congrats!
What's wrong?
This...
Oui?
It's him!
What about him?
He has mama's smell!
My, so I got exposed. Too bad.
Your mama sneakily put it in your bag?
Bingo, sir.
Thank you, Taru's Mama!
Mama!
Huh? I did what was required of me,
but where exactly is the hermit
who can bring me back to life?
Where-where Hermit-sama? Where is he?
Ugh! Hey, Mountain! There's no hermit here!
You're a fraud!
Rub-rub
Mountain-san, please tell us.
The Hermit-sama is right above us.
Okay! I'll jump there!
Jump!
Yay!
Huh?
Taruruuto?
Alright, now it's my turn to jump.
Wait-wait, I don't wanna! Not me!
It damn hurts!
Honmaru!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Thank you.
Damn it, Taru... Isn't there a better way?
Ah, I know!
Honmaru, what-what-what came to your mind?
Let's go, Taru!
I can fly with my wings! Me smart!
Well done, Taru!
Taru?
Even your magic doesn't work there?
My bum-bum hurts!
Little one, don't you underestimate my strength!
Ugh! What on earth should we do?
How can we see Hermit-sama?
Mountain-san, tell me, tell me, lick-lick-lick.
Rub-rub
Not happening. I'm not telling you.
Come on, you damn cheapskate!
Stop pretending to be a humble mountain already!
Get this!
Honmaru, don't do that!
Mountain-san, we're sorry!
Stung
Did you just kick me right here?
It's an eruption!
Ouch-ouch! He sent burning stones flying in all directions!
It's hot here, mama!
I urge you to rethink!
Ouch-ouch! What are these guys?
I'll ask Tama-chan what we should do.
Tama-chan!
Tama-chan, Tama-chan!
Always captivating Tama-chan!
Pwease twell me!
Please tell!
Give me just a moment.
Taru-chan, there's only one way to climb that mountain.
You've no choice but to spring up there after washing your head with this magic item, "Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo."
Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo?
Taru, you have that?
I don't.
Tama-chan, do you know where to find it?
I know...
Can you show us the way?!
Sure...
Just you wait, damned mountain!
Tama-chan, which way?!
Turn right.
Okay!
Now head toward that red ball on the left.
From there - right! Left! Down! Up!
Okay, where now?!
Just beyond that planetoid...
We're here.
Excuse me, you got any Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo here?
Yes, we have it.
That's it!
Whoa there!
Where are your scrolls?
Don't you have one?
When you win a magic duel...
You put a stamp on it
and when you collect them all,
you can exchange these scrolls for magic items.
Here's mine. Mine...
Just one here!
You've not been trying to collect them at all!
Taru, yours?
Here's mine...
You can have this Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo all to yourself
but only after you collect 70 of them.
All 70?
Tama-chan, is there really no other way?
There is none!
Getting 70 stamps means having to beat 70 magicians, right?
It won't do!
We definitely don't have the time for that!
The one I loved the most in this world...
was Honmaru-kun!
Shit! If I give up now,
I won't get to see Iyona-chan ever again!
Hey, Honmaru, you can do it!
That's what your Mama said too!
The Magic Realm is the world of heart!
Anything is possible if your thoughts are honest!
Alright! In that case, be it 70 or even 100,
I'll beat them all!
Yeah!
Um, dueling strong magicians
is a good way to quickly collect a lot of stamps.
Really? Then, does that mean
even one would be enough?
Yes.
You should've said so sooner!
So, who would be the strongest around here?
Let me think...
The strongest in these places is...
That'd be... Right. Mahalapa.
Papparapa!
On second thought, maybe you shouldn't.
You see, Mahalapa...
Oh? Gone already?
Tama-chan, which way?
Over there.
Let's go!
He's here!
I challenge you! Come out, Mahalapa!
Alright!
Papparapa!
He's huge!
What will we compete at, Mahalapa?
Hm. Anything's fine with me.
Hm... But what about water?
We'll have a duel in water!
Hey, Taru! It'd be better
if we got to decide what to compete at!
When you challenge someone for a duel,
the defender gets to choose the competition.
This is a rule of the Magic Realm.
Really?
But we've no time to babble around!
Let's defeat him quickly
and get our Heavenly Jumpin' Shampoo!
Now, what kind of magic can we use?
If you're not coming at me,
I'm coming at you first!
Tsunami Shnot!
Come on! Hurry up! Hurry, Taru! Find something! Hey!
You don't really live up to your boasting!
We lost!
Huh? Lost?
Now then,
the stamps are mine.
Papparapa!
Now, I wonder how much for each one.
What now? Just one? What a weakling you are!
Well, here's one more.
Young men, you just need to get a little better at this,
then I might see you again.
Ah! So frustrating, so frustrating!
Instead of beating Mahalapa and getting a stamp of him,
we got wiped away so helplessly!
It's okay, Honmaru. We'll duel him once again later!
Yes! Of course we will!
I've no clue what this Mahalapa and Papparapa mumbo-jumbo is about, but I can't afford to lose!
Papparapa!
Good luck, Taru-chan and Honmaru-chan.
But your time is running out. Make haste!
Papparapa!
Damn it! Whatever that Mahalapa-Papparapa
mumbo-jumbo is about, he's one strong bastard!
Strong bastard!
Taru, bring out the Hormonger!
We'll capitalize on this guy's lewdness!
Okay! Mahalapa is just about as perverted as Honmaru.
Taru-chan, that wouldn't be necessary.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Farewell, Honmaru.
Episode 62
Farewell, Honmaru
Everyone, be happy, will you?
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius