Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 41
Dishonest Neyo!
Honmaru with his impeccable dribble!
Riddle! Fiddle! Beetle!
Alright... He's going for a streak!
He escapes the defense!
And... One-two!
One shot!
Wan-woo! Bun with apricot!
With a single stroke, he scores a reversal shot!
After this, the ballads about him...
Honmaru, wanna eat a bun with apricot!
That's not what I meant, Taru.
For today's gym class, we're playing basketball.
So I wanna make sure Iyona-chan
sees my amazing shot in all its glory!
Huh? Is that Zakenja Neyo?
Eek! They're the infamous local middle-school group!
Yay! Neyo!
Taru! You idiot!
Taru, stop! They're the enemy!
Not e-nemy, but a-Neyo. Honmaru, you erred.
What?
What do I now? Should I get the teacher?
But then we won't make it in time!
Still, if I just run away now, Edojo Honmaru
will be an excuse of a man! Let's go, Taru!
Yeah!
Zakenja! I'll help you now...
Yay! Neyo! Neyo!
Neyo, teach me to play kendama!
Hey, Taru. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hey, isn't there some magic
we could use to fix her personality?
Now is good.
Huh?
Me like Neyo.
Honmaru like Neyo too!
Don't spew nonsense like that!
She's a hooligan! Totally unbearable.
Me know. Honmaru do like.
What is this? Hey, what is it? Huh?
Honmaru like Neyo!
Shut up already! I can only hate such a person!
True
What happened? It wilted.
Yay! This - Honestree,
when you say lies it withers. Honmaru, you lied!
Oh, is that so?
Honmaru likes Neyo, after all.
Yay! Honmaru loves-loves Neyo!
Ugh! Hey, Taruruuto!
Eh? We've no time for that!
Likes Neyo!
Honmaru!
Good.
Alright, time to do my best!
Do your best! Do your best!
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun, hurry up and chip in on the class expenses!
Lest everyone finds out...
Honmaru's the only one who came late today!
Only Honmaru! Only Honmaru!
Late! Late!
Late! Late! Belated Honmaru!
Shit. This is all Zakenja's fault.
Cretin.
Yay! Honmaru cretin! Cretin!
Okay everyone, have all of you figured out
which team you belong in?
Yes!
Yay! Yay!
Honmaru-kun, let's try our best.
Yeah! I won't let you down!
Success! I'm on the same team as Iyona-chan!
Hey, Honmaru.
If you bungle this, I'll make you pay dearly!
Okay...
But I'm also on the same team as Jabao...
Honmaru! Also on the same as me!
Now then, embrace teamwork
and fight hard enough so you don't regret it later.
1,
2,
3,
Hey.
4.
Huh?
Now that's strange.
Teacher! Our team is missing one player.
Huh? How odd.
Everyone was supposed to divide into teams of five...
Huh?
Zakenja-san? Aren't you also on Ijigawa's team?
Aren't you, Zakenja-san?
You can't build any teamwork
with irresponsible teammates.
I completely agree.
Okay!
Got it. Okay, get out of my way now!
Jabao! Pass! Pass! Over here, Jabao!
Pass!
Here, Honmaru!
Alright...
PASS TO ME! Neyo!
I'm ready too!
Super! Super!
Hey, Honmaru!
But...
Nice shot, Zakenja-san.
Well done indeed.
Still, passing would've been safer now.
I think so too.
Who does she think she is?
Not one bit appealing.
Ugh! Give me the ball!
Try to take it!
There! Jaba-Jaba-Jaba-Jabao!
Stop throwing it around, you! Damn...
There, there, there! Hey!
You wench! Put it down!
Try to take it, if only you can!
Get ready!
PASS TO ME AGAIN!
Yay! Yay!
JESUS CHRIST!
Tsk! That's why I told you to pass!
You even snatched the ball from me!
Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan?
Hang on!
Iyona-chan, are you okay? Iyona-chan!
Yes...
You rammed her on purpose!
Certainly looked to me this way.
You're all mistaken! That was a coincidence...
Exactly!
That was just an ordinary mid-game accident!
Honmaru-kun is right.
Iyona-san should let us deal with it!
I can't have any trust for a player who's oblivious to teamwork and only ever sticks to the stand play!
What's with everyone?
Let's continue the game.
Jeez. There's a reason I don't ever play ball with brats.
Zakenja-san!
No... No!
What's wrong, Ijigawa?
The money I had in my desk for the class supplies is gone!
What!?
And what happened to it?
The money that we raised together is gone!
Ah, and I'll be held responsible for that!
It's not here!
Hey, let's search together, shall we?
It could have fallen on the floor somewhere.
Everyone searches!
Found it?
Nah!
Are you sure you put it in your desk?
I'm sure I did. I totally did!
Searu-ru-rching!
Can't detect anything.
What?
I know!
Someone pocketed it!
That seems likely.
Even if it never happened before.
Until a certain someone transferred to our school.
It can't be!
Eh? What's this?
Is it me? Me?
What are y'all glaring at?
Are you suggesting I pocketed it?
A woman, smoking while still in elementary school,
would be the first on my list of suspects.
Are you kidding me?!
Wait, everyone.
Let's search again, more carefully.
Right, let's keep searching!
Honmaru-kun...
Yeah! I'll do the searu-ru-rching!
Searching, searching, searching...
Not here, not here...
Iyona-chan, I'll find it!
It's a promise!
Honmaru-kun...
Taru, lend me the Goggles.
Okay! Honmaru smart.
We'll use these to search!
Ouch!
I don't doubt Zakenja's innocence,
but for good measure, I gotta check!
Man, I'm such a troubleshooter!
Sneak Peek.
Seems like it's not in her desk.
But it sure is full of dangerous stuff!
I've got a hard choice to make.
Next, I gotta check if she's not hiding it under the clothes.
Sneak Peek.
Eh?! She's still in elementary,
yet she's already wearing black lacy underwear!
What kind of elementary grader are you?
I absolutely cannot use the spell any further!
Still... If the money happens to be inside that bra...
I can't help it!
This is all for the sake of uncovering the truth...
Sneak Peek.
Honmaru, what's wrong?
What happened, Honmaru?
No... Just had a spontaneous nosebleed.
Are you alright, Honmaru-kun?
Oh no, oh no!
I'll die from excessive loss of blood if this continues!
Honmaru never stops being funny!
Alright, let's knock the transparency down a tad bit.
Yeah!
Blind Eye.
Not here! Not here either.
As expected. 'Cause Zakenja pocketed it, didn't she?
What did you say?
Taru, give Zakenja the Honestree from this morning.
Okay!
I didn't pocket shit!
What's this thing?
It bloomed, bloomed! Honestree bloomed!
Neyo is honest, she didn't say the lie!
Exactly! She couldn't have possibly stolen it!
Why do you act like you know everything
when wearing some weird glasses?
Where is your evidence? Evidence!
Honmaru,
what is your game, defending me?
What?
Honmaru! In that case, where is the money?
Come on! Let us know too! Where is it? Huh?
Oh? Is that...
Ijigawa! What's this money you have on your belly?
Eh? Belly?
Look away!
Huh? Hey! I've got the money!
It's the money!
Oh, I know! I put it in there so as not to lose it!
Yay! Yay!
We could also check the amount!
Really, it was that easy?
Are you kidding me?!
After accusing one repeatedly,
you don't just laugh it off!
Sorry.
It's your daily lousy demeanor
that makes you a suspect by definition.
What?
What now, wanna go out?
Mind you, I'm the undisputed World Junior Champion
of Open Martial Arts, Harako Tsutomu-sama!
Wanna go out still?
This girl... Can be quite dangerous.
Can't believe I let myself get serious
when dealing with elementary graders.
There's a reason I ain't messing around with brats like you!
Zakenja...
Chickened out?
Leaving suddenly doesn't make you look cool!
What's with her saying "brats" all the time?
She just doesn't know how to be upfront.
The tongue is the root of calamities.
Okay, let's go!
She's probably feeling a bit low
after having been treated that way.
Neyo good person.
Yeah. She ain't a bad person for sure.
Yeah!
Oh! It'd be nice if Neyo married a man named "Good Person."
Huh?
What?
"Zakenja Neyo" would become "Good Person Neyo!"
Zakenja Neyo would become Good Person Neyo! Yay!
Jeez.
Say, Taru, if we would've used Yahoonest Feelings-kun on her,
do you suppose she'd be a little more honest?
Yeah.
Who did it?!
Pretty sure I just poked you a little.
Why'd a man yell like a banshee over it?
Zakenja?
Ouch!
For a little poke, that hurt way too much!
That's how it always is with you,
in all and everything you do -
you're putting in too much power!
For starters, you're supposed to be a girl,
you know that?!
For today...
Thank you.
Catch you later!
Honmaru's mouth like octopus! Octopus!
Octopus tentacle-long mouth!
Dammit, Zakenja Neyo! Why, you...
Octopus, octopus!
I wanna eat takoyaki!
Honmaru, I'll borrow your umbrella, alright?
Not one bit cute!
Thank you for today.
Say, Taru, could it be that someone used
Yahoonest Feelings-kun on her?
Uh? I didn't.
I see.
Neyo really very nice when honest.
Me like Neyo.
Honmaru like Neyo too. Love her!
You're a weirdo,
Zakenja Neyo!
Neyoyoyo!
Ah! Dad flew off the handle again.
And why am I always so gutless?
Taru, isn't there some nice magic for that?
Yeah!
This - True Storing.
Everything you say while wearing it becomes a true story.
Oh? Wait a minute.
I can do even this!
Could it actually be that ultimate universal item?
You've done it, Taru!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
The Tongue is the Root of Calamities?
Watch it, everyone!
Episode 42
The Tongue is the Root of Calamities?
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius