Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
To thwart Zakenja Nezo's ambitions
of assuming full control over Nannosho Elementary,
Honmaru bravely stood up
to face him and his dreadful deadly fist.
Even after he had been hit by Nezo's Tranquilizing Fist
thanks to all his previous special trainings, Honmaru managed to mount a fierce counterattack with the power of ki.
However, only Harako and Taruruto
felt this distinctly ominous premonition so far.
Honmaru...
Episode 59
Honmaru's Final Battle!
In this case, I've no choice but to use the Evil Blade Wave.
I'll put all my power into it
and send out a Genuine Evil Blade Wave!
Honmaru's unexpected counterattack
seems to have put Zakenja in a predicament.
Indeed, his countenance is now more like that of a demon!
What is Zakenja about to do?
He's accumulating ki at a tremendous rate!
However, all of his ki is evil ki!
Zakenja plunged his heart into darkness
and is accumulating bad power.
So far, I've only been using a fraction
of the Evil Blade Wave power.
Honmaru! This next shot will send you straight to hell!
Fight, Edojo Honmaru!
Do your best, Class 5-1!
It's getting too dangerous to watch, friends!
Keep your heads down, friends!
You might die otherwise!
Anything but this technique, Nezo!
You don't need to kill Honmaru!
Neyo.
Zakenja-san?
Are you kidding me?
Isn't Honmaru getting stronger and primed up
as he circulates that ki thing?!
Sure he is! No way he'll lose!
Is... Is this...
Before our eyes, here it appears
out of Zakenja's back... a devilish monstruosity!
Is he drawing the ki from Zakenja's evil heart?
Honmaru!
Please stop! You don't have to go that far!
This match really is too dangerous
to go on any further.
Stop it, you two!
There's no way you can withstand this blow!
Die, Honmaru!
Go straight to hell!
Demon Invocation:
Genuine Evil Blade Wave!
Mari-sensei!
Honmaru!
He got hit!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru-kun...
Look, everyone!
Honmaru?
What a strong attack to take on!
Yet Honmaru stands completely still!
Have nothin' to worry, Sensei!
Honmaru will get out of this without a scratch, you'll see!
I see!
He didn't try to oppose Zakenja's ki.
He's absorbing it in his body instead!
That's just like...
Kaze Kumagoro's... Fist of Cause and Effect!
Honmaru's heart was quick to embrace
the great value of Fist of Cause and Effect!
But it's no good, friend.
If Zakenja-sama's attack doesn't stop soon,
he won't be able to start a counter-attack!
When Honmaru accumulates enough of Zakenja's power,
he'll shoot it back all at once!
I wonder if Honmaru’s heart is strong enough for that?
What?
Ah! Is that...
Honmaru's face is becoming like that of Zakenja's!
Keep absorbing it.
Absorb it!
Absorb my hatred in full!
Of course. As the malice
in my pitch-black hatred stains your ki,
your own ki will overwhelm your heart
with my unbearable anger and sadness!
Zakenja's heart entered my heart!
People are quick to betray you.
Grown-ups are selfish.
Others are indifferent to you.
The only thing you can rely on is strength.
If you're strong, anything goes your way.
I don't want to be someone else's slave anymore.
I'll make others my slaves!
Taste it deep in your soul.
The agony of my 11-year-long life,
the sorrow of being betrayed by a grown-up!
Cruel!
Agonizing!
Exactly.
Now you too will live in anger and hatred.
Your soft and sweet heart,
nurtured by your warm and comfortable upbringing
is about to be dyed forever
with the red-hot anger of my heart!
Nezo.
This is the only time you've ever opened up your heart to another person.
You talk about how strong you are,
but you're just lonely all along.
It's so painful!
I hate everyone!
Why should I be the only one to suffer?
That's right, that's how it is!
Perfect!
Absorb that jealousy, those grudges, those grievances...
and fill your heart to the brim!
Curse others.
Let the heart of hatred burn hot in you!
Everyone...
I hate everyone!
I remember all of it,
all of you belittling me behind my back!
All you ever do is inflict even more pain upon me!
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru, it's a lie, right?
Ain't no way you really hate us all!
Don't you ever say things like that!
Honmaru!
Zakenja's conviction, and the intensity of his evil ki, are second to none!
Yes, that's blood-curdling.
Had my soul been hit directly with this woeful malice,
it would have been... I would have...
That's good, Honmaru!
Hate this world and all there is in it!
And then you'll follow my steps,
and go down the path of a demon!
Zakenja!
I'll kill you!
As for you, everyone! Get lost!
Honmaru... Friends... I believe!
Honmaru-kun.
I love you.
Honmaru, I know you're not that kind of guy.
Honmaru, I beg you!
I know this is within your power!
Come to your senses, Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Nonsense.
Honmaru must've absorbed
tons of ki of hatred that I released at him.
And still, the evil ki disappeared!
Nezo...
Your heart...
I understand it well.
However,
I will
defeat you.
Why are you willing to go that far?
Is this...
Honmaru regained his memory!
He even erased the evil ki from Zakenja's back!
Alright! Time for a counterattack!
Honmaru returned Nezo's soiled feelings back to clean!
Zakenja is sent flying outside the arena!
That must be Honmaru's win!
Class 5-1 of Nannosho Elementary wins!
Honmaru!
You did it!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru.
Zakenja.
You won, Honmaru!
Well fought, Honmaru!
That was a majestic match, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru.
With your own hands, you cleansed Nezo's soul.
Honmaru, thank you.
Honmaru!
Gramps! Fetch a doctor at once!
Honmaru-kun, hang on!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Honmaru, here's Power Upple Juice, try this!
Stay strong!
Everyone is around me...
I'm happy.
Is this what the path of fulfillment is all about?
The heck you're saying? You overcame so many trials already,
enough of this nonsense!
Route of fulfillment... What was it again?
Honmaru, drink juice now! Here.
Path of fulfillment.
Fulfillment...
Taru...
Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru!
What are you doing?
Wake up! Wake up, Honmaru!
Honmaru, don't die!
Honmaru!
Just you wait! Gramps will be here
on a helicopter with a doctor in no time!
I'll exhaust every option at Harako Conglomerate's disposal
to make sure that your sorry ass doesn't die in vain!
For now, we gotta at least try doing CPR!
Someone! Give him a mouth-to-mouth artificial respiration!
I'll do it!
Taru!
Aren't you a magician?!
If so, bring him back to life with your magic!
Me can't do that kind of magic!
Need to call Sister Ria!
I'm already here.
I'll breathe life into him.
With Ria here, he'll be fine!
Sister Ria - Great Great Great Magician!
Alright!
With that much "Great"-ness, she can't miss!
Hooray! He's saved!
This here is Breathing-Into-Liferog.
In emergencies, you can inhale this frog's breath,
then breath life into someone you want revived.
Quack, quack!
I appreciate the introduction.
Thanks a quack and stuff.
Big Sister, as beautiful and stunning as ever, quack!
Hurry up!
Nothing happened!
Apparently, even I am powerless here, quack.
I apologize!
Sorry.
Sister's magic powerless!
Honmaru died!
You can't be serious?!
Are you gonna give up just like that?
You can't be serious!
Isn't there anything we can do?!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru...
I got Ria to kiss me! Sorry, Iyona-chan.
Teacher, please let me take your place.
Then I'll do artificial respiration.
But I'm quite alive and well!
Hey, everyone!
I really am alive, can't you see?
Ah! Honmaru came back to life!
Hey, Taru! You seen that? I won!
Yay, Honmaru!
Taru?
Honmaru ethereal!
Oh, is that what it's all about ?
But it shouldn't be a problem for me
to return to my usual body, right?
Taruruto! The heck you're doing?!
Honmaru here!
Shh. Keep it quiet, Taru.
Nothing at all!
Honmaru just died!
Why are you romping about?
Sorry.
And I'm right here!
Do you really think I'm dead, everyone?
Annoying brats.
You still argue even at times like this.
What was that, Zakenja?
Honmaru died because of you!
Hey, Taru, follow me here!
Okay, Honmaru!
It's true that I caused his death.
However, you were the ones who watched him die.
If he surrendered, I wouldn't have gone this far.
What?!
Honmaru was happy.
What the hell?
Your life is remembered by how you die.
Wait for me!
Not only did Honmaru win the battle against me,
he even tried to save his enemy's heart.
He died as a true victor.
Except I'm alive!
He defeated me and died...
Nezo!
It's my fault for letting grade schoolers go this far.
I should have stopped them no matter what!
Forgive me, Honmaru-kun!
Ah... Don't blame yourself for that, teacher!
That's not like you at all!
You're not to blame for this.
You did attempt to stop the match.
I asked you to let them fight. It was me.
Forgive me, Honmaru.
I failed you as a father.
Dad...
I've been trying to build your character as a strong man...
But I forgot you were still a grade schooler!
I trained you harshly,
I made you go through hardships...
And the reward you got out of it...
was naught but this...!
Even dad is crying because of me!
Does that mean dad loves me, after all?
Honmaru!
You were my only true friend.
Huh?
My face is more mature than anyone else's around.
Despite my outstanding intellect,
my extraordinary reflexes, my athletic body...
As well as my enormous wealth...
I was still lonely.
No one there could understand how I felt.
There was no one to stand up to me!
But you were different,
Honmaru!
Only you!
Harako and Honmaru friends.
I bet Harako is the World Junior Dramatic Crying Champion too!
Honmaru, you dumbass!
How could you die in some petty brawl...
You had got to be a total cretin!
A blithering fool!
Ijigawa! I won't have you say whatever you want
just 'cause I died!
I'm here and can hear everything!
Why did you do this to me?!
I've only now realized
how madly in love I was with you!
Why did you do this to me?!
Honmaru,
why did you have to make me feel so bad?
Are you kidding me?
Oh? Even Neyo is crying.
Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan.
As for me...
It wasn't dad, it wasn't mom...
It wasn't anyone else...
The one I loved the most in this world...
was Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun.
I was selfish... I'm so sorry for all what I said.
But despite all that,
you were still so infinitely kind to me.
I...
I wish I had been more honest!
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan!
Oh no! I mustn't let Iyona-chan get that sorrowful!
I gotta return to my normal body soon!
Alright...
Iyona-chan, cry no more!
Huh? That's strange.
Okay, once more.
Alright!
Here!
Hey!
Huh?
I can't return...
Why can't I, Taru?
I wanna return into my body!
Ah! Honmaru! Thread on your head is broken!
Eh? Thread?
An invisible thread that connects
the physical body and the spirit.
And what happens when that thread breaks, Taru?
If it broke, you can't return.
Then you gotta return me into my body ASAP!
No way I can let Iyona-chan get any sadder, Taru!
Hurry up! Hurry the hell up!
Honmaru...
Taru! Come on, Taru!
Enough. Please.
You're really as dead as can be.
What's this?
Honmaru!
Don't suck me away!
I don't want to die!
Please help, Taru!
Honmaru!
It's over now.
Honmaru has departed for the other world.
Don't die, Honmaru!
I will never believe you're dead!
Shit... What's taking Gramps so long?!
Please! Open your eyes, Honmaru-kun!
Never!
I don't wanna part with Honmaru!
Honmaru! I'll totally bring you back!
Did I really die?
But it sure feels good up here.
Honmaru!
Don't go!
Taru?
Iyona is crying.
Everyone is crying!
I even asked my mama
to return Honmaru home!
Okay, just you wait for me, everyone.
I'll definitely make it back!
Yeah!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Magical World.
Honmaru, don't give up!
Episode 60
Magical World
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius