Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Summer vacation!
And where there's summer, there's the sea!
Our Class 5-1 went to a seaside school!
White sand beach on the blue ocean!
And ever the shining sun - everything is ours!
But if that wasn't cool enough as it is,
our gazes are glued to the one and only place -
Iyona-chan's swimsuit!
This high-leg is too revealing!
I'm getting dizzy!
Iyona-chan!
Meanwhile, Taru is busy pestering everyone!
He even infuriated Harako
alongside other boys and Oaya-sensei!
Well, let him!
As for myself, I was also riding high in surfing!
All sorts of stuff happened meanwhile,
and today is the final day.
Let's enjoy it to the fullest!
Right, Taru?
Yeah!
Episode 48
Exhausting Test of Courage
Now then, the long-distance swimming
you've been waiting for.
The course is simply around that island and back.
The distance is just some 2 km.
Do your best, everyone.
Okay!
Yeah!
Honmaru, do our best!
Taru...
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
No, nothing at all!
Teacher, what's long-distance-kun?
Long-distance swimming, you say?
It's when you swim on long stretches,
for distances you won't find in a pool.
Now, Taru-chan.
Why don't you go cheer on everyone?
Okay!
Witness!
The performance of the world record holder
in 1000 km long-distance swimming!
The unbridled might!
What swimming stroke did Harako use just now?
Can you even still call it a breaststroke?
What?! Honmaru!
What is he even thinking?
Hey, Honmaru!
If you suddenly start swimming crawl,
you'll wear yourself out halfway through!
Shut your trap!
Impressive vigor, Honmaru-kun!
He's just getting carried away by ecstasy,
'cos he only recently learned to swim!
Still... Up until last year, he couldn't swim at all, and now this.
I still think Honmaru-kun is amazing.
Dammit!
I'm nearly exhausted already!
Come to think of it,
Taru and Ria never taught me anything beyond crawling!
I should've learned some more
swimming styles on the occasion!
Since it came to this, I'll just keep swimming
to wherever my strength lasts me!
It's Harako!
Alright... I'll stick closely to him now,
and step off when we reach the island!
You damn turtles!
No one can get even close to matching my great speed.
What?!
Honmaru!
Is that all you got?
What? You're challenging me?
Did you really think that this is my true speed?
Seen this?
Not so fast, Harako!
Not bad, Honmaru!
But I ain't gonna lose either!
Not so fast I said!
No! Eat this, eat this, eat this!
Hey, stop already!
Never! Never!
Harako!
You two! Where are you going?!
This island is where you're supposed to turn back!
Do your best, Honmaru!
Okay!
What?
You can't be serious?
How come we swam so far away from it?
Honmaru heard what we said!
That's good.
I don't need to worry for Harako-kun,
no matter how far he swims.
Don't worry, don't worry!
Isn't it peaceful here?
Yeah, let's not rush.
Get this!
Everyone having fun.
I'll swim with Honmaru too!
Ah, Taru-chan!
Well, he received some of my training too,
so it's probably alright.
Honmaru!
Taru!
This is the end! My strength is gone...
Huh? Honmaru?
Ah? Honmaru, what did you say?
Want...
Can't understand Honmaru's words.
Taru! I'm suffocating! Please save me, fast!
What now, that's what this all is about?
Should've said sooner, Honmaru.
But it's Honmaru's own fault.
Not being able to swim, you pushed yourself so far.
Huh?
Disso-so-solve!
Oh?
Honmaru will be fine.
Me used a spell to turn into liquid.
Oh, that magic again?
This way, you can't drown.
Alright, we'll flow all the way to the shore this way!
When I become this serious,
be it #1 in America or in the world, I can take him on!
Oh! The sunset is calling out to me!
Let's go!
Now then, everyone.
Tonight, our trip to the seaside school ends.
On that occasion, so as to furnish it with a grand finale,
we'll hold a test of courage contest for pairs of boys and girls.
The course is as shown on this diagram.
Waseda-sensei will be waiting for you
on the viewing platform.
He'll affix a stamp on your palm.
You'll need to return with it.
Oaya-sensei,
Letting elementary school students out into the night,
moreover, wandering the seashore...
Well, aren't you finding it a little dangerous?
Don't worry, it'll be okay.
What kind of childhood
comes without these experiences?
Lottery
Now, we'll decide on pairs by drawing lots.
I so hope I get paired up with Iyona-chan!
Taru, Taru! Produce some item
that'd put me and Iyona-chan in the same pair!
Okay!
This - Drawpings-kun.
With it, Honmaru will win any lots drawing.
Counting on you, Drawpings-kun!
I'll do my best!
This Honmaru is wearing poop on his head again!
Damn, you're hopeless!
Shut up, you! This thing is bogus!
And now, the first pair...
Honmaru-kun and Kawai-san.
You're in luck, Honmaru-kun.
Thank you, Taru!
Iyona-chan!
With Honmaru-sama by your side,
you have nothing to be afraid of!
But Honmaru-kun, could you please
stop wearing this weird thing?
Let's do our best, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru! Stop pestering others with your filthy toys!
It's not one bit filthy!
Taru-Taru! I need you to ambush
me and Iyona-chan and scare her to death!
Are you sure, Honmaru?
I'm dead sure, buddy! Do it!
Okay!
It sure is dark around here at night.
Yes...
But you still have nothing to be afraid of,
as long as I'm by your side.
I'm so glad I can rely on you!
Iyona-chan who just finished bathing,
is oozing with the aroma of shampoo.
It's the best!
And soon, Taru will show up!
I'm a ghost!
He'll fly out at us, saying something like that.
Then, Iyona-chan...
No! I'm scared, Honmaru-kun!
And when she does, when Iyona-chan hugs me tight,
her soft and tender skin...
When this happens, I'll be like,
"Don't worry, Iyona-chan."
Completely unshaken, I'll tell her these kind words!
Don't worry, Iyona-chan. I'm with you.
Then Iyona-chan...
"Honmaru-kun, I'm glad to have you!"
And will become completely fascinated by me!
Honmaru-kun, I'm so glad to have you...
To which, I'll call quietly to Iyona-chan:
"Iyona-chan."
Honmaru-kun, I love you.
So do I.
That's what she'll say!
And then, finally...
Finally...
"Kiss!" I'll nail it!
Honmaru-kun is... weird.
Honmaru coming!
Incorpore-re-real!
I'll follow after them underground.
Maybe around here?
What's wrong, Iyona-chan?
Was it Taru?
Just now, over there...
Something like a severed head...
It's just your imagination.
Well done, Taru!
Honmaru-kun, please don't let go of my hand.
Sure thing!
I swear on my name that I'll protect you,
even at the cost of my life.
Thank you.
I wish I was as courageous as you.
Oh...
Well, let's keep going.
You'll be alright.
Okay...
So excited!
Excited!
See? Nothing here.
I never thought you were so prone to getting scared.
They're here!
Infattable Bulge-kun.
With this, can make hand go inflate.
Alright!
Come here...
She's squeezing me so tight!
So close... This is the best!
Honmaru-kun, I'm scared!
Still, as you'd expect from the athletic Iyona-chan,
she's got quite some strength in her.
She's squeezing me real tight!
This is like heaven...
Honmaru looks so happy!
Next is the skeleton attack!
S-s-s-skeleton!
Conjure!
Now I'll use it with Limpimpy.
Iyona would be even more scared!
Iyona!
No!
So fun!
I'll get ahead of Iyona and scare her even more!
That's where I'll ambush them.
Will draw a scary face on the road...
Scare!
Iyona, save me!
I'm getting eaten!
Save me please!
Taru-chan...
Caught by a land monster...
Disso-so-solve!
Iyona, I'm melting...
Did it!
Iyona passed out!
Honmaru! Honmaru! Honmaru, open your eyes!
How about this? I scared Iyona like never before!
Praise me! Praise me, Honmaru.
Teacher...
Harako-kun?
I also wanted to take part in the courage test...
Were you... still...
I'm the World Junior Courage Test Champion...
How could you start it without me?!
Great! That is admirable grit.
I will become your partner in the courage test myself.
Huh?
Thank you for staying with me all this time, Honmaru-kun.
Even though I lost track
of what was going on at some point.
No...
Iyona-chan was scared beyond imaginable!
Honmaru.
Was this enough or not, after all?
Honmaru, I wanna swim more!
But you've just got out of the pool!
Okay, let's swim in the river!
Don't say nonsense! You'll fall ill in no time,
swimming in water that dirty.
Ah? And what's that?!
Isn't that a kappa?
Yay! A lost child kappa!
Let's bring this fella home!
Episode 49
Down the River with Kappa
Alright, Fish-All-Around departs!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Down the River with Kappa.
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius