Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru, whatcha doing?
My homework for home economics.
I have to finish this apron by tomorrow!
Sounds fun! So-unds fun, right?
What's fun about it, you...
Fun, you say?
Episode 77
Calling on Hardworking Pixiervants!
Everyone—you've finished it, haven't you?
Those who didn't bring it today
can still bring their homework tomorrow.
Why, you...
Ah, no...
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
No, well... Here, see? Mine's not even half-done yet.
It's the same for everyone, right?
There's no way we could finish it
earlier than tomorrow anyway. Right, Jabao?
Huh? I've finished mine already.
"Jaba!" There.
No way!
Harako, you?
I'm the World Junior Sewing Contest winner, after all.
Korekiyo, you?
Sewing an apron is like taking a candy from a baby.
I had so much more time to spare,
I even made potholders!
Amazing!
The amazing one here is Iyona-chan.
She also made a pillow, a stuffed toy, a pajama, and a dress!
I really think it's nothing special.
What even is this apron, Honmaru?
You say it's half-done,
but really, it's as though you haven't even started yet!
No way!
Really!
Give it back!
Hey! Jabao!
Get back here! Give it back! Dammit!
What is he even thinking?
There really is no helping Honmaru's clumsiness.
That's what happened, Taru.
In the whole class,
I was the only one who couldn't do it.
Everyone but me
handed this homework in already!
You're not being very attentive
to my true stories of woe!
Sorry, Honmaru. I've just...
Go to sleep already, Taru-kun!
Okay!
I'm going to bed, Honmaru.
Yeah, good night.
I'll sleep, but you do your best.
Sure.
Trunsform.
Goodnight, Honmaru.
Good night...
It's not coming out at all...
What should I do?
Mom!
Please help me!
Hey, mom! Mom, please help! I'm begging you!
Mom, I can't do this...
Imbecile! Do your goddamn homework yourself!
I can't...
Honey, don't even think about helping.
Darling...
Dad...
How can you...
How can you be that cruel?!
Man, I'm sleepy.
Ah! I sewed it in the wrong spot again.
Back to square one...
Gotta... redo...
Sleepy...
Gotta do it somehow...
Ah... If I don't finish it until tomorrow...
Ria!
Should I help you just today?
Counting on you, Pixiervants.
If I don't finish the apron...
Tomorrow at school...
Gotta do it!
Let's go!
Let's go, gotta do it!
Before tomorrow morning, let's finish it!
Let's finish it!
Before tomorrow morning!
Gotta do it, gotta do it!
Ah! I fell asleep!
And it's 7:30! I'm screwed!
I don't have the apron ready!
What do I do? What do I do? What do I do? What...
Huh?
What?
Ah! The apron is finished!
Honmaru, good morning!
Now, let's go pee, brush our teeth, and eat our meal...
Taru, it was you? Taru...
Thanks so much! Thank you!
You finished the apron while I was sleeping!
With this... With this, I'll be fine!
Apron? Me not know.
Eh? Then, who did it?
Oh, Honmaru!
What's that?
This - Pixiervants house.
Pixiervants?
Sister Ria's smell on it!
I see! It was Ria, then?
Thank you, Sister Ria!
Honmaru, these Pixiervants are mighty useful!
But how did a house produce an apron?
Wrong, wrong! You wear it on head while sleeping.
Hey, Taru?
Wake up, go pee!
Brush my teeth!
Eat my meal!
Our meal...
Go pee!
Brush your teeth! Brush-brush your teeth!
Eat your meal!
Eh! Yummy, yummy!
Finished.
Finished!
Finished...
Taru!
So, Honmaru? You've seen these four
from the house do my work for me, right?
Yeah!
These guys are very responsible
and always bring the work to completion!
Impressive, Taru!
But remember, Honmaru.
Pixiervants only work while you sleep.
I see. In order to get the job done,
I have to spend that time sleeping.
But it's alright. I have Cloudrowsy.
You tear this up and rub it into your head
to fall asleep amazingly anytime.
Thank you, Taru!
Great!
Did everyone submit
their homework for home economics today?
Yes!
Okay, nicely done.
Well then, today's homework is a set of math problems.
Let's see. The range of problems are from page 65
through page 134. I hope it's not too much for you.
Is it even possible to do that much?
This amount exceeds even the scope
of the World Junior Math Contest.
Surely, it's not too much for you, friends.
Huh?
What?!
Oh? Honmaru-kun, that's unusual for you.
It's due tomorrow, are you sure?
I am. You can do that much
if you try really hard. Right, Jabao?
What are you saying?
Honmaru carried away.
Then, let's make it page 65 through 134.
A cakewalk!
Honmaru! We didn't get a cut on
the homework because of your nonsense!
Jabao, don't you need to hurry home
to be able to do that homework in time?
Homework in time?
We're going home, Ryoguchiya!
Ah! Jaba-san, wait!
Honmaru, Taru-chan!
Why are you two still up? It's time to go to bed!
Okay!
But I'm still not one bit sleepy.
I can't get the Pixiervants to do their job this way.
Honmaru, wanna use Cloudrowsy?
Yes. Let's do that, Taru.
Okay!
Then, I'm counting on you, dear Pixiervants.
Please do a set of math problems!
Math homework!
Gotta do it.
Gotta do it!
Math homework.
Gotta do it! Do it!
First question, hm-hm.
First question, hm-hm!
First question, hm.
First question, hm-hm...
317 minus...
Oh! We guys...
Are hopeless...
At math!
Who'd have thought?
Honmaru-kun, did you do your math homework?
Yes.
Super! Ah, you see, I forgot mine at home,
so could you show me yours?
Sure, here you go.
Oh? Wouldn't that make
for an interesting pattern reverse?
It's a matter of grave concern!
Honmaru-sama, Honmaru-sama!
Please let us see it too!
You guys sure are hopeless...
Well, they say we gotta help each over
at times of need. Very well.
Right, thank you very much!
Thank you, thank you!
Thank God. And Honmaru-sama!
Impressive! Every single one is correct!
Honmaru-kun, if you put your mind to it,
you can really do anything.
I suppose.
As a thank you, I think I should let Honmaru-kun
do anything he wants with me.
Oh, anything?
Yes...
Then, how about a... A kiss, huh?
Oh, what's gotten into me?
I don't mind.
Really?
It's morning already?
I'm still sleepy, Honmaru.
Ah, I wish I could sleep for a little longer.
Well then, I wonder if my homework is done.
Ah! Shoot!
What?
He's awake!
We're not done yet!
Deploy Cloudrowsy, quick!
Okay!
Alright! Let's not waste any time.
Yeah!
Iyona-chan, how long
have I been waiting for this moment...
I love you, Honmaru-kun.
Huh?
Honmaru, Taru-chan, it's morning!
You need to wake up, you two.
You'll be late for school. Huh?
Ah! Shoot! She's waking him up!
My, how cute! Are you friends of Taru-chan?
Cloudrowsy, quick!
Okay!
It's in our policy...
To use whatever means necessary...
To bring the work to the completion...
And not any other way!
Yeah!
We should be safe all the way out here,
Iyona-san.
Honmaru-san.
Die!
Where the hell is my breakf—
Taru-sama, good morning!
Let's play together!
Hey, Taruruuto! Flirting with Mimora-chan again, don't...
Did it!
Finished, finished!
We did it!
It's over!
Oh! They did it!
Well done, Pixiervants!
Huh?
Hey, what's with everyone sleeping here, of all places?
Shoot, it's 10 already!
Ah! I'm late, late, late...
Honmaru-kun, you're late.
Yes. I know I came to school late...
But look at this, Teacher!
I've done all of my math homework!
Isn't it amazing?
Why are you telling me
about your math homework now?!
You skipped school for a week straight!
And now you show up
to tell me about your homework?!
A week?!
Get your act together!
It hurts. It hurts, teacher!
I'm sorry! Forgive me!
Pixiervants are amazing! They worked on one set of math problems for a week straight!
I shouldn't have helped back then.
But perhaps, it'll at least teach you
not to rely on others.
Good luck, Honmaru.
Unforgivable! Jabao's continuous outrageous behavior...
It falls upon me to punish him!
Huh? Did he become a good guy all of a sudden?
Yeah! Jabao became a good guy
after eating the Good-Hearted Windowl.
Ah! Jabao is suddenly becoming popular!
Taru, give it to me too!
Honmaru, you mistook! That's Devil-Bowl!
Episode 78
Good Guy Jabao!?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Honmaru scary!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius