Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
At last, Honmaru was allowed to come back to life
by the Goddess herself.
However, in compliance with the laws of the Magic Realm,
all memories of Taruruuto were erased from everyone's mind.
Episode 63
Overcrowded with Magicians
I'm off!
Yahoo! What a pleasant morning!
It's great to be alive after all.
Did I really die and meet God, though?
It all feels like a dream now.
One's mission in life?
I wonder what that was about.
My goal in life is...
I know! My goal in life is
to marry Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan was the one most bereaved by my death, after all.
More than anything in the world,
I loved Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun, can you come out already?
Don't you worry about that, Iyona-chan.
Look, I'm this healthy!
I'm so glad...
Iyona-chan, no matter what happens,
I won't leave you alone ever again.
Honmaru-kun.
Right, like that!
That'd be perfect!
Right, Ta—
What's wrong with me?
Talking to someone when no one is around. Like a doofus!
To school, to school!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Hey!
Good morning, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan. Good morning.
Are you able to go out to school already?
Don't you worry about that!
Look, I'm this healthy!
I see. I really am glad.
Alright, the mood is perfect!
Iyona-chan, no matter what happens,
I'll never leave you alone again.
Balloon! Balloon!
Balloon!
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru-kun?
No... That boy.
Cute, isn't he?
Don't you have a feeling like there had once been a boy
like that between you and me as well?
Yes.
We're not even married yet!
Let alone having kids!
For starters, we two are still elementary school students!
You're awful, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
Why are you blushing so much?
I don't know!
Why did I said "Yes" when he asked, then?
Look at this!
What's all that flirting so early in the morning, you two?
You can't get your eyes off them at no time of the day!
I guess one can't be made un-perverted
even through death, Honmaru!
Honmaru,
I won't let you get away
with doing unseemly things to Iyona-san!
Talking big again!
But back when I died, who was on the verge of crying
over this and that, huh?
What?! Alright!
The next time, I'll make sure
you'll be on the verge of crying yourself!
That's interesting! We'll see which one cries first!
Alright, let's start, Ta—
Oh? I'm calling out to someone again.
Be careful. Honmaru is planning to cheat again.
Yeah.
Harako, what did you mean by cheating?
Why did I blurt it out that he needs to be careful
when Honmaru is alone?
It feels kinda off, after all.
My balloon!
There!
Ah! No good!
Leave it to me!
Ah-hop! Almost!
Just a little more!
No problem at all!
Alright, now it's my turn!
You should leave it to me, the World Junior
Balloons-Stuck-in-Trees Jumping Contest Winner!
What a nonsense.
Who cares for just a balloon or two?
My balloon flew away!
Shut it please!
A cheap balloon is not worth all this crying!
You selfish brat!
Harako is bullying children now!
Compensating for not being able to catch it himself!
Have you ever considered what'll happen
if Harako Tsutomu gets serious?
Behold!
The World Telephone Pole Climbing Contest
Special Jury Award winner's great deed!
How about this?
Watch out!
Here.
Amazing! Big bro, you were like a magician!
Honmaru is damn amazing!
Was he trained with magic or something?
Really. It was like magic.
Magician?
Magic...
Just for today, in consideration for that innocent child,
I'll let it slide. Be grateful, Honmaru.
You were the one who needed saving!
Harako's bravado is like a train that can't stop, I imagine!
Even though he's usually a weakling and a horndog,
in times of need, Honmaru has
some amazing side to him, just like before.
That's right. Everyone is the same as before.
But something's still off.
I also have a feeling like something is missing.
Yes. Definitely, something essential is missing.
Thinking about it, I used to be contented...
Path of contentedness.
Contentedness, route of sufficiency...
Hey!
Taruruuto!
Taruruuto?
Taru?
Ruuto?
The magician...
Taruruuto!
That's right! Taru-chan!
I see! It's Taruruuto!
How could we have forgotten?
Good day to everu-ru-ryone!
Taru... In order to save me,
he went back to the Magic Realm
and can't come here again!
Then, we won't get to see Taru-chan ever again?
Alright, you've got me interested enough
to lend a helping hand.
So, where can I find that place, that Magic Realm?
I can even use the power of Harako Conglomerate
to bring everyone along.
Afterlife...
The world where dead people go.
A bridge too far for me...
Will we really never be able to see Taru again, Honmaru?
You're his bosom buddy, ain't you?
You still okay with it?
I never said I was! Still...
Still, what can I even do, Taru?
Hey, Honmaru-kun, how did Taru-chan
come to this world in the first place?
That's right!
With the Great Magic Encyclopedia at our house,
I should be able to summon Taruruuto again!
Exactly! The first time, I said the spell
for summoning Taru completely by chance!
Alright... Wait just a minute, Taru!
Honmaru-kun, can I come too?
Yeah! Me too!
Sure!
Alright. I'm coming as well!
Never doubted you, Jabao-san!
Sounds interesting.
When it comes to summoning magicians,
you can't do without me, the president
of the World Junior Seven Wonders Study Group.
Honmaru, hurry up and summon Taru already!
What are you waiting for?
Don't waste our time and get it over with!
Be quiet, you! We'll be in trouble if my dad wakes up.
Alright, let's do it!
Exercise caution here!
Haste makes waste is what they say.
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
I forgot the spell for summoning him.
So...
What in the world was that spell?
Recall it soon!
Tarururuu or something like that?
You'd better recall it!
Well, maybe "Come before me, Taruruu..."
No, that doesn't sound right either.
Enough waffling around!
Just say whatever comes to your mind, you dumbass!
Elohim Essaim...
And please show yourself, abracadabra...
Ah, no! Not that either!
You can do it, Honmaru-kun.
Excuse me!
Is anyone home?
Everyone skipped class and gathered at Honmaru-kun's house.
I wonder what in the world is happening.
I can't recall it!
Get yourself together, Honmaru!
Asking for a beating?
I can hear the children's voices.
They're definitely here.
Alright.
EXCUSE ME!
Gaaawr!
You did it, Honmaru!
No! This is not a spell for summoning Taruruuto.
Oh crap! Looks like we summoned
something terrible instead.
It went outside!
Behold myself - the Great Magician Rival-sama!
You summoned me with your "Excuse Gaaawr" spell!
Huh?
It flew outside and disappeared.
What should we do, Honmaru?
For real, man!
Gwaaah!
Something else is about to come out!
Our house...
I am the Great Magician Mimora-chan.
You called me with your "For real, man Gwaaah!" spell, dear.
I did?
Yes, dear.
But we couldn't summon Taru!
And the house is lying in ruins now!
It's your own fault, idiot.
Cretin!
I'm really screwed!
Ngaaah!
Taruruuto!
Taru!
Behold myself - the Great Magician Taruruuto-sama.
Taru! We finally got you back!
Huh? Why is it that Honmaru remembers me?
How could I ever forget about you?
Been a while! Doing alright?
Here we meet again.
Taru-chan! I'm so glad.
Strange.
I went back to the Magic Realm
with the "Good day, nice to meet you-yu-yu" spell.
And when you return with that spell,
everyone here forgets all about magicians.
At one point, we forgot.
But we worked hard to remember you again!
I'm a bungler, sloppy at chanting spells.
It's not like that.
And your magic is not one bit sloppy.
I could never forget it!
Taru and I are friends!
Friends...
Honmaru...
Taru...
Please refrain from creating improper sentiment
between fellow men, thank you!
Mimora...
Oh my! So sorry, Taru-sama.
Taru-sama, can you believe that I too
have been summoned into this world?
To be summoned together.
What, oh what a most wonderful coincidence!
After all, Taru-sama and I are connected by the thread of fate!
It's so, definitely so!
Whoop!
There, see?
And... cut!
Rival!
I'm the only one connected to Mimora-chan
by the thread of fate!
Ray!
Accept my love.
Rival...
Why do you just keep standing in the way?
Mimora-chan...
I'm starting to hate Rival real-real bad!
How did it come to this?!
Taru... All of this is your fault!
Mimora-chan! Do something about Rival!
Why should I ever listen to what you say?
A Magician only grants one wish
to the person who summoned him.
Who?! Who was it that summoned Mimora-chan?
This maiden.
Seems like it's me!
Ijigawa! Hurry up and tell
Mimora-chan to stop Rival!
Nah.
You mean you don't care about what happens to everyone?!
If magic could make my one wish come true,
I'd rather ask for something else.
Ijigawa...
Damn you!
In this case, I'll do what is needed to stop Rival myself!
Honmaru, me help too!
It's no use.
Hey, who the blazes was that?
The person who summoned Rival?
Please stop Rival soon!
Stop it!
Your wish is that I stop?
That's one uninspired wish you got!
The teacher was the one who summoned Rival?
That's right. My wish is that you quit
that selfish and destructive way of life.
Let's make it that.
You want me to quit that selfish and destructive way of life?
What should I do?
I don't really understand...
Looks like you won't be able to quit that easily.
Fine.
That's great! She's uncertain about her wish! And if the wisher
can't make up their mind, I don't have to make it true!
Starting today, you're living with me.
What?
You don't mind me living at your home?
For you, it's not "you," but "Teacher!"
I'll take it on myself
to rebuild your character from scratch!
Is that clear?
Yes.
I can't hear you! Once more, with feeling!
Yes, Teacher!
Good.
As expected of our Teach.
Maybe this will knock Rival down a peg or two.
Yeah!
What would be your wish?
I'd like you to tell me sooner!
Let's see...
I know, Mimora-chan.
Until I come up with a wish,
I'll have you staying at my house.
With three meals a day and an afternoon nap, as well as
unlimited video games, you can just sit back and relax.
Is that true, dear? Thank you so much!
No-no, you're welcome.
I made you go to all the trouble of coming to here...
Ijigawa can actually be a mighty nice fella.
Mimora also honest, good maiden.
You can think of me as your older sister
and ask me for whatever you'd like.
This way, I'll also have a magician
freeloading at our house.
I'll be sure to make a good use of her.
I'm so glad you're that nice of a person!
By staying with this woman,
I would avail myself to being close to Taru-sama.
Honmaru! Honmaru, you speak your wish with me too.
Speak it, speak!
You too?
I've decided on my wish long ago, Taru.
It's for you to stay forever...
Taru got separated with his mama to come here.
If I wish for him to stay by my side,
that'll mean separating him from mama forever.
No, forget it.
Honmaru?
Alright, Taru!
Here's my wish:
Please come around to play together whenever you'd like.
Honmaru...
Honmaru!
Me... Me really wanna stay with Honmaru forever.
It's the same for me, Taru.
Honmaru, love more than mama!
You idiot, that's impossible!
But we'll be forever and ever together, starting now, Taru.
Honmaru!
I'm so happy for you,
Taru-chan, Honmaru-kun.
Peaceful days are finally here!
From now on, I will live and play with Taru every day....
All while continuing to make advances on Iyona-chan!
Oh? That's strange.
My body's moving on its own...
Ah! Ah! My hands are reaching out
to Iyona-chan's chest...
Not that I don't enjoy it, but what the hell?
Is this Ijigawa's doing?
Honmaru!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Combination! Ijigawa, Mimora.
Episode 64
Combination! Ijigawa, Mimora
Honmaru, you're so intrusive. Let me say something too!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius