Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 44
Please, Lightning-sama
Iyona-chan!
Iyona!
Honmaru-kun, good morning.
Howdy!
Hey-hey-hey, have you seen it?
What?
The new episode at 8:30 am yesterday!
"Are you serious?! Uraruuto-kun!"
Of course we did!
I'm telling you, this show's the best!
Especially that guy Korechiyo!
What are you saying?
Badjao is decisively the coolest one in it!
Ain't it?
What is this pleasant conversation about?
A TV anime that aired yesterday.
Are you serious?! Uraruuto-kun!
It sure is funny!
Just some cartoons, of all things?
How immature!
Oh, but it's a really interesting one.
And Ura-chan is an angel!
Ah! And get this:
the girl with slant eyes and the bob cut is very cute!
Harako watch it too!
Don't spew nonsense.
You'll grow stupid from only consuming cartoons.
In our house, we watch nothing but educational programs.
Did you know that...
Don't you think she really is a good girl?
I see. You've chosen to ignore me?
Honmaru, you ass!
When someone tells you something,
you listen till the very end!
Just some stupid cartoons!
Eh?! Think you're so smart you'd use it
to captivate the young gals' attention?!
Seriously?! Uraruuto, huh?
Is there anything more silly?
If it came to this, I'll leverage the Harako Conglomerate's influence to cut off the power supply to your house!
You're just not good at it, Taru.
Lemme show you.
A power outage?
Did you learn your lesson, Edojo Honmaru?
Harako!
The power supply to your place was cut.
Why's that?!
To prevent you from watching TV!
No way! You're out of your mind!
If you want your electricity back, apologize to me.
How come I have to apologize to you?
I guess you could do just fine without that TV game?
What?
Get lost!
Ain't nobody here gonna apologize to you!
Make sure you don't regret this!
What?
Because you quarreled with Harako, he cut off our power?
Honmaru.
We'll never cave in.
People can live just fine even if one or two lights go out.
Honey.
We're living without electricity now.
Okay.
Yay, looks fun!
I thought so too!
With or without electricity, we can live on.
Thanks, dad, mom.
Watch closely.
I ain't caving in to Harako!
It's so dark...
I can't even sharpen a pencil!
Plus...
This dead silence is disconcerting!
Life ain't easy without electricity!
I startled Honmaru!
Taru! When our life gets that hard,
you don't make it even harder!
Honmaru, Taru-chan, dinner is ready!
Let's go.
Yeah!
Thanks for the meal!
Delicious!
Delicious...
I cooked it in the open stove.
But because I'm not used to it,
I was worried about whether or not it'd come out good.
This is miles above the electric rice-cooker, mom!
Really?
Glad to know.
Fine!
Let's remodel the house and our ways of living!
We won't even have to buy coal.
Yeah! Life is more fun without electricity!
We're off!
We're going to school!
Because the electricity is gone,
we'll go to bed and get up early every day!
I'll never be late!
Honmaru, it's great!
Taru!
You moron! It was really cold! Hey!
Take this!
Sparkly.
Pretty.
I never had any idea! Without electricity,
you can see the stars so beautifully!
Yeah.
By getting swept away by the convenience of everyday life,
perhaps we lose sight of something important?
I hope the sky is clear tomorrow too.
Mama, you like clear sky?
Well, it's Tanabata tomorrow, after all.
Tanabata?
What we call Tanabata is when...
Two stars of two lovers named Hikoboshi and Orihime
can finally meet once a year.
So it's a very happy day.
Happy day.
We can't watch tomorrow's episode of Uraruuto-kun!
Honmaru-kun.
Have you seen it?
"Are you Serious?! Uraruuto-kun."
No, uh, well, about that...
You haven't seen it?
What, really? Lame!
Jabao-kun!
Hey-hey!
But...
Hey! Have you seen it, Jabao?
"Are you Serious?! Uraruuto-kun!"
Of course I did!
He was saying "stop it!"
Power... Power!
I want our power back!
I can't watch TV without electricity!
Wanna see Uraruuto-kun! Urara!
Honmaru, you caved in already?
At this rate, I'm gonna have to apologize to Harako!
You're pathetic...
Because if I can't see "Seriously?! Uraruuto-kun"
tomorrow, I'll fall out of all the class's circles!
Honmaru!
I don't remember raising you to be so gutless!
It hurts...
Ah! It hurts, but I still wanna watch Uraruuto-kun!
Hey, Taru!
I wanna watch too.
Taru, can't Goro the Thundercloud
generate electricity for us?
Yeah! Honmaru smart!
Goro the Thundercloud!
Yes? Goro the Thundercloud is here!
Thundercloud Goro, can you power our TV?
Trust me with this!
It's powered!
Thundercloud Goro!
This is...
The best I can do.
But it was finally just getting interesting...
TV, TV, TV!
Uraruuto-kun!
There's a way, I think.
Are you sure?
With power from Lightning-sama,
you can power anything, even your TV!
That's it! We should ask Lightning-sama!
Ah, but remember - Lightning-sama
can be terrifying if you anger her.
Taru, let's go find Lightning-sama!
No! Um... Don't go!
Yeah!
Taru, let's go!
The flight to Lightning-sama's place is departing now!
Yeah!
Oh, what enormous clouds!
Enormous, enormous!
That's where Lightning-sama lives.
Huh? It wiggles, wiggles, wiggles, Honmaru!
Eh?
You're right! It wiggles!
Wiggle-wiggle!
Is this hot big sister - Lightning-sama?
And that device in the back
is Lightning-kun, who generates electricity.
Then, how about we try to wake her up for a moment?
Be quiet!
Waking her up from her slumber
is a surefire way to reap her wraith!
Then, what do you suggest we do? Look!
If we don't hurry, the night will end
and Uraruuto-kun will start!
Honmaru, this is actually very fun!
He's got the Lightning-kun!
Well done, Taru! With those, we can finally watch TV!
Let's skedaddle, Taru!
Wait!
You again?
Eh?! She's catching up!
Hey you! Give back Lightning-kun!
Ah, no-no, this is dangerous!
Lightning-sama is livid now!
Didn't I tell you to wait, cheeky kid?
Honmaru!
Taru! Whatever it takes, you must escape!
As long as we have Lightning-kun, we can watch TV!
Taru, are you alright?
Yeah!
The cloud over there! Why won't you stop?!
Honmaru, you okay?
How can I be...
Goro, there's another one coming!
Taru, stop!
I can do lightning attack too!
Looks good, Taru!
What's going on?
There...
A lightning strike?
Atomic Jump!
Stop!
Ah! What should we do?
That's why I said you wouldn't wanna anger her!
This is way beyond "angry!"
My Lightning-kun...
Give him back!
Ah! We're done!
Honmaru, I'm done too!
Wait!
Ah, now that's a complete and utter "over" for us!
Now there are two Lightning-samas instead of one!
You should assume a brighter perspective sometimes!
Hey, what exactly is this strange atmosphere?
What? What?
That man is Lightning-sama's lover.
A long time ago, the two were lovers.
However...
Over just a minor squabble,
the two had decided they needed to live separately.
And due to their stubbornness,
neither of them could apologize to another.
That's what my grandpa told me.
They've got it pretty complicated between them.
Oh? Where's Taru?
Ah! Over there!
Quarreling is bad!
Go say sorry now!
Huru-ru-rry up!
In a quarrel, both are at fault! It won't do.
Well...
I'm... sorry...
No, I should be the one saying sorry.
We're sorry.
It's alright, since you returned it.
Moreover, I should probably rather be saying thank you.
We owe you one. Thank you.
Oh, no need!
It's not thanks to us.
This must be the magic of Tanabata.
The magic of Tanabata?
Yeah!
Tanabata - the day when lovers are happy.
That's what Honmaru's mama said.
The Magic of Tanabata, then?
Here, a present from me.
Would you kindly accept it?
We're the Crackling-kun!
Let's be friends!
Sure!
Okay, we're going in now!
1, 2...
Amazing, Crackling-kun!
You did it!
Lightning-sama, thank you.
"I say, don't hold no grudge against me!"
That's what I thought! Such an interesting episode!
Then, on the next Sunday
Seriously?
Seriously?!
Looks interesting.
Atomic Powerson? That's one hell of a guy!
Have you seen? Have you heard?
The adjacent class had a transfer student!
I love this unbelievable guy!
He looks fun!
Hey Taru, what are you saying?
He's been learning a 3,000-years-old kenpo in China!
But my magic will beat him!
Taru was outdone!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
New Rival Appears!
Eh? You can't be serious!
Episode 45
New Rival Appears!
I ain't kidding you!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius