Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 20
Skimaru of the Silver-white Slope!
Ski trip scheduled on January 18th through 22nd
Departing from the schoolyard at 8:30!
That's it, everyone.
Tomorrow, our long-awaited ski trip starts!
Hooray!
If you don't know how to ski,
I'll teach the ever-living soul out of you!
I'm screwed!
That day, when I tried to ski for the first time...
I'm scared...
Honmaru! You ain't no little baby!
It's unbearable. Children these days
are so fragile and spoiled.
Worst day of my life...
Oh no, no... Going skiing
is the last thing I'd do willingly.
Say, Honmaru-kun.
Aren't you excited for the skiing trip?
You weasel, what is it you're plotting this time?
You must be good at skiing.
Hey, how about teaching her?
Come on, aren't you qualified enough?
Iyona-chan...
Somehow, you got me with this one!
My incredible skii-lls
earned me the nickname of Edojo Skimaru!
Your hand...
Iyona-chan!
Hey, hey, did you know?
We're acquainted to Edojo Skimaru himself!
I've been trying to get into it for some time,
but my progress is less than impressive.
Honmaru-kun, I hope
you let me learn some from you.
Edojo Skimaru-kun?
I have also been educated in Swiss Alps
of Saint Moritz ever since I was just three years old.
And yet, even I was never admitted to such a title.
I'm sure you'll teach us all plenty.
Yeah...
This pesky guy!
Counting on you then, buddy!
Pure solidarity of men!
Turns out, even Honmaru
has some good sides to him.
Alright, let's have a fruitful trip,
supporting each other where possible!
This good fella Edojo Skimaru...
will be sure to look after you!
I'm gonna have to ask for a big one, Taruruuto.
Taruruuto! Taruruuto!
Spare me...
An artificial ski resort, then?
We can start special training now.
Yeah! I make Honmaru small.
Trunsform!
Just don't forget I'm fragile!
All right.
We get to the mountain top first.
Honmaru, can start skiing from here.
From the very top already?
Honmaru, Limpy-kun will aid special training.
Honmaru Jump!
Honmaru Grande Spin!
Honmaru, doing great!
Taru!
Sorry, Honmaru.
I don't know how to ski well.
Laden with bentos, our stooped backs,
Out we go, merrily, to have a picnic
Road of 500 miles begins with a step
So if we keep walking, we'll get anywhere
We're barely out of the tunnel,
but in the Land of Snow already!
I can even see the ski resort from here!
Quite a sight, isn't it?
Now, everyone, we're almost at the ski resort.
Make sure you don't forget your things.
Okay!
The scenery is heaven-like here, Iyona-san.
Skiing is so much against my nature!
Even dying in a car crash
seems actually preferable to this!
Me bored.
How'd you manage to get hurt here?
It hurts! I swear, gimme a break at least here...
Ah, this brings back memories.
The pristine-white snow of Alps...
Are you okay, Honmaru-kun?
I'm cool, cool.
The vast silver-white slopes of Matterhorn.
I know, Iyona-san!
Next time, we should go toge—
We would go ski together, right, Honmaru-kun?
Sure.
You promised to teach me plenty.
You can leave that to me!
I was dubbed Edojo Skimaru for a reason!
Looks like I'm relying heavily on magic today...
Please cover me, Taru!
Oh? Huh? Not here?
Why... Hey! Hey, where's Taruruuto?
Don't know.
But what's the meaning of this?
What's going on? Driver?!
Here! No worries, I'm covering for driver.
This very fun!
How did you even get here?!
I can't allow this!
Oh? Teacher wants to drive, too?
Slowly bring it to a stop, Taru-kun.
Teacher, be reasonable.
Dangerous
Curve
We'll crash now...
OH MY GOD!
Why me?!
Oh no, oh no!
I can't die while I'm still so young!
But I haven't even finished my lunch...
Out of the way, you all have to save me!
I am the only heir to the Harako Conglomerate!
Calm down, everyone!
Calm down now!
You're the one who needs to calm down!
Stop it! This is not the time for fighting!
Get along while you can!
So I'll really end up dying in a car crash!
In that case...
In that case, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun...
Happy at last...
Taruru!
Yahoo!
Like this!
A clean landing, like in the good old days!
What do you think?
I used to be pretty good at skiing.
I cast a Time-Freezing Spell to bring bus to life!
Oooh! A bus!
Make way!
This one is now
the ski bus lane!
So many snacks yet to try!
I don't wanna die!
Let me run the hell away!
Calm down! Calm down!
Iyona-chan's scent...
Honmaru-kun...
Making a shortcut straight to the hotel!
Any idea how in the hell we ended up here?
Beats me...
Honmaru-kun, thank you.
You did your best to protect me!
No...
Well, that was fun!
My safety should be your concern,
even over your own safety!
Calm down! Calm down! Calm down!
But you're the one who's least calm here!
What do you mean? I am calm!
And the weather is fine, too!
Just what we need for an ideal day of skiing!
Alright, Taruruuto.
I'm counting on you! Exhaust your magic,
but make a convincing Edojo Skimaru out of me!
Sure, I can do it!
Skimaru-sensei.
Looking forward to your teaching today.
Sure! I'll make sure not to disappoint you!
A snow! Snow!
Honmaru Skimaru-sama is here!
What sort of skiing do you specialize in?
They say Honmaru-kun was the interschool champion
when he was still in kindergarten!
This is bad! The rumors are exaggerating it
to impossible levels!
Impressive, Honmaru!
You keep rising in my eyes!
Honmaru-kun, while we ski together,
let me catch up with you once in a while, will you?
So cool...
Just trust me with this, people!
Prepare to witness this technique
of Edojo Skimaru-sama.
I've been secretly developing it since I was three,
and today I'm letting you take a sneak peek at...
Sneak Peek~
Taru! Aren't those your H-Filtering ones?
My bad! I mistook Honmaru's goggles for my own!
No, I mean, well...
I'm not complaining.
Okay, everyone!
Today, the beginners are handled
by Waseda-sensei,
amateurs - by Yamagata-sensei.
And I myself will look after the advanced skiers.
Dear advanced skiers,
we ain't slacking off here!
Yeah!
I'm done...
Right, beginners gather right here!
Honmaru-kun!
What are you up to?
Honmaru-kun, aren't you an advanced skier?
Honmaru-kun, I can't wait!
I just remembered, no matter how advanced you are,
you should first do a basic warm-up!
What are you talking about?
Not the time to crack jokes.
Beginners and amateurs should never ride this lift!
Even Stenmark had a heart attack from it!
Danger!
Deadly for beginners!
Don't let me down, Taruruuto...
Right, more enthusiasm in the hips!
Okay!
Eh?! Taruruuto!
Why are you there?!
Let's go, Honmaru-kun.
Hey, that's not how it's supposed to be! Hey!
Honmaru! I'm a reckless adventurer!
Hurry up and join us here, Taru!
Honmaru! Skiing is fun!
Taruruuto...
So fun!
Taru...
Taruruuto!
Honmaru-kun, what is this shiver I'm seeing?
Are you stupid?
I'm just that excited, head to toe!
Not everyone would dare throwing
an accusation that ridiculous at Skimaru-sama!
I just hope I muster enough guts
for something worthy.
This is still more or less doable...
There are but the four of you
brave enough to stay.
All are from my class.
I knew you'd have the courage for this.
I'm so royally screwed...
Then, let's start with a lightning-fast slide
all the way to the ground.
I will provide the rearguard myself, but we also need
someone with the top abilities to lead the vanguard.
Yes! That would be Honmaru-kun!
I actually like going after!
Huh? But...
I go after, that clear to you?!
Why are you getting so worked up about this?
Once everyone is away,
I'll come clean before teacher.
Then just take a lift down.
First - Harako-kun!
Okay!
Second - Kawai-san!
What a sight!
Both are moving like pros.
Not bad...
Time to witness the true extent
of Skimaru's talent!
But I don't know a thing about skiing!
This didn't come as a surprise to nobody.
What...
What!?
Amazing, Honmaru-kun!
Was this Edojo Skimaru hoax
a real thing all along?
Actually cool! Wow!
Not every gold medalist can be that good!
I can do that...
But why?
Heck yeah, that was my feat!
You'll say your thanks later!
I see! Taruruuto cast a spell for me in advance!
Alright...
People! Don't miss your chance to see
Edojo Skimaru's dazzling skiing!
A cloud descended on the slope?
It was me who brought us thus far.
Huh? Heck no, it was me!
What's this about, you cheap braggart?
The hell? Wanna go, you punk?
How can one be so thick-headed?
You're the wreck that always goes sideways!
You can't be fighting now!
Bastard! You can't even ski by yourself!
Don't you butt in when men quarrel!
Okay...
Working in tandem with you is unbearable!
I'm the one who's supposed to be saying that!
I'll better off by myself!
Smell ya later!
Disunited again?!
You idiots!
Incorpore-re-real!
Honmaru!
Hey, Honmaru!
Whoa! Taru!
Honmaru!
Make way!
Found you!
There, his true colors finally show through!
I know how to cast it right this time!
Taruru!
They're heading straight for the pit!
Danger☠
Deadly cliff ahead!
What happened?
No more infighting this way.
Single piece - single mind.
I see!
You see!
What do you say, Harako?
Think you can still keep up with me?
Amazing, Honmaru-kun!
You dare to defy me,
the Junior Champion of the World?!
Don't do this!
The other side is unfit for skiing!
This challenge,
is not something I would decline!
Whoa, not backing down!
I will never lose, Honmaru!
Such an uncontrolled reaction
won't do you any good, Harako!
No! With the prestige of the Harako family at stake,
losing is not an option!
Whatever thicket you're leading me through!
Whatever thicket you're—
The hell?
Make it stop!
Whatever steep slope you're taking!
I... lost?
Egh?!
We've flown quite the way from the resort...
You got carried away
and carried us all the way to the Sea of Japan!
It's sea! Sea!
Teacher!
Eh?
Wanna play some cards with us?
Cards! Cards!
It feels like I forgot to tend to something...
Oh, it'll be fine.
Hey!
Where the hell is the rescue team?!
Taruru!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Damn, it's cold!
Nobody would be okay like this!
I wonder who was bright enough to lock me in!
The cold is outside and inside!
Alright! Taruruuto!
Let's get in the hot springs!
Yeah! Get in, get in!
Iyona is here, too!
Honmaru, you nosebleed.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Hot Springs Give Rise to Love Divination.
Let's get in all together!
Episode 21
Hot Springs Give Rise to Love Divination
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius