Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Iyona-chan!
Huh?
Going home already?
Yes.
I have a piano lesson scheduled.
Unlike you guys,
we've got some real business to attend to!
Iyona! Play more with us!
I'm sorry.
But say, Honmaru-kun and Taru-chan,
aren't you lucky to always be so close?
Yeah! Honmaru and me friends.
Iyona too!
Friends! Friends...
Rui too!
Friends...
Everyone, everyone! Friends, friends!
Episode 37
Midday Dodgeball
Clumsy idiot!
Getting handsy with Iyona-san in the broad daylight?
Well, look now where it got you.
Harako, you shithead!
What's wrong with you?
Why the hell did you do that without warning?!
Honmaru, do you know what sports
we have scheduled for the next gym class?
Yeah! It's dodgeball, ain't it?
You actually remembered that.
Congratulations.
What the hell is that machine?
Your reward.
The hell?!
Can't even receive a ball like that?
If I were you, I'd quit jawjawing with ladies midday!
The hell did you want to say with that?
Honmaru...
Honmaru-kun!
Harako-kun, that was sneaky!
Nobody can receive a ball
sent by a machine like that.
Ha! As if he could receive it himself!
Very well, Iyona-san.
Let me, then, hold a small demonstration,
showcasing just a fraction of my true power.
Gramps!
Sir!
Multiply the power of this shot by 50.
Roger!
Honmaru, get ready to lose hard!
Now, Gramps!
Okay!
How about it, Honmaru-kun?
Harako is something else...
What do you mean?
For a winner of the MVP award at the World Junior Dodgeball Championship three years ago, it was nothing special, really.
Well, you'll see for yourself, when I beat you to a pulp
in tomorrow's dodgeball game, Honmaru-kun.
What now?! Ain't no way I'm losing to you!
Yeah!
Oh?
Well said.
Then, I propose this: if you lose tomorrow,
you won't speak to Iyona-san for the rest of your life!
Can you commit to it?
How'd you ever come up with a silly condition like that?
Shove it up ya ass, imbe-be-becile!
This moron! I can't afford backing down
after getting this far! Shit!
You spiteful coward!
You think I'll fall for that?
That's just ridiculous.
I'll never commit to that, you moron!
He didn't fall for it!
Honmaru-kun has grown so admirably mature...
Well, let's head home, Iyona-chan.
How about this much?!
Honmaru, you coward!
Chicken! Wimp! Worm! Pig's butt!
You self-pissing, shitting scum!
Idiot! Moron! Mongrel!
Piss off! You really think I'll commit to it
after you've shot some balls at me?!
Good! Don't forget those words now, will you?
Oh crap!
I fell right for his provocation!
Honmaru, what did you gather all these balls for?
How could you not have guessed?
We're conducting special training for tomorrow!
Ah? Special training?
Yeah. I'm counting on you, Taru.
Okay!
What?
Hey?
Why?
Hey, what's going on?
Eh? What?
What?
Everyone, please listen!
We're starting a special dodgeball practice session now!
Dodgeball?
But I don't know what dodgeball is.
You don't need to know it.
I just want you all to start shooting yourself
at me with all you got.
If I hit you, that's gonna hurt!
It's fine! I'll be trying my best to dodge it.
That's right!
For all my life, I'm been extremely clumsy
in running away from the ball!
In any case, I'm counting on you, guys!
Yeah!
What's the matter, Young Master?
Would you like to stop now?
Gramps! Are you sure
that machine isn't broken or something?
It's not shooting one ball at a time!
Exactly so.
What?
I was the one who tampered with it.
What did you say?!
I broke it on purpose.
You rogue...
That was for your sake!
That was because I concluded that in an actual fight,
if you're unable to catch every ball flying at you,
you can't get the better of Edojo Honmaru.
What do you say, Young Master?
Would you like me to bring a new machine?
No need for that! Go!
Coming beautifully!
Honmaru is starting to move really well!
Leave it up to me!
Getting ahead of yourself, Honmaru!
Right...
What?
Shit...
Gonna need more than that!
Now, everyone! It's dodgeball time.
Let's have a powerful game!
Okay!
Don't forget our promise.
Once your team loses, I'll have you fulfill it, Honmaru.
Shut it! No way our team would lose this!
Honmaru! What do you do in dodgeball?
Oh, come on!
We split up across the court
and throw the ball at each other.
If you get hit, you're outed,
so you stand outside the enemy court.
But if you hit an opponent who's still on the court with a ball,
you get to return inside and continue playing.
Do you understand?
The what...
What's the matter, Taru?
Honmaru, saying too much things.
Me not understand a thing.
Oh, come on! Just grab the ball and throw it at the enemy!
Why, and that's it?
Just need to throw the ball?
Exactly!
Shoulda said so sooner, Honmaru.
You telling things too complex make me thoughts
go tangle, no benefit for anyone!
Dodgeball looking fun!
Me'll hit everyone I can!
Will you really be able to handle it, Taru?
Okay, let's get the match going!
Are you ready?
The team representatives are Harako-kun and Honmaru-kun.
We're starting.
Here!
Not talking to Iyona-chan
for the rest of my life is not a joke!
It's mine!
Dodgeball!
What?
Taru!
He received it!
Impressive, Taru-chan!
Pass it now, Taru!
Harako, gonna hit you!
Pass it now, I said!
Hey, Taruruuto!
It's dangerous!
Toss the ball to me, Taru!
You passed it straight to me?
Crap! Harako got the ball on a silver plate!
The match has barely started
and it's already in its most feared stage!
Taru, you idiot!
What should we do now?
Everyone! Run for your life!
Taru! It's dangerous! Run!
The perfect prey for me!
Perfect, perfect!
Taru!
Taru-chan!
First out -
Taruruuto!
Taru...
Harako-kun is such a brute!
Even though Taru-chan is still so small!
Playin' dirty, Harako!
Taru...
Taru-chan!
Are you alright, Taru?
Whee! I love dodgeball!
Taru! If you got hit, you go outside.
You're an eyesore!
Okay!
Taru! I'll pass the ball to you in no time!
You fools!
This is my ball!
I walloped your team in one fell swoop!
The ball sent by me, the World's Most Valuable Junior Dodger,
produces a human domino effect!
Wow...
Not bad, Harako-kun.
There's this one anecdote.
They say, in America,
they surround the court with walls...
Hey! Stop giving them ideas!
Tsk... Damn this prick Harako...
Honmaru!
Make sure you avenge our team!
Okay!
Now then, Honmaru.
Why do you think I've left only you two standing?
It's so I could trample you into the ground
right before Iyona-san's eyes!
What?!
Behold! Powerful Ball!
You dumbass! That's exactly
what I took the special training for!
Seems like dodging is the only thing you've learned, Honmaru. However...
Dodging alone won't be enough to take me down.
He's right!
On my special training I practiced nothing but dodging!
I'm getting bored, Honmaru!
Well then, Honmaru.
Will you keep dodging it forever,
or would you rather fall prey to the ball painlessly?
If I don't find a way to stop the ball somehow, I'll never win!
Powerful Ball!
Damn it... If I don't catch that ball somehow,
I'll lose to Harako!
And if I do, I can't talk to Iyona-chan ever again!
That would be way too unbearable!
Whatever I do, I gotta catch...
It's too damn scary!
Dodge it! Honmaru-kun, you can't die!
Dodgeball.
Huh?
Yo! Cooking something?
Needja to bump-bump into as many as you can!
Understood!
There you go!
I go!
Got you! There!
I can easily receive such a rookie ball!
But can you catch it?
What's the matter, Harako-kun?
Is Taru-kun meddling again?
Fine, invoke the takoyaki protocol.
Sir.
Fantastic, Taruruuto!
Don't judge a book by its cover, as they say...
Hey, Taruruuto! You've been revived!
You can go back to there now!
Yay! I'm revived!
Huge takoyaki!
Taru-kun...
What is it, Takoyaki-kun?
Let's play a game of tag!
If you catch up with me, you can eat me!
Really?
Really!
Off I go now!
Yay!
What's going on, Taru?
What's with that guy?
An idiot once - an idiot forever, after all.
Taru! Where are you going?
It's no use calling if he decided to flee, Honmaru-kun.
Continue the match.
Okay...
We'll be a-okay, Honmaru!
Just leave this to me!
Ah! That's right! Dodgeball-kun is still here!
When he was throwing me,
he put in all his strength even against girls!
That rubbed me the wrong way.
Okay, Honmaru! Throw me now!
Sure!
In we go!
Yeah!
Ha! Another rookie ball!
I can catch it with my eyes closed!
Good. That's it!
Watch out, Young Master!
Dodgeball-kun!
Idiot!
What's there to be upset about over a burst ball?
Don't you trample on Dodgeball!
Or what's gonna happen?
I can afford donating to the school
as many balls as I want!
Here, Young Master.
See?
You're a cold-blooded bastard!
His name was Dodgeball,
and he was alive just a moment ago!
Quit feeding me your nonsensical bullshit!
I especially can't lose to someone
as cold-blooded as Harako!
I have to receive this ball, no matter what!
Meet your disgrace!
Iyona-chan...
I caught it within the court bounds. Honmaru-kun, you're not out yet.
Hey! Wait for me!
I'll get you! I'm closing in!
Honmaru-kun, you throw it.
I owe you one, Iyona-chan.
Shit... Flirting right there! I wanna do that too!
Alright! Here I come!
Caught you!
The takoyaki machine is transmitting an emergency warning?
Ain't no way I can lose.
Ain't no way I'll lose to a swine like him!
Harako! With this, I'll avenge Dodgeball!
Another one of your lame balls?
Honmaru, you ass!
When the hell did he learn to throw like that?!
Doesn't matter!
I won't lose!
Harako-kun, watch out!
You're about to smash into the school!
Why should I care?!
It's a work of art...
It exploded...
Honmaru can throw some impressive balls!
How did that happen?
I got the ball right here with me.
No! My takoyaki went boom!
I apologize, Young Master.
No! Still not there!
But... Young Master!
No! Shut the hell up!
Make it 100 times the power of that now!
Yay! Poop! Poop!
Eugh! Taru, why'd you place such a thing on my head?
It's fine. Wearing this fella makes you mighty lucky!
Are you sure?
Somehow...
Somehow?
Only bad things happen to me now!
Taru.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Honmaru's Worst and Unluckiest Day Ever!
Episode 38
Honmaru's Worst and Unluckiest Day Ever
What's wrong, Honmaru?
It's a nightmare...
Watch it, everyone!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius