Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
What now, dad...?
Honmaru!
I'm going to run a 3 km marathon every morning
Aim for the star of the marathons!
Who was it that promised to get up every morning
and run a marathon with me?!
But it's Sunday!
I don't want to hear any excuses!
I won't tolerate a man who breaks his promises!
You gutless wreck!
I'm sorry!
You left me running alone! There!
Looks fun! I'll play go chasing one another with you too!
Honmaru! I'll beat some proper grit into you!
I'm so sorry!
I will never again let this...
Episode 42
The Tongue is the Root of Calamities?
Say, Taru...
Don't you think dad's too harsh?
Honmaru, you brought this upon yourself.
You'd not get spanked if you kept it.
That much I can tell you myself!
I shouldn't have agreed on those weird enterprises!
But dad will rough me up again if I quit now.
Say, Taru!
Isn't there some magic
that makes things go exactly as you say?
Yeah!
Using this should help.
Mama comes in carrying takoyaki.
Taru-chan.
I bought you some takoyaki while I was shopping.
Please help yourself.
This - True Storing. As you wear it on your neck,
it makes your words true.
Taru! You don't understand what I mean.
What I need is something that makes things go
exactly the way that I judge to be the best!
Wait, though.
Maybe I can use this too.
Lend me it for a moment.
Sure!
Help yourself.
Let's say...
Dad will take me to a department store today!
Now realize it!
Honmaru, I'm going to the department store.
You coming along?
You go or you don't go!
Answer immediately!
I'll go, I'll go!
Gimme a minute.
Make it quick, I'll wait downstairs.
Oh, it works! I'm infinitely lucky!
Amazing! This is an item that gets you anything!
You should've shown me
something so convenient sooner, Taru!
Sorry, Honmaru.
The hell is taking you so long?!
Come right now, Honmaru!
Okay!
Fine...
At the department store, dad buys me anything I like!
Honmaru.
I'll buy you anything you like.
Jet Bomber!
PC drive!
And this... He'll buy me this too!
Aren't you glad, Honmaru?
I just can't stop laughing from this!
Crap!
I made myself literally unable to stop laughing!
My belly hurts from laughing so much...
My magic can't last for more than ten minutes.
In ten minutes, you lose everything you gained.
And those ten minutes just ran out.
What?
Is that to say I'm destined to lose
whatever he buys for me?
I knew I was getting too happy too fast!
So you're happy with all the stuff I bought for you
getting ran over by a car?
Tsk. As if I never bought it.
That's not it, dad...
Honmaru, are you okay?
This damned item leaves nothing but emptiness in my heart!
Damn it...
My guts rise up against it!
Honmaru's gu-gu-guts rose up!
What are you so happy about, Taru?!
Pull back! Pull back, you!
Nothing to see here! There was never anything.
Honmaru was fun to watch!
Where, exactly?
I have no more patience for this item!
As can be seen from this food chain...
So boring.
At times like this, I like to gaze at Iyona-chan longingly...
Both the humans and animals living on this earth,
and of course, the plants too,
are all a part of a single bigger process,
where they survive through helping one another.
In other words, if we value the animals and the nature,
that also means we value ourselves and all of the humankind.
Don't you think so too, everyone?
Let's see...
Kawai-san?
Yes.
I actually think, isn't it the same between us humans?
If we all help each other
and reciprocate the attention,
I'm sure everyone will become happy.
Very true, I think so too.
Nailed it, Iyona-chan!
I didn't really understand a thing though, Taru.
Great, Iyona!
I support that too!
And what exactly did you understand
from what she said, Jabao-san?
Shut up! I got it, alright?
Are you kidding me?
Really, it takes some guts
to be saying corny stuff without any shame!
Neyo, you jerk! How dare you
make fun of Iyona-chan? Alright...
Teacher!
Yes, Honmaru-kun?
I also think, cherishing nature is important,
so from now on...
Um...
What's gonna happen from now on, Honmaru?
Honmaru, you can do it!
I'll be grateful for the blessings of nature.
Like not being picky about school lunches
and trying to eat everything without leftovers.
Good idea, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, amazing!
He sure is aiming high!
But will he really live up to it?
They put in my most hated bell pepper!
Honmaru, what are you hesitating about?
If you don't eat it soon,
gym class will start without you.
I know.
Oh my, what's the matter, Honmaru-kun?
I know exactly!
It has that bell pepper you hate!
I don't suppose you're gonna leave your school lunch behind?
Hey-hey-hey, check this out, everyone!
Determined to put a stake in the ground earlier,
Honmaru is gonna leave behind his meal now!
What did you say?
What's wrong, Honmaru?
Do you mean to say
everything Ijigawa-san said was true, Honmaru-kun?
Eat it, Honmaru.
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, be so kind as to answer
for your own claims, will you?
Ain't you a man?
A while ago, when I overate bell peppers,
I was vomiting severely and fell ill with a fever!
That's when I came to hate them!
If you leave behind even a single pod,
I ain't letting it slide!
You get it now?
What'd you do that for, Taru?
Honmaru, this is yummy!
I know, alright?
It's the best thing ever!
Doesn't it look tasty?
Alright, let's get full!
Huh? Upon a closer look,
these bell peppers really look quite yummy! Peppers!
Delicious!
It's yummy! I'm telling the truth!
Make sure to leave nothing on your plate, everyone!
What's gotten into Honmaru?
I'm wearing True Storing. But when...
Oh, I see, Taru! When you pretended to strangle me earlier,
you were actually putting this on!
Yeah!
Thank you, Taru!
I see, as long as you restrain yourself while using it,
this might actually be a fantastic item!
I just had a great idea!
Friggin' good! Harako playfully vaulted ten at once!
Some vaulting boxes?
To me, the winner of the World Junior Gymnastics
Championship, it's like taking candy from a baby.
If you're boasting about it so proudly,
you're still a long way off, Harako-chan.
What did you say, Honmaru?
And how good are you
to be talking like that, Honmaru?
I'll show you clearly, when I playfully vault
over 80 boxes at once!
Vault, vault!
Liar!
For starters, we haven't got that many vaulting boxes
in all of our school. Right, Jabao-san?
Liar.
Then what's that thing over there?
Even I'm seeing it for the first time...
Hey, people! Don't be too surprised.
Don't be surprised.
Ah, hold up. If they're not surprised at all, it'll be a bummer.
People, prepare to be surprised!
For this Edojo Honmaru is going to vault over those 80 boxes
and land safely before your eyes!
Yeah!
A fool's errand. You'll smash right into your big mouth.
I'm starting!
Go, Honmaru!
Watch this, Iyona-chan. I'm becoming a hero now!
How about this?
Honmaru-kun, impressive!
Hey! He actually vaulted over it!
Alright! If Honmaru can do something,
there's no reason I can't!
Atomic Jump!
There can only be one hero in this class!
Oh no... Catch it!
Eh?! World's #1 nails, come on!
Just as I thought, no ordinary human can do that!
Ah, it sure feels good to finally be a hero!
Ouch!
When ten minutes pass and magic wears off, True Storing
exchanges good things happened to you for bad things.
What?! You should've said so sooner, Taru!
Sorry, Honmaru.
What's wrong, Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru hurt his leg while vaulting 80 boxes at once.
Eh? What? Vaulting over 80 boxes?
Iyona-chan forgot it all!
Sometimes people forget it too.
Like about the department store yesterday...
It's a devastating item after all!
Just as I thought I'd leave my mark
before Iyona-chan's eyes today...
I guess you can't rely on Taru's magic for anything.
It only lasts ten minutes.
Niruru, let's play with this True Storing.
Putting it on Honmaru's papa should be fun!
Let's go then!
Hey! Hold back with that one!
We can't risk angering dad, Taru!
Board-kun.
Body disappear!
Was I too late, after all?
How was work today?
Hm. I had to make a round on publishing houses,
been walking all day.
My legs are wood-stiff.
What happened, honey?
No, it's nothing.
Just my imagination.
It was nothing, right?
Ah, I'm starving, honey.
Is dinner coming soon?
Sure, sure. Almost ready.
The smell is tantalizing.
It draws my nose out.
What was that just now...?
Ain't it delicious, dad? Mom's cooking.
Honmaru's mama cooking genius today!
Thank you, everybody.
That's true. Makes my cheeks fall off.
Honey...
Taru, Honmaru, is this your doing again?!
No clue...
I can see you're lying.
It's written on your faces!
Crap...
We're sorry, Dad!
Sorry, Honmaru's papa!
I've heard it so many times by now,
I have parasites living in my ears!
What? Oh, I see.
Everything I say becomes reality?
Yes, Honmaru's papa.
Well, sort of.
Ain't this a powerful item, then?
Oh no, oh no.
I can't say it out loud.
Clearly, everyone would want such a powerful item.
I gotta be careful and consider well what I'm saying.
The walls have ears and the doors have eyes, they say.
So many popped up! Papa amazing!
I need to put in more thought when using it.
What would be my wish if I were Honmaru's papa...
Just ask it for whatever you want!
How about money, dad?
Cloven-hoofed idiots!
Cloven
Cloven-hoofed...
hoofed
Cloven
Idiot
Idiot...
You think I'd seriously wish for something that petty?
I'd sooner boil some tea with my bare hands.
What an annoying item!
Hey-hey, dad, say it sooner.
That's it, if I can wish for anything at all...
Right, now say it already!
It's quite hard to come up with something
when you're demanding it like that.
How about we first ask your mom to use it?
Yay! Honmaru's mama using it too!
Hey, honey!
Yes?
Eh? It makes anything you say true?
Anything is fine.
Just say whatever you want to come true.
Okay.
What does Honmaru's mama think?
Let's see...
Ah, I can't just say it on the spur.
It'll become a problem.
Mom weighing her wish so seriously.
I'd hate to bring bad news to her...
But even if her wish comes true,
ten minutes later Taru's magic will wear off.
And everything will become nothing.
I can't help but pity her...
Sorry, mom.
All right. With warmth in our hearts,
our family becomes eternally happy.
Right, and then, with peace and harmony,
we become a family that's always on good terms,
laughing endlessly.
It's true! I feel so much warmer and happier!
Taru, I wish it'd stay like this forever!
But before you know it...
Ah... Huh? But ten minutes ran out already!
What's going on, Taru?
Honmaru, the magic of happiness is a lasting one!
Magic of happiness?
Oh, I see, Taru!
Still, Taru! My belly hurts from laughing this much!
Honmaru, endure! Endure!
You're right! My tum-tum hurts too now!
Wow, yay! It's a pool, a pool!
Honmaru, let's swim, hurry!
Hey... Wait a minute there!
Taru... Taru!
Ah! Honmaru can't stop ogling at Iyona in her swimsuit!
She'll hear you!
Sorry.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
It's Summer! The Pool is Open.
Honmaru, your eyes are a little naughty.
Episode 43
It's Summer! The Pool is Open
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius