Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 46
Must Win Pool Showdown!
Come on, Taru! Why are you so lazy today?
We need to leave for school soon, Taru!
Honmaru...
Honmaru always sleeping till late, got up early today.
Eh? Don't you need more sleep?
I'll do fine, Taru!
After all, it's a vested duty of an elementary school student to go to school in time!
Definitely not because swimming is the first class today.
And I won't forgive myself if I'll be late
to seeing Iyona-chan in a swimsuit!
Taru!
Honmaru same pervert as usual!
A force to be reckoned with...
Ah! There's the pool!
Let's change quickly, Taru!
Yay! Pool, pool, pool!
What's going on there?
What, what?
What's going on?
Ah, Honmaru-kun.
Good morning, Iyona-chan.
What's the buzz?
Listen, I've told you time and time again.
Only our Class 2 gets to use separated changing rooms.
You'll be changing outside together.
What are you talking about?
Up to now, we haven't had a problem using them together.
Why did it had to change today?
That's just the way it is.
Only we use it because I say so.
You go change elsewhere, now!
I see those guys suddenly forgot their place?
Leave it to me.
I'll talk some sense into them.
I ain't swallowing your cockiness!
First...
I ain't kidding around!
Who did it?!
Zakenja Nezo!
Scary...
Your Class 1 was the only one to ever defy me.
As a punishment, you won't get to use the changing room.
What's all this nonsense?!
The changing room belongs to everyone!
He's right, Zakenja-kun.
To those who rebel against me...
I do this.
Zakenja Nezo's Chinese kenpo
is all too terrifying!
Shit, it hurt like hell that last time.
If only his dad wasn't the owner of the Zakenja Concern...
This guy won't listen to whatever I say.
What should we do?
The guys from Class 2 that Zakenja Nezo bullied
have become bullies themselves.
Indeed, they are like dogs that take after a tiger.
Wanna eat takoyaki.
We can't leave things like this.
Is there something we could do? Something...?
That's it!
Honmaru! You go do something about it,
just like the last time!
Come on, come on!
Very well, Edojo Honmaru.
We'll have a duel, to settle scores for the last time.
Honmaru-kun!
What's wrong, Honmaru?
Ah, right.
Just like last time, I'll borrow Taru's magic.
I've nothing to fear from this guy!
Alright! I'll be your opponent,
Zakenja Nezo!
Good! Way to go, Honmaru!
Now, Taru! I'm counting on your magic, Taru!
Taru?
Hey! Hurry up and change, everyone!
Pool, pool!
Taru, what the hell are you doing?
Let's do it!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and change!
What happened?
Teacher!
Zakenja of Class 2 is bullying us
and won't let us use the changing room. Please do something!
Changing rooms?
I see. Zakenja-kun,
I hear you're a master of Chinese kenpo martial arts.
However, forcing others to obey you
with brute force is called plain violence.
If you couldn't even grasp that,
your training must have been in vain, kid.
What?!
I won't tolerate you making a fool of me.
Oaya-sensei.
Do you know who Zakenja-kun's father happens to be?
We'd better keep things civil here...
Yes.
You can have a duel without resorting to violence.
Zakenja-kun!
Duel our class in swimming!
Telling me how to have a duel?
Hey-hey, teach, who do you think you are
to be giving me orders?
You're that scared of losing?
That's the quickest way to tell who's a chicken.
Ah! Teacher!
You're wrong! You're wrong!
I'm not a chicken!
I won't lose!
I heard you, I accept it!
We're having a swimming duel!
Alright!
Then, how about the winner
gets to use the changing room?
Fine by me!
Very well!
Once your damned class loses,
you'll all be changing outside for everyone to watch!
And then you'll become my servants too!
Sorry to disappoint,
but Class 1 isn't gonna lose.
Because I train them constantly.
Teacher...
That's right! That's right!
Our Class 1 is never gonna lose to Class 2!
Well said, Oaya-sensei!
Everyone, let's do our best!
Yeah!
I ain't kidding around!
Yay! Duel with Neyo's brother! Duel! Sounds fun.
The duel will be a 200 m relay race for four.
I can't have you lose to Class 2!
Okay!
Now, who'll swim?
I will! Choose me!
Honmaru, can you really handle it?
We can't lose this duel, y'know!
Eh! Jabao, you're the one to speak!
With your physique, you'll sink right away!
What makes you think so?!
None of them seem reliable enough.
However, if we let the world junior swimming champion
Harako Tsutomu swim...
Hey, hey, Harako!
Who was it that willingly became Zakenja's servant?
What? When did I become this moron's servant?
Remember - you bowed your head when you found out Zakenja's dad stands above Harako Conglomerate?
You betrayed us, Harako.
What did you say?!
Don't you call me a coward!
Then prove otherwise!
You two are so cocky!
Then, we need one more. According to the record,
the fastest one in the class...
Kawai Iyona-san.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Iyona-chan, you can do it!
You can do-do-do it!
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-san, the golden combination
of us two would bring us victory!
Don't get ahead of yourself, talking like that, Harako!
What?
You ain't that great yourself, Honmaru.
You heard me!
Listen, you two!
Honmaru and guys are excited!
Not so much excited as just fighting.
And there's no telling what'll they do next.
You blockheads!
What is it?
Everyone, let's join forces and do our best together.
Alright. We're never losing to their kind!
Without a doubt!
We're united!
Yes.
United!
Yeah!
Yay, united!
United, united!
Neyo, let's root for our Class 1!
Alright! Class 1 and Class 2, on your starting positions!
I'm swimming first in the sequence.
I'll immediately blow everyone away with my power!
Please do, Harako!
You've got this!
Save for Zakenja Nezo,
none of those Class 2 slackers are athlete material.
Or anything noteworthy for that matter.
Alright, Jabao! Our victory is all but certain!
Yeah...
You'll be in deep trouble if you take Nezo lightly.
What did you say?
What do you mean by that?
Are you siding with him 'cus he's your bro?
Are you kidding me?
I'm just giving you some advice as a classmate.
Yet here you go acting like an insufferable brat.
What was that?!
Right back at you, insufferable girl!
That's how you are every damn time!
Honmaru don't get mad.
Taru?
This - Seething Kettle.
You put it on an angry person's head to boil water.
The angry person also settles down.
Honmaru, drink some tea.
What the hell are you doing at such an crucial time?!
Ready!
These guys are just small fry.
They're no rivals to me.
Um...
I'm not really confident about this.
You'll be alright.
Time to show you my brilliant butterfly!
Go, Harako!
Keep going!
Eh? Where's the opponent?
Zakenja-sama!
My arms are suddenly swinging around on their own!
I can't stop!
It's fine, just jump in the water now.
Okay!
Insane speed!
Cool, cool!
At this rate...
Oh! He already overtook Harako!
What?
My arms are tearing off!
This is perfect.
Another 4,000-year-old secret Chinese technique.
What did you say?
Nezo used acupuncture on his critical points.
What's acupuncture?
A technique of pressing on secret points on someone's body
to make them move as you want.
Really?
"So-u-nds nasty" - like this?
Zakenja Nezo...
He's a truly terrifying dude!
Jabao! Hurry up to dive! Harako's here!
What?!
You ass!
Witness! Atomic Flying Fish Butterfly!
Yeah! Harako is catching up!
Dammit. I shouldn't underestimate him.
That's the way, Harako!
Go, go, go!
Almost there!
I won't lose!
Rock, paper, scissors!
What you just did was a foul!
What are you talking about?
Look, how could I've helped him at such a distance?
But I know you've done something!
It was ki. He used ki this time.
Ki? Is that another Chinese technique?
Nezo used magic, I use too!
Go, Jabao!
Okay!
Stre-re-re-retch!
Contra-ra-ract!
Wow! Not bad!
Well done, Taru!
Iyona! Iyona!
Taru-chan?
What?
Taru-chan, don't draw doodles on my swimsuit.
I need to swim now!
There!
What's going on? My body...
Let's do it, Iyona!
That's our Iyona-chan!
What an unbelievable swimming technique!
Taru! That's going a bit too far!
Iyona-chan, just endure it for a little longer.
You can do it!
Zakenja Nezo!
Looks to me like we're winning!
I can't lose.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Nezo!
Iyona-chan!
The victory is mine!
Iyona-chan, are you okay?
Hang on, I'll get there now...
What are you doing? Are you at it again?
I'm alright, no need to come help me.
We'll get disqualified.
I'll do it. I'll swim, all the way to the end.
Iyona-chan...
Keep it up, Iyona-chan!
You're almost there! Fight!
You can do it, Iyona!
Keep going!
You can do it!
Kawai-san, a little more!
Just one final push!
Right, right! Keep going!
Keep going, Iyona-chan!
Alright. I absolutely can't afford to lose.
I'll swim without a single breather!
If I breath in really hard now...
What are you doing?
Infla-la-late!
Honmaru-kun, the rest is...
up to you!
I'll do it!
I won't need breathers with Taru's magic!
Go, Honmaru!
Go, go, Honmaru!
Do your best,
Honmaru-kun!
He attacked Iyona-chan mercilessly.
Zakenja Nezo, you'll pay for it!
Honmaru is amazing!
That's the way, Honmaru!
I can't let this happen!
I need to attack!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru!
You're playing dirty, Zakenja!
Told you I'd win.
It's hopeless now...
I can't move...
Is this how we'll lose...?
After such a demanding special training with Taru,
I'm supposed to be swimming much better than that!
I guess, without magic, I really can't get anything done...
Without magic...
Magic...
Honmaru, use magic.
Magic...?
You lost, Class 1!
Get ready to change outside after this!
And to become my servants next!
What's the matter?
Like this...
No way...
I can lose!
Nonsense!
What just happened?
Magic.
Class 1 wins!
Honmaru amazing magician!
Really amazing...
Honmaru-kun!
I never thought I'd meet a man...
Who can defeat Nezo, Honmaru.
Hey, Class 2!
As a show of mercy, I'll let you
use the changing rooms. But in exchange...
You'll only call me your queen from now on!
Well, wouldn't that be unreasonable?
Doesn't that sound familiar to you, though?
What did you mean by that?
Well done, Honmaru!
Astounding finish!
Did I just lose again?
Frustrating, so frustrating!
I'll definitely win next time!
Honmaru, it's the sea! Sea!
Yeah! The seaside school starts today.
Blue sea, white sand beach.
Alright, I'll swim as hard as I can!
Honmaru looks happy.
But man...
Iyona-chan's swimsuit is too revealing!
Honmaru, why are you hiding in a hole?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Mischievous Seaside School.
Honmaru looks happy.
Me happy too!
Episode 47
Mischievous Seaside School
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius