Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Zakenja Nezo, who aims to control all of Nannosho,
is facing Class 5-1 in a martial arts tournament,
with their freedom and independence at stake.
With Harako and Taruruuto's remarkable determination,
it looked like the battle was all but won.
However, distracted by a sudden takoyaki delivery,
Taruruuto was disqualified.
But then, just as the referee
was about to declare Class 2 victorious,
it was cut short by Honmaru's voice, as he
had just returned from his training in a mountain retreat.
And here he is, standing firmly, facing up to Nezo!
Episode 58
Stand up, Honmaru!
What did you come back for, Honmaru?
Do you want everyone to witness
your resignation to becoming my servant?
If you meekly kneel on the ground
and apologize right now, I may go easy on you.
Zakenja!
I have only one piece of advice I can give you.
I'm not the same Honmaru as before!
And I'm here to show you that in this life
things don't always go your way!
Now, Class 5-1 vs Class 5-2.
Start the final match!
Now, the entirety of Nannosho elementary school
are holding their breath as the final battle between Honmaru and Zakenja is about to begin!
Whoa! An intense exchange of techniques right off the bat!
Despite being heavily attacked by Zakenja,
Honmaru does not yield an inch!
What we see is a technique-to-technique,
strength-to-strength clash!
Dear viewers, this really deserves to be called the final match
because both fighters have become extremely serious!
Way to go, Honmaru!
Honmaru cool!
Honmaru became stronger through training in mountains! Amazing! Amazing!
Honmaru-kun seems to have grown much more determined. He's like a completely different person now!
Yeah.
You can do it, Honmaru!
I can't help but commend you
for achieving this much in a mere month.
However...
In the end, you're still a wimp!
Honmaru!
Oh-oh! It seems like Honmaru is barely managing to keep up with the opponent's onslaught!
A strong counterattack from Zakenja sends him down!
Honmaru keeps doggedly rising up to confront him!
However! However! Neither has decisively the upper hand yet!
Was the difference in power too overwhelming, after all?
What the hell, Honmaru?
If you lose, we'll become slaves!
Get your guts together, Honmaru!
Build your happiness with your own hands.
You're our representative fighter, after all!
You're even weaker than Taruruuto!
Is it now just a matter of time for Honmaru?
Ugh! He really ain't worth shit without you, Taru!
Dammit! Honmaru, don't you dare lose!
Everyone, don't panic.
I'll make everyone happy with my magic.
Sli-li-li-lip!
Zakenja Nezo!
Do your worst, Taru!
Serves you well, Zakenja!
That's our Taruruuto, the Great Magician!
Yeah! Me the Great Magician.
Magician, you say?
Taru! Did you give it away?
Yeah! Me gave it away! Me...
Sorry, Honmaru. I wasn't cautious with magic...
It's fine, it's fine! Magician or whoever, it's all the same!
That's right! If that lets us defeat Zakenja,
let's put formalities aside!
I ain't understand a thing but I'm here for the fun!
What? His magic is discovered,
but it seems like they couldn't care less.
Then, what was the point
of trying so hard to keep it a secret at all?
I ain't kidding around, Taruruuto!
Magic or whatever, it's a violation of the rules
to interfere in a fight between two contestants!
Taruruuto, all you do is soil a noble face-off between men!
Me? Soil Zakenja's face?
I didn't soil it, but Zakenja says...
I see! Raincloud Taro!
Did you call me?
So cute.
You think he may be a true magician?
What are you doing, little one?
Some soil for Zakenja's face.
Here's your soil!
Nezo said he wanted me to soil his face, so I soiled it.
I ain't kidding around, Taruruuto!
All you're doing is dampening a face-off between men!
Dampening... a face-off.
Gotcha!
Nezo! I dampened your face!
Oh-oh, would it be wrong to say
someone is taking things too literally here?
Yay, yay!
Taruru, stop interfering!
Honmaru?
That's right, Taru-chan.
Magic or witchcraft - I don't know, but one thing is for sure: the third party interfering in a fight between the two is a foul!
Next time you pull something off,
I'll rule that Honmaru-kun lost!
Okay...
Sorry, everyone.
Alright, so be it.
Then Honmaru has to do his best on his own,
and that's that!
Go, Honma—
Tranquilizing Fist!
Zakenja's special fist is mind-numbing!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru!
Honmaru stood his ground!
Amazing! He received Zakenja's
deadly fist directly, but endured it!
With guts like that, Honmaru,
you oughta win! I know you'll win!
Not bad, Honmaru!
It's too early to rejoice.
Honmaru is already trapped firmly
in my technique's web.
What?!
Look, I'll hit him again!
Dodge, Honmaru!
Watch out!
There you go!
Honmaru!
Why didn't he even try to dodge a punch that slow?!
Alright! Honmaru, attaway!
What are you doing?!
Show some footwork at least!
Why are you just standing there blankly like a scarecrow?
Everyone is listening.
Wanna explain something to us, Honmaru?
Ugh... I can't move my legs at all!
You can't what?!
What? What?
I didn't do anything with magic!
My Tranquilizing Fist paralyzes your nerves.
Even if you faint or die,
you won't be able to move an inch.
If your only option is to keep receiving
my fists since you can't move,
you won't even be able to go down
unless you give up willingly!
It's time for you to taste the hell of agonizing cries!
Now, better surrender soon
and become my servant, my slave!
Otherwise you'll die!
Honmaru has truly become a human sandbag!
Zakenja's probably going too far.
Honmaru!
Stop it already!
Come on, say it now! Say that you'll be my slave!
We will never be slaves! We are free!
Who'd ever want to become a slave to you?
Sure ain't got a single such cretin in our Class 1!
I can see right through your ostensible toughness!
Now, say it! Say you'll become my slave!
Give up and bring an end to everything!
Exactly. If I say that, everything will be over.
That's why I can't afford to lose!
Honmaru, I can't do anything... I can't...
If this continues, Honmaru-kun will...
Honmaru-kun will...!
Stop it! It's dangerous to continue this fight any longer.
Honmaru-kun! Are you okay?
Please don't stop it, Teacher.
If I withdraw from the match this easily,
what am I even worth, then?
My training with dad up until now...
What was it for?
I haven't lost yet!
Attaway, Honmaru!
What a spirit, Honmaru!
Well said, Honmaru!
Taru-chan...
Taru-chan.
Taru-chan, please, use your magic to save Honmaru-kun.
Iyona...
If this continues, Honmaru-kun will die.
The match is resumed!
I want both sides to have no regrets later.
Say that you've had enough!
Taru-chan, please!
Taru, do it!
Taru-chan.
Okay!
Stop, Taru. Are you planning to cheat again?
Harako-kun?
Gramps told me everything.
To think that you were a magician...
This is the key to all those mysteries.
The reason why every time I competed with him so far
Honmaru always emerged decisively victorious...
Each time, I thought "I won't lose next time!"
And kept trying my best like my life depended on it!
However, Taruruuto,
I never even considered your magic from the shadows
to be what brings him victory!
That's the worst kind of cheating, Taru, Honmaru!
Cowards! Traitors!
Try fighting fair and square for once without relying on magic!
I defeated Kaze Kumagoro
with just my own strength, Honmaru!
You're wrong! Harako, you're wrong!
Where am I wrong, you phony brat?
Honmaru... Honmaru.
Didn't win with just my magic.
All I did was give him a special training with magic.
Honmaru defeated Harako with his own strength.
And now Honmaru had a special training without my magic!
Honmaru said he didn't need my magic!
You expect me to believe that?
Taru-chan is not a liar.
Honmaru did it honestly...
Iyona-san.
We were all letting ourselves be fooled.
By Taru and that Honmaru.
Say it's over!
Say you'll be my slave!
Never! Never!
Honmaru still hasn't collapsed,
despite sustaining the full onslaught of Zakenja's barrage!
Harako!
Honmaru is fighting without magic right now!
Rui-chan...
Fighting without magic?
Is that why the match is so one-sided this time?
Without magic, Honmaru is actually that gutless a man.
You don't know what you're talking about!
You're an idiot, Harako!
Did you ever get to receive Zakenja's iron fist?
It hurts like you can't even imagine!
But he's been receiving that fist one after another,
and still never said "it's over!"
Honmaru never said "I'm done!"
He's performing this great feat for our sake!
Just you watch, I'm sure he'll do it!
Do your best, Honmaru! I believe in you!
Jabao-kun.
Jabao!
Okay, we'll root for him too!
Do your best, Honmaru!
Honmaru...
I see...
I really do.
At the very least, that one punch
had nothing to do with magic!
It was your own.
That's what I'd like to think.
Honmaru hasn't collapsed yet.
However, Zakenja's merciless attack continues!
If my Tranquilizing Fist reaches your pressure point, it's over.
You'll never be able to move your legs on your own again.
Death may actually seem a preferable fate to this.
Your lower body doesn't belong to you anymore!
Move, legs!
I need you to move, legs!
Honmaru, even when the magic disappears,
we are still a part of you!
Up until now, you just haven't been
using your power to its full potential!
Make the most of your own power!
Come back to life, my legs!
Honmaru!
Bad news, Honmaru!
We are already trying our best.
But a greater force is holding us down!
Try... Try to give us more power and energy!
Power, energy...
Honmaru. Even though I didn't use magic,
I can see something in Honmaru.
Power, energy!
Isn't it the power of ki that dad told me about?
Dad, why are we doing this?
Why do I have to be blindfolded?
Rather than seeing with your eyes,
you need to feel the power of nature with your whole body.
Not seeing with my eyes,
but with my whole body?
That's right, Honmaru.
This is how you hone your ki.
Take a deep breath and let the ki energy of the nature
circulate throughout your body.
Borrow the power of nature.
Borrowing the life energy from all living nature.
You find it in your own body.
Rather than forcing your way against the flow,
find your way within the flow?
Even fire has a heart. Wind, water, and earth -
everything is alive. Everything is alive!
That's right, Honmaru.
Make sure to remember it with muscles!
You can see it with your heart, Honmaru!
Why won't you say "I'm done"? Eh?!
Honmaru no longer tries to move a single muscle in his body!
At this rate, he'll run out of energy!
No!
Teacher, please stop this!
Honmaru-kun... Honmaru-kun will die!
You're right... Honmaru-kun!
Wait! The fight is not settled yet.
Oh! Honmaru's dad!
Papa!
Teacher, please don't dampen this man-on-man duel.
Just this once, let them fight in a way
that'd let them have no regrets for the rest of their lives.
Why are you doing this, sir?
Don't you care if Honmaru-kun dies?
Honmaru will win this duel!
Honmaru, don't give up!
We're you, all doing our best!
Do your best, Honmaru!
We are you!
Make the most of your own power!
Make the most! Make the most of us!
Make the most of us!
Now, every cell in Honmaru's body is about to wake up.
About to wake up?
Then, does this mean that 50 billion cells in his body
have been sleeping until now?
Honmaru's heart is shining and he's amassing power.
Right. Honmaru is circulating the energy of life, the ki.
Ki?
Ki is the source of the human spirit,
the essence of life itself.
Normal humans only use a fraction
of the power they truly possess.
However, it is possible to wake up
all your cells by circulating ki.
And right now Honmaru is circulating ki,
just like he practiced every day in the mountains.
He is trying to absorb the energy of nature
and awaken all the powers still dormant in him.
Moreover, what Zakenja emits is a "minus" - a negative ki.
When he converts it into "plus," a good ki,
he can use it as if it was his own energy!
Does that mean Honmaru-kun is now actually
starting to feel better and better?
Exactly!
Is it true?
As proof, Honmaru's legs
will soon break free from Zakenja's earthly bonds!
He escaped the trap of my Tranquilizing Fist!
Honmaru!
You did it!
Go, Honmaru!
Did you really think it'd be that easy
to turn your legs back to normal?
What?
Oh-ho!
Now we see Honmaru mounting an intense counter-attack,
using his feet as hands and his hands as feet!
Where in the world did this power come from?
Impressive, Honmaru...
Using his hands and feet in reverse...
The same strategy he used
during our soccer showdown.
Oh! Honmaru, you turned to my special training again!
He never dealt with an opponent fighting upside-down.
Therefore he can't predict
where the next attack will come from!
Oh-ho! Zakenja is down!
Honmaru, way to go!
It's just as Honmaru's dad said.
Honmaru, became livelier instead!
Is his power of ki really this amazing?
He's not even unleashed it fully yet.
If he manages to accumulate even more ki,
he can make any miracle happen!
Honmaru!
Was this miraculous transformation
achieved in just one month?
I'll reveal your true colors!
Eagle Claw Attack!
Zakenja's strength will return to Zakenja.
How? How did he manage to get this far in just a month?
This power is not just the result of our mountain training.
Boxing, soccer, sumo, swimming -
it's all thanks to the special magical trainings
Honmaru received from Taru.
Honmaru developed his own strength
during Taru's magical special trainings.
He nurtured it.
And eventually he could quit
being dependent on magic.
He learned to move his mind and body
with the power of his soul.
Little by little, without even realizing it, time after time.
You've done well to make it this far, Honmaru.
I see. Well, ain't Honmaru lucky?
Taru, give me special magical training too!
Okay!
This is our special training for boxing.
Hot! It's hot!
I've got plenty of special trainings saved up!
This one was enough for me!
That's astounding. Were you always
subjecting yourself to special trainings of this kind?
Astonishing, Honmaru!
Volcano Rockfall Kick!
He did it again! Amazing, Honmaru!
Honmaru is in great condition, as if he had been reborn!
Zakenja can't get even close to him!
Honmaru! Wrap this up soon and let's go celebrate!
It's already clear you've won this one!
That's the way, Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun!
Are you really okay, Honmaru?
What the hell? Open your eyes!
Honmaru is completely invincible now!
No...
It's as though Honmaru's life flame
is burning the brightest right before it dies out.
Harako!
How dare you jinx Honmaru's death
when he's doing so well?
Yeah, ain't nothing personal, but that wasn't nice of you!
Harako! Aren't you just a sore loser
'cause you can't bear Honmaru looking so cool?
I swear, I'll never let someone
saying things so stupid eat at my stall!
Thank you, Taru.
All the special trainings that I've been through - I was only
able to manage it thanks to you casting a spell on me.
Taru, it was a magic of warmth.
Thank you for your friendship.
We'll remain friends forever, come what may.
Honmaru...
Honmaru!
Honmaru, be careful!
Nezo's heart is dark and cold!
Yeah. I know, Taru.
But there's no way our warm hearts will lose to it, right?
No! Nezo's fist is very dangerous!
It's a fist of hatred and evil!
Run away!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Honmaru's Final Battle!
Honmaru, don't you breathe in Nezo's hatred!
Episode 59
Honmaru's Final Battle!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius