Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taruruuto!
It's long past dinner, so where the heck are you?
Hey, Taru!
Watch it, watch it, watch it!
Eh? Since when do we have
such an apartment complex here?
Oops, I'm not here for this.
Hey, Taru! Where did you go?
Episode 40
Zakenja Neyo
Yay! Yay!
Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Matsu-san been awfully generous today!
Together with Honmaru,
will devouru-ru-ru!
Takoyaki!
Alley-oop...
Trunsform!
Takoyaki-chan!
Sorry. Please accept this as an apology.
Forgive me please!
I know!
If I use this! Alright...
I'll send you flying right now!
Dog.
Oops. I mistook Attractor for Repeller.
Sorry!
Just forgive me already!
Sorry...
Bye!
Hey, I wanna leave! I'm sorry, I really me... Hey...
Bad boy...
Huh?
Are you okay?
Yeah!
Taru!
Where in the world did Taru go?
Maybe the park?
Kichijoji Park
Almost...
Did it!
Hey! Look, dad!
I managed to catch the kendama!
Hey, look, the kendama...
Yeah, I'm glad.
Here, look. Here!
Sorry, but I'm going out now.
I have some urgent work to do.
Oh, right, I have some good news too.
Yesterday, I left a new doll for you in your room.
I'm sure you'll come to love it.
Because it is you who I always keep on my mind.
It is you...
Always on my mind...
Are you...
Kidding me?!
Hey, Taru! It's dinner time!
Hey, Honmaru!
Hm? Huh? Who's that girl Taru is playing with?
Honmaru! Honmaru! I can now catch kendama too!
Look. Please look!
Okay, okay. I got it, you hear? I got it.
I'll look at it! I will, you hear?
Okay...
Don't laugh so much, please!
My bad, my bad.
Are you okay?
Yeah! I'm fine already.
Good.
Me need to practice more.
Is this tot your little brother?
He's cute.
Just watch me try it out once more.
Okay!
Wow!
Oh! Amazing!
Well, see you around!
Goodbye!
Bye-bye!
Taru, what's that girl's name?
Don't know, first met her today.
She - my lifesaver.
Honmaru! Dinner, dinner!
The girl I first met sent my heart pounding...
But I already gave an oath to marry Iyona-chan!
Dinner, dinner!
Eh? Wh... What the?
Because you were too absorbed in thought,
I brought bicycle to life with Magic-kun!
And told him to dru-ru-rive at full speed!
Gonna get ya there!
Whoa! You can't be serious, Taru!
Zakenja Neyo
Today, I introduce to everyone our new transfer student.
Zakenja Neyo-san.
Oh?
Honmaru, it's her.
You know her, Honmaru-kun?
Yeah!
Yes...
Everyone, I hope you all make good friends with Zakenja-san.
Right, Zakenja-san?
Nice to meet you.
Does that conclude your introduction?
Yeah.
Then, you can take your seat at the furthermost row.
Okay.
Zakenja-san?
You've had no time to receive your textbook today,
so please ask your neighbor to let you see theirs.
Okay.
Yo!
Hey! I bought and brought my own kendama!
Huh?
Did we mistake her for someone else?
Honmaru, look.
I'll be the first!
Hey! No running in the hallway!
Teacher, in the test from the other day,
why did you cross this answer?
Eh?
Ah, you mean this?
Her air is completely different somehow, Taru.
Yeah.
Hey, Zakenja-san.
Where were you used to live before moving here?
Ah? Iyona-chan.
Hm, that was kinda to be expected.
Taking it on herself to break the ice
with a new transfer student.
Oh, how caring you are!
Honmaru, me too!
Whee... Taru!
You...
When asking others about something,
you first introduce yourself.
I'm sorry.
What's with that attitude?
My name is Kawai Iyona.
And this here is Ijigawa Rui-chan.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask me.
Jeez.
You guys are just incorrigible.
Elementary school students these days...
Don't know no manners,
no nothing.
You can't be doing that!
Elementary school students don't smoke cigars!
Huh? I know, alright?
Want me to open the window or something?
That's not what I mean!
Zakenja-san, smoking is very bad for your health!
What's it to you?
Damn, you're obnoxious. You don't go around
telling people this and that pastime is wrong!
But...
I still think... That one thing...
Are you kidding me?!
You don't get to preach others
just 'cause you have a pretty little face!
What kinda game do you think you're playing here,
you stuck-up arrogant whore?! Huh?
Enough!
Honmaru-kun...
Zakenja-kun,
I know you're not actually that kind of girl!
I saw your true face, when you smiled yesterday!
And I sincerely hope
to see that kind smile of yours once more!
Ah! She heeded to it!
So corny!
Really, I'm impressed that you can say such corny lines
out loud without even feeling slightly embarrassed!
Uh-huh.
A girl with a potty mouth is as far from cute as it can get.
Ah, Harako?
What's with this dino-mugged grandpa?
Shit... You even dare to call me a dino-mugged Grandpa?!
I won't tolerate anyone saying such things,
not even a girl!
I've won that already.
You've almost done it!
But I'm also the World Junior Endurance...
Wide Swing Brain Stem Wrecking Ball Hit!
No way...
Harako-kun...
All bark and no bite, as always.
Hm! Pathetic poser.
Whoever else has a problem with me, step forward.
I'm here to deal with you anytime!
That's one hell of a transferred girl we got...
Harako-kun!
Why are you giving me that look?
Got a problem with me?
Don't worry about me, Iyona-san...
I don't have a problem with you.
I just think violence is unacceptable.
For a champion of every world tournament
in any kind of sports...
How am I wrong for shutting up a guy
trying to pick a fight with me?
I'm sure you could easily get along
without resorting to violence.
Trying to preach again?
That's some guts you got, girl.
Taru!
Yes?
If it came to this, we gotta save Iyona-chan with magic!
Knock out the other girl!
Knock out? But me love both Iyona and the other girl!
Just what do I do now?
What now? Got nothing better to say to me?
Zakenja-san.
If a bunch of elementary graders look down on me
as soon as I transfer, I ain't gonna stand for it!
What now? Aren't you an elementary grader yourself?
Violence only leaves behind more hatred and deep scars.
It's a line I've read in some book.
I don't know what happened to you
at your previous school. But in our school...
Just cut the crap already!
You kidding me?!
Hold it!
I've already won this one!
Honmaru-kun?
What the hell? You won?
With this.
If I win, you apologize to everyone in class there and then.
Without violence, we'll hold a duel strictly with kendama!
Kendama duel?
Oh, I see.
Sounds like fun.
You plan to beat me in kendama mastery?
Don't let me down, Kendama-kun.
Aight!
Just trust me to deal with it all!
Are you sure, Honmaru-kun?
Don't worry.
I'll do whatever it takes to protect you.
Honmaru-kun...
What are you babbling about there?
You're leaving me no choice but to attack first.
Impossible!
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru will be fine! Duel, duel!
Okay... It's my turn now!
What?
Impressive, Honmaru!
What kind of technique is this?
It's almost like the ball is moving on its own!
Well, you could almost say it does!
Ah... But please, try to move just a bit slower!
That's about how much I can do,
only engaging a fraction of my true ability!
But that's enough playing.
Time for a grand finale!
There!
Eh?
Honmaru-kun!
Any elementary grader is about ten years too young
to even try to defeat me.
Can't you understand you're an elementary grader yourself?!
You brought this upon yourself
by being unable to keep your mouth shut.
Don't laugh!
At least Honmaru-kun was trying to push his limits!
Iyona-chan...
Are you kidding me?! He lost and that's it!
You whore, still trying to talk back to me?
Are you...
Right on the mark!
kidding me...
Ah! Taru!
Come on, Taru! Why'd you have to hit Iyona-chan too?!
I'm so glad to know a person so kind and caring as you!
You're the one most wonderful here!
Eh-heh-heh?
Taru...
Yeah. This - Sabro.
The two you strike with it become best bros.
Sabro
I see! You've really outdone yourself, Taru!
At one point, I thought the situation wasn't salvagable,
but with this, peace returned to our class!
Peace, peace!
But still, Taru.
What will we do after the magic wears off in ten minutes?
Just strike them again!
And in ten minutes more?
Strike again.
It's no use! We haven't resolved anything!
Honmaru, this is a disaster!
The "class needs" fund has disappeared!
Eh?
What did you say?
Alright, Taru!
Let's join the search with everyone!
Yeah!
Hey, Neyo! Start searching too!
Hey, Neyo!
Neyo, let's look for it together?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Episode 41
Dishonest Neyo!
But I really love Neyo.
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius