Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Unable to protect Iyona and Rui from delinquents,
Honmaru went to train in a mountain retreat,
so as to discover a new strength within himself.
Meanwhile, Harako and the others
try to resist Nezo's ambition to rule over all of Nannosho,
notwithstanding even the two kenpo masters
he summoned from China,
so they settle on a martial arts tournament against Zakenja Nezo, with the school's freedom and independence at stake.
Then finally, a month later,
the day of the martial arts tournament is here.
Yay! Me fight too!
Episode 57
Clash! Martial Arts Tournament!!
I've waited for a month, as agreed upon.
But Honmaru didn't come.
You can't trust such a man for anything.
Honmaru always coming late.
But I'm sure he'll come back stronger!
Honmaru-kun...
It's no use waiting for that weakling, Iyona-chan.
That's right.
Harako, you're the only one we can rely on!
Leave it to me! I can cook up
all three of them nicely, even all by myself.
Me defeat too!
Thank you for waiting, everyone.
We will now hold a Martial Arts tournament
between Classes 5-1 and 5-2!
The rules are as follows:
If you're downed and don't get back up on the count of ten,
as well as if you exit the arena,
or just decide to willingly give up,
you will lose.
Is that clear?
I'm the first fighter of my team!
Do your best, Harako!
Mop the floor with Zakenja's goons from Class 5-2!
First fighter from Class 2, Kaze Kumagoro. Go!
Roger.
Huge!
Looks strong too.
I am the World Junior Martial Arts Champion
Harako Tsutomu.
It won't take me more than ten seconds
to beat a blockhead such as you!
I'll make you realize that you're not
a real world champion, and I'll see to it, boy.
The world is a big place, boy.
I see it's not just your body that is big,
even your mouth is.
Start!
Here goes the super-powerful special fist, cultivated and honed by the Harako Tsutomu - Super Rolling Thunder Punch!
Oh, wow! Out of nowhere it comes!
Harako's surefire technique!
Dislocating your arm joints and winding the muscles,
spinning the fist with enormous speed on release,
enough to create static electricity from friction with air.
A deadly electric punch!
Idiot! You think you can catch
this deadly fist with your bare hands?
Your left hand is already dead!
Harako amazing!
Nicely done, Harako!
What?
That said, Harako is being blown away!
The stream from Harako's fire hose
was reflected back at him.
Runny nose?
What did you say?!
What's going on?
If you empty your mind, you can make your foe's
energy outburst flow through you harmlessly.
Then you complete the circuit
and release it back at your opponent.
Zakenja-san?
That's the First of Cause and Effect.
You need to have a mind of a wind bear-like body disposition.
Hence, only Kaze Kumagoro can perform this technique.
1!
2!
3!
Harako is knocked down by an unexpected counterattack!
He won't stand up!
4!
5!
6!
7!
Ah! Hey, Harako!
Well, looks like Harako lost.
Who is the next challenger?
Did you say... I lost?!
9!
Look closer before talking!
I said I'd defeat all three of you
so that's what I'll do!
Harako stood up!
I see that I need to engage even more power.
Super Powerful Deadly Fist:
Super Rolling Thunder Punch Special Two!
Last episode next week
Harako-kun!
The harder you hit,
the worse you're trashed, boy.
I don't approve of senseless murder, boy.
You just helped me realize
the extent of my power once again.
This is still a morsel of it.
I just need to raise my power furthermore!
Witness! Super Rolling
Thunder Punch Special Thr—aah, really?!
Whatever, it's still nothing!
Still Super Rolling Thunder Punch Special Four...
Five!
Six!
Seven!
Eight!
Harako keeps on fighting with unyielding determination.
But so far, it has been completely in vain!
Just you watch! I'll put so much energy into his body
that he can't bounce it back!
Just hurry up with something, dangabbit!
Let's finish this!
It's dangerous! You can't wind your hand any further.
Super Powerful Deadly Punch: Ultra Deluxe
Super Rolling Thunder Punch Special Ten!
Harako has finally been decisively knocked down!
Harako-kun!
Harako!
I can't move my body anymore.
Will I lose again? Just like back then with Honmaru? Shit...
Harako! You fought really well!
No need to get up anymore!
This is a lost cause.
Harako not lost!
He lost! Lost!
Not lost! Not lost!
Just look for yourself! He's all but defeated!
Defeated!
Argh! Don't just switch to the opposite point of view and catch me off-guard!
Switch up to saying the opposite, huh...?
I was driving full steam ahead
on a certain victory highway.
Did it suddenly turn into a
"consecutive defeats" backroad at some point?
Did it suddenly turn...
I see!
Seems like Harako finally ran out of energy...
Oh?
No! He stood up again!
Harako is still standing!
Harako!
He rose from the ashes, everyone!
Phoenix Harako!
Super Powerful Deadly Fist
Still wanna fight with a body that thrashed out?
It's all lost.
There's no longer any speed in his punches.
Very well.
Let's fight until the very end without putting our hands down.
Slow Train Fist!
Slow Train Fist?
You're already done for.
The energy is circling around Kumagoro's body and returning!
Harako!
Reversed rotation!
Super Rolling Thunder Express Train Fist!
The Super Express Fist, spinning in reverse,
follows the Slow Train Fist right after!
And then...
This flow is growing bigger...
It collides with the other flow near his right elbow!
He did it! Kaze's right elbow
is engulfed in a massive explosion!
What?!
1! 2! 3!
4! 5! 6!
7! 8!
9! 10!
Harako wins!
You made me go through all that trouble...
Who'd think? Harako pulls off
a massive comeback victory!
That's it! Just take care of the other two and we're done!
You'll embarrass me if you celebrate my victory
over such a trivial opponent.
Never missing a beat to boast, I see!
That was one hella big mosquito you squashed!
Kumagoro is defeated?
His weakness was his kindness.
That is, his refusal to cast the first stone.
Now, having won spectacularly in the starting round,
Class 5-1 cannot afford losing to the rest of Class 5-2!
Now, you two!
Who wants to get defeated next?
Fighter Two - Asuka Ryu!
Asuka is about 30 times stronger than Kaze Kumagoro.
Even Kumagoro gave him such a hard time,
yet despite that,
he'll now have to face a guy 30 times as strong?
Who the hell had a hard time here?!
I was just trying to liven up the match
by pretending to lose!
Look closely! This time, I won't be adapting to his strength
and will just deal with him in one fell swoop!
But Harako-kun, you've sustained serious damage already.
If it didn't cripple his sharp tongue, he'll do fine!
Harako! Just two more! We're counting on you!
Harako, do your best!
Harako is covered in bruises.
However, it doesn't feel
like his fighting spirit diminished one bit!
He seems full of confidence facing Asuka Ryu,
the second fighter of Class 2.
I'll give you a taste of it too.
My Super Powerful Deadly Punch.
Start!
Single Dragon Hair Slash Whip.
Harako falls down all of a sudden!
What the hell did Asuka do? I didn't see a thing!
Harako-kun!
Stay stro-ro-rong!
That was cool, Asuka!
Hey! Whose side are you even on?!
Fighter two of Class 5-2, Asuka Ryu wins!
Challenging the limits of his power.
This is exactly the education model I aim for.
Now, who's the second fighter of Class 1?
Yay! My turn!
Taru-chan...
Taru-chan, this isn't a game.
Yeah! Me fight.
Very well. However, don't push yourself.
Start!
Asuka's hair is standing up as if it was alive!
Asuka's weapon is his own hair.
He can freely manipulate his hair,
which is as strong and sharp as a blade.
The power that broke open Harako's brow earlier,
was just a single strand of his hair.
Wielding such a fearsome offensive ability,
he's worthy of the dragon's name.
This time, 100,000 dragons will simultaneously sprawl
from Asuka's head to face you, Taruruuto.
He'll strike you with all of them.
Even though he only needed one to defeat Harako?
Crossbow Dragon Hair Slash Whip!
A power 100,000 times more than what it took
to defeat Harako is about to attack Taruruuto!
Taru-chan!
Taruru...
Punch!
After a single punch from Taruruuto,
Asuka disappeared beyond the horizon, far outside the arena!
Class 1 fighter Taruruuto wins!
I did!
Amazing, Taruruuto!
Good job!
Now, next! Come, come!
Don't get carried away.
I'm 300 times stronger than Asuka.
That's it, Zakenja's turn!
Taru-chan...
Start!
I won't show any mercy, no matter how small you are.
Let's go!
Please stop!
Why don't you go on a date with us
instead of talking like that?
No! Someone, help!
No one can hear you here.
You'll like it babe, just don't resist!
That's enough, you bastards.
What the hell do you want?
Hm? Now that I think of it, haven't we met you before...
Wanna visit the world of pain again?
Fine by me! We get both the fun and the girls!
What just happened? That wimp kid from before...
Zakenja is the only remaining fighter for Class 2!
And he just mounted a ferocious attack on Taruruuto!
Croak, you little shit!
Sli-li-li-lip!
Come! Come, come!
Seems like I can't underestimate this little shit.
I ain't kidding around!
Nezo Fist!
Sli-li-li-lip!
Not bad, Taruruuto!
There are so many strange things about Taruruuto.
Taru-chan!
Iyona, me strong!
Worry about nothing!
Alright, now's my chance!
Watch out, Taru-chan!
Prepare to die, Taruruuto!
Evil Blade Wave!
Taruruuto!
Taruruuto's blown way out of the arena!
Bendpost!
Taruruuto!
I didn't fall down!
He disappeared from sight,
but didn't fall on the ground!
Taruruuto flew right back in, flying through the air!
It's too damn dazzling, Taruruuto!
Really?
Taruruuto! Are you actually a magician or something?
Yeah! Me the Great Magician!
So that's how it was?
And I always felt something was off about this guy.
Taru-chan was a magician?
Is that to say all the strange incidents up until now
were your work too?
Honmaru asked me not to talk about magic...
Honmaru will scold me...
But it's Honmaru's punishment for coming so late,
so we're equals here!
Everyone! I'll defeat Nezo with magic!
I'm a Great Magician!
Whatever works, just do it! Kick his ass!
Do it with your magic if you want!
Okay!
Taruru Punch!
Huh? Nezo not here.
Above!
Above?
I saw your moves from mile away!
Flying Swan Kick!
Perfect!
Way to go, Magician!
Go!
Yay!
This way, you can't dodge my punch.
That was a brilliant ploy to restrict Zakenja's movement!
Will Taruruuto win?
Hey, Taru!
The support has arrived!
Here's a special serving of Matsugoro-made takoyaki!
Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Eat 'em all to shoot your enemy to the moon!
Is... Is this what I think it is?
Taru-chan is outside the arena. Zakenja wins.
Well, friends, right on the verge of victory,
Taruruuto is disqualified for leaving the arena...
What the heck, Taru! Did I come in the middle of a match?
Yeah...
What were you thinking, huh?
You ass! Getting distracted for just some takoyaki!
Do you know what'll become of our class now?!
Oh no... Not there!
Suddenly, this is what our premature joy has come to -
the despaired Class 5-1!
You've no more fighters to put out, 5-1.
It's our victory!
Wait! Instead of Honmaru,
Jabao! You come out!
Eh? You... You can't be serious...
All the same to me.
No matter who comes out, I'll tear them apart limb by limb.
Tear... Them... Limb by limb...
Apart...
Ah! Jabao peed himself and passed out!
You're just hopeless.
That is the ultimate defeat of Jabao,
the third fighter of Class 1!
Does that mean Class 2 will be recognized
as a winner and superior?
It can't be!
You want us all in Class 5-1
to become slaves to Zakenja's gang?
Sorry, Iyona!
My sincerest apologies!
Honmaru-kun...
Nannosho's martial arts tournament is finally
about to be settled with the victory of Class 5-2!
Class 5-2, Zakenja wi...
Wait!
This voice...
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun!
Third fighter of Class 5-1 - Edojo Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Honmaru returns from a mountain retreat
exactly one month later, barely making it in time.
He stepped out as the third fighter for Class 1!
Perhaps Class 5-1 only has a tiny shred of hope left now.
The time has finally come for the final showdown of this stormy Nannosho martial arts tournament!
In the end, Nezo is insanely strong!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
I'll do something with my magic!
No... Stop it, Taru!
This is a battle between two men!
Oh... Okay, I understand.
I'm watching quietly!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Stand up, Honmaru!
Episode 58
Honmaru so cool!
You can do it!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius