Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru!
Give back my croquette!
Stop, you!
Taru!
Honmaru's mama.
Episode 24
Dreadful Grandpa
Honmaru!
Where might he be hiding here?
Honmaru! Come out now!
Where are you?
Lock on the beast!
Earth Defense Forces Commander
Edojo Honmaru...
will now put an end to Jababooey's rampage!
Who are you calling a beast?!
Engaging the enemy!
Bastard! You can only transfer "it" with a touch!
Taru! Tactical retreat!
Jababooey counterattacks!
Wait, I said!
Hey! Jabao!
Grandpa...
We need to be home for dinner soon!
Grandpa is waiting on me,
so I'm letting you go for today!
See you tomorrow!
At school, I think.
Bye-bye.
Want one?
Those guys ain't worth your trouble!
Thanks, grandpa.
Thank you for playing with my Jabao every single day!
We'll play with Jabao even more tomorrow!
I sure hope you do!
We're having croquettes today, do we?
Taru, Jabao's mom is an eldritch horror,
but his grandpa is actually very nice!
A grandpa, then...
That's right, everyone should have
at least one grandpa and grandma.
I wish we also had a nice grandpa,
who'd buy all sorts of stuff for us.
Honmaru, don't have grandpa?
Grandpa, then?
In high school, dad was a headstrong delinquent,
so parents disowned him.
And our grandpa from mom's side
also hates dad's guts.
Stop right there! I'll never hand Chizuru over to you!
Give me back my daughter!
More than ten years ago, while mom was still
in high school, dad took her away to elope with her.
And so, grandpa must still be trying to track down our dad
to take revenge on him for all these years.
But aren't you curious what our grandpa is like?
After all, you need a lot of character,
to even use firearms against our dreadful dad.
So grandpa must be even more dreadful!
Don't want to see him, Honmaru?
Maybe I do...
Seeing him sounds quite good.
Edojo Honmaru-kun, are you?
Yes! Honmaru here!
Would you mind going on a little trip with us?
Come on, this way.
Yeah!
Taru!
Did you forget what mom
always keeps saying?
When a stranger calls you by your name,
you shouldn't follow him under no pretext.
Most likely, this guy is looking to kidnap you.
Kidnap?
Yeah. Like when people snatch wealthy kids from the street
and demand some enormous money as ransom.
But Honmaru's family is not wealthy at all.
Let alone enormous money.
Right, right!
That was my point all along.
Mister, you're out of luck today!
Oh no!
Perhaps, this will make you reconsider...
Now! Run for it, Taru!
Wait me!
Hey! After them!
What do we do, Taru?
Honmaru, you'll be fine with these.
Right, Godspeed Slippers!
Egh?!
What are you waiting for?
After them, quickly!
Taru! Off we go!
Impossible...
How can a kid do that?
Keep going! After them!
⬅Hachioji50km
➡Shinjuku20km
No use, after all...
Godspeed Slippers may be divine,
but it's my mortal flesh that has to do the running!
Honmaru, we'll have wheels of our own!
Taruru! Grandma Pushchair!
You leave this to me, kids.
Here he is!
Cool!
Ride, ride, ride!
Hold tight now!
What the hell?!
That's just some shabby pushchair!
Make way!
Let us through, please!
Taru!
Hit the brakes!
Taru! Stop! Stop, I say!
Grandma Pushchair, we need to get off soon.
Gotcha!
Taru!
Honmaru, had so much fun!
Of course you did!
I feel that your stupid escapade
cost even me a few years of life, I swear.
Honey, any idea what Honmaru and Taruruuto are up to?
I'm perplexed myself.
Dinner is something those two wouldn't miss for the world.
Uh-oh.
Yes. Hello?
Yes...
Yes.
What is it, honey?
Darling! Honmaru and Taru-chan are...
What?!
Tasty, isn't it?
Delightful, grandpa!
You're the best!
You the best!
I see, I see.
Grandpa, you say your full name is Jinguji Ugunji?
That's quite the tongue-twister.
Right, Taru?
Jinguji Ugunji—
Bit it!
I see, I see.
Taru, ready?
Yeah!
Here we go!
Impressive, Taru! Nice catch!
Saw it, grandpa?
Impressive, indeed!
Kids these days never cease to amaze!
Oh my, oh my.
Me Honmaru's friend!
Me the Great Magician!
Careful! What'll we do
if he finds out who you truly are?
A magician, you say?
Very well.
I like you already!
You can tell he's mom's dad.
Never taken aback.
We got ourselves a nice grandpa of our own, Taru.
If only our dad would start getting along with him, too!
Yeah! Honmaru's grandpa to my liking, too!
Master!
A guest had arrived.
Show her in, please.
Dad! Mom even brought you along?
Honmaru's mama and papa!
Father, our parting was abrupt...
Chizuru...
Chi...
Chizuru!
I was looking for you.
Did he mistreat you, my dear?
I'm so sorry, father.
I never gave you my address.
A parent and child meet
for the first time in 13 years...
I'm so happy for you, mom!
I shan't lose you ever again.
Oh, father...
Mama not cry.
Taru-chan.
Ugunji not cry too.
Thank you.
I beg your forgiveness, father.
Father, you say?
I would sooner die,
than become a "father" to the scum like that.
How dare you snatch away my daughter,
you thief?!
Grandpa was gleeful just a moment ago!
Funnier this way!
Chizuru's upbringing
was the only thing driving my life forward!
Her marrying a man as worthless as you are
is a sacrilege against common sense!
Stop it!
I was doing my damnest to forget
that your despicable ass was ever born into our world!
But just as I thought
that you had learned some decency...
A fairy tail writer?!
Whoever writes such a sorry excuse for a picture book
deserves nothing but mockery!
Demon and the Princess
No way my daughter spends even a day more
in the company of a man that miserable and contemptible!
What is this piece of manure...
No more, father!
Mom!
Mama.
Mom...
Chizuru, your perseverance
in putting up with this man is remarkable.
You have a patience of an angel.
No need, my love.
Let him rough me up to his heart's content.
"My love?"
"My love," you say?
Bastard! Don't go pretending to be a proper husband
with another man's daughter!
so casually in front of another man's daughter!
Bastard! Don't go pretending to be a proper husband
Father, stop it!
Why, you!
Stop!
Father!
Grandpa!
Stop it, please!
You were so friendly to us two,
why are you suddenly so hostile to dad?
Taru! Do something already!
And... Taruru!
Wha... What's this? My body won't move...
What's going on?
Father, this is what Taru-chan can do with his magic.
This - Limpy-kun's buddy, Limpimpy.
If no picture at hand,
can move people while you point at them.
Oh, I see. You poor thing.
This vile man brainwashed you as well?!
It's not like that, grandpa!
Taruruuto is a real magician!
Oh, I see, I see. Through your insidious influence,
even an ordinary child can mutate into some freak!
This - body manipulating magic.
Like this.
I got it, I got it! It seems you can truly
wield some magic, after all.
I got it, alright?
Now make this magic leave me alone!
Sure!
I see. A magician! How most unusual...
Me unusual.
It worked! Grandpa's resentment subsided!
That may be so for now,
but don't think I'll ever forgive your despicable ass!
Yes!
Show this wreck of a man the door!
Sure.
Just a minute, father, please!
Let me have a say, too!
You prick! Stop resisting!
Father!
Your last chance to get out of my sight!
My daughter and my grandson
are staying here with me!
Father! Please come to your senses!
Taru!
Father!
Someone needs to stop him!
Mother!
Where could she be?
Chizuru...
Your mother died last year.
She was sure she would get to see you again someday,
and was looking forward to it.
Then, last winter...
all of a sudden, she fell ill.
Ever since you left, she was feeling lonely,
many days passed by without any progress.
And so, without ever finding out where you are...
Grandma... died?
Mom...
I don't pity myself.
However, if it's her...
Mitsuko's fate is breaking my heart.
And all of that...
All our misfortunes are his doing!
I had no idea...
The price for my happy life up until now
has been a grudge amassing in other people!
Taru! Use some magic to reconcile everyone!
Got it! Taruru... oh?
Honmaru, when in doubt,
ask Tama-chan for advice.
Good call! Tama-chan, we need your wisdom!
Give me just a moment...
I know, Taru-chan.
Itako-chan might help you now.
Right!
Thank you, Tama-chan.
Itako, Ittaro, Taruru and ru...
Taruru!
It's you, darling? It's you, isn't it?
It's been half a year.
Are you doing well?
Mitsuko! But how...
Mother...
This is supposed to be grandma?
Isn't she a bit young for that?
This - Spiritual TV-phone,
allowing to talk to the otherworld.
Hello-hello Itako-chan.
There's no age in otherworld.
Darling, my life here has been full of delights.
Don't you worry for me.
Instead, if you really want to make me happy,
leave behind your fixation on revenge
and learn to forgive people around you.
Shogunosuke-san meant no harm.
I want you to start getting along with him.
All our efforts should be directed
on making everyone get along!
Only then you can ensure that one day
you and me will once again be reunited up here.
Mother...
Grandma...
I got it. Forgive...
I will forgive, Mitsuko.
Chizuru, Honmaru,
I have no doubt you guys will live a happy life.
Remember that I'm always watching over you.
Mother!
Mitsuko!
Grandpa. This ain't as magnificent a feast
as they serve at your place,
but you still shouldn't hesitate to eat.
Delicious!
Chizuru, you've become infinitely better at cooking!
Honmaru mama's cooking is superb!
Glad you liked it. Thanks.
Agreed. Our mom's cooking is unrivaled.
Oh, my!
There's still some tension between them.
Well, whatever!
It's snowing, snowing!
Hurry up and let's go outside!
Come on! Don't you know it's cold outside, Taru?
Sorry, Honmaru.
Then, take this.
Thank you!
Gentlewarm-kun, then?
The name is kinda self-explanatory.
Yeah!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Dangerous Snowball Fight!
Children are as free as the wind!
Playing outside all togetheru-ru!
Episode 25
Dangerous Snowball Fight!?
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius