Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
So hot, Honmaru!
Yeah. At least we'll be able to go home soon.
Tomorrow, the pool finally opens!
Don't you dare forget your swimsuits!
Episode 43
It's Summer! The Pool is Open
They sure look surprised.
Having been impressed so deeply,
I don't think they'll forget.
At last!
To the pool! The pool!
Those who forget their swimsuits
will be forced to swim naked.
I'd sure fancy Iyona-chan forgetting her swimsuit!
That's some boldness!
You sick weirdo!
We can see you're aroused, Honmaru!
What's this horn dog thinking about again?
Taru!
Iyona-chan, what kind of swimsuit will you wear tomorrow?
Isn't everyone supposed to come
in the standard school swimsuit?
No use trying to excuse yourself, Honmaru!
That's not it!
It's just that you can swim faster
when you're naked, rather than in a swimsuit!
Right, teacher?
That's true.
What a strange excuse.
How do you like my great encyclopedic knowledge?
Leave it to me in all swimming-related activities!
What swimming do you want us to leave to you,
you brick-like kind of swimmer?
Humans are swimming creatures!
Dad!
Oh! Honmaru, where are you going?
After that, I've been so scared of water,
I couldn't even wash my face!
Honmaru?
Right, right! Before, whenever Honmaru needed to swim,
he'd start sniveling and crying!
He's too scared to even put his head underwater!
You idiots!
Last summer, I was already able
to go underwater for 20 seconds!
And I've made great progress ever since!
When you're in the presence of myself, the World Junior
1000-km Long Distance Swimming record retainer,
please refrain from discussing such amateurish topics.
So what's that to me?!
Don't make fun of me for beating my aquaphobia
so I could go underwater for 20 seconds!
When I get serious, I can blow even you out of the water!
Honmaru. Honmaru!
Is that last year's...
Why would you even keep something like that?!
That's because...
I like my little Honmaru-kun.
So I have your photo
pressed against my skin at all times.
Don't get burned, Honmaru!
Check this out, everyone!
Iyona-chan! Iyona-chan, you should see this too!
Iyona-chan...
On the verge of crying, drooling and whimpering!
Oh, so disgusting! Ah, ain't that embarrassing?
But he's doing his best.
Iyona-chan...
Okay, let's call it here!
Honmaru-kun, even if you can't swim right now,
as long as you keep trying, you'll be alright. Okay?
Yes!
Tomorrow, I'll be sure to leave everyone gaping!
Good luck, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan's such a nice girl!
For that alone, I'll do my best!
Honmaru!
Alright, Taru!
Special training?
Yeah!
Honmaru, you can do it!
You can do it, can do it! Honmaru, Honmaru!
Honmaru, amazing!
Held out for 25 seconds this time!
Oh, that's it! Record updated!
With "successes" like this, when it comes
to swimming tomorrow, you'll sink like a brick.
Sister!
Special swimming training, huh?
I'll lend you a hand too.
Ria...
Hello, everyone.
I'm Water Mi-chan. Nice to meet you!
Hello!
Llo!
Mi-chan,
can we count on your assistance
in Honmaru's special training?
Sure!
I'd be happy to help.
Ria, what kind of special training
can we conduct inside a tiny a Mi-chan?
Well, you'll see.
I'm starting, then.
Trunsform!
Mi-chan big!
Now, now, Honmaru-kun.
Let's begin the special training.
Honmaru-kun, don't you know how to swim?
Oh my!
I'm taking this special training because I can't swim!
Makes sense. Sorry.
Please help, Mi-chan!
Fine...
Honmaru, you eat this.
Crawl Cake-kun here!
Eep! The cake is talking!
Honmaru, if you eat this guy,
he'll become your swimming coach.
But I don't wanna eat no talking thing!
You don't wanna eat me?!
Delicious!
I swallowed it without thinking!
Taru, what's going on?
I can't stop my body from moving in strange ways!
When you eat Crawl Cake-kun, you can't move your body
in any other way than crawl swimming.
Exactly!
You can only turn your head for breathing!
Your hands will also only make perfect strokes.
That voice I hear from inside my body...
Is that you, Crawl Cake-kun?
Exactly!
Having become Honmaru's blood and flesh,
I'm continuing the coaching!
Fine! Let's start, Honmaru-kun.
Go, Honmaru!
I'll adjust the water flow to match Honmaru's speed.
Doing good, Honmaru!
If you overstress your current form and put too much strength
in the wrong places, you'll arrive to a cramp!
So cruel!
You can do it!
Let me make swimming a little easier for you!
Swimming is just not my thing, after all!
I wanna stop already...
Some air!
You can do it, Honmaru!You can do it, Honmaru!
You can do it, Honmaru.
You can do it!
Okay, I get it!
First, extend your hands forward
and begin paddling, starting with the right!
That's good. Don't rush!
Don't rush, Honmaru!
Take wider kicks!
Normalize your breathing!
Get used to that feeling of pulling water towards yourself!
It's true! I'm starting to understand!
I see. So that's how you wanted me to swim, Crawl Cake-kun?
Huh?
Crawl Cake-kun?
Hey!
Honmaru, my magic wears off in ten minutes.
You've been swimming for way longer already.
What?
I see. So I'm swimming with my own strength now?
Yeah! Honmaru became a swimming creature!
Yes! I can finally swim on my own!
Thank you, Crawl Cake-kun!
Thank you!
Now then, how about we take it to the next step?
Sha-sha-sha... Shark!
This would increase the speed significantly.
Don't die, Honmaru!
Now you're clearly taking it too far!
Yay, we're swimming!
It's a butterfly!
And now - a backstroke!
It's like he's sliding on the water!
A quick turn from the back!
How can you even be that fast with just breaststrokes?
Behold! Here is my legendary Flying Fish Turn!
Young master, you covered 100 m in 52.34 seconds.
It'll do for now.
Harako-kun.
Ah, I appreciate it.
Thank you, beautiful teacher!
Today, once again, more beautiful than ever!
Please stop...
Insolent broad! Do you have any idea
who you're dealing with?!
My student, as far as I'm concerned.
I explicitly warned everyone before
to not enter the water without permission.
I am tempering myself on a daily basis!
There's no way I'd get a heart attack from it!
I'm not here to give special treatment
to any single student.
What did you say?!
You'll be out of a job by tonight,
should I ask my father for it!
Go ahead.
No place in the world would wanna take you in!
Gramps! At least say something!
This one's a lost cause for you, Young Master.
Eat this, you dumbass!
Well then, because it's only the opening day,
let's just have some fun playing.
We'll do!
Teacher! Wouldn't there be a swimming duel?
Usually, your duels only disunite the class.
Harako! Let's play and have fun!
Are you doing this to take vengeance on me somehow?
Not at all.
It's universally undisputed
that you have impressive abilities,
but we shouldn't hurry that much.
Now, everyone, what should we play?
Tag!
Ah... How about something like cops and thieves?
Oh! The one where you can save the prisoner?
Yes, sounds good. Let's do just that!
Yeah!
Tsk. So damn childish. I've no interest in that.
Hey! Honmaru and Taru are tagged!
Yay! I'll pass the tag right away!
Taru! In this kind of tag game,
you can only pass it after you catch everyone!
Eh?
Those who get touched by the cop
hold their hands together to this railing.
Then, if someone else touches this railing,
we have to start collecting everyone anew.
Well, long story short, you just need
to touch everyone who comes close to here.
Meanwhile, I'll go catch everyone!
Okay!
Well then, let's start!
Alright...
Watch out for aquaphobic Honmaru!
If we all start splashing water on him,
he'll cry and vomit like last year!
Let's go!
Get this!
It's nothing!
The hell?!
Oh! Honmaru overcame his aquaphobia!
Touch, touch, touch, touch, touch!
What?
Is it really the same Honmaru-kun
who used to flounder and whimper in the water?
He's swimming now!
Touch!
Touch! Touch!
Touch! Touch! Touch!
Impressive, Honmaru-kun!
But when did you learn to swim so well?
Watch out! Honmaru can swim like a bat out of hell!
That's the ultimate feeling!
In the end, Sister Ria and Taru's special training
brought amazing results!
And all thanks to Crawl Cake and Mi-chan!
Thank you, guys!
Honmaru, you've gotten quite good, dincha?
Ijigawa, you won't stand a chance either.
Try to catch up with me, if you can!
Sorry to break it to you, Honmaru,
but swimming's my strong suit.
I can't believe I'm getting serious
about racing brick-like swimmer Honmaru!
He won't catch up with me in this life!
There, touched.
Didn't I tell you?
I had great coaches for my special training!
Though it was mainly thanks to the shark
that I became so fast.
Honmaru, you truly are astounding.
Whatever that special training of yours was,
you're nowhere near as messy as you were a year ago.
Honmaru, I actually kinda...
Iyona-chan!
Ah! Honmaru-kun is coming!
Iyona-chan...
That was impressive, Honmaru-kun.
But you won't catch me!
I'll catch you, Iyona-chan!
He's the worst!
I should start picking on him even more now!
C'mere, you!
Honmaru-kun!
Gotcha!
Got caught, after all.
Your special training must've been incredible, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan's soft...
Honmaru amazing! Caught so many!
Shit... I can't let Honmaru have all the fun to himself!
I can also get handsy with Iyona-san
under the pretense of saving her.
Turns out a game of tag can be good too.
Gramps!
Roger.
Hey, kid!
Kiddo?
Did you know it's takoyaki day again?
Come. Come-come.
Takoyaki!
Alright, now's my chance!
Ah? Harako-kun!
There it is! Iyona-san's chest.
And there, those tender, virgin...
Oh, Harako amazing speed.
Mosesu-su-su!
Ah? Harako-kun disappeared.
What is he, a submarine?
Touch!
We did it! We caught everyone!
I won't forgive you, Taru!
It was supposed to be a duel!
Can't you even play tag honestly?
Hey! Get back here!
Looks fun! A duel!
I guess we've no choice.
The game of tag was brought to a conclusion already,
so you can have your duel.
However, competing seriously with Taru-chan
and calling it a duel... Harako-kun sure is still a child.
Honmaru-kun, let's cheer Taru-chan up!
Yes, Iyona-chan...
Everyone ready?
Yes!
Yeah!
Ready...
Start!
I ain't losing!
You lose!
What the?!
What is this enormous leg strength in a baby?
Impressive jump!
Taru-chan, you can do it!
Iyona-chan...
Gramps!
Yes. I got you covered, Young Master.
Necessary steps have already been taken.
What happened with Taru-chan?
Huh? What's going on?
We've installed a transparent board on your track, Taruru-kun.
Hurry, Young Master. Now's your chance.
Smell you later!
For some reason, I can't pass through!
Here comes my victory!
Stre-re-re-retch!
Huh?
Iyona-san's chest, Iyona-san's chest, Iyona-san's chest...!
That's strange. Those last 5 m feel extraordinarily long!
Iyona-san!
Young Master!
I can't move forward!
Would this duel end with a draw?
Iyona-chan...
Go cool down some!
Damn you, Harako!
He's had enough of us leaving him out of the conversation,
so he cut the power to my house!
That's going way too far!
Don't get mad, Honmaru.
I quite like this kind of life.
We can do just fine without electricity.
Maybe you think so now, Taru,
but what about that tomorrow's program?
Don't you wanna see it?
Episode 44
Please, Lightning-sama
Me wanna see it!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Please, Lighting-sama!
Pru-ru-retty please!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius