The long-awaited match:
Edojo Honmaru vs. Harako Tsutomu.
The fight for the World Junior Wrestling Championship
has been going for 40 minutes. One match!
Which of them will the goddess of victory smile on?
Honmaru, you can do it!
The victory is mine!
Harako Special Atomic Needle Bar!
Honmaru! Remember the special training!
I got you!
Really? It's nothing!
I don't think so!
Magical Taruruuto-kun: Movie 2
Burn! The Magical Battle of Friendship
1!
2!
3!
Honmaru's knockout win!
Nice, Honmaru!
Amazing, Honmaru!
Honmaru so cool!
How about it?
That was impressive, Honmaru-kun.
Harako-kun too!
But I was the one who won, Iyona-chan!
Because Harako-kun was cool too!
Yeah! Harako looked good also.
I see. It was thanks to Harako being there
that I managed to discover this incredible power in me!
Harako! I was blown away by your techniques today!
It's a bit hard to get on the level of someone
who has no real ability, just luck.
What?
Harako...
Honmaru and Harako friends!
Me friends with everyone too!
He even managed to get me serious.
This Edojo Honmaru is by no means
a mere elementary school student.
A friend, huh?
What's wrong? Something's stuck in there?
Hot-hot-hot-hot-hot!
Why, you...
A cheap-ass shower in the backroom
of some elementary school...!
How dare you make fun of me?!
That got me seriously mad!
I'll remind you of your social standing now!
Hey, Harako!
You're not here?
Oh no!
He went home already?
He sure is hasty.
Them seeing me in a pathetic state like this now
would mean a stain of shame for the rest of my life!
Shit, what do I do now?
Slippery!
Hey, Taru!
Why are you in such a rush?
Sorry, Honmaru.
Feels nice!
Today as well, thanks to your magic,
I could overcome Harako! Thanks a bunch.
He said "magic?"
He's still so childish.
It's true. The fact I could beat a guy as powerful as Harako
in boxing, skiing, and sumo
was thanks to your special training with magic.
I really appreciate it.
Yeah! Me the Great Great Great Great Magician Taruruuto!
Alright, wanna get some takoyaki?
For the Great Great Great Magician Taruruuto-kun!
Right! Going to takoyaki shop with Honmaru!
So that's what really happened?
Edojo Honmaru, you bastard...
After all, I thought it was strange since the day we first met...
A wimp such as him isn't supposed to be standing as equals with me,
but it was magic! It was all the works of magic!
Exactly. My wealth, prestige, intellect, stamina,
as well as this sexy body -
without having any of that, he always managed to best me,
with the help of just one thing, namely - magic all along!
Honmaru, you shithead!
If I'd have understood that sooner, you'd be six feet...
It's a misunderstanding, friends! I was just...
Pervert!
I'm not! It's a misunderstanding!
Young Master, as per your request, we have secured
various treasured writings on magic from all over the world.
Alright, unload it!
Prague's monastery crypt, Cairo's Dead Sea museum,
the secret basement of London's museum of Great Britain, as well as...
Alright! Put the books separately there!
Letters are over here!
However, all of those were hidden
and well guarded treasures of the world
which resulted in our operatives
risking their lives to obtain it.
I've seen it too! Seen it all! Help me!
This book is useless too.
Dammit...
There must be a book somewhere
that can summon a real wizard.
Is this...
I wanna be cheating too!
And so,
summer vacation finally starts tomorrow,
so the last homeroom session of this month will be free time.
If there's anything anyone wants to discuss...
Ladies and gentlemen!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Harako Tsutomu's Great Miracle Magic Show!
When did I...
Thus, what you'll have the pleasure of witnessing now
is the star of the World Junior Magicians Contest Grand Prix
Harako Tsutomu demonstrating to you his magnificent magic.
The great sorcery that can make
any wish come true on the spot!
Hi!
Now then, those lucky enough to get their wish come true...
would be the three chosen by these cards!
Got it!
Like, any wish at all?
Comes true? For real?
And now, just say openly what you want.
Make wishes one at a time, in turns.
I'm wishing first! I want a hamburger!
An easy order.
Wow!
I want Super Micon Quest V
whose sales weren't launched yet!
A dress like that of Cinderella!
I don't want anything to do with this.
Bastard... What do you want?
To ensure that you don't act cocky in front of me ever again.
Think you can make me?
Are you kidding me?!
Only one thing left.
Do the same to Honmaru.
I can see it already!
That must be Harako Land!
We're here, Taru!
Aren't we lucky to have Harako invite us here?
Yeah!
And more importantly...
Looking at Iyona-chan wearing that swimsuit...
It's the best thing ever!
The sea here is extraordinarily clean, Honmaru-kun!
Wanna swim!
Umi-chan! Let's play together!
Alright!
What an elegant vacation...
To have this Harako Land reserved just for us.
Amazing! It carried us all the way here!
Let's take a break and have some juice, Iyona-chan!
I suppose.
Juice! Juice! Juice!
Oh?
Rui-chan, why did you climb up there?
Humph! I'm sunbathing!
It's none of your business, I do it wherever!
Iyona-chan! I'll go buy you some juice! Wait a moment!
Sure, I appreciate it.
It's great!
Juice, juice!
Good, here's your refill.
This is amazing too!
That girl...
Nusiad-san.
Madam is a distant relative of Harako-san,
who used to live away in a foreign country.
Harako-san... you say?
Wow! Thanks!
Well, go ahead, Honmaru-san.
Iyona-san's share is here too.
Thank you, Nusiad-san.
How are you finding it, Iyona-san?
My Harako Land.
The ultimate resort island,
equipped with state of the art equipment,
to complement this wonderful scenery.
Even this small island can be turned into a wonderful resort
in the hands of our Harako Conglomerate.
Moreover, the development is still in progress,
to make it the world's best resort island.
The sea is beautiful.
The sea, as well as the trees and grass on this island...
Really, I think they were the happiest
the way nature created them, untouched.
Iyona-chan! I got your juice!
Thank you! I'll be there now!
No need, Iyona-chan! We'll get down instead.
What an interesting guy.
Cute!
Lemme lemme, lemme...
Honmaru-kun!
Ah! Don't come near!
Iyona-chan!
What are you doing, Honmaru-kun?
Stop it, Honmaru-kun!
My, seems like I came just in time.
Harako-kun? Why did Honmaru-kun...
Whatever it was, he's a terrible person.
What could he have wanted from such a cute puppy?
I think...
Harako-kun, I was...
wrong about you.
I'm sorry.
Well, let me accompany you, Iyona-san.
Honmaru! Are you okay?
Honmaru... Hey! Hey!
Right! Where's Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan! Where did you go?
Honmaru, thing is...
Eh? Harako what?
It can't be! Iyona-chan must've actually been wrong about me!
Where are you, Iyona-chan?
Ah! There she is! Iyona-chan!
Hey! Hey! You gotta hear me out!
Iyona-chan...
Ah! She's hopelessly mad at me!
What do I do now?
Honmaru, use Yahoonest Feelings-kun.
If you pierce her heart with this,
Iyona will become honest!
Okay! That's one way to make her listen to me!
Huh? What's going on?
Iyona doesn't have a heart?
Tama-chan, what should we do in a case like this?
Let's see. Wouldn't it be a good idea to use Dream Magic?
Yeah! Dream Magic.
You touch the forehead of a sleeping person
with a piece of pork fillet.
Then you just eat Dreamen with that piece of fillet
to get inside this person's mind.
Went in with a swoosh!
Is this what Iyona-chan's mind is like inside?
That's definitely Iyona-chan's!
What a beautiful mind picture!
Honmaru, over there!
Inside her mind, Iyona is thinking about Harako.
We're a nuisance?
It can't be!
That's a lie! A mistake!
Something is terribly wrong here!
Honmaru, wake up!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru! Honmaru!
What's this?
Thank you for waiting!
Harako Tsutomu is making his entrance!
Wow! You're so cool!
Tonight's main event,
at last, the match is about to begin!
How the hell did I get here?
Honmaru, turn your head!
Honmaru!
That hurt, Harako!
What are you playing?
Kickboxing again?
The ultimate showdown of the world's martial arts!
Kicking, throwing, punching - anything would do! But...
Not magic!
What?
Let's do it, Honmaru!
Iyona-chan...
Taru!
Honmaru!
I need more
screen time!
I will also
return soon.
Ni
Taruruuto, let me give you a wonderful present.
A collar that chicks will fall in love with.
If you can't cast spells, you can't use magic.
Honmar...
Stop it!
Good choice!
This way, he can't use any magic.
He can't come to your rescue either.
Harako, you jerk! Why? Why are you doing this?
I've had enough of you making fun of me up to now, Honmaru!
In all the matches we've held before,
you always emerged victorious!
I admired it. I strove to become like you.
However, you cheated! You did it using magic!
All your previous victories
were achieved through magic! And I was naive!
There was no realistic way for criminal scum like you
to be standing out against me!
Harako, that's not what you think! I was...
Shut up!
I must be the only man able to use magic!
I'll beat you now, and then I'll get whatever I want in this world!
I see...
Iyona-chan is also affected by Harako's magic...
Taru... I'm sorry, Taru. I can't do anything on my own...
Take a look, Taruruuto.
Somehow, I'm sure even this Honmaru
regrets ever becoming friends with a brat like you.
After all, trying to become friends
with humans is a fool's errand.
Using them is enough.
You'd better remember it now.
I lost...
Hopelessly...
I can't move a limb!
Is this how I'm gonna die?
Helpless to save Taru or anyone at all?
It's just as Harako said.
On my own, without Taru's magic, I can't do anything.
Honmaru. Hang on, Honmaru!
Who's that...
Did I just hear someone?
It's me, Honmaru.
No way...
Exactly. It's us.
We've all have been thrown away
as trash and junk after we became useless.
But we're still alive.
Honmaru, you are different from us.
I'm sure you still have friends who really need you.
However, if you give up even on yourself,
what should they do?
Will you also throw your friends away?
Honmaru…
Even without Taru's magic, I can still hear clearly
what those various appliances are telling me.
That's right, Taru...
Taru must still be waiting for me.
Even when we're apart,
we're always together,
because we're friends!
I will save Taru, Iyona-chan and everyone else!
I will…
Never give up!
It's finally here.
The day when I'll become the man
with the most power in the world.
Entirely so, Harako-sama.
Everything is ready now,
so we just have to wait for the right time.
With this, I'll never let the scum like Honmaru
get the better of me again.
Harako!
What did you do to Taru?
Honmaru!
Let Taru go!
Taru!
The time is approaching!
Honmaru!
You absolute waste of a man!
What can you do without magic?
Wanna be torn to shreds again?
Harako!
Take this!
Honmaru!
Incorpore-re-real, Honmaru!
I'm so glad!
That's right. Taru, this is not the time to rejoice!
We gotta help Iyona-chan and the others!
Nusiad...
Where did you go?
Why did you leave me...
You left me when the time came to finish Honmaru off...
That was not what we agreed upon!
Okay, now only Korekiyo and Jabao left.
Yeah!
Give me more power!
Give me power, Nusiad!
Nusiad!
The time is ripe! Let's make your wish come true.
Pretty...
Nusiad!
what did you do to Harako?
Merely made his wish come true.
To become the king of the world.
However, the one using his body will be me -
the Great Demon King Zolmud-sama.
What?
Cool!
Harako Tsutomu's body becomes one
with Zolmud-sama's mind.
The Great Demon King is thus resurrected!
Harako…
Corporeal, for the first time in ages!
The ultimate subjugation of the humans,
the earth and everything else is imminent!
Big!
What's that thing?
Run away, you guys!
Yay!
At last, Zolmud-sama is revived!
Oh, how long have I been waiting for this day!
I couldn't wait to get it done!
We can't leave him like that!
Someone's gotta stop him!
Alright! Inflatable Muscles!
Damn it...
Are you stupid?
Ain't gonna work, after all!
Honmaru!
That - Great Demon Lord Zolmud, but also Harako!
Harako's heart remains inside!
I see. The body didn't become entirely Zolmud's.
But what do we do about it?
Taru-chan!
With Yahoonest Feelings-kun,
you can break through to Harako's real heart!
Harako's heart?
Yeah! Will use Dream Magic too!
Why, you!
Let's get right in!
That cocoon over there is Harako's true heart.
Honmaru, Yahoonest Feelings-kun!
Yeah!
What's this? Looks a lot like a fresh and tasty human soul!
Lick-lick-lick!
Tastes terrible!
Terrible
You think so?
Alright, I'll do it now!
Did it!
Tastes bad!
You don't say?
What's wrong?
Why isn't 't he becoming honest?
Destruction! No mercy! Hatred!
Let's make this world a thorough mess!
We've been waiting, Zolmud-sama!
At last, this world shall become yours!
Destruction!
Zolmud-sama?
Ah! Get off me!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Come on! We bought you some time!
You guys...
Let's move!
Honmaru,
You really thought botched magic like that
would work on me in this state?
Harako!
It's only a matter of time before this world becomes mine!
Becomes all mine, you get it?
Honmaru!
Taru!
Caught you... Caught you right here!
Damn... All is lost...
Honmaru!
Make Harako's heart come out by itself!
Honmaru is friends with Harako!
So save it as your friend's heart!
Harako!
Come out, Harako!
We need you to wake up and come out of here!
Someone like you can definitely do it!
Useless!
What's that putrid smell?
What's wrong, Harako?
Was it really your wish to become a monster?
I thought better of you!
Come on, you Dino-Mugged Grandpa!
What?
I've no need to negotiate with the scum
who cheated using magic!
But I still underwent a severe special training!
I didn't use magic to win over you!
I'm free to use magic however I please!
So you really are fine with turning into a monster?
Into a creature that's nothing like Harako Tsutomu?
Is that still okay with you?!
Ah, I heard you! Just do whatever you want!
That's 'cause you're too scared to face me in another fair battle!
But you can't win through becoming a monster!
This is cowardice, not victory!
Shut your damn trap!
Without resorting to someone else's power,
with my own blood and sweat,
I built the strongest man in the world - Harako Tsutomu!
Yes! Let's have a battle, Honmaru!
Sure!
Honmaru and Harako's hearts became one.
This means Zolmud's bogus heart lost!
Why is this happening?
Seems like it's over.
What's going on with this place?
This island is about to sink. Honmaru, hurry!
That's bad!
What is it, Honmaru? We have to hurry.
Taru! Fly ahead without me and save everyone else!
And you, Honmaru?
I'll come later, together with Harako.
Okay!
You guys!
Taru-chan!
Follow after me!
Alright, this way!
Harako!
Honmaru?
Everyone, hurry up aboard!
But who in the world can sail it?
Just leave it to me! Even I can handle this kind of ship.
Amazing, Korekiyo!
What is it?
There's no fuel.
We're starting!
Which one will get to the boat first? Let's have a duel!
Cocky idiot!
Before you is the winner
of the World Junior Swimming Championship.
How can I ever lose?
Honmaru, faster!
Do your best, you two!
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Puff-puff, I'm swelling and turning rounder
Magicians really do exist, they're real!
Where will we go today and what'll we do?
No need to worry about anything, nobody is perfect
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius
Bye-bye! See you again!
The End