Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 3
Dangerous Transfer Student
This should be here, I think...
Honmaru, let's go play around together.
Let's go.
Hey, Honmaru!
You're distracting me, Taruruuto.
My plan for today was to finish building this fellow.
I don't have the time to play around with you.
That so?
So, so.
You'll have to excuse me.
Guess I can go look around Honmaru's house.
Finally finished!
What do you say, Taruruuto?
Cool, isn't it?
Honmaru?
Honmaru? Honmaru, is that you?
How odd.
Is it just my imagination?
Taruruuto?
Honmaru, I knew it was you all this time!
My bad, ma.
Even having grown so big,
still dependent on mom's attention, are you?
Hey!
Highway on-ramp⬆
Central Expressway: 2.5km
You can't be doing that, Taruruuto.
How am I to explain it
if mom finds out about you?
You'll get driven out.
Sorry, Honmaru.
Can't have even a minute for myself.
At least, don't vex me now while I'm taking you out for a walk.
Takoyaki
Hey there!
What's this thing?
Never heard of Takoyaki?
Takoyaki? Are they good?
Putting it mildly!
They're so good,
you just keep eating until you burst.
Here.
Yeah, bring it, bring it!
Are you listening, Taru...
Taruruuto!
You sure have some iron stomach there...
Told you it's good!
Taruruuto! You need money to eat this!
What money?
Honmaru, I love takoyaki so much!
Honmaru, that looks like fun.
What's this about?
Some festival?
They say the heir to the Harako Conglomerate
is visiting the city!
No wonder they arranged a welcoming parade.
Ladies and gentlemen, in lieu of empty salutations,
please accept these modest souvenirs from Young Master!
Present
What is it, just a plaid?
It has an embroidery of gold!
Phew! Just some indifferent snob
bragging about his deep pockets.
Let's go, Taruruuto!
Honmaru, Iyona also came.
She really did!
To think I'd meet such a cutie girl in a city this mucky...
Pick her up.
As you wish!
You there, pretty girl.
To commemorate our fruitful meeting,
won't you join me for a drive?
Now, get aboard.
With pleasure!
Iyona-chan, have a ride with us too!
I was not talking to you!
Come, m'lady.
Well, I'll probably pass this time.
Don't be shy, Iyona-chan!
Iyona?
Such a piquant name to ideally match
her stunning picture.
My passion is ever-growing.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry after her.
Okay...
Young Master!
This way!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Now, get in.
No need to be shy.
Wait!
What are you trying to do to Iyona-chan?
Merely invited her to hang out during a drive.
That's right!
Nobody asked you to tag along!
Ijigawa!
Driving looks fun, Honmaru.
We should join them, too! Too!
Taru-chan?
Sup, Iyona.
Get your hands away! I can't see! Stop it!
Doesn't seem too difficult.
I can cover for you!
Wait, wait! Stop yanking the wheel!
If you need to ask someone out,
why not grab just Ijigawa?
That would be a win-win for everyone!
I'm privileged enough to choose!
Wait a moment there, you two!
After Young Master, this way!
Can't you steer with some more sense?
Taruruuto!?
Me the driver.
Stre-re-re-retch!
Huh?
Highway entrance
Central Expressway: 5km
Try to drive safer, damn it!
What happened to my real driver?
Gimme the wheel! Gimme it now!
Just hit the brakes already!
Can't reach.
Forget it! It's too late now!
Taruruuto...
The art of squeezing thru-ru-ru-rough!
What just happened?
At least we're safe, I guess.
Good job with that one, Taruruuto.
When driving with magic, have nothing to worry!
Well said, too!
But still, won't you mind looking forward?
Drop the speed
Taruruuto!
Board Pen Magic!
Taruru, Taruru.
Taruru!
Just let me handle this!
Like this!
Let's do it!
Soaring!
Perfect landing.
Iyona, have no worries.
You really saved us all!
Great job, Taru-chan!
When I'm around, you're safe and sound.
That tickles!
You there! Only looking to stick yourself under
someone's butt, as usual, you perverted thing!
Ijigawa... Let me...
Meeting Iyona-san was no accident,
but instead, a fate's great device!
The history will remember our love
that is only starting now!
What the hell? Let me go!
You can just hang there until the end of times,
for all history cares!
Hey, sicko, can't get enough of feeling
someone's butt on you, do you?
Why don't you get up yourself?
Take it easy, Taru-chan!
You're the only one
who made it out unscathed, Taru!
Will Taruruuto really manage
to sit tight at home?
I'm worried.
Who did that?
Japanese test
Edojo Honmaru
Why, you...
You again, Ijigawa!
Jolly time Honmaru having at school.
And I'm bored here.
Harako Tsutomu
Before we begin today's class,
I want everyone to meet our new transfer student.
Everyone get along, okay?
What kind of guy is he?
I'm excited.
Harako-kun.
Him again!
The name is Harako Tsutomu.
Often being mistaken for a college student,
I have today been admitted into your grade school.
Let it be no secret,
my impeccable appearances
are complemented by a shrewd mind.
A prodigy in every sport.
From his President's chair at Harako Conglomerate,
my dad manipulates Japan from the shadows.
He's so cool!
And handsome!
If you have a problem you want sorted,
that is my field of expertise.
Nice to meet you.
Let's see, where do we seat you...
Never mind it.
That mental strain is in vain.
My seat has long been predefined, beautiful sis.
If I were you, I'd drop that "sis" at once!
Sure, beautiful teacher.
This jerk has an eye on Iyona-chan!
When the weed grass, such as you all, proliferates right next
to one exquisite flower in a full bloom, I just can't stand it.
You think so too, don't you?!
Yeah...
As though guided by the invisible thread of fate,
we've met again, it seems.
Please accept this as a mark of our reunion.
Who are you calling the weed grass?!
Somebody has to put an end to this soap opera!
What a cocky moron!
A fine fragrance.
Harako-kun!
That's it! Meet the sensei's spanking!
This sweet scent of danger is enough to spellbind
any man in the world, beautiful teacher.
You think so?
That way is the infirmary,
and then we have the staff room here.
Iyona-chan, let me show him around, too!
Then it'll be my turn next!
Look, look, Iyona-chan doesn't seem
to mind his attention either!
Say, what will you do, Honmaru-kun?
Iyona-san, today after school,
won't you mind me walking you home?
It's unfair if you only take Iyona-chan!
Your turn will come too.
You prick...
To hell with it!
What is it you need at such a moment?
I was asking Kawai Iyona-san's permission
to walk her home.
I'm not letting you pull
any more of these cocky escapades!
I challenge you to a duel, Harako Tsutomu!
The one who wins, walks Iyona-chan home!
What a desperado one must be
to challenge me to a duel!
The deed akin to facing the king of beasts
with nothing but your bare hands.
Shut up!
Alright!
During the next PE class,
we'll compare our strengths with a shot put!
That would be our duel!
A move worthy of Jabao-san.
Bringing the game to your home field.
A guy who could rival Jabao-san, a 5 times in a row
boys' champion of shot put, has not yet been born!
Very well. I will rise to the challenge.
Wait a minute!
I can't allow such a competition!
Iyona-san, leave your worries aside.
There is no way I can lose to such a wimp.
You what?
So, shall we be on our way?
I gotta see it!
Me too!
I bet my breakfast milk on Jabao!
I'm with Harako!
Hey, wait for me!
I'm competing too.
Wait for us!
You want what again?
A duel with Iyona-chan as a prize?
Sensei, let me have this one duel
and I will never ask for anything more!
Teacher, would you be so kind as to attend
to my only request?
You two...
Have had a great idea!
Let's do it.
Look at this femme fatale go!
Time to challenge your strength's boundaries!
With our own hands, we'll shape
the new progressive model of education.
What is wrong with them all?
But can I really pose any challenge
with a body so physically underdeveloped?
At this rate, Iyona-chan will end up going home
with Harako or Jabao courting her...
Honmaru!
You won't lose, Honmaru!
Taruruuto?
Bold words to say,
but where will I get the power for this?
I just want a super power!
That I can.
Not the time to be playing around, Taruruuto!
Wait, what?
Muscles appearing out of thin air?
Inflatable Muscles-kun can make you
as strong as a burudozer.
For real?
Let's see.
For real! Super-strong!
My power has not yet lost to anyone!
Jabao-san - 18 meters!
No kidding around, Jabao-san!
You broke the record for the boys division once again!
How was it? Saw it, Harako?
Just as I thought,
you're nothing more than a musclebrain.
The goddess of victory never smiles
upon those not fighting for love.
Love is transient, for that reason,
love is the most priceless of treasures.
In his quest for love, Harako Tsutomu devoted his life
to Kawai Iyona-chan, whose beauty dwarfs that of roses,
and now he is putting it all,
his heart and soul into this one peerless ball,
Special Bright Trick Thunder Shot!
Harako-kun - 58 meters!
There! The current Olympic record
is by a long shot over!
Harako Tsutomu wins!
I don't feel like my usual self.
Must have gotten carried away for a bit.
Now, shall we head home, Iyona-san?
Wait a minute!
Don't put on airs after throwing a ball
that was all bragging and no action, Harako!
The Miracle Ball from Honmaru-sama you're about to see
will speak louder than all your boasting!
Honmaru-kun?
Your demeanor is suddenly so valiant!
And your body seems to have grown too!
Honmaru-kun, you also wish to participate? Very well.
Don't lose, Honmaru!
This is something only Honmaru can do!
The ball... Where. Where?
Where did it fly off to?
Sure you threw it this way, Honmaru?
Don't be stupid!
Didn't you see my Miracle Shot just now?
Honmaru-kun!
Now I see! This guy just threw it straight upwards!
What a doofus!
Harako-kun wins!
It was the victory of love, Iyona-chan.
Don't give up, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru, not good.
I remember.
I got hit in the head and passed out.
That means, the guy who won
and is now courting Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan?
You came to your senses, Honmaru-kun?
Iyona-chan, you didn't go home with Harako?
No need to worry about that.
Iyona-chan...
You look better!
Your bruise.
You were just checking the bruise?
I see. Well that explains it!
Iyona-chan is so caring.
But are you telling me Harako just went home alone
without raising a ruckus?
Taru-chan covered me
and went home with Harako-kun in my stead.
Taruruuto did?
And Harako also accepted it just like that?
I guess those two found a common language somehow.
Perhaps.
Turns out, Iyona-san's favorite dish is takoyaki...
Didn't see that coming.
And yet she is not gaining any weight.
Impersonating Iyona is not half-bad.
And I'm also helping out Honmaru here!
If you'd like it, you can have my portion too.
Bravo... You're a woman of many talents, Iyona-san.
Idiot!
And idiot!
Listen well, Taru.
That little thing of you being a magician
should by no means ever leak out to dad and mom!
Honmaru, I'll keep my promise!
I wonder if it'll really be fine.
Magical Taruruuto-kun: I Love Mama!
Honmaru's mama smells just like my own mama.
Episode 4
I Love Mama!
Everyone, roo-rook forward to it!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume