Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 78
Good Guy Jabao!?
Hey, c'mon! Jaba Jabao-sama needs to pass through!
Come on, make way for the boss!
Move it!
That jerk Jabao is strutting around with that bossy attitude again!
Bossy air again!
Asshole! Did you just hit me?
I mean... You're taking up all the space
when you're walking down the hallway!
What? You dare talk back to me, the boss?
Stop it, Jabao!
You always resort to fighting!
Stop!
You got a problem with me, Honmaru?
You're being an insufferable nuisance!
You're all so noisy!
Jabao, do you think you can
fight Honmaru and win?
He's no longer as gutless as he once was.
That guy he beat, Zakenja Nezo,
was the great master of Chinese kenpo. Remember?
Well, the only one able to fight
Honmaru as equals now,
is probably myself,
renowned as second to none in the world.
But you'll be in trouble
if you keep acting like a boss!
What?
Better to remain silent and be thought a fool
than to speak and remove all doubt.
It's best that you back down now, Jabao.
What was that, Korekiyo?
Even you?!
Honmaru-san!
Isn't that enough?
Even these pricks are looking down on me,
thinking I'm no match for Honmaru!
If I keep backing down like this,
Nannosho will never again recognize my importance!
The only way out is a big all-or-nothing showdown!
Let's do it!
Fine...
If you can't understand,
I'll knock some sense into you!
Don't fight, you two!
Iyona-chan...
I did it!
Honmaru!
Wait, Taru!
Honmaru?
Stay out of this!
Honmaru-kun...
Please, Honmaru-kun!
What's so special about that kenpo master?
Without Taru's magic,
he's just as gutless as he used to be!
Enough already, Jabao-kun!
I didn't have enough!
Hey, hey!
So? What's wrong, Honmaru?
Jabao...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru just...
Ran away.
Honmaru!
I told you, he's always
been a weakling from the start!
Hm! As expected of Jabao-san!
A spectacular win!
Korekiyo-kun.
Didn't you side with Honmaru just a moment ago?!
Even a good Homer nods sometimes, don't you think?
Both now and before, Ryoguchiya Korekiyo
had always been Jabao-san's most faithful squire!
If I also resort to violence,
I'll end up disappointing Iyona-chan.
Ah! Why is it so frustrating?!
What just happened, Honmaru-kun?
I wish I could convey to Jabao
just how I feel right now!
Honmaru, leave it to me.
This - Honmaru's Cakemotion.
Jabao!
What is it?
Eat this!
Actually yummy!
Taru! I didn't ask you
to feed this idiot a cake!
Jabao and Honmaru now feel the same.
What's the use of us feeling the same?
This is no time to be kidding around!
Jabao, what do you feel?
Ah, why is it so frustrating?!
Dammit! Taru! What the hell did you feed me?
The rice cake that Jabao ate
was the Cakemotion that allows you
to convey your feelings to others.
What? Cakemotion that allows you
to convey your feelings to others?
I fed Honmaru's feelings to Jabao.
Jabao started feeling the same way as Honmaru.
Taru,
I don't really understand
what the heck you're saying.
But why the hell is it so frustrating?!
I see! Thanks to Taru's magic, my infinite frustration
is shared by Jabao too!
Do you understand now, Jabao?
Ah! That's refreshing magic.
Ah! I suddenly feel so much better!
Now Jabao is laughing too!
Why's that, Taru?
Somehow, I feel like asking "Why's that?"
What's going on here?
With the magic of Cakemotion,
Jabao's emotions are now in sync with Honmaru's.
Ah, I see!
I feel like I suddenly understood something.
In other words, Jabao's emotions
are now whatever I want them to be!
Dunno why, but I feel so elated somehow!
You're laughing without even knowing why!
You dumbass! Dumbass!
What was that?
Whadya say?!
Does it work with this too?
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Serves you right!
It still hurts, but somehow
I feel like I got what was coming to me!
Mine still hurts too!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Taru, this feels kinda weird.
Korekiyo, I feel kinda bizarre.
Don't copy me!
No, you!
You're getting on my nerves, you jerk!
The feeling is mutual, you jerk!
Honmaru, don't get angry!
If you get angry, Jabao will get angry too!
Stop it, both of you.
Please, start getting along.
Iyona-chan?
Honmaru, Iyona's Cakemotion.
Iyona-chan's Cakemotion?
Can I have a half?
Honmaru-kun, Jabao-kun...
That's right, violence won't solve anything.
Let's get along.
I'm sorry, Jabao-kun.
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun.
Yay! Honmaru and Jabao made up!
I'm so glad.
Isn't it creepy?
I've never met someone more nauseating!
Can't you two be making up
in a more conservative way?
What's this?
Holding hands with Jabao
and looking at each other's eyes...!
What are you doing?
Let go of my hands!
You do that! It's creepy!
Ten minutes ran out!
My magic wore off...
You sick bastard!
Jabao-kun!
Stop it, Jabao!
Impressive.
Honmaru just barely touched his fist!
You don't wanna mess with Honmaru,
the master of kenpo!
Sorry, Jabao!
I accidentally got serious and let it out...
How brutal of you, Honmaru.
While telling me not to use it, you resort
to violence yourself as soon as you get a chance.
Did you see it, Iyona-chan?
Everyone did, right?
But...
Honmaru not a brute!
Jabao threw a fist first!
That's right! Honmaru was just
trying to block your punch.
Your utter defeat is irrefutable.
That's right!
Jabao is the one at fault here.
Right, everyone?
Tsk! You'd make me a scapegoat in any case!
Jabao!
What a truly incorrigible guy!
His attitude has been riling me for ages!
Right, Honmaru-san?
You went too far.
Korekiyo carried away.
If you can't beat them, join them.
Evolution is about survival of the fittest. Yes, sir.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't compete with Honmaru.
Korekiyo turned his back on me too.
And everyone treats me like a bad egg.
My life is already over.
If it came to this, I might as well do it...
I'll go full asshole!
My pencil case!
Got a problem with me?
No, I mean...
Jabao!
Stop this!
He's right. You should stop, Jabao.
Sup, Jabao!
You'll make me a scapegoat regardless.
What do you mean by that?
I don't suppose you're afraid
of Honmaru-sama's iron fist of justice?
Well then, go ahead and hit me.
You're all that strong and righteous
and I'm just an outcast bad egg!
Which means I'm gonna get beaten up,
making me the bad guy even more!
Hey, c'mon! No need to hold back, just hit right here.
Even if you say that...
Look! Ain't I a bag egg, eh?
Help me!
Stop it, Jabao!
The negotiation grace had run out!
Honmaru-sama, how about you introduce
the evil Jabao to your fist of justice?
I'm fed up with you, Jabao!
That's it, Honmaru-sama's iron fist of justice!
Then bring it on!
Why, Jabao-kun?
Jabao-kun, you're actually a good person, aren't you?
Yeah! Good guy.
You're saying I'm a good person?
What a stupid thing to say!
Well, when Honmaru-kun died...
That happened so long ago,
I've already forgotten all about it.
That's not true.
We're all friends, aren't we?
Let's start getting along.
Yeah! Get along well.
Taru, Iyona-chan...
That's right.
Why don't we get along, Jabao?
Exactly right! Even the strongest of our world
say that friendship and cooperation are beautiful things!
Honmaru, like hell I'm getting along
with a butt kisser such as you!
I am the evil Jaba Jabao, a lone wolf!
What's that guys's problem?
He's now in a perfect isolation.
What an unlikable fella!
That's right. We can do just fine
even without getting along with his kind!
Jabao-kun has shut his heart completely.
Please, be honest with yourself
and open your heart.
Open the heart...
Good-Hearted Windbowl!
If Jabao eats this Good-Hearted Windbowl,
it'll open a window to his heart.
Hey, Jabao!
Oh! Looks damn tasty!
Don't mind if I do!
You fed him a rice cake
yesterday and a rice bowl today!
Why are you doing all the wrong things?
Jabao, eat! Eat!
Delicious! Just as I was starving too!
Thanks for the grub!
Ah! A window!
Jabao ate Good-Hearted Windbowl
and opened a window to his good heart!
Something flew out of it!
That is Jabao's conscience.
When you eat Good-Hearted Windowl,
your true conscience awakens.
It's a magical bowl for becoming a good person.
Jabao, you're actually a good guy,
so live like befits a good guy.
Open your eyes, Jabao!
Go back to the real you.
To the one that is a good child.
The real me?
I see!
Sorry, everyone!
I've been so selfish up until now!
Jabao opened his eyes!
Looks like you've finally realized, Jabao.
Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry, for bullying you up until now, Korekiyo-san.
Well done, Jabao.
I gotta tidy up the classroom today.
I want everyone to feel comfortable while studying.
I should also make it up to Korekiyo-san
for all the previous trouble.
Good, good.
Jabao, me too!
Jabao, me as well!
And me!
Okay. Sure. Come on, line up now.
That's the way, Jabao.
So that's what the real Jabao looks like?
Yeah! Jabao good guy.
That's wonderful, Jabao-kun.
Iyona-chan?
Taru!
I also wanna eat the Good-Hearted Windowl,
become popular and be praised by Iyona-chan!
Sure, Honmaru will eat too.
Now...
Hurry up, you!
Honmaru!
Yeah, what is it, Taru?
That's Devil-Bowl!
Eating that bowl makes you a selfish and bad person!
Scientific name - Armagebowl.
Honmaru!
What?
Honmaru, you're an awfully strong fella.
How about acting more intimidating?
And don't worry about how one or another person feels!  Once you show them your strength, they'll all shut up.
Exactly.
From now on, your infantile ass can only use magic for my benefit, Taru.
Is that clear?
Honmaru!
Korekiyo...
Yes?
From now on, you must also only bow down to me.
Without a doubt, Honmaru-sama!
I will follow after you for the rest of my life!
Move it, you fatass!
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun.
You imbecile.
It's "I apologize, Honmaru-sama" for you.
That's the way, Honmaru.
Right, you?
That's terrible, Honmaru-kun!
You're going too far.
Iyona, ain't you a cute little thing?
Honmaru! Stop this improper
behavior of yours in the classroom!
That's right!
Rui, I'll make you my woman too.
Who do you think...
Honmaru-sama!
Devil-Bowl's magical power is amazing!
You heard it, everyone?
Starting today, Class 5-1 is my kingdom!
If anyone's got a problem with it, come out!
Honmaru-kun, that's not a very good thing to do...
Silence! You dare to defy Honmaru-sama's decree?
The next step would be taking over all of Nannosho.
Yo, Honmaru!
You swine! Where were your eyes at?
Weren't you the one who bumped into me?
Think of a better joke next time!
He dared to talk back to Honmaru-sama!
He's about to find out...
Asshole!
Ah! But I'm not a bird!
Please stop it, Honmaru-sama.
Refrain from any further use of brute force.
Aren't you just pretending
to be a bootlicker because of a spell?
Keep it up, Honmaru!
I'm just asking you
to stop being so violent, Honmaru-san.
Don't give up, Jabao!
Damn, you're all so noisy!
Where have I seen this pattern before?
Right now, I'm acting the same way
Jabao did yesterday!
Now, hurry up and smash his face, Honmaru.
The magic wore off after ten minutes.
Stop it, Honmaru!
Are you... no longer under the spell?
I was the worst for intimidating others with violence!
Having seen you just now,
I could realize it all too well!
But you're only evil
because of the Devil-Bowl effect!
The real Honmaru ain't nothing like that guy!
Don't talk like you know me!
We're friends, remember?
That's why you also tried
to stop me from being violent, remember?
I want to return the favor now!
Open your eyes, Honmaru!
Get it over with, Honmaru.
I plunged into the depths of despair,
thinking I couldn't ever match your strength anyway!
But really, I'm just lonely...
That's why I was sincerely happy
when you proposed getting along!
Come on, send that eyesore
to the gutter already.
Open your eyes, Honmaru!
I've had enough of you talking,
you little devil!
But why...? Ten minutes haven't run out yet...
Honmaru!
Jabao, I can understand how you feel now.
No, it's me who understands
exactly how you feel.
The two... the two finally made up!
I'm so glad, Honmaru-kun, Jabao-kun.
Well, isn't it a happy ending?
Korekiyo!
You were the one pitting them against each other!
Haven't you had enough?
Korekiyo!
I wish there was a hole for me to hide in...
Sure, Korekiyo! A hole for you!
Honmaru, you rogue!
What did I ever do to you?!
Answer me, you dunce!
What's wrong with you?
There's no reason to get so riled up, Korekiyo.
Just because I broke your shellfish money...
That's one menacing look he has...
That's right! What if I mend it with sellotape?
Not good enough, even so?
Ah, what should I do, Taru?
It's Honmaru's fault for destroying his memories.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Reconciling is Hard!
Episode 79
Value your friends more, will you?
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius