Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 45
New Rival Appears!
It's heading your way, Taru!
Okay!
You okay, Taruruuto?
This Roundy is better at flying than me.
Oh? Taru, let's go play in some bigger place instead.
Yeah!
Zakenja?
Honmaru, Neyo here! Right here!
She always seems to be alone.
Well, that is to be expected with a personality like hers.
She can't make any friends, I imagine.
Neyo good person. Me like Neyo!
Honmaru love Neyo too!
I told you already, she's not the one.
The one I love is the most wonderful
girl in the world, Iyona-chan!
Alright, we go play with Neyo!
Eh? Taru!
Yay! Neyo, come play together with us!
Hey, Taruruuto!
Uh, well... Taru asked me to play with him.
And we noticed you also look bored, sitting here alone.
Neyo, try tossing this Roundy.
You won't have to ask me twice.
Can twist it cool!
Neyo tossed! Wait for me!
Taru! Don't let it escape!
Oh, that silly Taru...
Oh no...
Before I knew it, I was one-on-one with Zakenja.
Keeping silent would be awkward.
That said, what could we possibly talk about?
Zakenja, is the house you moved into
somewhere in this neighborhood?
Do you live there with your dad and mom?
Maybe with your brothers or sisters?
Pretending this stuff has anything to do with you?
Are you kidding me?
Tsk. Is that what I get for trying especially hard
to start a conversation with you?
Why should I, even?
It's her fault for being so disagreeable.
Taruruuto!
I gotta hurry, lest the 23rd World Junior
Best Dressed Award Ceremony starts without me!
Hey, move it! Are you sleepwalking, you asshole?!
Dumbass! Do you even watch where you're going?!
I ain't kidding around.
Gramps! I need a reservation for a new car.
In addition, there's a man I need you to investigate.
Honmaru, Honmaru!
Let's play outside, Honmaru!
Okay!
Hey-hey, Honmaru-kun?
Hey, did you know? Something strange
is coming about in the class next door.
I heard about it too!
Honmaru? Honmaru, what's the matter?
Taru, we're having a talk now. This can wait.
The thing is, the boy who just transferred seems to be extremely violent.
He pushes everyone in the class around,
as if they were his servants!
And he has a face like you've never seen in this world!
Servants?
Even I'm scared somehow, Honmaru-kun!
Don't worry. Iyona-chan,
you have me in case of any emergency!
Oh, that's actually relieving.
Ah, what about me?
Honmaru, you go play with me!
Come on, Taru! Why'd you do that out of the blue?
Honmaru, please hit me back.
Right here, on my head, hit me hard, with a swoosh!
What the hell?
What are you doing?
This - my Sabro.
Two that you hit with it develop eternal intimacy!
Sabro, right.
That's an interesting toy.
Ah, isn't it great? Kids are always full of dreams...
I suppose.
Sure is great. Living without any worries or troubles.
Hey, Taru!
They'll learn about your magic this way!
Honmaru! We play outside together!
No we don't! I'm in the middle of a conversation!
Honmaru...
Ah, it bloomed...! So that's the intimacy
you were talking about?
Taruruuto! Let's go! To outside, or to wherever!
We're friends so it stands!
Taruruuto!
Honmaru!
He's an actual halfwit.
Isn't he caring?
He fulfilled Taru-chan's wish with passion!
Ouch!
Who're you?!
Out of my way.
Honmaru!
You okay?
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan, it's him...
From the adjacent class...
I'll interrupt you.
Who's the guy in charge of this class?
I want him to step forward.
Well, I'm the class representative...
I didn't mean you.
I'm asking who's the strongest guy in this class.
After me, Ryoguchiya.
Yes.
Got some business with me?
Surely, you don't intend to get into a fight with our Jabao-san?
Or maybe insult his highness?
If I were you, I'd stop!
Silence!
I'll do it myself!
You must try to avoid fighting!
I can't back off now.
Jabao!
To those deaf to words,
I explain things with my fists!
Yeah! Go-go, Jabao!
Keep going!
Don't be licking me, for God's sake...
A babysitter? So that's what you are? I see.
You're gravely mistaken if you think I'll let anyone make fun of my face!
Jabao... Wow...
Honmaru...
I'll be in charge of this class from today onwards.
Those who don't listen to me won't get away with it.
Taking over my class?
A foolish enterprise.
Who is it?
Harako!
It's only natural for strong men to become kings,
and for the weak to serve them.
You look a little old.
You don't strike me as an elementary grader.
Nobody talks to me like that!
It's just that my body was gifted
with perfect looks at any age.
And I like the subtly mature atmosphere it gives off.
And that's no wonder, for I am the heir to the Harako Conglomerate that controls the Japanese business world.
And you, some commoner of muddy origins,
claim to be the king? Don't make me laugh!
It's best that you laugh now while you still can.
For you'll end up the same way as the fatass before you.
What?
I'll call the teacher!
Nobody is coming out until I say so.
Have no fear.
I'll take care of everything, Iyona-san.
Harako-kun...
Harako?
Harako!
Asshole, I see you're a user of Chinese kenpo?
However, Chinese kenpo poses no threat to me!
Look!
Before you - the Junior World Champion in Karate.
This will be interesting.
Harako...
Be sure to avenge me!
Do your best!
What is it?
Wait a minute.
Hello?
This is Tsutomu speaking.
Ah, Gramps?
What's new?
Young Master, you absolutely mustn't defy that man.
What?
Forget about Japan - he's the heir apparent
to Zakenja Concern, pulling the strings behind the world's politics and economy.
Zakenja Concern?
What's wrong, Harako?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Compared to my dad,
your dad ain't worth shit.
Shit!
In the name of Harako Tsutomu,
the Junior World Champion of the endurance contest,
I'll endure this like a man for now!
What, really?
Alright. You are now my servants.
Those who won't obey will be demoted to slaves.
Even to slaves?
Shit, I can't stand this moron
speaking with his nose in the air!
I look, look, look, found it!
Come on, Taru!
Zakenja...
What's the matter? Won't you say at least something?
Like you always do...
Are you kidding me?
And then, you'd fight him with your kendama!
Alright, dear servants.
Listen well to what I say.
Now we're tear our clothes off and start dancing naked!
Should be fun.
Fun!
Yay!
Everyone would be dancing naked!
You can't do such a thing...
My, did someone just say I can't?
Servants defying the king doesn't sound right.
Iyona-chan is amazing!
So much courage!
Then there's...
me...
Can't stop trembling with fear!
Shit!
Hey, you! Boys!
Are you just gonna let him have it his way?
Why won't anyone say anything?
How can you still call yourselves men?
But think of it - the opponent is a master
of 3000-year-old Chinese kenpo.
Good.
Then, hear something the king has long wanted to say.
Dammit!
Come what may, I don't care anymore!
Interesting, you're the first to disobey me?
I can't afford postponing this!
After all, I already promised Iyona-chan
to always be here if she needs it!
Honmaru-kun!
It'll be alright, Iyona-chan.
I'm... I'm...
...the world junior boxing champion
who defeated Harako!
Edojo Honmaru-sama!
Wanna see a real fist?
Would this be enough of a demonstration?
Honmaru-kun...
Really, so many guys here and there
that you can't rely on for toffee!
Rightly said.
Naked heaven!
Yay, Honmaru lost!
Okay, I could use a friend.
Taru...
Okay, I'm starting!
Where? Eh? What?
What?
You little shit...
I'm not kidding around!
Zakenja Nezo?
Is it your name, Zakenja Nezo?
That's right.
Yay, it's great! I guessed right! Amazing!
Zakenja Nezo? Zakenja, that's...
My name is Zakenja Nezo.
I'm Neyo's twin brother.
What?
No wonder she's not interfering in Zakenja business!
It must be because the two aim
to establish absolute tyranny over our class!
Clan Chen Rocky Mountain
Sword of Evil Crushing to Dust Technique!
Taru!
I see! This is invulnerable even to Taru's magic!
Those who disobey me get no mercy,
be it even a woman or a baby!
Clan Bo Ultra-Destructive Blast Hell Fist!
Where have I seen this before?
Stop it.
There's no fun in squashing some brats.
It's not what you were training in the mountains for, is it?
Alright. As an exemption on my sister's behest,
I'll let the shrimp go.
Get lost!
Taru!
Are you okay?
Yeah. Honmaru, Neyo good person!
Yeah...
Just as you said, Neyo is really...
However...
You won't get that privilege, Honmaru!
Squishy!
Clan Tou Turbulent Pulverizing Fist!
I can't take it anymore!
No! Honmaru-kun!
Huh? It doesn't hurt at all.
I made Honmaru soft with Squishy spell.
Beat him all you want, he won't feel anything!
I see! It’s Taru’s magic?
That's weird.
Time to unleash an even more terrifying attack!
Clan Sai Deep Penetration Dagger Chop!
What's wrong? Are you kidding me?
I don't feel shit from any of your attacks!
Bullshit!
What's going on?
Honmaru keeps receiving his punches and kicks,
but is just smiling weirdly!
Amazing, Honmaru-kun!
Seems like Neyo's bro isn't really
as much a dander as he seemed to be.
I've read about it.
Thanks to the special training with me up to this point,
Honmaru's body had developed the endurance of steel!
Only one way to settle this.
Clan Boku Explosive Army-Style Attack!
Honmaru!
Bendpost!
What's going on?!
Nezo!
That's not where I aimed it at!
Cretin.
How exactly did he kick himself to there?
We're saved.
A bit more and we'd have all become slaves to him.
Right, Honmaru?
Here.
It was all thanks to Honmaru-kun.
Thank you.
Thanks to me, really?
Well, I gave you a promise, didn't I?
I only did what was natural!
Thank you, Taru!
I'll be sure to double what I owe you for today, Honmaru.
Looks like you ended up seriously pissing off my brother,
Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Zakenja Nezo!
That's right, we're not kidding around!
What the hell were you thinking,
not allowing our Class 1 to use the locker room?!
Yeah! We'll hold a duel in two groups!
We sure as hell will!
I'm burned up already!
I'll definitely beat him!
But Nezo uses magic.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Must Win Pool Showdown!
Everyone, do your best!
Episode 46
Must Win Pool Showdown!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius