Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Nannosho Shopping District
I overslept from my dad's lectures yesterday!
Overslept! Overslept!
At this rate, I'll be inexcusably late!
The teacher will take it out on my butt again!
I know! Taru, stop the time now!
Honmaru, you can do it! Keep ru-ru-running!
Lotsa thrill and fun!
What a stingy jerk you are!
I'm not asking you for anything ever again!
Episode 38
Honmaru's Worst and Unluckiest Day Ever
Pedestrian Zone
Whoa!
Ah! Even the traffic light turned red...
Faster! Faster! Faster! Faster! Whoa!
You ass!
Why am I all out of luck today?
Honmaru!
There.
Taru!
Why did you have to do this to me?
This - Little Forturd.
Wearing that improves your luck a bit.
Oh, I see! Kinda like the Oppoositer?
Yeah!
Thank you, Taru!
Ah!
Someone lost money right here?
Lucky! It paid off handsomely already!
Honmaru.
You find money - you bring it there.
We've no time for that.
I'm late enough as it is.
Honmaru...
Bring to police box...
Alright, alright.
Might as well hand it in.
Well!
Thank you guys!
I was the one who dropped this money!
There, see?
This is Mr. Policeman's!
Right! Very commendable of you to return it
even though you're running late!
I know! You deserve a reward of 20%!
No need...
Don't be shy, don't be shy!
Well, I'll be! Forturd-kun works great! I'm in luck!
Honmaru, aren't you glad?
That's right! The new issue of Shonen Jump comes out today!
Let's go buy it!
Honmaru, if you don't hurry, you'll be totally late!
With Forturd, I'll make it through somehow!
Ah? I see.
Oh no! This boy here is awfully late!
Even a good Homer nods sometimes.
Even experts make mistakes!
Even Buddha can misread the sutra!
Even a kappa can drown in the river!
Is that Honmaru?
Watch it, you clutz!
Look where you're going!
We're sorry. Ah?
Why, it's just Ijigawa?
What difference does it make?
It was you who bumped into me
because you were walking and reading!
Playful Comic
Weren't you walking
with your eyes on the book yourself?!
Ah! Ijigawa...
You're standing on a dog poop!
You're pathetic, Ijigawa!
Stepped in poop! In poop!
Nice, nice!
Damn, it stinks!
Oh! It stinks so much even my eyes are stinging!
That's rich of you,
wearing poop on your head yourself!
This one is a bogus!
I'll go tell everyone at school!
Wait I said, you!
Ijigawa the Stinker!
Stinker! Stinker!
If I hadn't bumped into Ijigawa,
I'd have stepped in poop myself!
Lucky!
We in school! Yeah!
Eh? What happened, Korekiyo?
I... Ah. Doesn't matter. Hurry up inside.
Tsk.
So... Oaya-sensei had to go on a business trip,
so I'm conducting the homeroom in her stead.
Oh? Honmaru-kun!
Kyodo-sensei! I'm so sorry for coming late...
Honmaru-kun, that was commendable of you.
A police officer called us earlier. He said you had to stop by
to return lost money, therefore you'd be late.
Yeah...
Right...
That's great!
I'm proud to know we have exemplary students
like you right here in our school.
Now, everyone, a round of applause for Honmaru-kun!
Attaway, Honmaru!
Alright!
Wow! I came late, but instead of slapping, I got an applause!
Really, I'm so lucky!
Why is it just me...?
Say, Taru, isn't there some item even more powerful
than Small Forturd for increasing my luck?
Yeah! A whole caboodle.
This - Medium Forturd. Wearing this
boosts luck even more than Small Forturd.
That's it!
Thank you, Taru.
I can get even luckier than before?
Can't wait to see it in action!
Iyona-chan in her underwear...
That's strange... Gym class
was supposed to be during the 5th period.
I see. Because Oaya-sensei is absent,
the timetable was altered.
Still...
Insanely lucky!
Now then, though it may seem a little sudden,
for the next class, we'll hold a mini-test in math.
Eek!
What the hell? A test?
Test
I don't understand a thing.
Even wearing Medium Forturd doesn't help...
I can glance at Harako's answers! Lucky!
Time to copy them all!
Did it, hey!
How about this, Jabao?
Ain't that impressive? What about you?
Piss off. Doncha get your nose in the air
just 'cause you racked up a good score once!
You're only saying that 'cause you're fuming with jealousy!
What the hell?! You'll pay for this!
Get this!
Ouch!
This ain't half-bad! Lucky, lucky!
Greatly lucky!
Taru, Taru! You got any other guys
in the Forturd Series?
Yeah! A whole caboodle!
This one is for oppositing your fate, Oppoositer.
This - for increased earnings, Fundung.
This - helps you win lotteries, Drawpping.
Then, there's...
That one brings bad luck, Catastrofeces.
And... This for happy love, Romanure...
And this... This...
What's the matter, Taru?
I can't remember all the kinds.
Then, how about we try them on
to remember better, Taru?
I need to study more!
Using things you don't understand is bad.
Don't you be such a bore!
Honmaru?
Mom!
Wh... What... happened here?!
The room is covered in poop!
Taru! Hide them all now!
Yeah! I'll do right now...
This, and this too.
And I'll keep this one...
Huh?
But what was that?
Uh? What was what, mom?
No, nothing.
That's strange...
Taru, let's go to school.
Me sleepy. Come later.
Your loss!
Well, let's get started!
How about I try it out?
Something this big surely makes one insanely lucky!
Perfect!
What's with that guy?
Instead of holding up an umbrella,
he put poop on his head?
Is he a local yokel?
Good morning, Iyona-chan.
Honmaru-kun, what the matter?
You're dripping wet...
You didn't bring an umbrella?
But it started raining out of the blue!
Didn't you see the weather forecast on TV, Honmaru?
They issued a warning for heavy rain
that was starting as soon as this morning.
Why should I...
Or perhaps a dunce such as you can't even understand
what the weather forecast says?
Now, let's be on our way, Iyona-san.
It's best that you don't associate with such miserable men,
wearing poop on their heads. Now...
This is the latest fashion!
DON'T TOUCH.
Eh?
If you get any closer,
you'll get Iyona-san's beautiful clothes all wet.
Now, let's not linger, Iyona-san.
Shithead, literally!
Dammit...
Edojo Honmaru-kun.
Yes?
Come to the staff room later.
I'd like a few words with you
regarding yesterday's mini-test.
Eh?!
Did someone notice me cheating?
Honmaru, did you do something?
Cheated on it, perhaps?
So that's how it is?
I also found it was strange that an idiot
such as Honmaru would get the same score as me.
That's very low, Honmaru!
Teacher!
What is it, Ijigawa-san?
Honmaru-kun is a brute!
He pushed me yesterday on purpose
and made me step on dog poop!
You did that on your own!
Hell no! You caused that!
Teacher, yesterday, Honmaru-kun
looked into the class while the girls were changing.
No, I wasn't trying...
Everyone! Honmaru is a coward!
I was fighting him with my bare hands,
but he used a stone!
I saw Honmaru buying a manga magazine
even though he was terribly late.
You're a devil, Honmaru-kun!
Pervert too!
And what's the deal with that stupid hat?
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun, it seems you'll have plenty
to answer for in the staff room.
I'm sorry!
Never again!
I regret it!
The hell...?
My luck is ridiculously bad today!
You can't be serious! Geez...
Honmaru!
Taru! Why didn't you come to school?
All hell broke loose today!
Sorry, Honmaru.
What's wrong, Taru?
Honmaru...
That...
That... The Great Shitaclism,
summoning only the worst disasters upon the wearer!
The Great Shitaclism
What did you say?!
This is serious, Taru-chan.
Tama-chan...
He'll have to repay
the luck Forturd-kun gave him all at once.
If you don't take it off soon,
Honmaru-kun might even die.
No, no, no! I can't take it off! It won't come off!
I see. So this thing is responsible
for all of my misfortunes today!
Ouch-ouch-ouch...
Tama-chan, is there some good way to do it?
I'll let you know as soon as I find one.
In the meantime, try your best to take it off fast!
Alright. Honmaru! Gotta take Forturd-kun off! Now!
I can't take it off... What... What do we do now?
Honmaru, watch out!
What? What just happened?
What? What is this? What is this thing?
Honmaru, hurry up! Hurry and take it off!
It's no use! It won't budge!
Honmaru, please use
whatever magic you have to take it off!
If I keep attracting nothing but disasters,
no amount of lives would be enough!
Wait, now that you mention it...
Emergency! Emergency!
Control lost! I repeat! Control lost!
A plane this time? It's over...
Is my life coming to an end now?
All because I put this item on my head!
Control regained!
Lucky!
Huh?
Ah! Oppoositer Mk-3!
I don't understand how, but I'm saved!
Sister Ria!
That was dangerous, Honmaru.
You're lucky I put Oppoositer Minus Mk-3 on your head
and reversed the power of your previous poop.
Taru is also quite a dum-dum.
You could just make Honmaru smaller
to take it off at once.
Trunsform.
Honmaru.
This thing called "luck"
is something you carve out on your own.
If you rely on magic, you'll have to pay the price someday.
You should only shape your fate with your own efforts.
By doing good things for those around you,
you'll have good things coming back at you.
And doing bad things
will bring back things in return.
That's really all there is to it.
Sister Ria said the same thing
mom told me back in the day.
Honmaru, remember. If you're kind to people,
you'll only ever get happier.
Yeah.
I guess it really is the whole gist.
Still, I was way unluckier today
than I was supposed to be!
Right, Taru?
Poke-poke.
He put out another one
from the Forturd Series to play with?
No. Wait a moment.
What if it's another one of the Shitaclism kind?
There, there. There-there!
Well, it's just some small one Taru wants to play with.
It's gotta be harmless!
I'll have this, thanks!
Honmaru, that's real dog poop.
Some of the Great Shitaclism power rubbed off on you!
This is the worst day ever!
Stinker, stinker!
Damn it, this wretch Ijigawa is getting too comfortable!
Making fun of me getting bad test scores!
Hey, Taruruuto, isn't there something
that'd help me show her her place?
Yeah!
I wanna hear you show her her place!
You gotta do something, Taru!
Okay, try this...
Episode 39
Good Honmaru, Bad Honmaru
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Good Honmaru, Bad Honmaru.
But these glasses are a truly dreadful tool.
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius