Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
From now on, the next program slot
is Magical Taruruuto-kun.
Taruru!
Behold myself, the Great Magician Taruruuto-sama!
For whatever reason, trouble is brewing around me.
Why so, Honmaru?
Don't you really understand yourself?
Everyone ru-ru-root for our show!
New program: Magical Taruruuto-kun.
Don't miss it!
Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Name:
Raser♥
Iyona-chan,
here.
Thank you, Honmaru-kun.
Did it hurt?
I'm sorry,
Raser.
Raser?
Is that... Iyona-chan,
is that how you named your gum eraser?
Is it weird?
Not at all.
It's cute and becoming for a girl.
True?
True, I say!
I give names to my supplies myself.
Protractor-man Kitaro.
Not quite it.
And this...
Columpass.
Then this one can be...
Capchick!
Sounds great.
And then... Is there more?
Also, this guy.
The Unyielding Ruler.
He seems like a real deal.
You should keep it up, Honmaru-kun.
And together,
they make this:
The United Pen-box Family.
Will you let Raser keep them company, too?
Why, of course!
I see. When you give them names like that,
somehow, even simple things can become living.
Like wonderful magic, right?
Episode 1
Me, The Great Magician
Raser is getting closer!
Pen-snap, pen-snap!
Era-ra-ra-ra-ra-rase!
Won't get me that easy!
Pen-snap, pen-snap! Pen-sna—
What is all this pen-box ruckus?
This buffoon is feverishly
giving names to his stuff!
Must be one big doofus!
Just an overgrown kindergartener.
You're messing with the serious people, Jabao-san!
But Jabao-kun, I think,
when you give names to things, if...
If it's the things you care about,
there's nothing wrong with it!
Quite so!
Nothing wrong with it!
Then, I'll do some naming, too!
Righteous iron fist,
Saitama Prefecture!
I'm not done yet!
Aichi Prefecture, Aomori Prefecture, Oita Prefecture!
ABCDEFG!
Roger that.
Honmaru-kun...
You're not safe yet!
Osaka blow!
Who's there?
You wanna die or what?
"You'll-Regret-Teacher!"
It's "You'll-Regret-Teacher!"
Save yourselves!
My name is Oaya Mari!
Jabao-kun, haven't I told you
many times before to quit picking up fights?
Yes...
When are you going to listen, then?!
I'm sorry, teacher!
I'm so sorry!
Sorry...
I'm sorry, Honmaru.
It was my fault that you got beaten...
It was not your fault in the slightest.
Instead, look at the wreck that is Jabao.
His butt is tattered and he's about to cry!
Teacher!
I believe both parties are at fault for the fight!
Ijigawa...
One moment, teacher!
Especially for a boy,
such behavior
is unacceptable!
How come me and Jabao
are now having to sit next to each other?
Why am I always out of luck?
Because of Honmaru,
I had my ass whooped!
Because of Jabao,
I've been humiliated in front of Iyona-chan!
Today, thanks to you,
the teacher tattered my butt.
We should settle this score
once and for all!
You're cocky just because everyone else
is too afraid to fight back!
You're not getting away with it!
Morons! Morons!
Screw you, Jabao.
Welcome home! Honmaru?
Dad! Be it boxing or magic, anything will do.
You gotta teach me how to win in a fight!
Wake me up and I'll show you hell on earth
Hehehehehe
Sleeping again...
Now's not the time to be sleeping, dad!
Wake me up and I'll show you hell on earth!
If I wake him, I'll only dig myself deeper to hell.
I'm screwed....
I'm screwed!
Honmaru!
From now on,
we'll be the best buddies!
At least 30 days more
of sitting next to that caveman, Jabao...
By the end of that time,
Iyona-chan is going to forget my looks!
I'm screwed!
I really am!
I'm really screwed!
ARE YOU REALLY SCREWED?
What is it?
Taruru me!
Behold myself, The Great Magician Taruruuto-sama!
The Great Magician, you say?
Is this one of those popular gags nowadays?
For real, for real!
Sure, for real!
Shucks, dad is waking up!
Me, The Great Magician Taruruuto!
Good lordy! Draw that gross playful thing
back where it belongs!
Figures. The Great Magician, then?
Still, where have you been hiding all this time?
In here.
Here-here, here-here.
It was your "I'm really screwed!" spell
that brought me here.
You can ask for one wish and I'll grant it.
Is this kid not right in the head?
Look, you. I don't know where'd you get the funny idea,
but you can't just claim to be a magician.
You have to look something like...
This! The kind of guy you
wouldn't wanna mess with!
Prepare your bluff better next time!
This is Taru's papa.
I see.
I reckon your pops is a big shot kind of guy.
Hurry up and tell me your one wish.
The little one is just looking for someone to play with.
Not leaving me alone, are you?
Hurry up and speak you wish!
I have one and only wish, my good sir!
From now on,
I want you to grant me a wish every single day!
Too bad you can't...
What was that now?
You tried to cheat.
This crystal ball Tama always watches over
to prevent cheating.
My bad, my bad. So the ball is looking?
Does it have a name?
It is an all-knowing clairvoyant.
Showing me and teaching me
a million of different things.
It can even show
what you're thinking about now.
Always Captivating Tama-chan, please, let us see.
I got you, Taru.
Give me just a moment.
The secret to asking something from Tama-chan
is to ask nicely and cheerfully.
Tama-chan, please.
Tama-chan! Please!
I can't be looking at this!
I can't! I can't look...
I can't look!
What was that for?
You were thinking lewds right now.
Speak for your own thoughts, you charlatan!
Tama-chan sees and knows everything.
Tama, Tama, Tama. Tama!
I'm sorry I lied to you,
Always Captivating Tama-chan!
Board Pen Magic!
This kid is dangerous!
Now you've doodled my chair.
Taruruu!
Yahoo!
Honmaru, howdy?
Chair-chair-chair-chair!
Taruru!
Chair!
A roller coaster!
Honmaru!
With magic, everyone is your friend!
Do you fancy my wizardry?
It has to be for real.
This kid is a true magician!
A real one?!
Honmaru?
Have you decided on your wish already?
One moment!
Taru?
Honmaru is also a magician!
Cool! Cool!
I knew we'd get along well!
Hurry up and speak your wish!
Speak!
Let me think... Alright,
I want you to become my friend!
A friend?
I want you to become my friend.
Friends with Honmaru!
Let's go play outside right away!
I want to go play at the Heart Park!
Honmaru, are we there yet?
Almost there, almost there.
I wonder if Iyona-chan is there.
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan.
Honmaru, what sort of unique kid is this?
He's cute!
This is my friend Taruruuto-kun.
So your name is Taru-chan?
And mine is Iyona. Nice to meet you!
Taru.
The hell? Look at that bizarre kid!
This is friend Taruruuto-kun!
Taruru!
Taru-chan, impressive!
Stop it, Jabao!
Honmaru, got something to say to me?
That's the way!
Taru.
Honmaru! Your little friend
exercises some positively outrageous antics!
Prepare to get taught some manners!
Taru!
Taru-chan is cute!
Isn't it supposed to be our children's playground?
Jabao-kun! If you're a true man, go talk to them!
You gotta be kidding.
There's no way we can confront them
even if we stick together!
Let sleeping dogs lie, lest you get bitten,
isn't that what they say?
Iyona-chan...
Alright, time to restore my honor.
Let's go, Taru!
Hey, Honmaru!
What are you up to?
Honmaru-kun...
They should understand if I ask politely.
After all, I'm just an elementary school student.
Even they won't raise a hand against me.
Don't you know a thing about caution, you brat?
Well, this is a children's playground, you see...
Don't you know a thing about caution, brat?
Taruruuto...
Kiddy, got a problem with me?
This kid-d-d-d-dy got a problem with you?
This shrimp clearly doesn't know when to shut up.
Shri-ri-ri-ri-ri-rimp shut up!
Insane!
This guy is picking up a fight!
No way they let it slide now!
I believe in you, Honmaru-kun.
A thing about ca-ca-ca-caution...
Hey, what's cooking?
Are you stupid?
Wanna die in a place like this, huh?
You know it's dangerous here.
And we are the most dangerous of all things!
Well, I just wanted to say
we can both use this playground comfortably as friends.
Heard it, people?
The shrimp wants to make friends with us!
Yeah! Making friends is nice!
Watch your tongue, Taruruuto!
A lick?
If you have a problem, put it frankly,
you cheeky midget!
Honmaru, watch out!
Tataruru Punch!
Shit'd just hit the fan!
If you want it badly,
we can play together as friends!
Ain't that what we're all about, people!?
Hey, now this spells real danger.
What do we do?
I'm sorry, Honmaru.
Cretin! The time for apologies was about yesterday!
Taru...
Yes, Honmaru?
Let's flee.
tire skid
We'll gladly play with you!
Didn't you wanna play with us as friends?
Get this!
Taruruuto's meddling
turned "bad" to "worst" in seconds!
Honmaru, don't give up!
Honmaru, show them your magic, too.
You picked the worst time ever
to play with an RC helicopter!
Throw and gro-ro-row!
No way!
Honmaru, with magic, I made your Arsie big!
Just... Where did it come from?
Now this is fun!
Holy cow...
Amazing!
This thing is enormous, Taruruuto!
Taruruuto, it was as though you're a true magician.
Honmaru still doesn't believe?
No, I didn't mean it that way.
Yo! The Superstar of the Magic Realm!
My mentor, The Great Magician Taruruuto!
Affiliation not identified!
The on-site protocol authorizes the interception!
What's this?
Eda Hospital
It pains so much...
I'm getting battered so hard
on that shortie's behalf!
Honmaru!
Just stopped by
to say that this world fits my liking.
I guess I'll stay here for some while.
It's a dream after all!
I'm just seeing a dream, that must be it!
Me - Honmaru's friend!
Happy to be hanging out
with you from now on, too!
I can't take it anymore!
No way I keep this feeling in check!
I made up my mind, Taruruuto!
I'll give Iyona-chan a love letter!
You'll help me, won't you?
Cause you're my friend!
Taru!
We're friends, so it stands!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Reaching out to Iyona.
Watch it, okay?
Episode 2
Reaching out to Yona
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume