Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru! I'm looking forward
to sweet toasts for lunch today!
Yeah!
Ah! That deep-fried toast covered in sugar...!
Honmaru, me love sweet toasts too!
But takoyaki love even more!
Really? Well, I'm still on the sweet toasts team!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Oh?
Look!
What is it, Honmaru?
Isn't this a tanuki?
Huh? Oh, you're right!
Now that's unusual. Hey!
That was scary...
This tanuki not feeling well.
I'll give him Power Upple Juice.
Be careful, Taru.
It's small, but it can be quite ferocious!
You'll feel better when you drink this. Here.
Spilled it...
Let's go, Taru. We'll be late for school.
Taru! Hurry up, we're leaving!
Hurry up!
Okay!
Honmaru, tanuki got better!
Oh, glad to know. Let's hurry!
Episode 81
Bon-Bonanza Tanukichi-kun
I've been looking forward to the day we meet
again for a whole month, Sweet Toast-chan!
Move it already!
Don't push me, Jabao! What's your problem?
Jeez, you're a noisy bastard.
Just do it faster!
What's wrong with you?
Really, this guy...
My sweet toasts!
What the blazes, Korekiyo?!
I know you love sweet toasts
just as much as I do!
The hell are you doing?!
What's the meaning of this, Korekiyo?
I'm snorry!
I didn't mean any harm, snort...
It's true, snort.
Tanuki?
And it's talking!
Hey!
Taru, you know him?
It's the tanuki we met in the morning.
Ah?
But the one at the pet shop
looked way more normal.
This - that tanuki.
That's snoright.
You saved me this morning.
I'm a baby tanuki of the shapeshifting tanuki tribe.
Name's Tanukichi, snort...
Actually...
A heartless person took me away
from my home in the mountains.
I was toyed with, dragged around, and abused,
until I became completely unwanted...
So they decided to get rid of me!
Humans are inexcusable villains!
While I'd have liked to yell that, I couldn't even make a sound and was already prepared to die!
Until this morning...
Taru-sama and Honmaru-sama
rescued me from the depths of despair!
It was nothing...
So it seems there are folk
like that, even among humans?
I was gobsmacked,
and I felt I should express my gratitude.
Thus, I followed you here... Just to make
such a blunder before I could say anything.
Don't need thanks. Friends with Tanukichi.
Huh? Friends?
Yeah! We're friends.
Let's get along.
I hope I can become your friend too,
Tanukichi-kun.
You shouldn't think us humans are all bad eggs!
Tanuki isn't supposed to know
how to serve a school lunch.
Well, I guess I'll forgive you
for my ruined toasts just this once.
Thank you very much, everyone!
This is the first time someone
has ever been so considerate to me, snort!
Tanukichi!
Ah! Wait...
Come to think of it,
how did you escape the cage?
Well, I come from a shapeshifting tanuki tribe!
Therefore...
Oh! Tanukichi amazing!
This is how I escaped from the cage.
But until you helped me this morning,
I never had enough strength to afford a transformation.
Then, if I'm not wrong,
Korekiyo had been this Tanukichi guy today?
But where's the real Korekiyo?
This is a disaster!
Sorry! I'm truly snorry!
Jeez... you should've spotted the impostor sooner.
Ah, Korekiyo.
Well, this tanuki didn't mean no harm...
I know. The walls have ears
and the doors have eyes, remember?
I heard it all from inside the locker.
I won't get angry.
Thanks a snort!
Yay! Everyone Tanukichi's friends!
Oh-ho! And just like that,
he's shapeshifted into a teapot!
Tanukichi-kun can do so many different things!
That's true, he's one exceptional tanuki!
Thanks for your attention!
As a descent of the shapeshifting tanuki tribe,
I can transform into various things and do tricks.
And of course, I'm a little more brainy than the others.
Even I, the World Junior Know-it-all Contest Champion,
had no idea a tanuki tribe like that existed.
Where do you live, Tanukichi-kun?
Dotamakin Valley.
This place you call Dotamakin Valley,
it's near the Shinkin Valley Driveway, isn't it?
Shinkin Valley Driveway?
Isn't it the road ridden
with mysterious accidents lately?
What? What is it?
What's wrong, Tanukichi?
I can't be playing with you at such a crucial time!
Kaka-sama is still lying there, bedridden!
Exactly so, snort.
Because of the farts produced by cars
and bikes driving down that driveway,
she developed a disease that makes her cough a lot!
Farts?
Maybe he means the exhaust gas.
Toto-sama keeps smashing people's
cars and motorcycles in a rage of fury.
But what Toto-sama does...
I know that it is not a good thing.
He only brings more trouble to our friends!
Because we are friends with people, aren't we?
Yeah! Friends.
If Kaka-sama's illness is cured,
Toto-sama will be placated.
So I went and asked Tanuki Hermit
for a way to cure the illness.
On the Kobonchi Mountain far away,
there grows a medicinal herb called the Rainbow Color,
from which the medicine can be made.
Alright, let’s set out!
I’m going to the Kobonchi Mountain
to get that medicinal herb!
I’ll cure Kaka-sama's illness
and stop Toto-sama's rampage.
So thinking, I set out on the journey.
That is, until I got caught
by a human during my journey.
The rest you already know, I believe.
It must’ve been hard for you!
Tanukichi-kun...
This guy's been through a lot.
Hey, everyone! Let's go look for the medicinal herb
together with Tanukichi-kun! Okay?
Yeah! Good idea, Iyona-chan.
Yeah! We’re going.
I knew humans are our true friends!
Thank you, snort! Thank you!
Always Captivating Tama-chan, please tell us...
Where is the Kobonchi Mountain on which the herb grows?
Give me just a moment.
Try turning to the next page.
It’s right here.
Okay, let’s make haste.
My car, Perillo Rastatessa
boasts a top speed of 290km/h.
Naturally, its driveability and comfort are also world class...
No! We can’t take a car.
After all, Tanukichi-kun's mother...
It was the cars that caused her to fall ill.
Yeah! We'll all walk on foot.
That's stupid!
It’d take us a month to get there,
walking on our itsy-bitsy pace!
It's alright. With my magic,
we can make it there by walking.
This - Stretch-Beer! If you drink this,
you can stretch your body however you want.
Taru, are you sure it’s alright for us to drink beer?
It’s fine.
This Stretch-Beer is a magical beer,
different from the beer dad drinks.
Though, the side-effect
of feeling drowsy is still there!
We’ll be fine if we drink just a bit.
I see. Then...
Rich flavor and pure taste.
That’s yummy!
I think I'm pretty drunk already.
Then, set out to the Kobonchi Mountain!
Yeah!
Drunk...
Ah, I beg your pardon!
Jabao-san, that’s a strange way we grew up in.
Yeah...
Look! An astonishing view!
Taru-chan, Kobonchi Mountain is over there.
Alright, let's go, everyone!
He covered it in just one step!
All the way over there?
Let's go!
This way,
we can walk there...
Hey, did you find it?
Not yet!
I can't find anything even remotely similar!
Is it really even here?
Found it! It’s this!
This is it. The medicinal herb.
Honmaru-sama...
Thank you very much!
With this, Kaka-sama's illness can be cured!
Well done, Honmaru.
Well, let’s hurry to Tanukichi-kun's home now.
Yeah!
Cheers!
Still, it makes me feel kinda weird.
So hot here...
It's great!
How 'bout it? Are we goin' to Dotamakin Valley or not?
Yeah!
Jabao-san, we’ve done it again.
These things the people ride
do like to fart a stupid lot!
It's not a fart.
It's called exhaust gas.
Looks to me like a fart, alright.
This guy Tanukichi sure loves a good joke!
It’s here.
Climb down here to get to my home.
Shinkin Valley
We’re almost there, snort.
Taru!
Taru! Are you okay?
Me weak from beer...
Honmaru! Is Taru al... right?
What a truly captivating place!
Thank you, everysnort.
My home is a snort walk from here.
Well, farewell!
Tanukichi! Are you safe?
Toto-sama!
I was worried, son.
Toto-sama! Those people are friends of mine, snort!
Friends?
That's right! Please let them out of the cage!
Cretin!
Tanukichi!
Humans are the enemy! The devils!
Why’d you ever think they’re friends?
Go cool your head!
I’m drowning! Drowning...
You humans are the root of my wife’s illness!
You also capture our kin, put us in cages
and toy with us to death!
Put in cages... as toys?
That's why I too
took it upon myself to
do exactly the same to you people!
I’ll keep you in that cage until you die!
You can’t do that!
That's right!
That’s awfully tyrannic of you!
Taru!
Hey, Taru, wake up!
Keeping me, the World Junior
Pet Contest Champion as a pet?
Hey, what are you saying at a time like this?
He’s right. So far, we humans
did nothing but harm them.
Are you scared? Are you terrified?
Still, it’s exactly what you humans do all the time!
We’re sorry, Toto the Tanuki.
You have every right to lock us up in this cage.
Oh?
I...
will stay here.
What are you saying, Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan,
I'm staying too.
Tanukichi's father!
I want you to play with me as
your pet for the rest of my life!
Honmaru-kun...
Maybe this'll lead to everyone
leaving me and Iyona-chan alone here?
Doesn’t sound half-bad, actually.
Staying here exempts me from school and studying!
Besides...
Iyona-chan!
What?
Why don’t you move closer to me?
Honmaru, I'm the World Champion of the Being Played Around to Death Contest!
Think I’ll let you have all the fame to yourself?
You cretin!
I’m the one who'll stay here!
Jabao-san, are you quite in your mind?
If Iyona-chan stays, so do I!
Oh, you...
These children...
Toto-sama!
Is that...
These people went there to look for this herb with me!
They’re my precious friends!
What?!
Well... I'm awfully sorry, alright.
I put our virtuous friends who went to all the trouble of finding it in the cage!
Thank you so much!
Thanks to you, I feel a lot better now.
Really, you’re so quick to jump to wrong conclusions, Toto-sama.
This was a piece of cake anyhow!
But...
Humanity will only keep encroaching
more and more on this peaceful mountain.
Tama-chan, please!
Let’s see.
For that case, you could use Protectapple.
Yeah!
What do you do with this thing?
Bury.
This - tree of Protectapple.
This tree will protect the valley
from the car farts and bad humans.
Then, if we plant this tree all around Dotamakin Valley,
we could live forever in peace, right?
Precisely!
But Taru’s magic only lasts ten minutes, doesn’t it?
It'll be alright.
This tree is not going to grow
as a result of Taru-chan's magic.
Therefore, it’ll stay forever.
Oh! Ain’t that great?
Good for you, Tanukichi!
All's well that ends well.
Well, if there's something you don't understand,
please feel free to ask me,
the World Junior Intellect Champion, anytime.
Don’t give up, Tanukichi!
Everyone...
Thank you ever so much!
Don’t need thanks. We’re friends.
Yes, friendsnort!
Friends!
In the warm spring sunset,
the sakura petals flutter down.
Showered in the slanted rays of the springtime sun,
you’re singing absentmindedly in the heat haze.
Iyona-chan, why do you dance so cheerfully?
Iyona-chan! Is your love really infinite
for everyone and everything?
Can’t I make that love mine? Just mine?!
Episode 82
I Love Everyone❤
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
I Love Everyone!
In spring, people are enshrouded in love!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius