Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Once upon a time, a Prince of the Star
landed on our earth.
However, a family of very wicked people found him, and made
the star prince go through many wicked tribulations.
He couldn't bear it and died!
But the tears he shed then became stars.
And thus, the star prince
had returned to the sky where he belonged.
Poor thing!
My poor Taru-sama!
Episode 30
Mimora's Great Rampage!
Come on, we can start now, Taru.
Okay!
Rinse-rinse! Rinse-rinse!
Alright!
It tickles! Rub-rub.
Catch this!
Touch!
Taru, we've almost finished doing the dishes.
Yeah! Not holding back!
Mimora?
Why, if it isn't Mimora-chan?
Your bullying of Taru-sama ends here!
You talking to me?
Exactly so!
What more proof than this do you need?
But you're mistaken! Right, Taru?
You may have pulled a wool over Taru-sama's eyes,
but you're not pulling anything over mine!
Isn't that one of dad's recent fairy tales,
Prince of the Star?
I know it's no mere fairy tale!
It's just your papa retelling the true events,
bragging about his fortune!
My poor Taruruuto-sama...
Being made to work for this wicked house,
you'll end up withering yourself away!
Whose house are you calling wicked?!
My dad made up this story all along!
And who in their right mind
would call Taru a Prince of the Star?
Taru-sama!
If only you insist on staying in this world no matter what,
I shan't bother you any longer.
However, should this wicked house fall out of your favor...
Listen, you...
There's always a more suiting house,
where you'd be altogether welcome and surrounded with love!
And you definitely want me to show you the way!
Very well. Just follow me, Taru-sama...
I love Honmaru's house.
Taru-sama...
My!
The clean-up here is already over.
Thank you, Taru-chan. And Honmaru, too.
Here, for your trouble.
We got it, Honmaru!
Thank you, mom.
So you're the mama of the Wicked House?
Mom, remember how I told you
about Taru's girlfriend, Mimora-chan?
My! You've an eye for cute girls, Taru-chan.
Mimora-chan, I won't get in the way.
Please enjoy each other's company.
Honmaru! I go to buy Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Yeah! Not without me!
Let's go!
Taru-sama...
If Mimora-chan cries, we're six feet under!
Taru! Console Mimora-chan this instant!
Mimora... Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Mimora... Matsu-san Takoyaki!
Mimora-chan! No need to cry! Taru is right here, see?
Now, feel free to love him to your heart's content!
Taru-sama!
Good thinking, Taru.
Niruru won't ever give us away.
It's not very fair towards Mimora-chan,
but it's just until she returns home!
Yeah!
Hey, Matsu-san! Business goin'?
Taru-sama, we've finally been left all to ourselves.
You're being so unbelievably bold today!
Then, I should return your love using the same language.
Lick-lick.
Huh? Ah!
A yumster! Matsu-san's takoyaki never disappoints!
Matsu-san! Give more!
As usual, your enthusiasm at gobbling 'em is spectacular!
Aight! Matsugoro's original invention,
Naniwa's famous takoyaki!
Ain't nothing you can't bake
if you put your guts into it!
Matsu-san's takoyaki is still the best ever! Right, Taru?
A fine example of abusing my trust on your part.
Mimora-chan...
Mimora... For me...
You needn't say anything,
as I already know you better than anyone else.
Once again, you've been tempted away by this man!
But I shall put a decisive end to this!
Who might this tiny thing be?
Her name's Mimora-chan.
She's Taru's girlfriend, sort of.
Taru-chan is already a hitched fella, huh?
Aight, then! Here's a wedding present
for Taru and his lass from Matsugoro!
Takoyaki!
Taru-sama, your infatuation with takoyaki
must have also been a result
of you feeling underfed in this man's house!
Oh, my poor Taru-sama!
But that's so obviously untrue, Mimora-chan...
Takoyaki, takoyaki, takoyaki! Takoyaki.
The way you used foods
to control Taru-sama's mind is just disgraceful!
Such a thing...
only deserves this!
Whoa! Takoyaki!
Da hell's the meaning of this?
Those were the takoyaki
I made by putting my whole heart in!
I daresay they're like my sweet children to me,
and then ya go ahead dare stomping on 'em! Yes, you!
Not even to a little girl could such a thing be forgiven!
Matsu-san, this is bad!
Takoyaki, so happy you safe...
Matsu-san, this is bad! Very bad!
You're probably right. I've been rash,
raising my voice at Taruyan's girlfriend.
Aye, my bad, ma'am.
I didn't mean this!
Taru-sama, that...
was the final straw!
All hell's broken loose...
Taru-sama's love for takoyaki is bigger than that for me!
It's a misunderstanding, Mimora-chan!
Taruruuto may be head over heels for takoyaki,
but even more so for you!
Is that so, Taru-sama?
Come on, come on, come on, Taru!
Yeah! Me love Mimora.
Taru-sama...
And love Honmaru, too...
Don't pay me no mind!
Would you ever be able to forgive my short-sighted self
for doubting your love, Taru-sama?
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama, you should be careful not to catch a cold,
going to sleep in a place like that!
Let's return to the suspicious person's house for now.
Okay!
Well, isn't that a great promotion -
from wicked to just suspicious house?
Even should you get mistreated
in the wicked house once again,
I, Mimora, will always be there to protect you!
Shall we go, Taru-sama?
Yeah.
Say, isn't Taruyan's girlfriend a mighty jealous lass?
Honmaru, look after the house, will you?
We should be back by evening.
Okay.
I'm counting on you, Honmaru.
Left behind to look after the house now, of all times!
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama...
Taru-sama, I'm the happiest I've ever been!
Oh, I can't take any more of this stupid show!
I so wish Iyona-chan would be making out with me, too!
Calm down, Niruru.
I appreciate it that you're comforting me.
Thanks, man!
Honmaru, me comforu-ru-ruting, too!
Taru-sama...
You brought me to tears!
If Mimora-chan cries again,
the whole city will go rack and ruin!
Taru, you gotta do something!
Okay!
Mimora, comfort-comfort.
Mimora, not cry, not cry.
You can do it, Taru!
That's the way, Taru!
Just a lick more!
Magic: Funny Face.
Oh my, Taru-sama!
Mimora laughed, all's well.
That's well for certain.
Good job, Taru.
Taru, you gotta stop her now!
Oh, I'm gonna laugh my head off!
Taru, make haste!
Mimora!
Gyahahaha
Taru!
Honmaru buried under!
Right, Attractor-kun can...
Honmaru!
Honmaru secured!
Taru...
Honmaru, Power-Upple Juice will help.
Hooray, Honmaru!
Nothing to "hurray" about!
Look at this! Our house is reduced to shambles...
When dad and mom return home,
they'll be mad beyond belief!
Taru, where's Mimora-chan?
Ah! I laughed so heartily!
Taru-sama!
Can I have your funny face just once more?
Sure!
Like hell you will!
Stingy!
Mimora-chan, take a look
at what you did to our wicked house...
We don't even have a roof over our heads,
let alone any means to feed Taru!
Even though for me, for my dad and mom,
it was the most precious palace of a thousand memories...
It was the only house we ever had!
All of that is smashed to smithereens now!
By this stupid girl!
I'm... stupid?
Crap! Taru!
That was the final straw!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, some more of Power-Upple Juice should help.
Here.
Mimora,
this house Honmaru valued a great deal.
This you collapsed, Mimora.
Oh, really?
Oh, really, you questioning it?!
It's like this wrench
is trying to vex me with her feigned ignorance!
But if I let my anger rein,
it'll be another "final straw" for me!
Mimora, show me something you value.
Sure. The star-shaped stone you gave me once.
I value it the great deal!
Bam!
Taru...
What have you done, Taru-sama...
So cruel! How come...
How come...?
Know some shame, Taru!
That was a thing Mimora-chan really valued...
This star-shaped stone - Mimora valued a great deal.
Me crushed it. Me did.
I'm so sorry, Honmaru-sama!
You valued so deeply this house I destroyed!
I can finally understand your feelings right now!
Forgiveness... I beg your forgiveness!
It's fine, it's enough that you figured it out.
So you don't have to pull it so hard...
Oh, you just let me fix this inconvenience
with my magic at once!
Matches
Problematches-kun. When you got a problem,
these matches help with it in a variety of ways.
Let's see... This color should do.
A step back please, you two!
Turns out, even she has some good sides
to complement her destructive ones.
It's not every day that she apologizes so sincerely.
Go for it, Mimora-chan!
What did you do this for?!
All's become fire, instead of fine!
What's this?
Let me mold out a house tenfold as gorgeous!
Knead-knead, let's knead you good.
It's done!
Taru-sama! Would you do me the honor
of casting an enlarging spell?
Sure!
Grow like mushru-ru-rooms!
What do you think?
A gorgeous house, isn't it?
How do you expect me to live in this?!
I should be too ashamed to even admit I live in this!
Wow! Gorgeous!
Iyona-chan?
Honmaru-kun went ahead and renovated his house?
It's incredibly cute now!
I'm not sure if it'll do for us, a house like this...
Certainly!
Then, wanna check it out?
My, I'd be delighted. Thanks.
Whoa! It's even more gorgeous from the inside.
A world straight out of a fairy tale.
Wish I could live in a house like that, too!
Please do, please do!
Good job, Mimora-chan!
Mimora, here.
Star-shaped stone! But how?
Me the Great Magician.
I crushed faux stone.
Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan, it's been a while.
Well, what do you know!
Time to start making out with Iyona-chan, too!
Ah? What's that?
Shoot! Ten minutes passed and Taru's magic wears off!
My! What happened here?
Hang on, Iyona-chan!
Taru! Enough laughing! Do something about it!
Taruruuto, Honmaru,
where the hell is the house?!
Here, Taru-sama. Say "aaah".
Aaah.
How odd. Was I merely daydreaming back then?
Iyona-chan, better not get hung up on it
and finish your meal!
Mimora-chan, Niruru, make sure to eat until you're full.
Right, right!
Still, even if it was a dream, it was a lovely one.
My, my! Turns out, Honmaru-sama
and his house are nowhere near wicked!
Right, Taru-sama?
Is that all we deserve?
But well, that's about as much
as you can get out of Mimora-chan, I guess.
Hey, Honmaru, what's the matter? Looking dazed.
Eh? Taru? Oh, it's nothing.
But Iyona-chan sure is cute...
Especially, at this time of the year.
It's spring, after all!
If only she'd fall in love with me...
Honmaru, trust me to do this.
Episode 31
In Spring, Love is in the Air
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
In Spring, Love is in the Air.
I'll handle this, too!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius