Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
I forgot to do my homework!
Episode 15
Cold Outbreak in Honmaru's Family
What to do, what to do, what to do, what to do?
What to do, what to do—
If Ms. Oaya finds out...
Taru? Taru! Taru-chan!
Please!
You have to help me with magic, somehow!
Come on, Taru!
Crap, time's almost up!
Looks like I'd sooner do the homework myself
than get Taru to wake up!
Gonna start right now!
Honmaru, are you awake?
Honmaru!
Get up, or else you'll be late again!
Honmaru?
I heard you, alright?
I'm up already!
Then hurry up downstairs!
If you don't finish your breakfast soon,
you'll be late for school!
School-school-school-school!
I don't wanna go!
Might as well play hooky!
Playing hooky...
That last time three years ago.
That's enough!
I won't ever do that, dad!
Honmaru! I don't remember bringing you up
as a kind of man who'd be playing hooky!
Not an option!
If only I could catch a cold or something!
Cold-cold-cold-cold, need to catch!
With a cold, I can catch myself
a day off from school! Cold!
Taru's sister?
Say... What was it you made me drink just now?
A cold medicide that gives you a cold
if you drink it - Virus-kun.
You said you wanted a cold, didn't you?
I swear to God...
Still in bed?
Oh?
Oh dear!
That's a terrible fever.
Stay put while I fetch something, okay?
Honmaru, what's the ruckus?
Sister Ria's cold medicine...
made me catch a cold.
With this, I get a day off from school...
And in ten minutes, I return to normal.
Just gotta hold on for ten minutes.
Honmaru! Sis' magic
doesn't expire in ten minutes!
Wha...
My magic lasts for ten years.
Ten years?
Did she say "ten years?"
Honmaru, congratulations on your coming of age.
Coming of age ceremony
Yes, quite the feat.
Today, you can drink with us, too.
Lies!
Sister's magic lasts ten days.
Come to think of it, I guess you're right.
Still, suffering through this for ten days straight?
No way, I can't take it!
You can transfer it to anyone with health weaker than yours,
then you'll recover immediately.
However, the person receiving it
will suffer twice as much.
I can't possibly do that!
Taru! You should be able to cure me with magic!
Alright! Honmaru, transfer it to me!
Honmaru, you'll bonk me with this.
This Hale-Pale Hammer Switch-kun.
Hale
Pale
Hit one with pale side - he becomes weak.
So let's weaken me!
You reap what you sow.
Even I myself don't know a spell that'd lift that cold.
But you can always just wait ten days.
Alright... Let's make big sister into weak sickster.
Aren't you glad, Honmaru?
You get to rest from school for ten whole days.
Well, I don't plan on catching it myself, so adieu.
Crap!
I accidentally hit myself with the hale side
and became stronger. Sorry Honmaru.
So much stronger!
Honmaru.
Oh my! We need to get him to see the doctor ASAP.
Doctor cures if you go see him?
Doctor great magician!
Darling. Darling!
Papa. Papa!
What is it?
Honmaru has a terrible fever.
Can you get him to see the doctor?
You half-wit!
Isn't it just a cold?
A true man should be hard as stones,
provided yours are still in place!
Stones?
In place!
A true man needs but willpower to recover.
Darling!
Stones seem in place!
Honmaru, don't you lose heart.
Mom will get you examined in the shortest time.
Mama, quickly, put these on!
I think they're a bit tight for me.
You'll be fine.
They'll adjust to your feet.
Mama-san!
Rushing where to?
Well, could you rush us to Kobayashi Clinic?
Kobayashi Clinic then?
Aye, roger that!
Calculating shortest straight course.
Target acquired!
Let's go!
Ignition!
Running Godspeed!
When wearing Godspeed Slippers,
you can run and jump at a great, divine speed!
Keep it up, mama!
They're such a hard-working bunch!
Pardon the intrusion!
...intrusion!
Honmaru...
I'm running late!
Attending school at full power!
What was that just now?
Mama, Godspeed Slippers
sure are convenient, aren't they?
But this all seems just a bit dangerous.
Kobayashi Clinic
Have no worries, nothing more than a common cold.
He just needs to take the medicine
and have a good rest.
Thank you very much!
I only said that to spare her some worries,
but what the hell was that, really?
I've never seen a cold like that before!
Even after he took the medicine,
the fever won't ease off one bit!
That magician is not to be trusted.
Mama, I will help, too.
Thank you, Taru-ch...
Mama!
I'm cured!
Honmaru, it's mama!
Mom!
Mom, hang on!
Mama!
I ended up transferring my cold to mom!
Mama got her health weakened
from running in Godspeed Slippers!
If you transfer it to another,
you're immediately cured.
However, the one receiving it
suffers twice as much.
Things deteriorated to this
just because I wanted to play hooky once...
Mom!
Don't worry about me.
Instead, Honmaru, return to bed soon.
I don't need curing anymore!
It's not me you should be concerned about!
Really? Isn't that a relief, Honma...
Mom!
There's nothing relieving about this!
Mama, sleep tight.
What was that roar just now?
It was as though it came from the bathroom. Let's go!
What was that?
Sister!
Nothing serious.
A guy tried to peep into the bathroom from over there.
So I summoned Hanako the Thundercloud
to send him my frying regards.
Hanako Thundercloud here.
You won't find better deals on lightning anywhere!
Honmaru, did you transfer the cold to somebody else?
This time, mom caught it.
Sis, is there really no magic to lift it?
Not to my knowledge.
Taru, your sister is heartless!
Papa!
Honmaru, did you recover?
What in the world happened to you?
All charred!
No, nothing...
There was a bolt from the blue.
Dad was the one
spying on sister Ria taking a bath?
Papa!
Mama is ill!
Dad, I need your help!
Dad!
Do you know a way to cure a magical cold?
Mom caught it now!
Papa has the Great Magic Encyclopedia!
Shut it! I'm busy now!
Instead of goofing around,
you could at least try to look after her!
Dad!
Mom is suffering right now!
You have to tell me
how to cure magical ailments!
It's no time to lock yourself away
because you've been exposed peeping!
Mom is already suffering
twice of what I had to go through!
Dad!
Dad, open up!
You're one rotten dad for playing deaf like that!
Honmaru, let's ask Tama-chan.
Tama-chan knows all and every thing!
Of course!
Pretty and magnanimous, omnipotent...
Is there anything at all?
Tama-chan, hurry up and show us!
Please, Tama-chan, let us know.
Give me just a moment.
With the Sorcera-masaron herb,
you can make the medicine.
I've never heard of any such thing!
Where do we find it?
It's some rare grass, isn't it?
There's some in your garden.
In the garden?
Are you sure you ain't messing with us?
Let's hurry, Honmaru!
Yeah...
Tranquility Leaf
Cardiac Cranesbeard
Wound-healing pyrola
Sorcera-masaron
There it is!
We've been cultivating it right here!
And it's been reduced to this...
The lightning that Thundercloud Hanako
dropped earlier fried those as well!
Because dad couldn't handle
his peeping urge, it came to this!
The herb!
Okay...
Mom, just a little longer!
Honmaru!
See you!
Take care.
Farewell.
Jabao!
Honmaru?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you miss school
cause you caught a cold?
Told you he was just playing hooky, Jabao-san.
Exactly!
I just wanted to play hooky.
But I ended up catching a real cold!
And now, because I've been selfish,
mom went down with the cold next!
She's suffering twice as much!
What's all that nonsense?
Just forget it and hit me as hard as you can!
Even if you're asking for it yourself,
this is all so sudden...
Either you hit me,
or I'll make you regret you didn't!
I say, Honmaru seems
mighty short-fused today, Jabao-san.
Better safe than sorry, my good sir!
Jabao! Will you hit me or will you not?
Decide already!
Okay, okay. I'll hit.
I'll hit, ya heard me?
No hard feelings!
I even hurt my own hand.
What a crank!
Jabao!
Not there yet!
Are you even trying?
At least put some spine in your hits!
Not there yet... yet...
What have I done?!
Jabao-san!
Now, with my body so weakened,
mom should have no trouble transferring her cold to me.
Honmaru...
But why?
Why won't it transfer to me?
What's that nonsense you're saying?
Must be Virus-kun not sticking to those
who had already been through cold.
That's just absurd!
Mama looks in pain.
Damn... Sister Ria is an iceberg,
and dad is a scoundrel!
Even when mom is in such a sorry state,
there's no one able to help her!
Honmaru, we'll ask Tama-chan
once again where to look for herb.
Alright, Taruruuto. If need be,
we'll travel to the end of the Earth, looking for it!
Hang on just a bit, mom.
We'll be back with it in no time!
Mama, don't give up!
Not a step more, you two!
Firstly, have you got any idea what time it is?
Kids have no business
roaming the streets at night by themselves!
Honmaru, you've been confined to bed yourself
just mere hours ago!
You shouldn't be worried about me...
Mama.
Mom!
I understand.
Honmaru, tonight I look after
and don't go to sleep!
Yeah. And first thing in the morning,
we go look for the herb!
Well, that's a pleasant morning
if I've ever seen one!
Yeah!
Ah, I'm starving!
Mom, how's breakfast?
...fast!
What's that?
Did mom oversleep today?
Honmaru mama's cold!
Honmaru, Taru-chan?
Mama lively again!
Mom!
Sorry for making you all so worried.
Great Magic Encyclopedia!
Following the recipe from the Great Magic Encyclopedia,
dad prepared a treatment for me.
It's working wonders already.
Papa good guy!
That means... you went there
not to peep into the bathroom, but for herbs...
I'm sorry for misjudging you!
Darling.
Thank you for sacrificing your night's sleep
in order to look after me.
I got much better already.
Papa, thank you.
I see. Dad did, huh?
I need to return to my own work.
Dad.
Exactly what I'd expect my dad to do!
Dad!
Father... This is bad!
I don't like that face color!
Magical cold transferred to papa!
We'll all be looking after you,
so set your worries aside, dad.
This time, Taru and I will make the medicine for you.
Cut that crap!
I need but my own determination to recover!
Papa so cool!
Don't exert yourself, dad!
Papa...
Dad!
Honmaru, whenever you feel
like skipping school again, I'm here to help.
You won't trick me into playing hooky again, no sir!
Pain, oh pain, fly the hell away!
Honmaru, this looks like lots of fun.
Don't you know, Taruruuto?
We're having a Christmas party at school!
What present should I give Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, unfair, unfair!
I make a present for Iyona, too!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Takoyaki Christmas.
Episode 16
Takoyaki Christmas
Everyone, celebrate with us!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius