Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru, impressive! Got 5 points.
Ah, idiot...
Taru!
Ah, why is it that I'm so stupid?
What is it again? Your test score.
Ijigawa!
Honmaru, you truly are
one he...
...ll of a blockhead!
What the hell?
Who are you to be talking like that?!
Someone better than you.
Who cares about tests?
At least I'm nowhere near as mean as you!
I'm Ijigawa Rui, remember?
My name is literally "mean-spirited!"
Taru!
However...
You're both dense in the head,
and fragile in a fight!
You're a bungler, plus terribly short-tempered!
Fickle in love and inattentive in life!
What's more, with that unkempt
bed hair on your stupid round head!
Weak ankles, and drooping outer corners of the eyes!
I can't get a break...
Honmaru-kun...
And somewhere in there, there's stupidity so profound
it's irreparable at this point. Right, people?
Exactly! Not only is Honmaru's intelligence
pathetic, so is his face!
Weak in a fight, yet extremely touchy!
Let's not forget selfish.
Shit, shit, shit... I still can't come up with a retort...
Episode 39
Good Honmaru, Bad Honmaru
Dammit... They really didn't have to go that far!
Everyone is telling me off,
all while turning a blind eye to their own shortcomings!
Ijigawa in particular, but at least
she doesn't usually go that far!
Isn't there any item that'd help me outargue Ijigawa, Taru?
Taru!
Honmaru, me starving.
Taru, hear me out at least once, please.
Sure!
What is it, Honmaru? Speak out.
Thing is...
Oh?
What happened to Honmaru-kun?
Getting withdrawn
from embarrassment somewhere, I imagine!
Oh?
What's this thing?
This - Perspective-Changing Spectacles Good-Bad-kun.
When wearing them this way, you can only see
everyone's bad sides, and can't stop badmouthing them.
But if you turn them around, you start seeing
everyone's good sides and become all-loving!
Oh? Sounds like fun.
But this is a dangerous tool.
Honmaru.
Is this really how Taru looks?
He's somehow repulsing this way.
Taru! Do you find joy in constantly harassing me with your weird magic gizmos that get me in all sorts of trouble?
I don't, Honmaru!
I only ever use magic for your good.
Ha! For my good? I ain't buying it.
I see! You use magic to mess with me
to make me into a bad guy, don't you?
I don't!
Always pulling that cute and innocent act.
And what's with those fat puffy cheeks, huh?
I just keep and keep slandering him!
Honmaru...
You're the most disgusting type of guy!
Keep crying, you wimp!
Oh no!
Honmaru came to hate me... Hate me!
I'm sorry, Taru!
I don't know what's gotten into me just now!
Honmaru, do you hate me?
No! I love you!
Really?
Really, I say. Really!
Yay! Honmaru!
Alright. Using these spectacles involves a bit of danger,
but it's just what I need against Ijigawa!
Ijigawa.
What is it?
You have the look of a demon in your eyes!
And where did this come from?
And you don't even realize that ribbon
is not one bit becoming to your face!
What the hell?
Lunch!
Funny how you're usually the one so igno...
Man, you sure have one twisted friggin' personality.
I can see right through you.
I know you're actually a "faint of heart" kinda girl.
What did you say?
So to keep it a secret,
you turn to hurting others!
Ha! Pardon my frankness, but you're a mess, girl!
What's gotten into you, Honmaru?
Telling me things like that...
Jeez!
That's just the kinda fella you are.
Rui-chan...
Please call me the black magician of words now!
Alright!
There!
That's it, Jabao-san!
Just as I praised you...
Why, you! How can you be so gutless, Korekiyo?
Jabao.
What is it, Honmaru?
You wanna play with us?
Eck! And you have a face like a worn-out boot!
Your hair's growing like an eggplant!
The hell?!
In class, you're the only one
universally hated by everyone.
Some just hang out with you reluctantly,
knowing you'll beat 'em up otherwise.
What?
That's not true!
You have absolutely zero merit to you,
and you're stupid to boot.
Also with 30 kilograms of fat in that belly.
You ass...
Look, just as I said!
Brandishing your strength as soon as you have a chance!
That's exactly what everyone hates you for!
Huh? Huh? Huh? What's wrong, Jabao-kun?
Shut up!
You'll regret it, Honmaru!
Flawless.
Telling Jabao-san off like that...
A terrifying audacity!
Harako.
You have the face of a grandpa!
Aren't you embarrassed?
Consider comparing yourself to the others someday.
Wh...
What?!
Frankly speaking, it's abnormal!
Did you say, "abnormal?"
You'll pay for it, Honmaru!
The world's Pretty Boys Carnival special prize winner,
first president of the Dreamboats League,
as well as the undisputed favorite
of the "Blonde Beauties of the World" convention,
I won't tolerate your "grandpa" insult!
Huh?
This guy's an amazing find!
Once I've started, nobody can put up any resistance!
Best feeling ever!
Best feeling ever...
Ah! Iyona-chan's there.
Honmaru-kun, um...
Whaddya want?
Wanna give me a lecture, young lady?
Foisting your ostensible kindness again?
I'd never...
This is bad... What the hell am I saying?!
Lecturing you...
Is there really any point for a woman as stuck-up as you
to try to understand the feelings of a deadbeat like me?
Oh, I just keep digging myself deeper!
You casually succeed in everything you do,
making us earthly beings look miserable in comparison.
Gotta stop. Gotta stop!
The very existence of people like you is the root of evil.
Honmaru!
Take Good-Bad-kun off!
This is getting dangerous!
Piss off!
I've realized it myself a long time ago!
But still...
If you don't do it fast, you'll be under
the slandering spell for the rest of your life!
Eh?
How did it come to this?
Honmaru. Honmaru!
Help me, Taru!
Honmaru-kun...
You think tears look good on your pretty face.
You just self-induced that, didn't you?
Don't bother answering!
I've no fancy for talking to the likes of you!
How can you...
Honmaru! Take off Good-Bad-kun, fast!
Feel free to break into tears
and dash away from me to all four winds!
You know everyone else
would welcome you with open arms!
"Oh, our poor sweet girl!"
No way! Ain't no way! I need to take it off at once!
This is an item of unfathomable power!
Honmaru-kun, what's gotten into you?
Still hasn't given up on me?
I'm just telling you the truth, nothing more!
The worst part of saying such horrible things to her
is that it feels so good! Shit...
Honmaru! Hurry! Take them off!
Honmaru!
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun.
When you told me about it, I could understand.
So many things came to mind...
Ah, I'm so screwed...
I said some terrible things
while under the spell of the spectacles!
I'm truly sorry.
I hurt you deeply, without realizing it.
Forgive me!
There wasn't anything of the kind!
When you turn them around, you start seeing
good about people and become all-loving.
What do I do?
Come what may!
Iyona-chan suddenly looks like an angel!
This light, this warmth...
How could I say something like that
to a divine being?
I deeply apologize for saying such lousy things.
Iyona-sama, is there any way I could make amends?
Honmaru-kun, you... Really...
All the time, I'm only thinking about myself.
While you bestow the world with deep affection...
Ah, the light is too dazzling.
I don't deserve to stay in your presence any longer!
I'm sorry!
Jabao-san, Korekiyo-san, Ijigawa-san, Harako-san!
All of them are people of the highest virtue!
And me... Me?
How may I ever come close to that?
Young ladies.
Fancy a cup of tea?
Elementary school students
grow like mushrooms these days.
Let's hang out a spell, okay?
Hasn't you teacher ever told you
not to make detours on your way from school?
Right. That's what the teacher said.
The teacher said so, huh?
Look...
Stop it, please.
Honmaru-kun?
And who might you be?
Iyona-san and Ijigawa-san are in trouble.
Ah Lord, thank you so much
for bestowing this chance upon me!
You tryna start something with us?
Out of the way, kid.
Come on, Iyona-san and Rui-san, hurry up!
Honmaru-kun...
Please grant me this one favor and leave.
Iyona-chan, let Honmaru deal with all this. Let's go.
But...
Hold it, ladies.
You ass!
Honmaru, is that really you?
Iyona-chan, hurry up!
Please beat me up to your heart's content.
You pissed me off!
Get this!
I'm dreadful when I'm roused!
I'm so happy...
For giving me this chance to make amends,
I think you, gentlemen, are truly virtuous!
Something's wrong with him.
Damn right.
Do you feel relieved now?
Nasty brat!
Were they able to understand
the big words of a small man such as me?
It's true what they say about the elders
all being wonderful people...
Honmaru, where did you go? Me bored.
I sure am happy!
There's not a single bad person in our world!
Honmaru!
Oh, Taruruuto-kun?
Honmaru, where were you? I've been looking.
So sorry, Taruruuto-kun.
But I assure you that not even for a moment,
I've forgotten about you!
Really?
Why would I lie to you?
Yay!
Jabao-kun!
What's wrong?
There was a TV program I wanted to watch,
but I've been made to run an errand.
If so, please let me run it in your stead.
Eh? Oh, really?
I'm kinda embarrassed.
Yay! Going shopping, going shopping!
Shopping, shopping!
Jabao, we're here!
Thank you, Honmaru-kun.
It was my pleasure.
Jabao!
Mom?
Did you send someone else instead?
No-no, I volunteered to...
Don't you embarrass us like that ever again!
Honmaru, it's all your fault!
Ah, so sorry! I've been inexcusably intrusive!
Shut up!
Please keep hitting me until you feel better.
Can't believe you've done something so unnecessary again!
Tsk! Hitting you only made me even madder!
Jabao-kun, you're granting me forgiveness
after just one beating?
Ah, what a virtuous man you are!
Your frank and straightforward personality
is what I love the most about you!
And I love Honmaru!
Taruruuto-kun, there are no words
for how marvelous these spectacles are!
I'm happy no matter what happens.
I'm glad, Honmaru.
Taruruuto-kun, thank you deeply
for coming to my rescue time after time!
Ah, what a wonderful person you are!
Wonderful person...
Eh...
What's wrong, Honmaru?
I inflicted an irreparable wound on wonderful Harako-kun
by saying he has the face of a grandpa!
I can't live if I don't make up for it somehow!
Taruruuto-kun, would you mind granting me a favor?
If possible...
can you give me a grandpa face?
Yeah!
Grandpa face...
This - Aging Pack.
Sacred Box Cream.
But this magic is a little difficult to use.
It takes overnight to start working.
If we apply the pack like this...
Honmaru, you'll have a grown-up face tomorrow.
As always, thank you for everything, Taruruuto-kun.
I'll have to return the favor one of these days.
My face...!
I have a grandpa face!
I'll be way too embarrassed to show up
before Iyona-chan and everyone, looking like this!
Taru, what did you do this for?
Honmaru, need to hurry! You'll be late again!
Ah... Shit!
Taruruuto, I'll remember it, you hear?
Honmaru!
Yesterday, Honmaru. In order to soothe Harako,
you asked me to give you the face of a grandpa.
Eh? Did I really say something like that?
Shit, I ended up saying some nonsense
because of those spectacles!
Even if I wear those spectacles with the other side out,
it's still a disastrous item!
I'm not putting those spectacles on ever again!
It's Harako!
Alright...
Harako!
Who the hell are you?
I'm wearing the very same grandpa face as you now.
Eh? Honmaru?
This makes us fellows, Harako.
Now that we have the same kind of face,
I hope you're happy.
Don't try to affiliate with me.
Nothing is grandpa-like about me.
Tsk. What's even the point of doing anything for anyone?
Eh? Honmaru?
Eh... Here we go again!
Wow! So cool!
I wonder why you've become so adult-like all around!
Honmaru-kun, thank you so much for yesterday.
And sorry we ran off without you.
Kinda sorry for yesterday, Honmaru-kun.
After all, I was the one who asked you to do the shopping.
I sincerely hope to remain friends with you
for the rest of my life.
Honmaru-kun, what happened?
You've suddenly become so cooler!
Honmaru-kun, you're really brave, aren't you?
Even with a grandpa face on,
you're still no match for me.
Taru! I'm insanely popular now thanks to that item!
Spectacles that let you see people better!
Ain't they good? The best, I say!
Honmaru seems happy.
An insanely dangerous transfer student comes to our class.
Well, that sure sucks!
All of a sudden, she tries to mount an attack on Iyona-chan.
But yesterday, when I just met her,
she seemed like a kind, innocent girl.
What the hell is going on?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Zakenja Neyo.
Episode 40
Zakenja Neyo
Alright, let's have a kendama duel!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius