Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru, go to sleep already!
Okay...
And brush your teeth before going to sleep.
You really don't need cavities in your age.
Yeah...
Did you even listen just now?
You should take after Taru-chan a bit more.
Are we clear?
Tsk, mom never stops with her tirades!
It may not look this way,
but I'm actually a master of kenpo!
I ain't so delicate as to develop a cavity!
Now, to bed we go, Taru!
Episode 70
Throbbing Tooth Bugs Infection!!
Thanks for the meal!
Today's between-meal snack​ is cake!
Between-meal snacks with Taru-sama!
Mmm, I'm so delighted!
Delicious! Me happy...
Taru, you should eat it slower!
Savor the taste and all.
I savored it plenty.
Delicious indeed! So delicate!
Really! Very sweet!
Ugh!
What's wrong, Honmaru?
Ouch-ouch-ouch! My tooth hurts!
Why?
I have a cavity! Ouch!
Cavity?
It's when bugs eat into your teeth
and it starts hurting!
Bugs? Are there bugs living in Honmaru's teeth?
Funny!
Yay! Me go catching bugs in Honmaru's mouth!
Taru, it's not the same bugs
as the insects you catch!
Alright, I'll look at bugs in Honmaru's teeth.
I see so many of them!
Don't be stupid!
The cavity bugs are just a figure of speech!
Me stupid?
Taru-sama is not one bit stupid!
Honmaru is the stupid one here
for not brushing his teeth!
What? I'll make you take that back...
Ouch-ouch-ouch-ouch...
Funny! Mimora, Niruru, let's copy it, we too!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Ouch-ouch-ouch! Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Because of the cavities, I can't eat the cake!
And now Taru is also mocking me!
Yeah!
My cake!
As expected of Taru-sama! Spectacular!
Honmaru said he can't eat any cake,
so I went ahead and ate it for him.
We're friends so it stands!
Taru!
Friendly slap!
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
Honmaru funny! Ouch-ouch-ouch!
You're so right!
Ow... Why can't magicians
do something about the cavities?
Me not have cavities.
It's the same for me.
Me wanna try keeping teeth bugs too!
So do I! It looks like lots of fun!
Are you really that amused
by the misery of another person?
If you really were my friend, you'd think
of some way to heal the cavities with magic, Taru!
Yeah! Magic for healing cavities.
Taru!
Me not know.
Honmaru, dinner is ready!
Come down soon!
Are you feeling unwell, Honmaru?
No... Not at all.
It's just that my stomach is acting up, but I'll be fine after I sleep some more.
If mom finds out I have cavities,
she'll make me go see a dentist for sure!
How can I bear going to a place so terrifying?
Then, it's better that you don't eat for some while.
But what a pity. It's the sukiyaki
you've been looking forward to.
They're also having sukiyaki now of all times!
Taru-chan, Mimora-chan, please help yourselves
to Honmaru's portion as well.
Delicious!
True! Taru-sama is lucky to have such a wonderful family!
It hurts!
You think that the man, Edojo Honmaru,
would let himself be defeated by some cavities?!
That's right! If I go to sleep,
I'll be able to forget all about the tooth.
One sheep, two sheep, three sheep...
Because the tooth started hurting so much yesterday,
I couldn't sleep a wink!
Dental Checkup Notice
A dental checkup now of all times?!
Hey, Iyona-chan.
Are you confident about your teeth?
Yes. I always brush them just in case.
I've not brushed my teeth even once in my life
and I'm feeling great!
Rather than your teeth,
your brain could use some cleaning!
What do you mean, Ijigawa?
Friends, am I the only one
actually looking forward to today's dental checkup?
What's with the bragging of confidence, Harako?
Behold! These are the beautiful teeth that shined at the
World Junior Glittering White Teeth Contest Grand Prix!
It's true! They're beautiful, Harako-kun.
What did I tell you?
So pretty!
Everyone sure is excited.
Honmaru, why unhappy?
We've a dental checkup coming up, Taru.
Yeah!
Deer.
Sword.
Lead!
Thing is, if they find out about my cavities,
they'll make me go to a dentist.
Honmaru not like dentists?
Of course I don't like them!
Ouch!
Show me the face of a guy
who'd really like to go to a place that dreadful!
Me'd like to go see the dentist.
Tsk! That's only because you've no idea
what you're talking about.
Okay, everyone. Dental checkup time.
Hurry up to the nurse's office.
Okay!
Crap! In a situation like this,
your magic is my only hope!
Taru...
Isn't there some magic
that'd help me pass the dental checkup?
I know! Taru, can't you summon Niruru?
Yeah! I have Niruru here with me.
Alright, let's do it!
He bragged about it earlier.
Harako's teeth is the safest bet!
Honmaru!
They're glistening!
Taru, make Harako open his mouth wide!
Okay!
Niruru! Only look at his teeth!
Oh, it worked!
What?
Alright, if I now stick these perfect teeth
above my own teeth... How does it look?
So?
Honmaru, it's no use.
I see... You're planning to use magic to cheat even on a dental checkup?
Better give up, Honmaru.
My distinguished teeth would never look natural
on a vulgar and rough face like yours.
They're like heaven and earth!
I thought I had a good idea for once!
Ah, Honmaru, you should be fine with this.
Lighter-ego-kun.
What does it do?
Now, let's have Niruru carry it.
Lighter-ego-kun can project the image
of the person holding it anywhere.
Honmaru, make "aah"!
My teeth look perfect,
not a single cavity!
Okay, no dental checkup can scare me now!
Scare me!
Yeah!
Okay, next one.
Thanks for your work!
Counting on you, Taru.
A beautiful set of teeth!
No cavities...
Alright, looking good!
No cavities anywhere in sight!
Those are wonderful teeth you got!
Success!
Thank you, thank you so much!
How about that, everyone? I even got praised!
Good for you, Honmaru-kun.
Honmaru, that jerk! Ain't he lucky?
I'll make everyone praised too!
Oh-ho! Not a single one!
Hooray!
No cavities!
I'm so glad!
Okay, next one.
Next one - no cavities either.
Yahoo!
Yes, next too. Next too!
Everyone has wonderful teeth!
Something's wrong with this class.
Everyone has the same set of beautiful teeth.
Everyone happy! I came up with a good idea, Niruru!
Taru-chan?
What are you doing here?
Teacher! I used magic to make everyone's teeth clean.
Really? And who asked you to do it?
Honmaru did!
Really?
Honmaru-kun!
What are you trying to cover up here?
In reality, you have a mouth full of cavities, don't you?
Must be so. I also thought it was strange.
Now you're totally going to the dentist!
Or else you'll face a severe punishment!
Okay, Teacher.
Honmaru going to the dentist!
Me going too!
Ah, in the end, they did find out...
Dentist, dentist!
Taru, lend me the Goggles for a second, will you?
I'm worried, so I wanna peak inside.
Sure! Here.
Sneak peek!
Run!
It hurts!
My tooth hurts!
I can't go to a dentist, yet my tooth hurts!
And now Oaya-sensei will also scold me!
Hey, don't worry, Honmaru.
Mimora is looking for a way
to fix tooth bugs in her magic book.
I got it!
You make yourself ethereal with Dreamen
and enter the tooth as a ghost.
There, you kick the infected tooth bugs out.
Oh, so then, becoming ethereal with Dreamen?
Whatever is fine! Let's start sooner!
Dreamen
Here, sorry for the wait.
For becoming ethereal
My teeth still hurt, but the Dreamen is good.
Delicious! Mimora's Dreamen.
I'm so glad you liked it!
Thank you for the meal!
Ouch! My teeth hurt even more as a ghost.
Becoming smaller! Trunsform.
Alright, let's have a word with the bugs!
Yes!
So that's how it is inside my mouth?
It sure could use some cleaning!
I guess I should've brushed it properly
like mom said.
Who is it over there?
That's the infected tooth bugs!
They're having a feast!
They're eating leftovers of Honmaru's food!
Dammit!
Well, I sure am full!
About time we got back to work!
Yeah! Let's get back to work!
Teeth! Teeth! Bugs! Bugs!
Your real body transmits its pain to the ethereal body through the thread.
Dammit, it hurts bad, you bastards!
You jerks!
Have you any idea how much pain you've caused
to people's teeth? You think it's all fun and games?
Get this too, you scum!
What's this? Whenever I kick one's ass,
two more appear in his place!
That's just stupid!
It hurts, it damn hurts!
Taru, help me, come on!
Honmaru, leave it to me!
Hey, everyone!
I got chestnut! Come here to munch some!
What a welcome surprise!
This is just as delicious!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
After they've eaten this, they'll feel even better, Taru!
Please have no worries.
You just need to believe in Taru-sama.
Now, I'll use this pause
to clean Honmaru's teeth with Attractor!
Yes, so will I.
Dross from Honmaru's teeth!
Yay! It's great!
I'm sorry. If only I brushed my teeth in time,
Taru and Mimora wouldn't have to go through this...
Honmaru!
Honmaru, look how much we gathered!
You must've neglected them for a long time
to accumulate this much!
Just throw it away somewhere already!
Okay!
There!
Hey, Taru!
What Honmaru forgot to eat,
we helped him to eat without forgetting!
Precisely so!
Oh, and Honmaru's teeth are now shining!
You're right!
Thank you, Taru, Mimora-chan!
Chestnuts were darn good!
Now, back to work! Let's get busy!
Taru, what are we gonna do about them?
Yay! It worked!
I'm starving...
Eating this Starvinuts makes you so hungry you can't move!
Starvinuts
You've done it, Taru!
My tooth doesn't hurt anymore!
Taru-sama never ceases to amaze me!
With this, I can now eat to my heart's content!
Man, I'm so glad!
Delicious!
Whatever I eat, it's insanely delicious!
Who'd think not having a sore tooth
can make one this happy!
Oh my...
This is all...
Thanks to Taru!
Ow!
My magic wears off in ten minutes!
It hurts!
Honmaru would have to go to dentist after all!
Dentist! Dentist! Dentist!
Why did we go through all this trouble, then?!
In this case, I wish I could at least
swap places with you...
Swap?
Sure!
I hope everything goes fine this time, Taru.
After you eat Dreamen and become ethereal,
you can switch bodies!
Thank you for the meal!
Change!
Come back soon, Taru.
Okay! I'm off!
It worked!
I had no idea such useful magic even exists!
Taru will face the most painful part for me
and my cavities will be cured!
Two birds with one stone! Yay!
Yay, yay! Dentist! Dentist!
Alright! With my cavities cured,
I could eat to my heart's content again!
That's the mother of all cavities.
It'll hurt a lot, but try to endure it.
Yay! Interesting!
Do some more of it! More, more!
More? What an enduring child!
Alright, I won't hold back.
Ah! It hurts! It hurts!
Why?! I can't take it! Come on...
Why? Ouch-ouch-ouch-ouch-ouch!
When you switch bodies under the effect of Dreamen,
you still feel the pain of your original body, Honmaru-sama!
Ah! Come on! The cavities...
I've had enough of cavities!
What?
Iyona-chan is said to be flirting profusely
with someone named Otoko?!
Iyona-chan, why? Why? Why?!
Me like Otoko too! So fresh and cool!
But I won't lose!
I'll definitely outshine Otoko
and make Iyona-chan only look at me!
Alright! Honmaru, special training!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Fresh Otoko.
Honmaru, you're about to lose...
Episode 71
Fresh Otoko
Gawk...
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius