Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Damn punk!
...With boxing!
The time is now for you to restore Japan's boxing
to its former glory with your own hands!
Episode 12
Honmaru's KO Punch
And now, finally,
the battle of the century sets off!
Coached by the World Heavyweight Mack Tynso,
World Junior Champion
boxer Harako makes an appearance.
Will his opponent, boxer Honmaru,
pose any actual challenge today?
I expect you both to show a magnificent fight.
10 seconds!
It will take me but 10 seconds
to KO his sorry ass.
You'll get a good taste
of how dreadful I can really be.
My descendants will pass it through generations.
The birth of the Legend of Harako.
Honmaru!
Don't you dare lose to this Harako dirtbag!
Try to land at least a single punch on Harako, Honmaru!
But why...
Why is exchanging blows the only option?
Can't Honmaru-kun and Harako-kun
both just get along?
With someone as prone to swinging his fists as Harako,
how can one ever get along?
The only way to get him to understand the message
is to SMACK it into his head!
Not with a sweet talk!
Round 1!
Expect a bumpy ride, Honmaru.
Do your best, Honmaru.
This pest... Gotta make sure to beat him.
After that bonkers special training from Taru and dad,
there's nothing I can't handle.
Watch closely, Iyona-chan.
At last, the starting bell rings! Ah! Boxer Honmaru
is heading straight for Harako with a rush!
Just some jabs?
I guess they taught you some basic conduct.
Honmaru,
here's your reward!
Honmaru!
Blasted idiot!
What's that about, getting hit so soon?
Boxer Honmaru is already knocked down!
Down!
Boxer Harako to a neutral corner.
The opponent is but an ordinary elementary grader.
He is no match for World Junior Champion Tsutomu.
Better call for the doctor soon.
Poor feller may kick the bucket from another one.
No, I wouldn't expect one "down" to suffice.
That kiddo definitely rises at least once.
You're kidding, right?
7!
Honmaru! Keep it together!
8!
Honmaru, stand up!
He got up at the count of 9!
What?
Honmaru-kun, are you alright?
Fight!
Honmaru, go, go!
Where are you? Harako, you pest...
I can't lose yet!
Nice balance, Honmaru!
Don't stop, Honmaru!
He did it!
That was Mack Tynso's trademark defense technique.
It requires surgical precision.
He dodges the opponent's punch by a hair's breadth.
An authentic cutting-edge technique.
Honmaru!
The hell?
What's that sudden charge?
Pesky rogue!
You've overused the trick!
Keep going!
Damn you... You still have the strength to attack?
What's the matter, Honmaru?
We're not seeing any punches land,
and yet something's hitting Honmaru!
What in the world...
Wrong.
Honmaru is receiving all of Harako's punches.
Harako throws punches
at a speed imperceptible to the eye.
Then returns the hand in place
in the same manner.
What a fearsome punch!
If he's downed again, Honmaru loses!
But we won't let Honmaru go down!
This guy, hit after hit after hit...
He won't collapse!
It's almost supernatural.
He doesn't even bother to use his eyes!
Am I merely fighting
Edojo Honmaru's spiritual projection?
First round is concluded.
Abilities' ratio has clearly been skewed towards Harako's side,
but Honmaru still managed to put up quite a fight!
You're starting to pick up the pace, Honmaru.
Good. Enough for a decent start, Honmaru.
Honmaru...
Maybe it would be better
if I just leave him to sleep like that.
After all, the gap between their abilities
is rather insurmountable.
Gloves of dad youth's blood and sweat
fight on our side, too.
It's our turn to make an appearance.
Let's do it, Honmaru!
Round 2!
Honmaru!
Came to your senses?
And now, the second round begins!
Don't hesitate, Honmaru!
Go, Tsutomu!
Just keep a cool head in the fight and you'll never lose!
Turns out, Honmaru can sting quite a bit.
Let's make it a second round KO!
Yeah!
No way in hell am I losing.
Not to a dross of your ilk!
Incredible rush!
Keep pushing! That's the way!
That boy is suddenly moving with renewed energy!
Hey! Shoots! Cross-counter! Oh my god!
Well, what do you know?
Honmaru just hit him with a cross-counter!
Boxer Harako is down!
You did it, Honmaru!
Don't give up, Honmaru!!
Burn till there's nothing left but Victory
You showed him, Honmaru.
Yeah.
7!
8!
Boxer Harako playfully rises to his feet!
Seems you got me.
He's going for it! Another cross!
Not for long!
Oh my, now it's Honmaru's turn to be down!
Get up!
Stand up, Honmaru!
6!
7!
Against all odds, Honmaru rises once again!
Fight!
Honmaru, let's go for another cross.
Go-go, Honmaru!
Such a doofus!
What?
He landed it!
Splendid, Honmaru!
Tsutomu!
Get up!
5!
Tsutomu! Unsheathe it! That punch!
OK!
That punch?
What now?
What is he trying to do,
dislocating joints in his hand?
This is
the unleashed might of the great Harako Tsutomu.
Ultimate Unstoppable Grim Reaper Technique.
Super Roaring Thunder Punch!
Honmaru, watch out!
That punch...
A variety of corkscrew with twisting the fist?
No...
To this day, no twisted fist technique
ever went beyond 180° of twisting.
This guy, however, went as far as dislocating his joints
to allow for multiple twists.
That's why he is now "winding up" his arm,
curling it clockwise.
Like this?
It makes use of the same forces as rubber band toys.
And then, all the energy that Harako accumulated
in his muscles like in a spring,
is instantaneously released
in one continuous whirl.
With dislocated joints,
it makes for an extremely far-reaching punch.
...Punch.
Sway back all you want,
you're still within his point-blank range.
Guard all you want,
it will be all for naught.
A surefire technique
for smiting the opponent.
To think that an elementary grader
would be able to throw a punch like that...
Harako Tsutomu is a monster!
They say the apple never falls far from the apple tree...
Mack Tynso!
No, no. It is not called Ultimate Unstoppable
Grim Reaper Technique for that reason.
What?
The supersonic whirl of Tsutomu's fist,
through friction with the air,
generates an enormous electric field.
That electric power
is what smites the opponent.
Therefore it goes...
Super Roaring Thunder Punch!
Don't give up, Honmaru!!
Burn till there's nothing left but Victory
8!
9!
Honmaru up!
Need one more Limpy-kun.
With Harako's photo.
My body won't move!
Honmaru has Unstoppable Shock Technique too!
No way this lowbrow is also wielding
a variety of my unique Electric Power Punch!
Anyone can get electric if they're hit in this spot.
Second round concluded!
Whatever it takes, we gotta win, Honmaru.
Ain't no way this snob is getting away with it!
Next time you faint
would be your last one!
Yeah! I won't let the special training go to waste!
Fight with all you've got, Honmaru!
Honmaru, you'll get through!
Round 3!
Now that Harako has shown his teeth with the Unstoppable
Grim Reaper Technique, how is Honmaru going to respond?
Third round begins!
Hurry up to meet the Maker!
Super Roaring Thunder Punch!
It's over.
Honmaru up!
The hell?!
Hey kid. Been a long time.
Takoyaki gramps!
Today is a Takoyaki Day, too.
Want some?
Stop it, Taru!
You shouldn't take things from strangers!
You're the father, aren't you?
For you, I might have something, too.
Secret Garden
I had you both under the magnifying glass
this entire week.
With this bizarre tyke incapacitated,
nothing stands in the way of Young Master's victory.
Can't rely on Taru to rescue you any longer!
It's up to just three of us now.
Uh-huh!
What's the point of just getting up?
Ultimate Grim Reaper Technique!
Don't run away, Honmaru!
There, you bought it.
It was a feint!
Honmaru! It is imperative that the three
work in a combination!
Stick to the teamwork!
It's a waste of Grim Reaper Technique
to use it on someone so craven!
For scum of your kind,
ordinary punch is more than enough!
Go straight to hell!
Yes, take it off...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, if you're refusing to fight,
I'll keep going even if it's just me!
Down you go!
Right Glove!
I used to be the girls' magnet, once...
But look how far I've fallen...
Honmaru, don't you let your
memories of our special training fade as well.
Don't mind me.
Move forward.
You can do this for me, right?
Right Glove!
Right Glove died!
Super Roaring Thunder Punch!
Bastard! You made my brother pay the ultimate price!
Ain't getting away with it!
You're not getting away...
Spectacular! A punch and a punch connected!
Not getting away...
Pointless.
Just tattering your own glove with electric shock.
Not getting away!
Honmaru, I can't... go on any longer...
Honmaru, you can't lose.
Win by any means!
I'm just gonna catch a shuteye...
But remember that the soul springs eternal.
The three are fighting side by side
till the end of times.
Win by any means!
There's always a way!
Third round concluded!
What a dogged renegade!
Sorry, Honmaru!
Honmaru not perky.
Drink Power-Upple Juice!
Honmaru perked up!
Why'd you do that, Honmaru?
Taru.
We've had enough of magic.
Why is it, Honmaru?
Round 4!
Honmaru, why?
Tsutomu! Finish him!
And add two more revolutions to your fist twist.
OK, Mack.
Harako Tsutomu                         Edojo Honmaru
(atomic power)                                                           (Edo castle)
Super Roaring Thunder Punch - Special!
Honmaru!
Get up! Do you really wanna lose to Harako?!
Harako! Have some honor to not go any further!
For some mechanical pencil scratching your cheek
during class, this is already overkill!
What you talking about?
It all started when Honmaru tossed a mechanical pencil
at Harako's face during class one week ago.
Back then...
Honmaru was actually trying to cover me?
Honmaru!
Did a fairly good job standing up
to the Super Roaring Thunder all the way till now.
You're done for.
I see now...
Even without Taru casting a spell on them,
gloves have a soul of their own, too.
A fire has a heart of its own, too.
Wind, water and soil -
everyone is animate.
Honmaru-kun, can you keep fighting?
Honmaru! You've done enough! Don't get up!
Honmaru wins.
This time, it's a certain damn finish!
Super Roaring Thunder Punch -
Special Two!
Electricity is alive, too.
If you touch us, you'll get electrocuted!
You'll go numb!
Let's get going, get going!
Cross-counter... Pointless.
You're just gonna get your hand zapped with the current.
What...
He's manipulating plus and minus,
going through where the current is zero!
Honmaru discovered a way.
That's it! He may have circumvented the electric charge,
but the supersonic whirl is still enough to suck him into a vortex!
It's the end for him!
It's fine.
Honmaru merged into the natural flow of things.
Power that Harako sprouts forth
will return to Harako.
What?
Boxer Harako is down!
A KO by boxer Honmaru!
Hon   Maru
V
He wins!
Honmaru! Me, me
grew to love Honmaru even more-more!
Get up, Joe...
Taruru!
Nicely done, Honmaru!
Yo!
It's been a while, no?
Atoms in the arm rebelled somehow
and electrocuted my whole body into paralysis!
You'll have a lightning-fast recovery!
Let me continue!
Please be reasonable!
Show me...
Honmaru realized the gist of magic.
Honmaru, Iyona so good with piano!
But of course, Taruruuto!
Iyona-chan excels at anything she does.
And so, I will complement it
by winning in this trump game!
Complime-me-ment her!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Unruly Birthday Party.
Honmaru bit off more than can chew!
Episode 13
Unruly Birthday Party
Everyone, look forward to it!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius