Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 84
Maddemboldening Samurai! I choose you!!
Quiet, everyone!
And now, let's start with the test.
Welcome home, Test-sama.
Test
Yeah, it's good to be home.
Would you like to take a bath?
Or do you want to eat first?
A bath.
Ah, this hot water is so nice...
Very much so.
What are you doing?
Hey, Honmaru!
You can afford being carefree,
free of any tests!
Honmaru, come take a bath with us too!
Now's not the time for that!
Honmaru's heart is pounding.
You bet it does!
I've had enough of being made fun of
as a 0-point bozo up until now!
I've studied this time around!
But the worst has yet to come -
when my results come in.
Harako, how about you?
Oh! Just what you'd expect! 95 points!
Always getting perfect scores feels trite.
I do other numbers too for diversion.
And I have 98!
What?
Oh! Iyona-chan with a perfect score of 100 points, amazing!
Your own score is just as amazing.
As expected of Iyona-chan!
Everyone performed so well on this test!
I can do it too!
What's Jabao's score?
Jabao is my only ray of hope.
No matter how bad my score is,
at the very least I won't flunk it as hard as he did!
Oh! 55 points!
What score again?!
What?! Jabao scored 55 points?
Eek!
Jabao, my eternal companion in the "0-point-brotherhood," got 55?!
When I put my mind to it, I can do it too.
You did a great job, Jabao-kun.
It sucks to be always
associated with Honmaru.
After all, you need to study to grow up -
ever heard of that?!
As expected of Jabao-san!
Catching the gist of it in a snap of a finger!
Remember, we live in an age of academic society.
Jabao got 55 points.
I'm under enormous pressure right now!
Edojo Honmaru-kun.
Yes?
0 points...
Harako got 95.
100 for Iyona-chan!
Ijigawa is at 98.
Even Jabao scored 55 on this test...
Don't look!
If anyone sees my 0 points,
they'll be laughing out loud.
Honmaru, good luck with the next one.
Yeah. He's right.
Good luck, Honmaru.
Life isn't all about test scores.
Everyone...
Through Taru's special trainings and kenpo,
he managed to develop a strong side or two.
I actually thought he was improving,
but really, his brains were shrinking...
Poor guy. 0 points again?
Somehow, I even feel bad for
mistreating someone as incapacitated as you.
So no amount of magic can help him?
This is all he got...
They say there's no cure for stupidity.
But seeing how perfectly incorrigible he is,
I'm starting to feel kinda sorry for him.
Honmaru-kun...
Even Iyona-chan is giving me a condescending look!
Stop it!
Looking at me like this...
Better just make fun of me and mock me
and laugh out loud openly like you always did before!
Even getting laughed at was still better than this!
Ah, I'm so pathetic...
It's sad, even.
Honmaru, cheer up.
Look, a beautiful bright red sunset in the sky.
Like a freshly baked takoyaki!
To me, it's the shining "0 points," Taru.
Honmaru, cheer up. There.
What's wrong, Honmaru?
You've been sighing heavily since this afternoon...
You're not feeling unwell, are you?
Not at all...
Did something happen at school?
Oh, I was just thinking,
maybe I should go on a diet or something like that...
What's this effeminate bullshit?
Oh, honey...
These days, it's a given for girls,
even in elementary school, to be on a diet.
So boys doing that sometimes
is nothing special either.
Right, right, get it?
Honmaru, dinner is delicious.
Sure. Good for you.
You'll also cheer up after you've eaten! Here!
Did it! Do more, more.
Honmaru in the bath!
Rub-rub, cheer up! There!
Like that? Honmaru cheered up?
Honmaru...
Wake up, Honmaru!
Did you wake up, Honmaru?
Look at this.
This - WhaTVer are we watching today? Telewhere.
It's a TV that lets you watch whatever you want
any time of the day.
Right now, it's Iyona taking a morning shower.
Wow, it's Iyona herself!
Honmaru's favorite nude Iyona!
Are you feeling better, Honmaru?
A morning shower, huh?
Iyona-chan sure loves keeping herself clean.
Even nude Iyona's not helping...
Honmaru seriously depressed!
Alright! Let's give you some emboldening.
How has it been going?
Honmaru not cheerful.
Please give him your emboldening.
Very well. You can leave it to me.
Are you Honmaru-dono?
Yeah...
Cheer up at once, Honmaru-dono!
Honmaru-dono is truly the man this world needs the most!
How dare you lose your spirits
over matters so insignificant?!
Somehow, my whole body is filled with strength!
Life has its hardships and its pleasures!
The secret is not to run away when facing a difficulty!
The one who stands fast and fights back
is the one who can call himself a man!
Yeah, right! Exactly!
How can I ever be stopped by something like this?
I'm the man Edojo Honmaru!
I can do this!
I'll go to school and study hard, Taru!
Yeah, I got 0 points, so what about that?!
When you're at the bottom, the only way to go is up!
I'll climb and climb, until I can score 100 or 200,
or even 10,000 points, I'll keep climbing!
That's it! Honmaru on fire!
This - Maddemboldening Samurai,
Muchaha Gemasuke.
When you hear him yelling at you,
you become madly emboldened and feel better at once.
Muchaha-sama, thank you very much.
Wait, Honmaru!
I'm coming too!
Oh! Isn't it Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun?
Morn', Iyona-chan!
Iyona, good morning.
Taru-chan...
What's wrong?
Feeling dispirited, Iyona-chan?
Iyona-chan!
My friend, angelfish Payan-chan, died.
Muchaha-sama, counting on your emboldening.
Right, feel free to leave that to me.
Iyona-dono, cheer up!
All who live will die someday!
Rather than mourn the parting, cherish the memories
you made together while they were alive!
And so, etch it in your mind that you must live
each moment to the fullest from now on too!
That's right! No matter how sad I am,
it won't bring Payan-chan back to life!
Yeah!
Instead, I will cherish each moment of my own life,
with memories of them forever in my heart!
Oh! Iyona on fire too!
That's the spirit, Iyona-chan!
I'll support you by swimming too!
What are they doing so early in the morning?
Hey, Neyo! You don't look cheerful. What's wrong?
'Preciate the attention and stuff, but unlike you,
I can't be carefree for no reason. Leave me alone!
Muchaha-sama, your services are needed here.
Got it!
Cheer up at once, Zakenja Neyo-dono!
For I have the most recent insight
into the matter distressing you right now!
Rest assured!
The one constantly on your mind, Nezo-dono,
is doing well and perfectly fine!
Nezo is?
Dwelling in a mountain retreat,
Nezo-dono strives to overcome himself!
Day and night, he's putting
his every effort into training!
Before long, having acquired even more marvelous kenpo
and changed beyond recognition, he'll be back home!
Once Nezo-dono comes home, starved,
a delicious meal must be waiting for him there!
The duty of preparing it falls on you!
Yeah! I see!
I'm relieved, Nezo!
I'll be waiting!
Yay! Neyo also on fire!
I'll be waiting, Nezo!
You'll have as much meat and potatoes as you want!
Yay, yay, yay!
Ah... I got a whopping 55 points yesterday,
but mom still wouldn't give me any pocket money.
Just when I thought I'd buy and play
that newly released game...
There are no other interesting games
to play these days.
They keep churning out new ones.
All boring, sir.
Please take care of Jabao and Korekiyo's moods as well.
Sure. There!
Cheer up, Jabao-dono, Korekiyo-dono!
What?
Sumo, sir! Sumo is more fun than any of that!
And the proof of that
is that it's Japan's national sport!
Yeah! The most popular sport right now is sumo!
Let us all stay forever young and sturdy! To battle!
Yay! It's true what they say.
Sumo is the ultimate martial arts for entertainment!
With it, you wouldn't even wanna
look at all the other games!
Ryoguchiya!
Belt grab!
Good, good! Yay, yay!
Let's embolden everyone around!
Okay!
Samurai!
Come on!
Right, to battle!
I got 95 points and Iyona-san got 100.
While I'm a whole 5 points behind,
I'm not qualified to love Iyona-chan.
Please embolden Harako too!
Oh?
Ah!
I've just bought this uniform!
Rui too!
There, there, no need to cry.
It's not a serious injury.
What do I do with you?
Teacher too!
Looks like a cloudburst is coming.
Maybe we should stop just in case?
Everyone at school, cheer up!
Cheer up at once, great many of folk!
I'll study hard so that I don't slip up,
scoring 95 ever again!
I must score the same 100 points as Iyona-san
and not a point less!
Yeah!
Who even cares if the clothes are new or not?
The woman's strength is in her body
which is under the clothes!
Shape up, shape up!
Yay! Looking good, everyone!
Yeah!
If you fortify your body,
you won't ever be afraid of injuries!
Fight! Fight!
Yeah!
Rain or no rain, it's all the same to us!
We ain't so delicate as to catch a cold!
There!
Honmaru-kun! The Warbler cries,
"Let's move to Heian-kyo" - 794 CE!
"Let's build a good country" -
Kamakura School District, 1192!
Did you get that?
Yeah! Let's go!
"A good man is he who doesn't even kill insects,"
Taika Reforms of 645 CE!
Nezo! Better come back soon!
To battle!
Yes!
Yay! Everyone motivated!
Splendid, splendid!
My magic wore off after ten minutes.
Eh?! What's this?!
Ah! All my hair fell out
and my head is as smooth as a melon!
What the hell?!
It's Taru's fault!
Taru! What the hell did you do to us all?
Ah, that's right. I remembered.
He's a Maddemboldening Samurai Muchaha Gemasuke.
Everyone emboldened. Everyone emboldened.
Everyone boldened!
Everyone balded!
Fine. Counting on you one more time.
Here.
Cheer up you, great many of people!
Why do you even care any for your head's baldness?!
The best we could do is to laugh at that!
Look at you all, having your heads
so smooth and shiny like the temple monks!
Yes, that is true!
It feels great to go home with a clear and fresh head!
Looks pretty good on you, Jabao!
It's true for anyone, Harako!
Always so neat and clean!
It's super trendy!
Yes!
Yeah!
Yay! Everyone is okay being bald!
Right, right. That's the spirit, sir!
Today at Nannosho Elementary School,
a peculiar incident occurred, during which,
all the pupils and teachers, dressed and shaved like monks,
were dancing and laughing out loud in the schoolyard.
The Ministry of Education took this situation seriously
and an investigation committee was assembled...
Yay! Honmaru, they showed us on TV!
Taru...
You have some way to fix my haircut, right?
Don't worry, Honmaru.
Your hair will grow back in no time.
Yes, yes.
Even if you say, "Yes, yes..."
I was such an idiot
for counting on magic to cheer me up.
Honmaru-dono!
Yes?
This is no way to go.
Cheer up, you!
Ah! No, I don't need no more emboldening, I assure you!
I'm cheerful enough as it is, just look, I'm telling you!
See? See? See? Like this, like this!
That's right, study! Study!
Shit, I'm not getting 0 points ever again, goddammit!
Splendid, splendid.
Honmaru studying with enthusiasm.
Great!
Rui, where the hell did you go?
Don't you know how much
your big brother is worried for you?
Hey, Honmaru! Dead end, not here either.
Where did Rui go?
I see. Dead end here as well.
Nothing after all that searching!
I wish siblings wouldn't quarrel.
Honmaru.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Ijigawa's Sibling Duty.
Rui, I won't let you feel lonely ever again.
Episode 85
Ijigawa's Sibling Duty
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius