Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 32
Come Alive! Giant Monster
For today's art class, I'd like to ask everyone
to draw their favorite creature.
No restrictions on which creature it can be.
I see, any creature I like?
Anyone I like? Anyone I like...
Honmaru lookin' happy.
Let's share his happy thoughts with others.
MY FAVORITE CREATURE - IYONA-chan!
Oh, I see - Honmaru set his sight on Iyona-san,
not even realizing she is obviously out of his league!
You didn't need to shout like that!
Taru... You just revealed
what's on my mind to everyone again!
Ah, Iyona-chan...
I'm royally fried...
Honmaru-kun.
Well, as a matter of fact, humans also count for creatures,
so feel free to draw her.
Are you serious? Alright!
Oh, my Iyona-chan...
So cute, my Iyona...
I'll draw the best Iyona-chan ever!
Nothing less from our Jabao-san.
Shut up and draw.
Mari-sensei! Naniwa Matsugoro announces his arrival!
Mari-sensei?
Oh, my...
Oh! Matsu-san!
Taru, you?
Business goin'?
Doin' a buck here 'n there!
Taru, whatcha kids up to today?
Drawing pictures of favorite animals!
Matsu-san, wanna try, too?
Arts class
Your favorite creature:
- squirrel
- cat
- dog
- fish
- bird
Drawin' favorite animals, eh?
Ain't nothing I can't do!
That loony takoyaki seller is here again, Jabao-san.
Not enough!
Such determination...
Never before has Jabao-san displayed it
for things ouside brawls or school lunches.
Eh?! And it's the same for Honmaru?
This sounds like a certain harbinger
of something disastrous.
Who's there?
D'you like that?
Taru-chan?
Ah, but I totally like that. Oh...
Iyona, whatcha drawing?
Our boy, Primal Rage.
Rui, you?
Stop it, you! Don't you know it tickles?
What thing is this?
Can't you tell by looking? It's a bird. A bird.
Taru-chan, what did you draw?
Honmaru!
Look at this! The resemblance is undeniable, Iyona-chan!
Taru!
Honmaru, why so angry?
Maybe 'cause I'm no freak like that!
Honmaru, you were asking if humans count, right?
Who might this be?
Don't you mean to say it's supposed to be Iyona-chan?
Don't laugh...
So that's how I look in Honmaru-kun's eyes?
No, that...
Honmaru's drawing packed with strength, me like it!
And I've done drawing mine!
Look!
Not bad at all, Matsu-san!
No wonder - before opening a takoyaki booth,
I used to be a professional sign maker.
Oh?
Whoa! Gorgeous!
Harako's drawing here is a masterpiece!
No big deal at all.
For someone like me, living in the aureole of glory
from winning the special "jury choice" award
in the Boys and Girls Section of the World Painting Expo,
such a picture is but a trifle.
Furthermore, I'm told my family
descends from Toshusai Sharaku himself.
People! Check out my picture, too!
The hell's that?
A frillneck lizard!
You still don't know any better than a frillneck lizard?
The guy is in no hurry to grow up!
Such an old story, Jabao!
How primitive are your thoughts, really?
Old?
Let's call it enough of showing our works to everyone.
Ha-ha-ha
You thickheads! Stop laughing!
Don't you realize my deep artistic intent behind this?!
What is this thing, even? I would have drawn
a better picture when I was just three years old!
Take a look, the difference is overwhelming.
The mastery like mine
is obviously unattainable for you.
Harako-kun, I think it may just be nicer of you
to stop slandering others like that...
Well, you can't deny how immature it is, can you?
This primitive doodle is inherently
at odds with refined taste.
Give it here!
There, there! There and there! What do you say?!
Now he also has long-ass horns!
Damn you! Alright! I'll also add thorns. And a carapace, too!
And lasers out of the horns!
Spotlights in the eyes! And fur growing right on his heart!
Super strong and cool! A giant guy!
Jabao so serious. Amazing.
How about this?! Let's have a duel, Harako!
My champion - Monster Jababooey!
What's this nonsense you're blabbering about?
How do you suppose we'll hold a duel of drawings?
What a stupid idea, Jabao!
Jabao will have his duel.
Pictures come alive!
Huh?
Yes?
Taru, was it you just now?
Ah!
What is it?
There!
What's this?! What's going on?
Jabao-san, why did you do that?
Don't be stupid! I've nothing to do with this!
Taru! Everyone's going to find out about magic!
It'll be alright. I cast it in quiet voice.
That's it! My inner determination
communicated with the picture!
Do it, Jababooey! Tear Harako's lion to shreds!
See?
You cretin! No lousy-drawn monster of yours
can be any match to my well-bred lion, Papanja...
Ah! Papanja!
Idiot! It's not the time to be worrying about that!
What was that about Papanja again?
See now? That's the power of my Jababooey!
He gobbled him in one gulp...
He ate and merged with him!
It's hostile!
Run!
You cretin! Go hide elsewhere!
Where else?!
There, see? The thing is looking this way!
Why did you have to do this?!
Well, maybe because it's the way towards the exit!
Speaking of which,
getting out would be anything but easy.
It is apparent to the naked eye that the door
is jammed with desks and won't budge.
At the same time, the window appears to have been deformed
in the turmoil, so now it won't open.
Cut to the chase already!
What should we do now?!
At this point, our options are limited
to resigning ourselves to getting eaten...
No way! I don't want to be eaten! Not here!
Cretin!
Hold up! This monster came out of your drawing!
You're the one who should be dealing with it!
It's easier said than done...
Well, if anything, you go get your sorry ass eaten first!
You've gotta be kidding!
Taru, at least do something!
It'll be fine, my magic wears out in ten minutes.
No way! Iyona-chan and I
will be tasting his gastric juices a lot sooner than that!
Ain't no matter what happens, I'm gonna protect Mari-sensei!
Damn paper monster! I, Matsugoro, will be your opponent!
Matsu-san! You're still here?
Hey! Giant lizard! Don't come near here!
We're in trouble! Matsu-san is getting eaten next!
If Matsu-san is eaten, we're not tasting
his superb takoyaki ever again!
Oh, think of something already, Taru!
Don't eat him!
This thing's gotta have some weak spots!
Lessgo!
Right there!
Didn't work.
Mari-sensei, I... I... Tried as best I could...
Mari-sen...
I know, Taru!
If you bring Matsu-san's drawing to life,
it may help somehow!
Yeah! Got it!
Pictures come alive!
- like that.
It worked!
Still useless...
What now, Taru?
Leave it to me, Honmaru!
Pictures come alive!
No!
Sorry...
Wha-ha-ha-haaat?
Ah! My Otter-chan!
Imbecile! Couldn't you draw anything better than a lousy otter?!
It's no use! The squirrel and the otter
stood no chance whatsoever!
Caw! You stupid baboon!
Your face looks like an ass! I laugh!
Ijigawa, why is your drawing
doing nothing but running away?
What do you mean?! What else is it supposed to do?
Can't catch me, ass-face!
Show us how you can fly!
Cretin! Cretin! Dumb to boot!
Well, how do you like my bird now?
It worked!
You smart!
Fool! Can't reach me!
Well, they say loose lips sink ships, right?
Incredible! It's growing in size now!
And it's about to gobble everyone in the schoolyard!
If we don't stop it, everyone at school is getting eaten!
And we'll bear full responsibility for it!
Mom would be broken, and dad would be livid!
Taru, at least do something now!
Taru, if I draw a jet bomber, will it fly?
Your emotions decide how it'll perform.
Put your heart into drawing.
Taru, make sure nobody discovers us!
Aight. Pictures alive!
Honmaru, that's a clumsy plane.
I didn't have time for a good one! It'll have to do!
Preparing for a sweep on the enemy!
With bombs!
How is it?
Didn't work either?
Damn you, missiles then! Missiles!
Still no use! Evasive maneuver!
Haphazardly-drawn missiles do no damage.
Jabao’s drawing is strong. Jabao’s determination was strong!
And it's fused with the others now!
Crap! Is Jabao’s drawing invincible?!
Damn it! Let’s try a tank now!
Do it right, Taru!
Alright! This one might just do it!
Do your best!
Fire!
But why? Why didn't a single one hit?!
Oh, right! I drew the cannon curved!
Oh, why am I so bad at drawing?
Don't lose your heart, Honmaru.
I really like the way you draw.
This time, it’s big, big, big, big!
A battleship!
Open fire!
...fire!
Keep firing, firing, firing, firing!
Fire!
With enough of them, even curved guns should score a hit!
Keep firing, firing, firing, firing!
It’s coming! Command a full speed astern!
We’re beached, battleship immobilized.
Still have Honmaru’s most determined drawing!
Pictures come alive!
My drawing of Iyona-chan!
How dare you bully everyone like that?
This is unacceptable!
I’m serious!
She hit it...
You’ll be alright now.
I sent the monster to the outer space.
Ah! My drawing of Iyona-chan
even defeated Jabao’s drawing!
Honmaru-drawn picture is the strongest.
Honmaru’s determination was the strongest.
Thank you!
Oh, I was happy to help!
So Honmaru’s determination was the strongest?
No, it might still be that my drawing is stronger.
Picture come alive!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru’s drawing put to flight.
My drawing is the strongest!
No! Leave me alone! No!
Iyona-chan...
A monster that popped out of a drawing?
It’s bad to mix dreams with reality.
I suppose the weather is good, so you all saw the same dream.
But I’m telling the truth, Teacher!
Teacher, Jabao's monster even ate the lion
that popped out of my drawing! How do you explain that?
Let’s pretend we were seeing a dream. Alright, Taru?
Yeah!
Oh, I swear! I can’t stand his guts!
This yellow Dobe-chan, the book protagonist!
Honmaru, not get mad, not get mad.
We’ll fix it ourselves by joining him inside the picture book.
If only we could...
Ah! Iyona!
Eh? Iyona-chan is also there?
Magical Taruruuto-kun: The Grand Adventure in a Picture Book.
Everyone, join us on our trip inside a picture book!
Episode 33
The Grand Adventure in a Picture Book
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius