Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Alright, everyone. We're playing soccer for today's gym class.
Do your best, Honmaru-kun.
Thank you, Iyona-chan.
Iyona, I'll help as well!
Taru-chan, you do your best too.
Okay!
Episode 52
Soccer Duel!
First of all, let's divide into two groups:
the attacking side and the defending side.
I'll be throwing the ball myself
for the attacking side to dribble and shoot.
The defending side tries to drive the ball out.
Okay!
Okay.
Honmaru... Whenever I see him, he's such an eyesore.
A harebrained, wimpy show-off such as you
will never be worth anything.
Even him just talking to Iyona-san...
Ah! It's so irritating!
Dammit...
You're some million years too young
to even try challenging me.
Screw you! I'll take the damn ball!
Challenging me despite countless previous failures?
So far, how many times did you...
So far?
So far...
How come...
I've been humiliated by this asshole time and time again?!
Time and time again!
Why?
Why can't I crush this bastard?!
Edojo Honmaru!
There are no words for how much you nauseate me!
Honmaru!
What are you doing, Harako-kun?
Stop right now, Harako-kun!
I apologize, Teacher.
While I was handling the ball, Honmaru suddenly appeared
right where I was intending to kick it.
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun.
It was your own enthusiasm to take the ball from me
that caused this accident.
Still, you put up a magnificent fight!
I don't think so. Just now, you did it on purpose.
Hold on, teacher!
Nobody dares to talk to me, the World Junior World Soccer Championship "Most Valuable Player" Award holder,
in that insolent tone!
I never make mistakes!
Doesn't it feel good, Honmaru-kun?
Even as a worthless excuse of a man,
you still get to have our teacher doting on you!
The smallest accident is made into my fault.
But whatever, so be it.
I'm a man too.
Feel free to fancy me as a bully...
Harako-kun!
Teacher!
Just as Harako said, it was an accident.
Please don't find fault with Harako.
Honmaru-kun?
I was too engrossed in chasing the ball,
I messed up and didn't dodge Harako's kick.
Oh, now you get it?
What a worthless man you actually are.
Yeah. For now, I don't have enough soccer prowess to stamp you out yet.
It sure is frustrating.
You're a world champ and all.
However!
Give me two weeks!
With two weeks of special training,
I'll develop my own skills enough to defeat you!
Well said, Honmaru-kun!
So, a soccer duel in two weeks, right?
Yes.
Oh! Honmaru, you're on fire!
Duels without purpose are boring.
Let's throw in a condition -
the loser fulfills one wish of the winner.
Alright, works for me!
No matter how you spend these two weeks,
you won't stand a chance against me!
I don't mind showing Iyona-san your miserable side.
I won't lose.
I'll do whatever it takes to beat you!
Taru, I'll do it!
Whatever special training, bring it on!
Make it more intense than ever!
Sure! You won't lose, Honmaru.
Soccer Ball-kun will give you special training.
I'll work you hard!
Come, Honmaru!
Wait for me, hey!
Alright, first - let's do dribble!
You dunce, watch the ball closely!
Okay.
Alright! Next, pass me to Taru.
There!
Piece of shit!
What the hell was that pass just now?!
You're supposed to send it ahead of Taru! Ahead!
Do you even watch the ball as you handle it?!
Alright, Honmaru.
Use this.
With this applied, look at the ball right away.
I'm looking at the ball...
So what of that?
It stings! My eyes hurt!
Honmaru look at the ball.
Huh? It doesn't hurt.
This - Well-Seeing Eye Drops, Eyetension-kun.
With it, as soon as you lose sight of the item, your eyes hurt.
...My eyes!
But they don't when you keep looking.
Don't look...
Doesn't hurt.
I see!
This will help you not to lose sight of the ball.
This is pretty useful!
But does that mean, if I give it to Iyona-chan
and show her myself...
Honmaru-kun, please stay forever with me.
Whenever I can't see you, my eyes are sore!
Honmaru weird.
What's with that lewd face?
Is he really that spineless?
This guy needs to be thoroughly chastised!
There!
Wait! Where are you going, eh?
When you're running away so fast,
my eyes would totally end up uuuh-hurting!
What? We absolutely can't go to a place so crowded!
Ha! If you're feeling shy, stick with me!
Wait! My eyes are swelling up!
Watch your...
Sorry...
Alright! Alright, I heard you!
I'm sorry!
Wait I said, Ball!
I keep bumping into other people
because I have to look at you!
Honmaru, dodge them with your instincts!
Instincts, you say?!
Sorry!
You little...
Bumping into others is impolite!
What's that stare for?!
Piss off!
Ouch, that one...
Honmaru, sorry for this special training.
I'm really sorry, sir!
Taru, you gotta do something!
Honmaru! Get undressed!
Will something happen if I undress?
Yeah!
Is this...
Please leave it to us to watch for surroundings!
Oh! Well done! This sounds reassuring!
You can do it, Honmaru!
Soccer Ball, you bastard!
Hold it!
Impressive, Honmaru!
You don't bump into anyone!
How did he...
Honmaru, look!
Great dribble!
Yeah!
Dammit! Don't just kick me around!
There!
Heading!
Huh?
Well, well, Mr. Soccer Ball?
If you wanna run away, what's stopping you?
There, there!
That moron has already adapted.
And how about here?
D'you think that'll help you?!
How dare you!
Where?! Where is he hiding?
Come out! Come out, you... Ouch-ouch!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
It hurts! Dammit!
Get hit right in the back of your head!
He's got eyes on the back too?!
Alright! Do it now, Honmaru!
Overhead kick!
You're amazing, soccer boy!
I'm impressed!
Nah...
Honmaru got good at soccer.
Okay, next special training!
Eh? You have more of it?
Yeah!
Cu-cu-cu-cut!
Eh? The hell?!
Atta-ta-ta-tach!
What did you do this for, Taru?
Now use your feet like hands.
This way, Honmaru's feet become dexterous.
That's easy to say...
It's no use, I can't use it well!
Even eating a single takoyaki takes ridiculously long.
You can do it, Honmaru.
If you learn to use your feet dexterously,
you'll become very good at soccer.
I know that, alright...
Honmaru's entrance!
And that was just about how I spent the next two weeks.
Now then, today we're finally holding a match.
It's a showdown between Honmaru-kun and Harako-kun.
Everyone else is welcome to join the team of their choice.
Are you guys sure you wanna be on Honmaru's team?
The bet is one wish fulfilled, remember?
Shut it, Harako!
Everyone is just about fed up with your stuck-up attitude!
Exactly!
Harako!
I ought to take your pompous-ass down a notch!
You guys can just relax and wander around.
Just make sure you don't get caught up in my legs.
Okay.
However...
Everyone, let's do our best, okay?
Yeah!
Even Iyona-san chose Honmaru's team...
Unacceptable!
Well, so be it, Honmaru.
I'll tear you to shreds before Iyona-san's eyes.
Taru, during this match, don't use any magic.
I wanna test my own strength.
You get it?
Yeah!
Yay! I'll get the ball!
Eh?
You're all about a century too young
to take the ball from me.
What?!
Hey, Harako!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
What the hell?!
He's holding the ball with his foot!
Thanks to my special training,
I got more nimble with my feet than with my hands!
What a dexterous foot!
Honmaru, amazing!
You ass...
What's going on?
I just can't take the ball from him...
That's not how it's supposed to be!
Asshole! Do you have a pair of eyes on your back or what!?
You could say so. I have eyes all over my body!
What?
Blame it on the special training!
It's amazing to have eyes all over my body!
Thank you, my feet!
Alright!
Hands!
Leave the flanks to us!
Back!
The rear is OK!
My head!
Hey!
Chest!
Yeah!
I feel like I wanna hang out with you forever!
Thank you, Honmaru!
But remember, Honmaru,
all of us are just a part of you!
Taru cast a spell on me so I can talk to you now.
However, it seems, as soon as the magic wears off,
we will all just disappear.
But if you could remember this sensation right now,
and let it diffuse throughout your body...
If you could make use of your soul to the fullest...
You could also move your hands and feet like you do now!
We are you!
We are one!
Exactly! We are one!
That's right, even if I can't use the same magic now...
Hands, feet, chest, also head, and back!
Your souls are tightly intertwined with mine!
My soul is diffused to every corner of my body!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
Just what you told us to -
staying low and not getting in the way.
Well done, Honmaru-kun!
Thank you, Iyona-chan!
I'm happy for you, Honmaru!
Thank you, Taru!
Thank you, everyone!
Alright, let's go get some more!
Nonsense!
Must've been a fluke. It HAD to be!
That bastard Honmaru...
He hecame the class hero before my own eyes!
Don't mind if I do!
What?! Honmaru!
This can't be... I'm already playing seriously, but he's still...
As easy as that!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru!
This makes it 1-1!
No goal! Honmaru team - free kick!
What? Why is that, Teacher?
You know why! You just kicked Honmaru-kun on purpose!
Now that'd be obviously untrue, Teacher!
Are you okay, Honmaru-kun?
Teacher,
nobody kicked me on purpose just now!
That was just me being clumsy.
No, I won't accept that.
Even if you say so, I judge this as a foul.
Like clockwork. Spoiled by Teacher...
What did you say?!
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun!
Honmaru-kun...
Will you be alright, really?
Someone, please lend me a hand.
We'll take Honmaru-kun to the infirmary.
Teacher! Please let me stay in the fight, Teacher.
There's no way I can quit now!
The score now is 1-1,
the duel is nowhere near resolved yet!
Harako! The one to score the next goal -
wins, how about that?!
Fine by me.
Alright, teacher!
Let me do at least that!
Very well, you can do it.
Alright! The match is resumed!
Let's do our best, people!
Yeah!
Honmaru can't even stand on his legs.
What to do? Use magic?
No!
My legs hurt so much... I can't stand.
Honmaru, magic!
Never!
Honmaru, Honmaru!
Don't you worry, Honmaru.
It was just because you've not been using
your own power enough up until now!
Even when the magic disappears,
we are still a part of you!
Use your own power to the fullest!
My own power... To the fullest!
Alright, Honmaru! I'll try my best too!
I got this duel in the bag!
Alright! There's no room for mistake!
This goal is mine!
What?!
What the blazes?!
Honmaru, you've done well!
You can leave the rest to us now!
Ijigawa! Pass!
Got that!
Alright, Korekiyo!
Roger!
I'm not giving this ball up!
Don't get ahead of yourselves!
What?!
Are you kidding me?
You again, dirty broad!
We gotta score a goal
on behalf of Honmaru-kun who can't move!
Sorry to disappoint, Iyona-san.
Your strength won't be enough to hit a goal!
Mind if I have it?
Iyona-chan!
Do centering! Pass the ball here!
What?!
He's running on his hands!
Running as though they were his feet!
Honmaru-kun!
Here!
But how?!
Thanks to swapping my feet and hands during
the special training, I can now use my hands like legs too!
OH MY GOD!
Now then!
What should we ask Harako-kun to do?
He promised, remember?
Honmaru-kun, do you mind if I make the wish?
You, Iyona-chan?
Of course I don't mind!
Harako-kun,
start getting along with everyone, please.
Sure...
Hey, Neyo! Happy birthday!
Happy birthday, Neyo.
Look, birthday cards from everyone!
Next time, let's play kendama together!
Hey, what's the matter, Neyo?
Neyo? Why aren't you happy?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
A Forever Lonely Birthday.
Alright, let's investigate Neyo's secret!
Episode 53
A Forever Lonely Birthday
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius