Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
There was a dark page in my life, some years ago,
when I peed myself after being sent flying in sumo by Jabao.
Because I was made into a laughing stock
before Iyona-chan's eyes, I have to accept this challenge,
in order to restore my good name!
With Sister Ria's magic,
we made it to rocky mountains of Canada,
where we started the special sumo training
with the great wilderness as the opponent!
Episode 27
Honmaru, Enter the Ring!
Taru! Niruru, wait!
Hey?
Somebody in there? Hey!
Gosh, I need a break.
Honmaru!
I'm going through the ordeal of special training here!
So insensitive of you to be playing around, Taru.
Honmaru! Meet my newest fri-riend!
What in the world?!
Honmaru!
Why did you lead him here?!
This will help us. Honmaru, go for it.
You did a good job,
finding just a sparring partner for you!
I think so, too.
Alright...
Miracle Star!
Now, you can continue your special training, Honmaru.
But be mindful, that bear woke up from his winter sleep
and is not very happy about it. Be careful!
Being careful would be not fighting this thing!
You've no right to lose!
Honmaru! Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Grab the enemy by his belt!
Cannot reach it, dad!
When the enemy slaps you with an open hand,
you swiftly crawl under him to grab him by the belt!
Easy for you to say,
but try being swift when you're looking like this!
This is not what you've been undergoing
the special training for! Stop disgracing yourself!
Did you forget your balls at home, Honmaru!?
It seems, without a real enemy before his eyes,
it's impossible for him to enter the fighting mood.
There!
Miracle Star!
Jaba Jabao!
Go for it, Li'l Pants Wetter Honmaru!
Li'l Pants Wetter Honmaru!
Yay! Yay! He'll wet any pants!
Hooray for Li'l Pants Wetter!
Better run off before you pee yourself again!
Things'll go nasty if you do!
Crap, I'm not losing again!
Not to this swine Jabao!
Alright!
To battle!
Save me, someone, please!
Still no use?
Don't you whine pathetically!
Me do special sumo training, too.
Niruru.
Squeeze!
Please don't do this to me, Jabao-san!
Silence! Everyone should be
yielding their snacks to me obediently!
After all, we need to bolster my precious body
by all means possible for the upcoming sumo match!
I can't build up my stamina otherwise!
You too have an obligation before the whole class to assist
its unrivaled champion Jabao-san in all his undertakings.
You got that?
Counting on your cooperation!
Blood, muscles and bones - an ideal diet for building...
Right?
This prick Jabao acts as though he won already!
But I guess he has every reason to do that.
We can only count on Harako to pose any real challenge
to Jabao. But in sumo, even this guy might just fall flat.
Even if there's still Honmaru,
also using special training as an excuse to skip school.
What is he thinking?
Right, Iyona-chan?
Yes...
But still, what if somehow, just like the last time with boxing,
Honmaru-kun manages to figure it out?
Oh, drop it, Iyona-chan!
It was nothing but a fluke back then, a miracle!
You can't expect that daft blockhead to do anything more
than just peeing himself in front of everyone again!
Honmaru-kun, where are you now...
That right there is a foul!
You can't use that technique in sumo!
Never mind.
Taru! How can you still be playing around
even as I'm getting tortured right next to you?!
Wait, though.
It's the same
both with the bear and with the river rapids!
Forcing your way through the stream gets you nowhere,
but merging with the stream opens up a secret path!
To battle!
Honmaru, you did it!
Way to go, Honmaru!
Exactly! That's how you do it! You redirect
the bear's mindless power back at him with a throw!
Right! Grip above his arm and throw!
Free your elbows!
And throw him with an underarm grip!
Twisting throw with underarm grip!
Taru! Don't let it get away!
We're not returning without a side dish tonight!
Yeah!
In the end, nothing rivals the original Canadian salmon!
Exactly! It's delicious!
Delicious.
Make sure to get full on it.
It's a blessing from the great wilderness!
Alright! I'll eat so much,
I'll get even fatter for tomorrow's special training!
Yeah!
But Honmaru, I still prefer takoyaki.
Is there original Canadian takoyaki, too?
As a wise man would say,
"Quit. Don't quit. Takoyaki. Don't takoyaki."
Next one, start!
I am the man who excels at everything he ever does!
Not even the sumo can be granted an exception!
Let's call it enough for today's practice.
Gramps! Is my special sumo meal
for the special sumo training ready?
Yes, Young Master. The Special Harako Gym
Protein Bursting Dish is served.
Let's eat!!
The water, the trees, the sky and the animals - if you manage
to merge with everything that is alive in nature,
no river rapids...
No waterfall...
No force of nature
will stop you!
Nobody can stop me!
To battle!
Good, Honmaru!
Honmaru!
The ten days are up, and yet both Harako and Honmaru
are too weak in the knees to show up and face me?!
Where's the fun in that?!
It hurts...
Jabao the Mountain wins!
Witness! I win again without even trying.
Told you Jabao would trounce everyone.
This is nothing new.
Now, it's time to determine
the #1 sumo wrestler in the class,
through a bout with the winner among the girls,
isn't that right?
That's right. In the girls' division,
the winner was Kawai-san.
Okay...
Iyona-chan! You should ask the teacher to let you quit!
I can see that in Jabao's eyes,
there's something wicked!
Iyona-chan, let's not waste any more time.
We'll never know who's #1 in the class
until we settle it with a sumo bout!
Not so fast!
Who could you be?
I beg your pardon for leaving you
for ten days straight,
Beautiful Teacher!
Harako-kun?
Are you really Harako?
I was lucky to have made it in time, somehow.
Now, witness the result of my special training!
Just being fat won't help you!
Funny how those words
only apply to you in all exactness!
Whaddya say?!
Just... let me warm up!
Like that!
And... another one!
Harako, hey...
Are you ready now,
Jabao-kun, Harako-kun?
Watch me do it, Harako!
You're saying a lot of my lines for me today.
In the ring!
Harako, do it!
Jabao-san!
Like hell! I'm not letting you have it!
Is that all you have to offer?
Looks like my special training was a waste of time!
Whaddya say?!
Jabao-san... The champion
of the kindergarten sumo contest, Jabao-san...
Sent out of ring in a single throw
as if he was just some feather!
Jabao had wetted his own pants this time!
He peed himself!
Jabao-san...
You're dreadful, Harako Tsutomu!
Too weak... He's just too weak!
Almost embarrassing that I had to fight a bastard so gutless,
he peed all over himself when I was merely warming up!
Don't you dare insult that defenseless Jabao!
Who else could that be?
You...!
Hi! Honmaru here!
Don't you start putting up airs now
just because you made Jabao a Li'l Pants Wetter, Harako!
It's Honmaru!
I have just returned from my own special training!
Some years ago,
Jabao's throw made me a Li'l Pants Wetter.
In order to throw off that stigma, and to overthrow Jabao,
I underwent special training!
Let it be known, that from now on,
Harako is my one and only rival!
Yeah! Everyone, cheer for us!
Watch me do it, Iyona-chan...
My triumph!
What's going on?
Even Honmaru is as fat as a hippo!
Just being fat will not avail you, Honmaru!
Funny how those are the words
I can return to you, in all exactness!
What did you say, you fatass?!
You're the only one fatass around!
Both are posed for a verbal battle today.
Have you ever even seen
that chubby thing that is your body in the mirror?
Shut it!
A mirror?
Alright...
Sure!
Here, mirror.
You're taking things too literally, Taru.
But at least I know this is just sister Ria's magic.
Did you only just realize?
You're the fattest fatass
and you can't dispute that!
Harako, did you try looking in the mirror yourself?
What...
is this disgusting thing?
Trembling
I'll be damned! I got so absorbed in my special training
that I turned into a literal obeast before I knew it!
Damn it! A Kindergarten Style Contest Winner,
Special Award of World's Dreamboats Carnival Winner,
always shining with numerous other honors and awards -
and look at what became of me now!
This is all Honmaru's fault!
Unforgivable!
I'm going to tear you to shreds...
I'll throw you hard enough to seal that Li'l Pants Wetter title
before Iyona-chan's eyes!
You get to taste my power!
You're oblivious to the inner sorrows of someone
repeatedly ridiculed for falling in a battle and peeing himself!
My mom once said to me,
"By mistreating others, you bring about your own misery!”
“By ridiculing others,
you subject yourself to that ridicule in the future!”
Honmaru...
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru, you’re right!
That was damn well said!
Harako, you’re beaten flat!
Ijigawa-kun, weren’t you the one
ridiculing Honmaru more than anyone else?
Shut it, you! Looking for trouble?
Ready, everyone!
Too bad, it’s all in vain.
Honmaru cannot win this.
That power, that speed...
The guy is a beast.
It took him a split second to throw me -
by the time I realized it -
the full extent of his strength, my heart
immediately sank, I lost it completely, and just peed myself!
Jabao...
On the ring!
Before you, the one who defeated
even the Canadian grizzly, Honmaru-sama!
Harako is no threat to me!
Laughable!
If this is the best attack you got,
you ain't got no right to tell others off!
Move it!
I’ve been coached by Dekanishiki,
the strongest wrestler in history!
Meet the technique of the great Harako,
extolled as being on par with the world’s best wrestlers!
Atomic Megaton Slap Bombardment!
Is it really still sumo?
He’s just aiming for a KO punch at this point!
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru...
Honmaru! Special training in Canada! Remember!
Taru...
Right, forcing your way through
won’t get you anywhere.
Merge with the stream
to find your own path inside it!
Have you finally accepted your fate, Honmaru?
What?
Huh?
Finishing blow!
Harako Special Thunder Attack!
Not a step more!
Hold fast!
You can do it!
Don’t give up, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona, Honmaru found his own path.
He’ll be A-okay!
Taru-chan?
You’re done for, Honmaru!
It only befits a man such as me
to be standing in the spotlight of victory!
You’re bound to stay everyone’s laughing stock
as a Li'l Pants Wetter till the end of your days!
I said, no rapid, no waterfall,
no force of nature will stop me!
To battle!
Canadian Bear Throw!
Got it, Harako?
You did it, Honmaru!
It was just as Taru-chan said!
Impressive, Honmaru-kun!
Not wasting any breath, but just going and doin’ it!
This big stupid ass-whooping guy!
Damn it! How did this happen?!
Dirty soul ends up in dirt!
But then, Iyona-chan and Honmaru must now hold
a sumo bout to finally decide who's #1 in the class.
Between me and Iyona-chan?
I can see I’m no match for Honmaru-kun!
Which means the #1 sumo wrestler in the class
is thus declared to be Honmaru-kun!
This still doesn’t feel right.
What if I end up losing to Iyona-chan, after all?
Maybe we should try, Iyona-chan?
Just kidding, kidding.
Aren’t you happy enough as it is?
Honmaru, you’re #1 now.
Yeah, it’s cool, too.
But only if you stop calling me Li'l Pants Wetter!
However, there’s one more thing you’re #1 at.
I won something else?
It’s something you can’t control.
In our class, Honmaru is #1...
What...? What...?
Fatass!
This point is pretty valid, Honmaru-kun.
It's really fattastic!
Right, Iyona-chan?
Isn’t it impressive how fat Honmaru has gotten?
I guess so.
He was trying his best to become stronger,
and may have gained some on the way.
This was probably unavoidable.
At least Iyona-chan understands!
And still, this kind of fat Honmaru-kun is somehow eugh.
Eugh
A slip of the tongue...
You’re right, right!
Right, all this fat
is the product of sister Ria’s magic!
If I just unplug Infattable Bulge-kun from my neck...
Huh? I'm not going back to normal.
Honmaru, those are your own muscles
that you built during the special training.
Honmaru, you won with your own powers! What a feat!
What do you mean those are my own muscles?
From now on, we’re starting a dietic special training!
We made it all the way to Egypt for you!
To lose weight, you need guts too, Honmaru!
Do your best, Honmaru!
If I don’t lose weight,
Iyona-chan will scorn me!
But why am I always the only one
doing special training?
Honmaru, I found a wow-how-delicious takoyaki stall!
What's the matter, Taru?
You’re speaking strange.
Japan’s #1 takoyaki chef Naniwa Matsugoro
is waiting for you!
Ah, just thinking about it makes me dru-ru-rool!
Oh, I see. Is it really that delicious?
Alright, we’ll go buy some right away!
All of them!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
A One-in-a-Kind Guy Comes From Osaka!
Come witness Naniwa’s great pluck!
Episode 28
A One-in-a-Kind Guy Comes From Osaka
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius