Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Fine, take this!
Tsk.
Yuto-kun!
What are you doing?
Hurry up or we'll leave you behind!
Mama, that big sister there is amazing.
Oh no! You shouldn't hang around
with people you don't know.
I'm freezing.
Are we having a hot pot tonight?
I suppose.
Yes!
Episode 76
Special Training for Neyo!
Taru, when you said let's go for a drive,
was this really what you had in mind?
Yeah! I drive a Three-Wheeled
Attack-Type Combat Vehicle Tricycle-kun.
You don't call that a drive!
Oh? Look at that!
Oh my, what's this?
Howdy, everyone!
Yay! It's like we're celebrities!
No we're not.
They're just laughing at us.
Can't you ride it any faster, Taru?
Sure! Tricycle-kun, let's go fasteru-ru-ru.
Alright, I'm starting!
Starting!
Waah
What do you think of my driving, Honmaru?
Quite impressive, Taru.
I almost died there.
Alright, Honmaru, another round of cycling!
What's the matter, Taru?
They're beating Neyo up!
She's in danger! We gotta help!
What should I do to help?
Consider blasting through them!
Got it, Honmaru. Gonna go easy on them.
Tricycle Gun, ready!
Ready!
Come on, you!
Neyo!
Hey, is that all you got?
Tricycle Gun, fire!
Okay!
What's that?
You start feeling the same way
as the Tricycle Gun at the time of shooting.
Shooting!
Hey! Hands off Neyo, you bastards!
Honmaru?
Honmaru Kick!
Wham!
What's this kid's problem?
Well, ain't it interesting?
You got some business with us, kid?
Doncha look down on us!
Did you come here to get killed?
Shoulda kept your mouth shut
and fled while you had the chance.
You must be an imbecile for
attempting to take us on!
Wait.
This just got personal, you punk.
What kind of trick did you use
to bring him into this state?
I can't tell what kind of shit
you are until I measure by feeling.
Because of that, I often end up overdoing it.
But even then, you're not getting any mercy, kid.
Hey, what's the matter? Why aintcha attacking?!
Sure is an unlucky little shit.
Those caught by the boss never return home safely.
Well, he has some balls to bark at us,
even knowing we occupy this area. I gotta respect that.
Those guys are practicing karate!
Moreover, there's five of them.
I have no idea what approach to use.
Can I even win?
One way or another,
I'm the kenpo champion among boys!
Taking out all of them is too much,
but two or three, I might try...
But still, after that...
I can already see him peeing his pants!
Quit playing around. Just get this over with it quickly!
Shit...
Honmaru, I can try my hand too!
There!
What the hell is that?!
I tried my hands, Honmaru! Honmaru?
Uh? Honmaru, where did you...
Hide and seek? Alright!
Honmaru here?
Honmaru!
Where, where?
Honmaru?
Honmaru!
Not here. Where did Honmaru go?
Alright, will get him with Attractor.
Honmaru!
Found Honmaru! Honmaru is seeking now.
Why'd you seek me if you sent me flying yourself?
Taru, you...
Neyo!
They did her badly, goddammit!
Pain, pain, fly away!
Cheer up with Power Upple Juice.
Neyo, hang on!
Are you okay?
Neyo?
Neyo! Thank god!
Neyo!
You're safe now.
Why did you help me?
I don't remember asking anyone to help me.
I don't.
Spare me your unwanted solicitude!
Are you kidding me?
Like I ever needed you!
Sorry, Neyo.
Don't worry, won't help next time.
What the hell was that?
Zakenja Neyo, why do you have such a hard time being honest?
Alright.
I'll make Neyo honest with Yahoonest Feelings-kun!
Taru!
Neyo be honest!
Neyo?
Honmaru.
Taru.
I was in a tight spot.
Thank you.
Sorry for having said some
nasty stuff about you saving me.
Don't mention it, no offense taken.
No offense, Neyo!
Really?
Glad to know.
Neyo!
Neyo, me catch you!
Oh, we'll see about that!
Come on, this way!
You'll tumble if you keep running so recklessly!
I'll be fine.
Wait, Neyo!
Yay! Caught Neyo!
I lost. Can't compete with you, Taru.
Yay! Neyo lost, lost!
I lost?
Right.
That's true.
To them... It's so frustrating!
I couldn't stand my ground at all.
Neyo, listen. For all your toughness, getting in a fight against
five high school students who practice karate is a no-go.
I know that.
But isn't it frustrating?
They threaten little children
to extort them for pocket money.
I can't stand it!
Be it even all five of them, I'll show them one day!
One day, I will...
Neyo, if it's frustrating,
you should take special training to win.
Yeah. That's right. I need special training.
You could ask Nezo for guidance.
He's away for practices
and won't be back for a while.
Well, I can take care of myself.
Don't worry.
I've been living by that motto
for a long time already.
You're amazing, Neyo.
What's amazing about it?
I'm always by myself...
Thank you, Taru.
You're such a kind child.
Neyo, do your best!
Okay.
I see. She got into a fight trying to help children.
Your real self is extremely nice, Neyo.
No, I mean...
Why are you always acting so stiff?
But think of it...
If you show your weakness,
someone will exploit it.
In reality, this life of putting up a tough act
feels just as stuffy to me.
But so far, there's just been
too much things I detested.
And so, I adopted this line
of behavior to protect myself.
Sorry, sis! Can you throw the ball back?
There!
Thank you!
Still...
At least, with this way of life,
I don't need anyone except myself.
I won't let anyone else
find out about those painful memories.
Neyo...
Nezo told me.
Actually, I'm just a crybaby
who can't stand staying on her own.
Even though I never showed him that side of me.
After my mom died, before I knew it,
I developed a habit of crying silently.
But Nezo still managed to see right through me.
I too,
want to become as strong as him,
whatever it takes.
Both in body and in mind.
Neyo...
Neyo becomes stronger for sure!
I hope so.
Me love Neyo!
Neyo totally good fella!
Are you kidding me?
Don't be shy, Neyo.
It's exactly as Taru says.
Why am I blabbering with you about trifles?
My magic!
Oh no! Ten minutes ran out.
Honmaru!
Spill anything I told you today,
and nobody will ever find you!
Alright...
If you as much as think about spilling it...
And this...
Better remember this well!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Zakenja Neyo, you dumbass!
Honmaru?
Honmaru became a muscleman
with Inflatable Muscles-kun.
What?
Listen! I've had enough of you!
Yay! Neyo and pro-wrestling techniques! Fun!
Are you kidding...
Are you kidding me?!
Don't you pause to peek!!
Slip!
Come on! What's wrong with you?
Dammit...
Get this!
Did you really hope to defeat me with that?
Don't make me laugh!
Move it, move it!
Come on! Out of breath already?
You jerk...
Your punches bounce off me, you dimwit!
Get this!
Hey, Neyo!
Are...
you kidding me?!
You're the one kidding here,
despite being such a wimp too!
Asshole!
What's wrong?
Can't you put up anything better than that?!
Something's off with Honmaru.
Hey, what's with all the bruises?
That stench too!
Got into a fight again, didn't you?
Zakenja-san...
Still, what kind of guy is strong
enough to rough her up that badly?
Good question!
Hey! Who was it that did this to you?
Come on, spill it!
Either way, these wounds need treatment.
Can I walk you to the infirmary?
Iyona-san, please let me help as well,
to the best of my capabilities.
Deserting an injured lady
is an affront to me, the...
Shut up!
What do you even care?
Bristly again!
That's what we get for caring about her!
Don't let that get to you, Jabao-san.
Some people are just that incorrigible.
Let sleeping dogs lie and all.
You reap what you sow!
Because you've been so insufferable,
the divine punishment...
Hey, you!
Why don't you just piss off...
Neyo!
You broad!
Why do you have to be so cheeky?!
You swine!
Bring it on!
Honmaru! Honmaru!
Honmaru!
Neyo!
Come on!
I'm so fed up with your act!
To battle! To battle!
Are you kidding me?!
Take this, and this! And this!
Still too weak!
To battle!
Honmaru.
You wench...
I'll beat that shit out of your head!
Are you kidding me?
Shut up, you maggot!
Honmaru.
Taru-sama!
What's going on here, Taru-sama?
Somehow, this feels awfully unfriendly.
All Honmaru does every day is fighting Neyo.
Doesn't have time to play with me.
Why are you being so insensitive, Taru-sama?
I'm always there to play with you anytime!
Mimora...
Mimora!
What were you thinking,
destroying the bathroom in our house?
Come on, let's go now.
Sure!
I beg your pardon.
Clumsy!
Going to the public bathhouse once in a while
is fun too, isn't it? Right?
Potty!
Waste!
Lowbrow!
Honmaru...
Shit...
You've learned some powerful punches, haven't you?
Honmaru?
You idiot! Why are you letting me catch my breath?!
Alright! I'm not gonna give you a breather!
Are you kidding me?!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
That's quite the catch, isn't it?
Just be good kids and hand over
your pocket money already!
You have some, don't you?
You can trust us to put it to good use.
We're doing you a favor, actually.
Huh? What now, the babe from the other day?
What's with you making such a face, little sis?
Wanna meddle in our business again?
I thought you learned your lesson last time.
Oh! Wait, you!
Return home!
You rogue!
Are you kidding me?!
Get her!
Back at you!
Is she...
You're done!
What's with that bitch?
She's nothing like the other day...
Neyo beaten again, me go help!
Hold it, Taru.
Honmaru?
Are you kidding me?!
Listen, you...
You see me in such a dreary state...
Take this!
This too!
I can't help feeling frustrated
Perhaps, if I put it into words, it'll disappear
But I try to convey it in my heart's cry
Even if it hurts me, I don't care
I ain't kidding around!
Next time you try to mess with children,
I ain't stopping at this!
I am no longer alone? Starting now...
I get it! Never again.
Jeez...
I'm so glad I got to meet you
A new me emerges from my yesterday
You bitch!
Am I still cute in your eyes right now?
Stop staring at me, you weirdo!
Everything only starts now, I'm just a lady
A newborn naked heart
You can't command others.
Shut up!
You forgot this!
Everything only starts now, I'm just a lady
A newborn naked heart
Tsk! A noisy brat!
Tsk! A bristly girl!
Honmaru looks happy...
Ah... I see! Honmaru gave Neyo special training!
I get it, Honmaru! Honmaru a hero!
Tsk. Are you kidding me?
One day,
I hope you feel strong enough to return to your true self,
Neyo.
I'm sleepy! And I can't finish my homework—the apron!
For real, what should I do?
Hey, Taru, do something, please!
Sleeping, huh?
Ah! They'll make fun of me in class tomorrow!
Even so, I'm still sleepy...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Calling on Hardworking Fanatics!
Episode 77
Calling on Hardworking Pixiervants!
Ah, Honmaru! The apron is finally completed!
What?
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius