Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
It happened on a clear day during the winter...
The gym class was about to start,
just like it always does.
That was when this guy beyond anyone's comprehension
made an appearance before me.
Huh? What's everyone up to?
Episode 17
Friends from the Magic Realm
Why is this fellow hanging out with our class?
Why wouldn't he?
It's Taruno-kun, after all.
Isn't he cool?
So gorgeous, Taruno Rival-kun.
Taruno Rival
Taruno Rival?
This name doesn't ring any bell.
Huh? Iyona-chan?
That performance was gorgeous!
Here, a towel.
Aye. Thanks.
Iyona-chan...
What did he do to earn that?
Honmaru!
Let's show people Honmaru can be cool, too.
With Limpy-kun? Good...
Now it's my turn to shine.
Iyona-chan, before long, you'll be squealing
"Honmaru-kun, gorgeous" from the bottom of your lungs!
People!
Take a look at this! My horizontal bar!
Okay, counting on you, Taru!
'Kay, Honmaru spinning!
Taru, hurry up, damn it!
Weird, my magic out of tune!
What's up, Honmaru?
Did you want to show off
your prowess in dangling feebly?
Well, "the most good-for-nothing guy in school"
is still a vacant position, too!
Taru...
I'm trying as hard as I can! Work... Work!
Work, work, work...
This guy's hopeless!
Even Iyona-chan is laughing out loud!
That swindler!
Acting so brazen towards Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan...
She doesn't mind it one bit, either...
How could I miss the moment when they became
this close, this close, this close, this close...
I want it too! Taruno-kun!
Honmaru...
Hey, Harako!
At least say something to this guy!
Well, it's well merited, I guess.
As expected of Taruno.
What... Harako, even you?!
Teacher! That all right with you? We're in the middle of a class!
Perfectly all right.
After all, Taruno-kun is so handsome.
Even the teacher...
How did this happen?
Why is everyone like this?
Iyona-chan, what's gotten into you?
Taruno Rival...
Who or what the hell is that fellow?
For how long has he been here?
Why is everyone so comfortable with him?
I'm the only one seeing him for the first time!
I'm seeing a fever dream now,
that must be it!
Honmaru, not a dream.
Taru...
Cheer up! I'll think of something with magic.
This time, it'll work!
Iyona-chan!
Wanna go home together?
Did it, Taru! Just as planned!
Love-Wow Coupler makes inseparable
two people affected by it.
This time, it'll work!
Sorry, Honmaru-kun.
I had already promised Taruno-kun
to stop by his place, on my way home today.
You're not invited.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Huhuhuh?
This is hopeless!
Sorry, Honmaru!
This is beyond weird...
For how long has this guy Taruno
been in our school?
It was also the first time
when Taru's magic went out of tune.
And then also the way Iyona-chan looked at him...
The way you look at someone
you're deeply in love with.
Crap... What the hell's going on here?
Honmaru, cheer up.
If you're so worried about Iyona,
just ask Tama-chan to check on her.
Right!
Tama-chan, please.
Show us what Iyona is up to now.
Just a moment, Taru-chan.
Iyona-chan...
I've planned something piquant for today.
What is it?
A secret.
Tell me! Hey, tell!
That swine...
Huh? Tama-chan, what's going on?
Very odd... I can't see anything past that point.
Iyona-chan...
Since things came to this,
we've got no choice left but to sneak into his house!
There goes nothing, Taru.
Yeah!
Incorpore-re-real!
Magic is really out of tune here.
Take care from now on, Taru.
This would be our entrance.
Taru!
Know what "taking care" means?
Sorry!
Honmaru, this room feels off.
Oh, has it only now dawned upon you?
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan!
I'll get there to save you right away!
Hold it!
Surely, you didn't actually believe that after sneaking in,
you'd be left with a free hand in my mansion?
Taruno?
You scum! What did you do to Iyona-chan?!
Something piquant.
What... is all that piquant something about?!
A se-cr-et.
Disheartening? Disheartening?!
More, more!
Get disheartened more!
Honmaru! Honmaru!
What a sorry sight, Taruruuto.
Your friend is in agony right in front of you.
Yet you can't do a thing about it.
Taruno...
Taruno Rival, what are you...
Just what kind of thing are you?!
Still didn't figure it out?
You're just another impudent idiot.
What you're seeing is...
What you're seeing here...
Impudent idiots,
what you're seeing is...
What you're seeing is Taruno Rival!
Taruno Rival!
Behold myself, the Great Magician,
Rival-sama!
Taruruuto! Your rival! Rival-sama!
Didn't you forget?
I forgot.
Quit messing with me!
I've been...
I've been robbed viciously of Mimora-chan's love
that is more precious than life itself!
I've been sent to the depths of unrequited love hell,
d'you forget that as well?!
Just remembered, Rival!
Long time no see!
Don't you pretend we're bosom buddies!
Taruruuto!
You scum! It was you who pulled this delusion
over everyone's eyes today!
Has it only now dawned upon you?
That's right, everyone Taruruuto
became friends with in this world -
my mission is to scourge them all!
That's what I made it here for,
all the way from the Magic Realm!
Even if this one here is a burning hot lass.
Still, with magic,
I can hold her hostage whenever I so wish.
Damn you! Why are you doing this to her?
All you cherish will perish in our blood feud,
all the things you hold on to in this world -
for throwing me into this sea of desperation,
Taruruuto is bound...
to lose it all!
Honmaru...
You may not survive this one...
Rival, no more!
Honmaru...
Iyona-chan...
This is the fate of anyone
becoming friends with Taruruuto!
Honmaru, I save you.
Ball Blast!
Barrier!
Didn't get it yet?
No magic school dropout
will ever be able to compete with me!
Bowl Blast!
Hot!
Taruruuto!
Are you in such a hurry to meet your end?
How rude!
Rival!
That voice...
How dare you bully my Taru-sama?!
Mimora-chan?
Mimora?
Rival!
I'm utterly disappointed in you!
Anything but that!
I beg. Beg! Beg! Forgiveness!
Taru-sama, it's been literally ages!
I missed you so much!
Taru-sama, I was growing impatient
because you wouldn't return to the Magic Realm!
Taru-sama...
Let's return to the Magic Realm together!
Will you? Will you?
No can do!
Me not returning!
Taru-sama!
Mimora-chan!
Am I forgiven?
Taru-sama!
Not returning!
Mimora-chan, hey! Mimora-chan!
Taru! Have you forgotten about us two ?
Well...
Whatever.
Least I know it was his magic
that addled with Iyona-chan's mind.
My sweet Mimora-chan! Wait, please!
Rival, then?
I should keep an eye on him from now on.
Taru-sama!
Won't you return to the Magic Realm with me?
No can do!
Let's return-turn-turn-turn-turn-turn!
No can, no can, no can, no can, no can do!
Be quiet!
Will you ever settle down?
You've been going on about this for literal hours already!
That's right! Six sweetest hours by now!
I'm trying to get my homework done here!
Can't you bring your squabble elsewhere?
Honmaru, would forgive me?
Spare me your amiability, Taruruuto!
What's going on? Both are men,
yet indulge themselves in this? My, my.
That's a gross apology, Taru!
Taru-sama...
You used to be so cordial to me...
Like back then, during a lunchtime
in the Magic Kindergarten.
Children,
Nothing left on the plate -
you'll look and feel great.
What do I do?
They mixed it with carrot that I detest!
Empty.
Shoot. Ate before I know it.
My, that's remarkable, Mimora-chan.
You've eaten it to clean plate!
Carrots that I detest...
He downed it all in one go,
so that even teacher wouldn't notice.
Even after saving me from this great ordeal,
he is being unaffectedly kind towards me, like it's nothing.
That was when I knew -
I fell in love!
Huh?
I swear, that Taru-sama...
Here I go, Honmaru!
There!
Got it!
Taru-sama! Let me join, too!
'Kay, Mimora!
They say soccer is not for women,
and for a good reason.
That hurt a lot! You can be a thousand times Taru-sama,
but you still gotta be mindful of lady's feelings!
Taru, you alright there?
Yeah!
Great, where were we?
Taru-sama...
Honmaru!
Waaaa~
This is bad! Let's stop her, Taru!
Yeah...
Taruruuto!
How dare you make my precious Mimora-chan cry?!
I'll never forg—
Mimora-chan! Watch out!
I see...
At this rate...
Mimora-chan, I got it, I got it!
We'll play all together, you hear?
I won't be taking lightly
whatever it is you have to say!
Did you just promise to treat seriously
whatever I say from now on?
Yeah...
I think it'd do me good
to stay in your world with Taru-sama!
Yeah, sure.
Guess you could stay.
I'm so glad!
Taru-sama, here. "Aaah."
Didn't you guys mix something up?
Taruruuto...
I'll make sure to repay this humiliation tenfold!
Better remember this!
Taruruu...
Mimora, I'm in pain!
Honmaru, need your help!
So bothersome...
Why should I even help you?
You started making out with Mimora-chan!
Nobody would be able to bear that!
No wonder Rival went livid!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Rival Strikes Back.
Don't you miss it, guys!
Episode 18
Rival Strikes Back
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius