Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 80
Classified Scoop Battle
The culprit was finally arrested
and the rabbit was rescued safely.
Now, my fellow Nannosho students, if you wanna know
what happens next, you'll have to read this!
Ryoguchiya Korekiyo is honored
to present to you: Ryoguchiya's Newspaper!
Yes, ladies and gentlemen,
please stop by and take a gander.
What is it? A mysterious lost item
in front of the infirmary?
Looks interesting.
A school lunch gourmet corner?
That's Korekiyo for you!
Good job on him for
collecting this much news together.
Thank you very much, everyone.
True talent always finds a way.
I decided to try myself in news
and that's where I hit gold.
How trivial!
What?
Oh, Harako?
Can you really call such a newspaper
a product of talent, Ryoguchiya-kun?
Today, your fame will come to an end.
Prepare to be outshone by the World Junior
Single-page Newspaper Contest winner...
Behold! From Harako Tsutomu-sama himself,
Harako Times!
Pompous!
It's on a whole other scale!
Shaking hands with the American president?
That's Harako's level, alright!
Yeah. Ryoguchiya can't hold a candle to this.
Right!
For today, I'll let Harako-kun
stand in the limelight. However...!
For the next issue,
I'll take the bull by its horns, you hear?
Oh? Sounds intriguing.
I'm in for that duel!
This spells some real fun!
I won't lose, Harako-kun.
Honmaru! We'll also write a newspaper.
What are you talking about, Taru?
Taruru Newspaper is number one interesting!
That's impossible, Taru!
That's the spirit! Do it, do it!
That's right, don't be shy!
Taru!
It's alright. We'll just take
some special training on newspapers.
Taru, is there really special training
for writing a good newspaper?
Leave it to me, Honmaru.
Even if you say so, do you know
how hard it is to publish a newspaper?
Taru, I like that spirit!
True.
A newspaper duel sounds like a lovely idea.
It's much fairer than settling things with violence.
It's a battle of wits!
It's wonderful and manly.
Alright! Let's do it, Taru.
Yeah! Taruru Newspaper is number one!
Honmaru is no competition at all.
Will Honmaru even be able
to put together a single issue?
I wonder what kind of articles
we should publish to make an interesting newspaper...
Honmaru, let's print my face.
Huh?
Look.
Do you seriously think you're that funny?!
Really...
Sorry, Honmaru.
Articles make it interesting.
It's called a scoop. A scoop.
Scoop? Ah!
How about this, Honmaru?
Yes, that's it!
We'll bang it on your head to make a toll...
Just one small detail, that's a spade!
What I meant is scoop!
Honmaru, like this?
Wrong! That's skipping!
Then what?
To explain to you what's a scoop, that's...
What I mean is...
Exclusive news! Exclusive!
Here. I bought this 500 yen plunger for just 100 yen!
Oh! That sounds like a bargain!
Honmaru doesn't know
I got an exclusive discount!
Well, it looks like you're having a jolly good time!
We're honored to be performing for you!
Taru, we're not here to do a two-person skit!
It's news that no one else knows.
Getting access to exclusive
news is what you call a scoop.
Are you listening to me, Taru?
Honmaru, I got this!
What's that? A turtle?
Perfect Timing Camertle, Skoopun!
Turtle-turtle. I'm the Camertle who rushes
to take pictures whenever there's an incident.
With this, we can see interesting things all around us.
A Camertle rushing to get the scoop first?
Turtle-turtle.
Is this a game where we
turn usual things into scoops?
That's it! With this, our victory is secured.
Honmaru-kun is wonderful!
Alright, counting on you!
Counting, Skoopun.
You just make sure to catch up with me!
Leturtle's go!
Yeah!
Alright, let's find some incident to cover!
Turtle? I smell an incident, turtle!
Hey! No running in the hallway!
Teacher!
My, how hard can it be
to just conform to the rules?
Turtle-turtle, I see some good exclusive news, turtle.
Such a chance to click the shutter
comes once in a lifeturtle!
Honmaru, we got our exclusive news picture!
This looks interesting.
Turtle-turtle.
This - for our interesting Taruru Newspaper.
Listen, there's no fun in making a scoop
out of our own embarrassment!
Oh? No good?
Turtle? Another incident, turtle?
Oh, already?
Is it really a scoop this time?
Turtle-turtle. A large scoop, turtle.
Honmaru, let's go!
Are you sure about this?
A big incident! A scoop for certain!
Taru's magic items have a reputation
for being unreliable!
Turtle-turtle!
Scoop, turtle!
Now that's a scoop, indeed!
We did it, Taru!
Taruru Newspaper is the most interesting!
That's just great! The supreme scoop!
The teacher can even
land in trouble because of this!
"Which one is the bigger embarrassment?"
I can't really understand the joke, but it's funny!
That's true, for sure!
I'm in a pickle.
We suffered an utter debacle today.
Hm. Almost unbelievable.
Was that a coincidence?
Nicely done, Taru!
Yeah!
This really is hilarious!
Good job taking this photo!
Taruru Newspaper wins this battle, hands down.
Got it, Ryoguchiya, Harako?
I'm looking forward to the next issue!
Make sure it's just as entertaining!
Yeah! I hope it'll be just as fun!
This has to be a fluke.
I won't lose next time.
Taruru Newspaper interesting!
Please come see our next issue as well!
We're counting on you to make it even more fun!
Sure thing!
Oh my, Taru-sama...
Oh no, how could I...
I wet the bed again!
I saw it! I saw it all!
No, that... Um...
Mimora-chan, you wet the bed, didn't you?
How old are you again?
My, how embarrassing!
I should let everyone know!
Crying and denying won't get you anywhere!
Sleepy-sleepy Mimora!
How dare you make a fool of me!
You'll pay for it now!
Change, Mimora!
That's so strange...
How old are you again?
Must be awfully embarrassing!
That's news, big turtle news!
He found it!
Yeah.
Ah! No! This is a misunderstanding!
Turtle, turtle, turtle!
Ah! Stop it, I said!
Ijigawa is still a bed-wetter herself!
Unfortunate.
Taruru Newspaper is fun!
Well done, Taru!
Me happy too.
I am also happy to have been able
to assist Taru-sama in his endeavors.
I know there's been a misunderstanding.
That newspaper is no good.
Turtle-turtle? Where is the incident?
Incident, incident!
Let's go find an even more interesting story!
Turtleave that to me!
Rampage!
Goose chase after Madonna!
Shotman
Tables are turned on the heroes?!
Don't come close, you stinker!
The great failure of Miss Fresh from Class 3!
Man, it's really nothing to look at!
Stinker!
Stepped in poop! 💩
Look at this!
He's still sleeping with a stuffed bear!
It's our Harako!
True, it's Harako-kun!
My, how infantile!
He still needs to hug this while sleeping?
Revelation! Sleeping with a bear
Harako-kun can't sleep without his stuffed animal.
What a pathetic exposure!
"Jabao's weakness revealed"?
It's just as pathetic!
Our Jabao can't even beat his little brother!
That's a face of hopelessness!
Makes me laugh!
Nothing like what we see at school!
Busy babysitting his younger brother.
Jabao's weakness revealed!
Oww! Pathetic!
Honmaru, you little...
Should I put this fuming face in the next issue?
Or perhaps, should I make a scoop
from the scene of you hitting me?
Taru, Jabao is going to hit me.
Exclusive news!
Taru-chan, Honmaru-kun,
aren't you going too far?
It's not polite to poke at the sides of people's lives they're not too proud of.
That's right!
But, Iyona-chan...
You wouldn't want such a thing
to happen to you, would you?
I don't think doing this is a good thing to do.
Iyona-chan...
Let's go.
I ain't looking at Taruru Newspaper ever again!
I quit too!
It would appear that the Taruru Newspaper
is growing old on its audience.
Now's my chance!
If I announce some scoop
that gets everyone moved...
Oh! I'm drowning!
Iyona-chan's right. Poking at people
at unfortunate moments is not a good thing to do.
Turtle-turtle? Another incident, turtle!
Yeah! We found it, Honmaru!
Taru!
It can't be helped, I guess.
Ah! Help me!
Good. Hurry up, Jabao-san!
Just you wait, young man! I'll help you in no time!
Great job! That's a supreme great scoop!
Camertle failed to win the race...
Ah, Korekiyo's here?
We've been beaten to the punch with this.
Lost the scoop...
That's Korekiyo for you, after all.
Let's call it a day, Taru.
Leave running the newspapers
to Korekiyo and the like.
Wait a turtle, look at thatle!
Well, well, congratulations, Jabao-san. Excellent job.
Something fishy is going on.
That was an impeccable performance.
We're a great duo.
Did you take a good photo?
I nailed a whole bunch!
At this rate, we'll blow
Taruru Newspaper out of the water!
This is our secret weapon for restoring
Ryoguchiya's Newspaper's dominance.
All through your tenacious labor!
Well, well, as promised.
Ah, much obliged, alright.
Honmaru!
I saw it, Korekiyo!
I saw, I saw!
No, this is just a debt from the other day...
Too turtlate.
Korekiyo, you can't go around
devising your own incidents!
Yeah! Korekiyo cheating.
He hired them!
That's terrible!
Ryoguchiya's Newspaper is a contrivance?
Taruru Newspaper
10th issue!
Editors:
Edojo Honmaru
Taruruuto
Sensation!
Ryoguchiya exposed staging his own incident!
Staged!                                   The truth!
Tsk! It was all staged!
I wonder if everything they
published up to now was a hoax too!
That was dishonorable, Ryoguchiya.
Don't you have any pride as a journalist?
I'm not looking at Ryoguchiya's Newspaper ever again!
Taruru Newspaper is always to the point!
It's a newspaper of justice.
Turtle-turtle.
Our scoop isn't about poking
at people's unfavorable sides this time.
Scoop of justice.
I wish Iyona-chan could see it too.
Journalism for justice, huh?
It feels great to be doing that, Taru.
I had fun, Honmaru.
Iyona-chan would probably also praise me
for a scoop in the name of justice!
Honmaru, Iyona there.
Oh? Lucky!
Hey, Iyona-chan!
Have you seen our newspaper?
Are you okay, Iyona-chan?
Nailed these, turtle!
Perfect view of Iyona's panties.
Honmaru-kun, will you publish
that in the newspaper as well?
Yeah! Big news!
No, we're done publishing news like that...
Will publish.
Taruru Newspaper number one!
So you're that kind of person...?
No, I'd never...
You didn't even bother to help Iyona-chan up!
How can you call yourself a man?
Ah... It's not like that, you hear?
We do news in the name of justice!
It's fine, do whatever you want!
Iyona-chan!
You're human waste, Honmaru!
This is a journalistic masterpiece, turtle.
Scoop, scoop!
Full view of the panties! Turtle-turtle-turtle!
So you're that kind of person?
You're human waste, Honmaru!
Iyona-chan...
What the turtle are you doing?!
Why, Honmaru?
I'll never post a photo like this.
Turtle, turtle!
How dare you tear up my perfect photo?
Taruru Newspaper is a newspaper of justice!
I'm gonna report on anything, with no discrimination!
Everyone loves Taruru Newspaper!
Forget it!
Absolutely not!
I don't want to have anything to do
with Taruru Newspaper!
Honmaru...
We can still do it on our own.
Wow! An incident!
Interesting incident, turtle!
This is big, turtle!
But...
Wait for me!
How should I go about apologizing to Iyona-chan?
I'd probably only end up alienating her completely.
Turtle-turtle-turtle!
We're in trouble, turtle!
What now? You again?
Didn't I tell you I quit? Tsk.
Not that, turtle! Taru is in danger, turtle!
Taru is?
Big incident, turtle!
What is it? Where's Taru?
You'll see! Hurry up after me, turtle!
Wait for me!
Dammit...
Now that it came to this,
I couldn't care less if if I kill one or two of you today!
Careful! Put your head down!
Taru!
Quick! It's just around that corner, turtle.
The big incident only starts now, turtle.
Taru?
Ah... It hurt, pops.
Watch out, will you?
What was that, you brat?
Did you come here to get killed?
What happened?
It's dangerous!
Let them go!
You need something from me, boy?
Ah... No. It's just that Taru is... Taru is...
Taru? What the hell?
Like the tartaru sauce?
No-no-no, it's not that.
It's just Taru that... Taru that...
Stop prattling, I don't understand a thing!
Taru, where are you?
Me right here!
Ah... Hey!
Wait!
It's dangerous! Come back!
Honmaru!
Taru, don't come close! Don't come, I said!
Took you long enough, Honmaru.
Who the hell are you guys?
Are you the bad guy?
So what if I am?
But are you an awfully bad guy?
Stop it, Taru! Stop, I said!
Alright! I'm the awful bad guy! So what about that?
Yay! Found it! A major incident!
What?
Scoop, scoop! We found a big scoop, Honmaru!
A scoop! Amazing!
Stop it already, Taru!
Yay! Yay!
I've had enough of you messing with me!
I ain't letting it slide, even from a kid!
A gun?
Bang-bang!
Taru!
Watch out, Taru!
Run away!
Taru!
Incorpore-re-real!
Nothing happened!
I'm sure... it flew right in!
Run, Taru!
Now's our chance! Advance!
What do you know! A grand scoop!
I still can't believe there's no bullet hole.
I really thought I was already dead.
Honmaru smelling of piss.
I... pissed myself!
Li'l Pants Wetter!
I'm in a pickle! I can't let anyone find out about it!
Stinky.
And another great photo to end the day!
Honmaru! Did you get the scoop on the current incident?
Harako?
No, I mean...
Seems like I've been beaten to it again...
Well... We're already done with the whole newspaper thing.
Right, Taru? Let's go!
Why are those two in such a hurry?
Turtle-turtle.
Harako, boss.
Got some good photos for you, cheap!
Aren't you the Taruru Newspaper's...
Please buy it, turtle. A major scoop, turtle!
Sorry, Iyona-chan.
Why is it just Iyona-chan?
Well, really, I feel
that I'm guilty before everyone.
You understand now,
that's all that matters.
Good to know.
Well done with this one!
Oh? Is it the Harako Times
that gets a standing ovation today?
Honmaru wetted himself right there!
I know, right!
The great scoop from Harako Times!
Major Robbery Arrest
Hostages are saved!
Honmaru is so scared he pees his pants!
You filmed that...
Honmaru Li'l Pants Wetter!
Taru, stop it!
He's wrong, you hear?!
Harako-kun put one over on you!
That's what you get for laughing at others!
Oh my, Honmaru-kun.
But it's not true!
Disgusting, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
Turtle-turtle. Got some good photos here.
I'll make it a real bargain for you.
Lunch!
Lunch! Such a fun time!
Hey, Korekiyo! I'm trusting you to take care of me, okay?
My precious school lunch is ruined!
Why are you so begrudged with me?
A tanuki!
Oh! Did you feel better
when you woke up in the morning, tanuki?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Episode 81
Bon-Bonanza Tanukichi-kun
Bon-Bonanza Tanukichi-kun.
Oh! Started crying? What's with you, little one?
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius