Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Papa? Just stopped by to say
we all appreciate your hard work!
Bet you're pretty tired, aren't you?
Let me rub your shoulders for you!
What's gotten into my Honmaru?
Are you unwell?
What are you talking about?
Any diligent child inherently looks after their parents!
Could it be that pocket money is the reason?
Where'd you get this idea?
You have a telltale reflex of twitching your ears
when it's money you're after.
Therefore...
Keep rubbing my shoulders.
In for a penny, in for a pound.
Much better...
Actually...
Just remembered I got something for you.
Would you look at this!
Just a tattered map.
You can have it as a tip
for rubbing my shoulders.
What secrets will this map reveal?
It happened during the prime years
of the Yamatai Kingdom in Western Japan.
In the eastern side of the country, a phantom kingdom
emerged, by the name of the Jamatai.
Jamatai Kingdom
Not long before its downfall, the king hid his riches
and marked their resting place on this map.
Did he really?
In today's money,
the value of the hidden riches would be...
a whopping 5 billion yen!
Honmaru,
you are a lucky one!
A tip of some 5 billion for a shoulder rub!
Five billion...
If I had 5 billion...
No-no-no, that's all too earthbound.
That's right! I can ask Iyona-chan...
Like that!
Episode 6
The Great Quest for Treasure!!
Thank you, dad!
A shabby 150 yen treasure map
from a second-hand bookstore.
No way it can be a real thing...
Still, children need something to dream of.
Hey, Taruruuto!
Hey, Taru! You need to hear this!
Hurry and get up already!
- Taru, come on! Taru-Taru-Taru! Taru! Taru!
- Just let me wash my face!
Listen here, Taru.
Dad just gave me a map to the treasure!
Shall we look for it together?
Treasure hunt?
Sounds exciting.
But this map is kinda convoluted,
I can't make heads or tails of it.
If we ask Tama-chan, she may advise.
Brilliant, Taru!
I'm counting on you!
If we find the treasure, you'll also get a share
biiiig enough for a life of luxury!
You'll eat takoyaki until you're full!
Eat takoyaki until full?
Treasure hunt begins!
Wait for me, Taruruuto!
First - head north-northwest!
Hey! Wait, I said!
Iyona-chan!
What a doofus!
You must still be half-asleep
to believe in something like a 5-billion-yen treasure!
Right, Iyona-chan?
Actually, I think treasure hunting
is a very inspired thing to dream of.
Well, would you look at that!
Look, look!
You're not tasting any of my hospitality
once I find the treasure!
That was dangerous! Open your eyes!
Yo, Iyona-san. If you happen to go out,
let me be your guide to the city, will you?
Harako! Who in the world figured it'd be a good idea
to let an elementary school student drive a car?!
Aged appearance is a useful asset.
Even if someone finds out, the head of the
Harako Conglomerate, my papa, will hush things up.
By the way, what are you up to,
equipped like that?
Man, you should hear this!
Who'd believe you even if you tell them?!
Honmaru desecrated my maiden's lips!
I did what?
We're going treasure hunting!
Look. Got a map here.
Treasure - pile of coins and stones!
Lemme see...
Look closer.
Thank you, baby!
Iyona-san, we'll meet again soon.
Map snatched...
Taruruuto...
Sorry...
For crying out loud!
What are we to do now?
Someone's just an incorrigible goof.
Little to see here. Let's go, Iyona-chan.
Not just that, you handed the map over to Harako!
Still...
Forget it, move!
Rui-chan...
Iyona-chan...
I lost both the treasure and Iyona-chan
in a course of one day!
Taru! All thanks to you!
Sorry, Honmaru.
No need to worry.
I memorized the location marked on the map.
Really? You did? That's just big!
You're overdoing it, Taru!
Come on! We need to cross the mountain
before Harako does!
Let's go!
What was that... just now?
Honmaru, lend me your ear.
Came up with an even better idea, did you?
Here too.
Soari-ri-ri-ring!
Honmaru, if we fly, get there faster.
Hold up there, Taru!
You can't just leave me behind!
Honmaru, if you flap your ears, you fly.
I can't do that on my volition!
You have a telltale reflex
of twitching your ears when it's money you're after.
That's right!
Hunting for treasure. 5 billion. I'm after the money!
It worked!
Honmaru, impressive!
Money!
Money! I'm as light as ever!
Honmaru! Wait for me!
Are we there yet, Taru?
Taru-chan, past that mountain.
We're here, Honmaru.
That mountain, then?
Harako's goons!
Young Master, the express
archaeological analysis has shown that...
This drawing is, without a doubt,
an authentic and accurate map of the place.
This discovery is sure to cause a sensation.
Treasure hunting in my leisure time?
Would do for a diversion.
Taruruuto, if we mess around any longer,
he'll beat us to it!
Leave this to me!
~Sneak Peek!~
Found!
And treasure is...
Hey, Taru!
Let me see it, too!
Ten minutes passed already?
Garbage!
Don't throw it here!
Taru, help!
Incorpore-re-re-real!
Stop!
Magic for passing through things,
brought us straight to the place.
Honmaru, we made a clean landing!
Clean what now?
Honmaru stinky.
Don't run away!
Don't get your stinky on me!
What can this be?
Hey! Don't touch things haphazardly!
Broke off.
This is serious, Taru!
Why is it serious?
In the movies I've seen, these kinds of places
are always full of traps protecting the treasure!
You can't touch any...
Too late now...
Run for your life!
What are you waiting for, Taru?
Can takoyaki grow that big, too?
Cretin!
Taruruuto! Next time you'll think twice
before touching strange stuff!
A dead end...
There's nowhere else to run!
Taru! Stone!
It turned the other way?
Repeller
Attractor, when you cast a spell of "Taru,"
becomes Repeller.
Repeller pushes away anything you command it to.
So we're saved...
Alright, the treasure hunt continues!
Tama-chan, please direct us to the treasure.
Sure thing, Taru-chan.
Start by passing through this wall.
Honmaru! It's here!
Well, what do you know. Turns out,
that boulder was driving us in the right direction? Gee...
Gosh, Taru.
Honmaru! Why the wait?
Eh? Where did you go, Honmaru?
Here...
What now, been here all the time?
After me, hurry!
Taru!
Honmaru! You should tread carefully,
there's a water basin that way.
Very timely!
Taru, more of deadly mechanisms
might hide beyond every corner.
Be cautious, will you?
Worries aside!
We'll be A-Okay, Honmaru!
Taru! You triggered something again!
Taru, you cretin!
Trunsform!
Treasure hunting is fun!
Good Lord...
Puffed you up!
Right, right!
Honmaru, you okay?
Taru!
Are we not in the treasure room yet?
Almost there.
Stre-re-retch!
This was fun, Honmaru!
Let's hunt treasures more often!
What part of it was fun, exactly?
Just now I thought I'd be a goner because of you!
Learn to self-reflect at least a bit!
Taru, you did it again...
Taru!
Now we're screwed.
Now we're for real darn screwed!
Sorry, Honmaru.
Young Master,
I regret deeply to inform you of this.
It appears we still are unable
to locate the entrance.
Obtaining a goal without any opposition
is devoid of excitement.
Well then, it's about time
to start playing trumps.
Taru!
Taru-chan, the treasure room is in front of you.
Finally!
My treasure!
Who dares to intrude,
snatching away the treasure?!
I am the treasure's guardian!
No tomb raider shall leave this place alive!
Taru!
Just what for...?!
We're done now...
Can I have treasure? Can I?
Rub, rub.
Now that I think of it,
my lifetime was still so short.
I guess I don't have a choice.
Look, I can't decide such matters on my own.
Though I'm not giving you the treasure...
Look. You should make do with this.
The seeds that grow into a money tree.
Honmaru! Got the goods!
What a... Nonsense!
Auntie, thank you!
See you again!
Be careful on your way home!
"Auntie" is what I least expected...
All's well that ends well, Honmaru.
Let's hurry home
to plant those money tree seeds right away!
Though not 5 billion,
1 billion is good enough, too!
Harako!
Treasure obtained.
Give it back!
Property deed, belongs to Harako Conglomerate.
Young master bought this mountain, you see.
You cannot take away anything that lies in this land.
That would be larceny, otherwise.
Or would you prefer us
to hand you over to police custody?
Tree that bears money?
Even more of it for me?
Crap!
One billion...
No, I wouldn't have minded even just 100 million.
But now all of that just turned into a flat 0.
Honmaru, cheer up.
Besides, you not hungry yet?
It's good to be the always-carefree-Taruruuto.
Taru-chan! Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan!
I'm so glad I found you!
I've been so curious about what happened after,
and was on my way to your house.
So, was it fun, Taru-chan?
We saw many interesting things, Iyona.
Glad to hear that.
Here. They are my first home-made ones.
Takoyaki!
Having grown branches so heavily laden
in a matter of just few hours!
No less from the treasure of Jamatai kingdom!
This should serve as an indisputable proof
that money circulated in the form of stones then.
It is certain to cause a sensation!
Still, it's a bit of an overkill
to call it money-bearing tree.
Ya friggin kidding me?!
Ooops.
Young Master...
Young Master!
So tasty, Iyona.
Your takoyaki are the best.
Thank you, Taru-chan.
Honmaru, Iyona's takoyaki
is even better than the treasure.
And Honmaru-kun...
Deli-li-licious!
Glad to hear!
I guess you're right, Taruruuto.
The takoyaki that Iyona-chan put her heart in,
and that cute sincere smile...
We stumbled upon a treasure way more precious
than that found in any crypt!
Delicious! Irresistibly delicious!
Right, Taru?
Iyona, make takoyaki again sometime.
Promise me, promise!
Actually, I always considered the hotcakes my forte.
Hotcakes are fine, too!
Nay! Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Taruru!
I earned the disgust of Iyona-chan!
It's Ijigawa!
All because of her pranks again!
What do you mean? If you got something to tell me,
then put it frankly, you bed-wetter!
My patience is on its last legs!
Taruruuto!
A magic punishment.
You can count on my help!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
I am Ijigawa Rui.
Every-ry-ryone, watch!
Episode 7
I am Ijigawa Rui
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume