Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 26
To Battle, Honmaru!
Jabaoyama's victory!
That should teach you!
I don't suppose anyone else
wishes to become my opponent?
Come on, let's do sumo! Sumo!
Yeah! Sumo! Sumo!
Tsk. That prick Jabao is at it again.
Took him just one victory in Kindergarten Sumo Championship
to start putting on airs. Tsk.
What's worse, girls are also gluing
their eyes to this place.
And blabbering about it incessantly!
Jabao seems to be pretty well-built for it.
Right, Iyona-chan?
I like sumo, too.
Honmaru! I do sumo, too!
Jabao, you do sumo with me!
What?
Don't do it, Taru!
Got some audacity, don't you?
This was ill-considered of you, Taruruuto.
Alright, I'll show you why you should rethink!
In position!
Okay!
Enough warming up, Taru!
Now, come at me!
Okay!
The hell was that, you bastard?!
Saw it in TV sumo yesterday.
Did just what they did.
But that was with salt and before the match!
You little...
Get back here, you ass!
Jabao!
Can't we play any other fun game besides sumo?
Why should we?
Could it be because you're weak?
Whaddya say?!
Well, you know, last time we tried
doing sumo with you,
one half-assed throw was enough to bring you to tears, wasn't it?
Dripping...
In the end...
I ended up peeing my pants!
Ah! I just remembered!
Right, right!
It was when Honmaru became a Li'l Pants Wetter!
Oh, I see.
Honmaru became a Li'l Pants Wetter
after just getting thrown by Jabao-san once?
He really did!
Honmaru at any other age
would still be Honmaru!
Honmaru! So you're just like me!
Hooray! Honmaru, Li'l Pants Wetter!
Honmaru Li'l Pants Wetter!
Yay! Yay! The Great Pants Pisser!
Me too! Me too! Me peed myself a lot, too!
Me and Honmaru friends!
Iyona is watching, too...
Honmaru's inner Li'l Pants Wetter might get evoked again,
so better run away while you can.
Things will turn nasty if he does.
Honmaru! With magic, I can make everyone
wet their little pants with us! Everyone friends!
Taru, I need you to just watch silently.
We need no magic today.
Jabao!
Be it sumo or whatnot, it won't frighten me!
Don't you look down on me as a Li'l Pants Wetter
just cause I lost to you in the past!
Honmaru-kun!
Huh?
Say, I did it with even less effort than the last time.
Damn you...
Once again!
Why can't I do a single thing to Jabao?!
Ouch!
Potato Chips
Ugh!!
It hurts!
What the hell?!
Teacher...
Your class had started a long time ago.
Didn't you hear the school bell?
Why didn't you tell me before, Taru?
Taru!
Honmaru told me to watch silently!
I watched and kept silent.
Teacher, it was Honmaru who kept asking for it,
notwithstanding the fact that he's such a weakling.
Who're you calling a weakling?!
How about you beat me before you say anything?
It's the only sport that fatasses are cut out for.
Whaddya say!?
You heard me!
I get it!
For ten days, starting today
we'll be doing sumo for PE class.
Then, on the last day, we'll hold a match
to find out who the strongest wrestler in the class is.
How about this?
Is it fine with everyone else, too?
Sumo...?
Eh? What's the matter, Harako-kun?
You're unusually quiet today.
Rightly said.
Harako, what became of your usual enthusiasm?
Aren't you some Junior Sumo World Champion Wrestler
among kindergarteners?
Sumo doesn't fit my style.
If you just look at me,
it'll be clear as day: becoming a fatso
just for the sake of some sports is below me.
It goes against my sense of beauty.
Right, right!
Sumo is a sports for fatasses!
Even you say smart things
every once in a while!
Don't you make fun of sumo!
Sumo has always been
Japan's trademark sport.
Moreover, it is rooted in a tradition
that had persisted with us since ancient times.
It was 2500 years ago in India, when the original Buddha
won a beautiful princess as his wife in a sumo bout.
Sumo is by no means superficial!
Sumo is the most strenuous one
of all the known martial arts!
If you lose a sumo bout,
you lose your masculinity along with it!
If you can't win in sumo,
you will never be able to make your woman happy!
I never had any idea!
Sumo was actually
such a noble sport all this time!
Who's the blockhead now?
How do you like it when even the teacher says that
sumo's the most strenuous and the manliest of martial arts?
I'm already looking forward
to our match in ten days!
Damn you...
Ha... ra and ko...
Old man!
I need a sumo champion this instant!
Arrange an emergency coach for me!
Harako!
Teacher, in order to undergo special sumo training,
I would require you to grant me a few days' leave!
Much obliged.
But I never allowed it, Harako-kun!
Young Master, we'll get you straight to this man.
We need to hurry, Old Man!
We can't waste a single moment!
Harako, you prick...
No way I'll let him seize this victory without a fight.
If it comes to this,
I'll undergo special sumo training, too!
Taru, let's go!
Yeah, Honmaru!
What?!
Skipping school for ten days starting now
to undergo special sumo training?!
Yes...
Honmaru...
Dad! Losing a match in sumo
means losing your masculinity as well!
He who can't win a sumo bout
will never be able to make his woman happy!
Just like you did with boxing before,
teach me how to do sumo!
Dad, I beg you too! Need your teaching!
Not a word more, Honmaru!
Not less to be expected from a son of mine!
Alright! A secluded special training in the mountains!
Yeah, dad!
Dad!
Time to become as strong as 100 people!
Honmaru!
Seclusion in the mountains? Sounds fun.
Sis!
Sister Ria...
Even though it's still the height of winter,
your outfit is already that exposing?
The young ladies of recent years are all like this...
That previous dress was growing old on me,
so I decided to try a new one for a change.
Like it?
Looks mighty becoming on you, sister Ria.
Ten out of ten.
Right, dad?
That is very well said.
Let's see...
If we need a secluded mountain, Canada has...
Just a spot for that right here.
In Canada?
Should I get us there all together with magic?
Yeah!
A special training
in the great Canadian wilderness!
How about that?
Sounds good.
I've also been wanting to visit Canada
at least once since long ago.
Brilliant as always, sister Ria!
Sister, please do!
Taru, what's with that globe?
This - Hop-globe, you need but to point where you wanna go
and it hops you there.
It really sent us all the way here!
No doubt about it, we're in Canada.
Honmaru! Let's do a snowball fight,
just like the last time!
That's not what we came here for!
And it's so cold!
Taru, do something about it with magic!
Idiot!
While losing even to the cold,
you can't expect to win in sumo!
Got it!
Now!
The special practice!
Miracle Star!
What's that for?
Sister's Miracle Star changes things
into whatever she has in mind.
Looks becoming on you, Honmaru.
Do your best, Honmaru!
By the time you're back,
I'll be waiting with dinner!
First, you need to get used to being heavy
by running in the deep snow!
Fight, Honmaru!
So cold! At this rate, I'll freeze to death
before the special training is concluded!
Wow! Canadian snow!
Tsk. It's good to be Taru!
He can just play around casually.
Harako
Harako Gym
Do you like this pick, Young Master?
Before you, the strongest and most acclaimed in history
grand champion of sumo.
We have secured the finest coach to teach you,
in the form of Dekanishiki.
Alright, let's not waste a minute more.
Counting on you!
Look closely, Iyona-san.
That's one mighty river! Falling into it would mean
getting carried away by the stream and a certain death!
Canada is not fooling around!
Honmaru, for your next training, I need you to enter that river
and walk it upward through rapids. Could you do that for me?
Eh?! No way!
Yes! Now that's what I call special training!
If your legs learn to withstand a stream that mighty,
you'll become immovable on the ring!
Dad, please be reasonable!
I'll be dead long before that becomes true!
Don't you worry.
Inflatable Muscles?
Heavenly... Ah... Sister Ria's breath
is spreading through my whole body.
Muscle
The raw power is blown into my body!
I no longer feel cold, and instead, radiate the heat myself!
Inflatable Muscleman Honmaru!
Muscle
Snap!
Sister Ria, why did you inflate me this much?
That was not the Inflatable Muscles-kun,
but Infattable Bulge-kun instead.
It suits you greatly, Honmaru.
No way...
This ushers in the high tide of the special training!
When your body is made chubby with Infattable Bulge-kun,
the small injuries should not bother you.
But I'm a bit unsightly this way. Sister Ria,
how about you blow me with Inflatable Muscles-kun instead?
Enough dilly-dallying!
Get in the damn water!
Honmaru! Take a grip of your lower body
and keep it close to the ground, like during sumo line-drawing!
Take this pose!
Draw the line now!
I see, this stance is the key!
I can withstand the stream!
Good! Now start moving upstream
with your feet on the ground!
Feet on the ground?
But first, keep both your arms
pinned down to the body.
Then, start moving forward,
sliding your feet against the ground!
Oh, I see! By raising the leg, you disturb your balance,
then the stream can easily carry you off!
Also think of the water trying to carry you off
as your opponent.
To be able to advance,
you need to push it aside first!
To battle! To battle!
Keep trying, Honmaru!
Okay!
To battle! To battle! To battle! To battle!
Come, Jabao! Come, Harako!
Damn it all! Never again am I giving Iyona-chan
a reason to think of me as a Li'l Pants Wetter!
To battle!
Right! That's the spirit!
Honmaru, great progress!
To bat—
Cretin! You raised your waist again!
Start anew!
Shucks! To battle! To battle! To battle. To battle...
Honmaru! Your waist is not low enough
and your center of gravity is too high!
And mind your hips when moving forward!
Damn it all! To battle! To battle! To battle!
Lower your hips more!
To battle! To battle!
That's the way! Stay collected!
To battle! To battle. To...
Dad! This special training is still too much for me!
Let's return to Japan...
What's so good about this special training
in the great wilderness?!
I'm fed up with trees, mountains and people -
everyone is getting on my nerves!
And this stupid body -
the most deplorable!
Honmaru!
Honmaru is playing in the wateru-ru-ru with us, too!
Tsk! Where I'm facing the ordeal of special training,
he's just splashing around!
So cold and so refreshing!
Niruru, let's have a race!
It's good to be always carefree.
Like those two. I swear!
The hell?!
But how...
How is it possible for Taru
to just swim through the rapid upwards so playfully?
Honmaru! Canadian Creek-chan is friend, too!
Nice to meet you, Taruruuto!
Let's play together!
And look out, I can go pretty high!
Alley-hop!
I see. It just dawned upon me!
Damn right, Honmaru!
This is something your body had already learned long ago!
Using your whole body
to read the flow of nature, not oppose it!
Seeing through it with your heart!
I had completely forgotten…
Taru doesn't have to cast a spell on it
for the water to be alive.
The trees, the soil, and the sky...
Everything around me is alive!
Alive...
Alive!
To battle! To battle! To battle!
Honmaru, you came to see the water's alive!
Exactly! Opposing the stream gets you nowhere!
Merging with the stream is the way to go!
Merging!
Way to go, Honmaru!
To battle! To battle!
Keep going, Honmaru!
Looking good! Keep this up, Honmaru!
To battle! To battle!
If you merge into it,
the nature and your body work in perfect harmony!
Then, no wildest rapid...
No steep waterfall...
No force of nature...
Can stop me!
Can't stop me, I said!
Can't stop me...
I'll show you the ways of nature as it is now, Jabao, Harako!
To battle! To battle!
To battle!
Right! I'll fix you now!
The disgraceful defeat of a kid who peed himself
will forever be erased from everyone's minds!
Come at me, Honmaru!
Magical Faturuuto-kun:
Honmaru, Enter the Ring!
I'll tear you to shreds!
Episode 27
Honmaru, Enter the Ring!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius