Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
I love the sea, wherever it may be.
Faint scent of sea breeze,
Here I come.
The sea... We'll meet soon enough.
The whispers of the waves.
Episode 47
Mischievous Seaside School
No matter the time, Iyona-chan always looks lovely!
I love her so much!
And that soft sensation...
I got so close to her!
Seaside school!
Soon enough, I'll see it - Iyona-chan's swimsuit!
Honmaru!
What is it this time?!
Look, look! This newest high-leg swimsuit!
This summer, I've decided on going audacious!
My swimsuit would wipe the floor with that.
It's by a famous Italian designer from Milan.
Vittorio himself designed my swimsuit
Therefore! My looks will be unrivaled.
Harako-kun...
The privilege of wearing an unrivaled swimsuit will be mine.
Alright, let's have a duel!
Do it, do it! Looks fun!
Christ, someone here sure likes jumping to duels.
Things are never easy with these guys.
Welcoming Nannosho Elementary School Group
Beach House
Everyone!
Huh?
How about this?
I wanna throw up when I see a male high-leg!
Hey, everyone!
You've hit the bull's eye, Ijigawa!
It becomes you so well, Ijigawa-san!
Honmaru!
Oaya-sensei looks amazing too!
That's our teacher, alright!
Ijigawa looks stunning,
but Oaya-sensei can make you lose your head!
Are you okay, Honmaru?
Impressive, Iyona-chan!
As audacious as it gets!
My mother said...
Iyona-chan,
I've picked a perfect swimsuit
for you to wear at seaside school.
Look.
That'd be awfully embarrassing, mother.
What is embarrassing about it?
That's exactly what your young, vivacious body needs.
But it's just some strings, not a swimsuit.
As a daughter of the Kawai clan,
how could you be embarassed in any way
by such a swimsuit?
As you're being gazed at, your body is kept in tonus,
and so you become even more beautiful.
Can you imagine what a stunning young maiden
you'll be when you grow up?
I'm looking forward to it.
Mother, I'm sorry.
Maybe I am a bad daughter, after all.
Ah! My normal cute swimsuit is not here!
Mother?
You won't make light of my words and get away with it.
Let us meet again after your body has learned
to wear this swimsuit unabashedly.
And that's why...
My, isn't your mother a lovely woman?
But that's fine too. It befits you greatly!
That's right, Iyona-san!
You wouldn't believe how good it looks on you!
The gazes are swarming all over me...
It is too embarrassing, after all!
Iyona-chan, no need to worry.
I'll also wear a high-leg matching with yours!
What are you talking about?
Look!
My high leg swimsuit!
Iyona-chan...
So embarrassing!
I wish there was a hole for me to hide in!
Hole?
Honmaru!
Where are you taking me, Taru?
To where I was playing in the sand earlier!
Taru!
Why are you doing that?
Honmaru hid inside a hole!
That's not it!
It's a saying for when you're embarrassed -
"I wish there was a hole for me to hide in!"
Honmaru, why you embarrassed?
'Cause my pants went bust
and my willy was on display for everyone!
Now, dear ladies.
How about you leave behind the willy-displaying idiot
and join me for a swim?
Harako too.
I got pants! Pants!
Wait, you!
Harako embarrassed too?
Damn right I am embarrassed!
Give it back right now!
Everyone laughing! This seems pretty fun!
On display!
Huh?!
One more.
No! No! Please stop it!
Jabao too, Korekiyo too! Everyone embarrassed!
Wait a minute!
Trunsform...
Get back here!
Stop, Taruruuto!
Alright! Let's catch him!
This - Smooth Mermaiding-kun.
Wearing this, you can swim as fast as as fish.
Try to catch! I'm here!
You prick!
Get back here!
We'll get you!
What?!
Isn't that dangerous?!
I'm exhausted...
True...
On display!
Taru sure knows how to make a show of it.
I hope he doesn't regret it when he's scolded later.
Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan?
Thank you for what you did for me earlier.
The risqué swimsuit shines brightly
I'm all jittery today, on this white sand beach
Whaa...
Ah! Weirdos!
Hold the board in your right hand
and smash the accelerator of your heart
Toot-toot! Let's go to the surfing beach!
Your gaze lingers on my white bare skin
My heart palpitates wildly in the orange sunlight
We would carefully decide on sunglasses,
So raise that volume on the radio
Toot-toot! Wait for me, surfing beach!
The sea in midsummer is full of excitement!
And I'm aiming for a thrill, like what they have in movies...
Woo, if it's for you...
This sun in a big blue sky
Is burning brightly
Woo, forever and ever...
The sublime vacation, feeling better than ever!
Let's make some splashes, then scuttle away!
Woo, gladly!
Wait!
This earth is only ours!
This earth is yours!
Well, everyone, let's do some special surfing today.
Any volunteers?
No, thanks...
Yes, teacher! I'll do it.
Iyona-chan is coming along, right?
But I...
Iyona-san, if you'd like it, I would gladly teach you.
Beautiful teacher!
With consideration to my prior abilities,
I believe I should be entrusted with coaching the female group.
After all, for someone retaining the
World Junior Surfer Champion title for five years straight,
there's no need to be showing off.
Very well. Please do just that.
Now, among those who remain,
anyone would like to enjoy riding with me?
Damn this prick Harako!
We let him look so cool before Iyona-chan!
Me tired. Can't hold buckets any longer.
Right! If Taru's with us, we can work something out.
Alright...
Teacher! I'll do that too!
Honmaru-kun, do you have any surfing experience?
No... But I have a feeling
that something good may come out of it!
Admirable! Athletes who constantly look
to challenge themselves - now that's what I love!
Teacher, also me and this guy!
Eh? I'm fine enough here!
Okay, everyone. I'm counting on you to train intensely.
Okay!
Counting on you, Taru!
That's all the basics,
you'll have to memorize the rest on your own.
Now, who wants to start?
Start, like there?
You mean, in that sea?
That's right. Isn't it perfectly rough?
You can't be serious!
You're asking for too much, teacher!
So, what's up with everyone?
Jabao-kun, maybe you?
You want me to do it? To tell you the truth, I have second thoughts about this, so I'd rather do it later.
Quacking in your boots, Jabao?
What?! Are you calling me a coward or something?
Am I wrong for this?
Alright! Courageous boy Jaba Jabao
will show you what's what.
Hey, come, Korekiyo.
Just as you said, I have
some second thoughts about this!
Like it or not, we're in the same boat!
Now come!
Jabao-san, please let go of my hand!
Last warning to everyone, don't come near that ocean!
It's deadly.
How trifling.
Teacher, I suggest we leave those cowards on the shore
and have me riding alone.
That was a skillful getting out.
Do it in the same fashion, everyone!
Impressive!
Isn't he cool, Iyona-chan?
Yes...
I'll never be able to do it in the same fashion!
I guess I'll have to rely on Taru, after all.
Hey, Taru...
Can you use some magic to enable me to surf?
Honmaru, that impossible.
Me don't know surfing.
You shouldn't be talking like that,
just help me out a bit, Taruruuto!
Okay...
Oh, I know! I should ask Tama-chan
for everything I don't understand...
Right!
But I remembered I left Tama-chan behind.
Honmaru-kun, let's do it while supporting each other.
You can count on me, Iyona-chan!
After all, nothing is impossible for me!
Then, Honmaru-sama, let me accompany you
to where the waves are!
Taru!
Honmaru, do your best! I'll be rooting for you.
That's not what I meant...
Now! Iyona-chan, you come too!
Okay.
Do your best, Honmaru!
Taru...
I'd sooner die on these waves!
Honmaru, stay strong!
We're riding for real this time!
Oh! Taru's magic?
Yeah.
Now, Honmaru, get up!
And I'll be sure to hold your legs up.
Alright...
That's it, let's start, Honmaru!
Been a while since I could roam waves freely!
After me!
What just...
What?
How is he able to surf in the opposite direction?
Just what I expected from Honmaru-kun.
He had known long ago everything I was teaching them!
Amazing!
He's riding better than professionals!
What?
He even nailed the loop
that's said to be every surfer's dream?
A piece of cake!
I'm glad for you, Honmaru!
Thank you, Taru!
It's coming...
Yes. No doubt about it.
This tide, this wind...
A perfect sibling synergy that only
comes together once every 20 years...
We were waiting dormant for long enough...
Giant Swell is finally here!
Giant Swell?
Young man! You seem to know your way around surfing,
but you shouldn't even think about riding those waters.
That's right, those waves are a brutal beast indeed.
If you value your life, don't come near it.
Well, that sure sounds like fun!
Ain't it, Honmaru?
Why don't we also try our prowess
against that Giant Swell thing?
Yeah! A combination such as us two
can get anything done!
Idiot!
Let's do it!
We were once in that age too.
Yeah.
Alright, are we going too?
Yeah!
The overturning pace is getting somehow strange...
Guys, it's about time we returned ashore.
Harako, some phenomenal waves are coming soon.
Wanna try to ride them with me?
Curious! I accept that duel!
It's dangerous! Stop while you can, you two!
Keep going!
Honmaru-kun...
Let's do it, Harako!
I won't lose, Honmaru!
Ain't no way I'll let you look all cool and manly!
Aren't you guys quite experienced in this?
Get ready to see just how experienced we are!
Let's go!
Harako, now's your time to quit
if you don't wanna end like them!
Don't you look down on me!
He's also pretty determined,
isn't he, Surfboard-kun?
Uh?
My magic ran its ten minute course!
Uh? Then...
And how am I supposed to come back from here, Taru?!
Idiot, don't come near!
Really, you're lucky that neither of you got seriously injured.
This means you'll be able to enter
the long-distance swimming contest tomorrow.
Long-distance? But do they specify
just for how long we'll have to swim?
Alright, Honmaru! We'll settle the score
for surfing with swimming tomorrow!
This!
Yay! Won! Won again!
Dammit! Taru, let's have one more round!
Sure! As many as you want.
We'll do it! I'm locked and loaded, Honmaru!
It's the final day of the fun seaside school adventure!
We'll hold a test of courage tonight!
After taking a bath, me and Iyona-chan
go out to the beach at night...
I'm counting on you big time, Taruruuto!
Honmaru, what's courage test?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Exhausting Test of Courage.
Ghost...
Episode 48
Exhausting Test of Courage
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius