Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Honmaru...
The river is dirty.
That's 'cause everyone keeps throwing their trash in it.
It's like they're forgetting we've only got one Earth.
You have smart thoughts, Honmaru.
That's just what someone on TV said.
Taru, let's go home to try mom's snacks.
Yeah!
Episode 86
Special Training with Personal Flovirtue-kun
Korekiyo-kun! Today, we'll finally
settle the scores in that game.
When it comes to games, I can't lose!
We'll see about that!
Ah! They're throwing their litter.
There's no helping those two...
Huh? Did you say something, Honmaru?
You got a problem with us?
This won't do. You gotta throw the cans
into the specially designated bin.
Like this.
Empty cans can be reused too, you know.
We gotta be frugal with the resources we have.
I did something good today.
You ass! Since when do you think
you can walk around telling me what to do?!
Are you a busybody for the Environmental Agency?
You obnoxious worm!
Honmaru, witness the
deadly technique I devised myself!
What the hell is that?
Jabao Special Number One!
How about this?
Disgusting!
Jabao, you jerk!
Do your best, Honmaru!
You're not getting away with it!
So what?
Wanna taste my deadly technique once more?
Jabao Spe—
How about this?
Stop it, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona?
Fighting is bad, Honmaru-kun.
No, it was Jabao...
Iyona-chan, Honmaru-kun
attacked me unprovoked!
That's bullshit! Hey, Jabao!
Exactly! He was bullying us...
Honmaru-kun...
Save us, Iyona-chan!
It's not true!
Jabao and Korekiyo are the ones at fault!
Jabao at fault.
Jabao Special Number Two.
If Honmaru is speaking like that,
I'm scared he might attack again, so please walk us home!
Please don't leave us to our fates!
Well, let's go now.
Okay...
As a thank you, I've got some
delicious soda for you back at home.
Alright, let's have a good time there,
all three of us!
They left, Honmaru.
Iyona-chan...
Eat this, Honmaru.
Damn it! All I did was toss an empty can into the right bin—a supposedly good deed!
Why?
Mom, why do you say,
"do good things and good things will return to you?"
Let's see... Just like the sun and the Earth
are round, people are all big circles to each other.
That's why good things that you do to others,
come back to you after making a full circle.
And with bad deeds, they'll travel the circle,
coming back to you as even more bad things.
Maru-chan, let's do lots of
ood things and be happy, okay?
Sure.
Mom! You lied to me, didn't you?
How does doing good things
make good things return to you?
Whenever I do good deeds,
I only get the most horrible things in return!
You're a liar!
I'm done with good deeds!
Hey, mom, please say something at least!
Something.
A dead end. I can't even talk to mom about that...
Eat mama's snacks, Honmaru! It's yummy!
What's the point of trying, even?
Tasty, isn't it?
No, it's not.
Honmaru, do you know what a personal virtue is?
I don't.
People who have personal virtue are
liked by everyone, which is a good thing in itself.
Huh? A good thing?
That is also a good thing all around.
Personal virtue
Once you build up your personal virtue,
lucky events will follow one after another.
You'll also be popular with the girls, big time.
Really?
Hey, how do I build up that personal virtue?
It's easy.
Then teach me how to do it, mom!
Listen, then. By performing many good deeds,
you build up your personal virtue.
Back to square one, then?
Honmaru, do your best!
Is mom trying to take me for a ride again?
Enough already!
That personal virtue thing is a nonstarter for me.
What's the point of good deeds?
Honmaru. Honmaru!
This - Personal Flovirtue-kun.
What's that?
You sow the seeds of Flovirtue-kun...
to know what Honmaru's personal virtue is.
Hey! What are you doing on top of my head, Taru?
Sprout up, sprout up, Flovirtue-kun.
Sprout up!
Taru! Taru, stop it, you!
Stop it, I said! Taru!
If it sprouts up and the flower appears,
Honmaru has personal virtue.
Eh? The flower?
Honmaru, it sprouted up!
Oh! And the flower bloomed!
That means I have personal virtue, right?
Have, have! Honmaru has personal virtue!
I did it!
But it's still small, Honmaru.
Taru, do you have personal virtue too?
Let's try it on you.
Yeah!
Sprout up, sprout up, Flovirtue-kun!
Don't get your hopes too high.
You can't beat my gracious flower, that's for sure!
For sure!
Look at my personal virtue flower!
Ah, it's enormous compared to mine!
That's amazing, Taru-chan.
How about this, Honmaru? I beat you!
Why's that?
Why is Taru's personal virtue so huge?
Hey, stop, Honmaru!
Damn it! Why's that? Why? Why? Why?
Well, that's because Taru-chan
is always working so hard for Honmaru.
You're heavy, Honmaru.
Because Taru-chan is such a good boy,
his personal virtue is big.
I see...
Come to think of it, only good things
have kept happening to Taru up until now.
Everyone likes him too...
And back then...
Back then too!
I see!
Alright!
I'll build myself some big personal virtue too!
Here I come, life of good fortune and popularity!
Just doing good things is enough, right?
Mom, I'll do all the dishes today!
Keep it up, Honmaru.
Taru, look at this!
I won't lose to Taru, alright?
Just you watch! I'll grow myself an enormous flower too!
Good deed, good deed!
Honmaru, doing good things with a smile
is even better!
Okay!
Doing things where no one
can see you is also really good.
I get it! Asking others
for anything in return is a no-go!
Great, Honmaru!
Thus, I did every single good
thing around I could think of.
Then finally...
You did plenty of good things, Honmaru.
Taru, hurry up and sow the seeds of Flovirtue-kun!
Here it goes.
Amazing, Honmaru!
How about this?
It grew much bigger, didn't it, Taru?
That's how my fortuitous life starts!
Skip-skip, la-la-la!
I hope something good happens soon!
Hey! Honmaru-kun, Taru-chan!
Don't you know you can't skip in the hallway?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Good, I appreciate your honest remorse.
Be careful from now on, will you?
Okay.
Honmaru-kun, did you
understand the math class today?
No, I...
That's alright. Come to the staff room.
I'll tell you more about it.
We also have delicious steamed buns there.
Okay!
Staff Room
So good and tasty!
Come on, try some too, Honmaru-kun.
I'm sure you'll nail the next math test.
You're so smart, after all.
Thanks for the meal!
Eat as much as you'd like.
Delicious, Honmaru!
Yeah! It's good!
Why did he get steamed buns
for being caught skipping in the hallway?
The teacher seems to be in a good mood today.
Alright, we'll ride this train too!
And... start!
Skip-skip, steamed buns!
I wanna eat them sooner, steamed buns!
Hey! You two over there!
It's here!
We'll get it, right?
Right?
You can't skip in the hallway. Don't you know?
Teacher, steamed buns are...
Are?
I won't tolerate you messing around.
Why do you always have to be such a bad boy?!
Why is this happening?
Teacher, mercy!
Taru, I guess we got lucky, didn't we?
Thanks to personal virtue, Honmaru.
What is it, Ijigawa?
Why did you want to meet me here?
Eh? Ah...
It's just...
You're being weird, Ijigawa.
Um... I baked these cookies myself.
If you'd like it, you can eat them.
Sure. Thank you.
Smells good cookie! Cookie!
But... why?
Hey, Ijigawa!
What kind of lightning struck her?
It was because you're so wonderful.
Iyona-chan?
What did you just say?
It was because you are wonderful.
Iyona-chan!
You've finally understood, haven't you?
I'm tickled pink!
That's right.
Because you've been such a nice person lately,
both Rui-chan and I couldn't help admiring you.
Taru, you can have this!
Oh! Cookie! Cookie!
Iyona-chan...
I wonder what's going on...
It feels like I can talk to Honmaru-kun
openly about anything.
Come on, leap straight into my arms.
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan admires me...
Cookie, cookie, lucky!
Honmaru, you're going home, right?
I'll give you a lift.
Awesome! Are you sure, Harako?
I prepared it specifically for you, no need to be shy.
By the time we get there,
I hope you enjoy yourselves thoroughly.
Yeah, I owe you one, Harako!
Taru, happy times are here!
Times are here!
Look at that, Taru.
We can see our house from here.
Home looks small.
Why, of course it does!
Did I succeed in entertaining you?
Yeah, it's superb!
Superb!
Hearing that from you guys makes me happy too.
Honmaru, you truly are a good guy.
And my best friend.
Please be my friend forever.
Sure...
Well, see you tomorrow.
See you.
This is a token of my appreciation.
Please accept it.
Sure.
I feel bad, though. Even getting a present for it...
Aren't you glad, Honmaru?
I wonder what the present is.
Show me!
Oh! Amazing!
A wristwatch!
Thank you, Harako!
Thank you!
What a fluke! This is just what I wanted.
Because Honmaru has personal virtue, everyone is kind.
I suppose so.
I have personal virtue, that's right.
There is no other student in our elementary school
with quite as much personal virtue accumulated.
There is no, is no!
Ah! Honmaru-kun!
You're wonderful!
Here, Honmaru-kun. It's for you.
You didn't have to...
Honmaru-kun, please accept this too.
Mine too!
From that day on, my popularity and fortune
have been steadily on the rise.
Doing good things daily...
...brought in return lucky days
where everything went as I wanted.
Hey, Jabao-kun! Move outta the way!
What was that?
Who do you think you are, Honmaru?
That's right.
I am Honmaru, the master of personal virtue.
Virtueless and universally-hated people like you
should keep it closer to the edges.
That's right!
Move to the edges, you!
What's your problem with Honmaru-sama?
I don't wanna get even close to Jabao!
Out of my way!
We're terribly sorry!
Having such great personal virtue,
I had no enemies wherever I'd go.
I didn't have anything to fear either.
Splendid, splendid!
Your subordination to me is now unquestionable.
What now? Is that all
you brought as a tribute today, Harako-kun?
Yes?
Didn't I tell you? I wanted a super TV game and...
Hm... Let's make it a mountain bike.
This guy is forgetting his place.
When you're so rich, being stingy is a no-go.
Wasn't it you who asked
me to remain as your friend forever?
If you do enough good things for others,
you may also accumulate personal virtue
and have good things happening to you, Harako-kun.
I'm fed up with this!
Thou is a foolish kin.
Some cakes again?
I'm tired of that.
What the hell are you doing to the foodstuffs?
I hope divine punishment hits you, Honmaru!
It's wasteful behavior.
Not my fault I'm so tired of them.
Sup. What happened here? Ah!
Hey, you're wasting that!
You can eat it if you'd like to, Jabao-kun.
You jerk... If you're throwing it away,
at least throw it in the trash can!
That's right.
Korekiyo-kun, throw it away for me, will you?
You can also accumulate personal virtue and have
a life of good things if you do enough good things for others.
Isn't that right, Iyona-chan?
That's what you get for flying too high, Honmaru.
Serves you right!
What's going on? You're sickening me.
What happened, Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru-kun, that's indecent!
Still no divine punishment!
Even divine punishment
won't be enough!
The world doesn't revolve around you!
How can you decide what I deserve or not?!
Did you forget who I am?
I'm Honmaru-sama himself!
Right, Iyona-chan?
Honmaru-kun is the worst.
Iyona-ch—
I can't stand this side of yours!
Ah! But, wait... I'm the king of personal virtue!
Look, my personal virtue flower is enormous!
What flower?
Enough saying nonsense!
Liar!
Let's go.
No, it's true!
Right, Taru?
Yeah!
This - Personal Flovirtue-kun.
Okay, now sow the seeds quickly.
It's a huge flower, I'll show you all!
My personal virtue is extraordinary!
Taru, please hurry up.
Don't be too surprised when you see it.
Sprout up, sprout up, Flovirtue-kun.
Are you starting to wake up to my greatness?
My flower...
What is this?
Something is rotting!
It's rotten!
Ugh! Don't come near me!
Hey... Please wait! Hey...
Run!
No!
Run, Iyona! Faster!
Wait, please!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, they're all done for.
That flower is rotting!
Why?
From getting carried away,
you lost all your personal virtue!
Is everyone going to hate me again?
You'll be fine.
Honmaru, if you work hard again, doing good things,
beautiful flowers will bloom.
Really?
Honmaru, this time, you'll become
a good guy for real. I believe in you!
Taru... Thank you!
I'll try that!
Taru!
Let me go, Honmaru!
Taru...
It stinks!
Don't come close, Honmaru!
Wait for me, Taru!
Alright! I'm on fire!
Me on fire too.
The main event of the cherry blossom viewing
is the big obstacle race. Iyona-chan's lips will be mine!
Honmaru drooling. Drooling!
Alright!
Go for it!
I'm excited to fight!
Yeah! Excited!
But remember, magic is forbidden, Taru!
Okay!
I'll only kiss the takoyaki!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
The Most Important Kiss.
Episode 87
The Most Important Kiss ❤
I'm on fire-ru-ru!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius