Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Please take a look. On our island, we use shells to coin money. These Shell-Coins circulate as money.
Isn't it strange to use shells as money, Taru?
Yeah, they're so pretty...
I'd like to see it at least once though.
Me'd like to see it too.
Taru!
Sorry, Honmaru.
Episode 79
Reconciling is Hard!
Have you seen it?
The Worlds of Love yesterday.
Of course! How could we have not seen it?
That was one interesting issue, wasn't it?
What a beautiful and lovely idea,
to use shells as money.
Wish I could also go there
and bring back at least one of those coins.
I think they called it Shell-Coins, didn't they?
Isn't it a Shell-Coin?
Where'd you get it, Korekiyo?
I went to that island last summer
to spend my vacation there.
I've been holding on to this since then.
Well done, Korekiyo.
It brings back so many memories
of that everlasting summer paradise.
Just recollecting it now sends my heart fluttering.
What took you so long?
Don't you know time and tide wait for no man?
No, I mean... Well... Thank you, miss.
Impressive! That's a real Shell-Coin!
It's much prettier than what we saw on TV!
That's wonderful!
Hey, Korekiyo. Lend me this for a moment.
But this is an important memento.
If it gets destroyed...
Show it, Korekiyo!
Okay...
Well, my bad! It almost felt
like I forced you to do something just now.
Oh! It's real pretty!
Take a look, everyone!
Huh? Show me!
Here!
Really pretty!
Um... Please handle it with care.
Lemme see it too! Hey! I wanna see it!
Okay, that's it.
Hey! Don't be so stingy!
I haven't had a chance to look at it yet!
My Shell-Coin...
Sorry, Korekiyo!
Why did you do this?!
It was my precious memento!
But I apologized, didn't I?
Honmaru, you destroyed it
out of jealousy, didn't you?
What? Why are you still after me
even though I apologized?
What's your game,
destroying others' precious possessions?!
Korekiyo, you shouldn't be fuming so much over it.
If anything, they said this thing would cost
about 1000 yen in normal Japanese money.
So how about I bring 1000 yen tomorrow
and we forget about it?
Don't give me that nonsense!
Return it back to me in its original state!
Ah, I know!
There, see? Stick it on cellotape
and it's back to how it was!
I would never accept this kind of hack job!
Well, ain't you a nitpicking type, Korekiyo?
Nobody wants to hang out
with someone who's constantly complaining!
What was that?!
You're a monster, Honmaru!
Damn right, Honmaru!
You can't talk like that, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
Aren't you getting cocky, Honmaru?
Taru! Please do something!
Honmaru's are white too!
Hey, it's not the time to be talking in riddles!
Give me some magic item
for restoring broken things back to how they were!
An item that can restore broken things to how they were?
Okay...
That's it! As expected
of the Great Magician Taruruuto-sama!
Ah, damn... Even Taru's magic is of no use...
Honmaru! What are you gonna do about it?!
Wh-What?
Don't avoid the question!
Adieu, Ryoguchiya Korekiyo!
Wait! That's cowardly!
Later!
Honmaru-kun...
Does he have any shame at all?
Dammit! I'll never forgive him, I swear!
Nobody likes guys like him!
Honmaru…
My precious Shell-Coin...
Give it back!
Korekiyo seems awfully mad.
But I've no magic item for
restoring broken things to their original state.
Me - dropout magician...
Hey, Taru! Let's go to school!
Me still sleepy.
Let me sleep, Honmaru...
If you don't hurry, you'll be late, Taru!
Wakey-wakey!
Hey, Taru!
Ah, you're so troublesome...
Uh... This isn't getting anywhere...
Come on!
I wonder if Korekiyo is still mad.
Good morning!
Sup!
Sup, Korekiyo!
Restore my Shell-Coin.
Look, 1000 yen.
Korekiyo!
Hey, don't be such a sourpuss.
Here, accept this already.
I don't wanna hear any of that!
Please don't compare my precious Shell-Coin
to such earthly things!
What did you say?
What did I say?
Stop it, Honmaru!
It's just as Korekiyo said.
You're so insensitive, Honmaru-kun...
In one ear and out the other -
it's like talking to a horse.
To a horse?!
Honmaru!
Well, if you ignore it, it'll go away.
Yeah.
I'm no horse!
Ah? A drop?
Ah! Hey, Taru!
Taru, you're drooling!
Why do you need to be
such a pain in the ass, Korekiyo?
I even offered to compensate you justly!
Right? Right, Taru?
Some of us sure are fond of sleeping.
Hey, Taru.
Stop sleeping all the time
and do something already!
If you don't have an item to fix what's broken,
just some item for placating someone, or anything, would do!
Hey, Taru! Listen to me!
A nice morning to you, Taru-kun!
What's this?
Isn't that Taru?
What in the world is going on?
Oh? This doesn't look like Taru's living room.
Somehow, it feels like a portal to another world.
Ah! Sister Ria is looking so hot again!
Let's go, Taru.
Yeah.
Now go, Rookanga-kun!
Kanga, kanga!
He just hit Taru!
What kind of thing is this?
What's wrong, Taru?
If you can't even beat him,
you won't ever get the items you want!
Yeah!
Alright.
Taruru Punch!
You can do it, Taru!
That won't do, Taru.
Didn't you say you wanted
that item by any means?
I see!
This is how Ria is giving him private tutoring.
Is it possible that Taru can still get
new magical items even while he's in this world?
I remember now.
When I died and went to a magical land,
because we needed Jump to Heaven,
we had to duel other magicians.
We had to get stamps from them
and exchange those for magical items.
Do your best, Taru!
Even if I don't know
what item it is that you want.
What now? Giving up already?
That way, you're light years away
from the item you want.
Me not down.
Me beat this guy. Beat and stamp him.
Will get the magical item Return-to-how-it-walrus.
With Return-to-how-it-walrus,
return the seashell to how it was!
Honmaru and Korekiyo will reconcile!
What?
Taru is doing that for me...
To make Korekiyo and I reconcile...
Not yet...
Taru, what's the matter?
Me win and get a stamp.
Me do my best for Honmaru!
Not yet...
I'm sorry, Taru.
You work so hard for me,
instead of sleeping at night?
No wonder he's sleeping all day long!
Taru, I'll reconcile with Korekiyo
using my own strength!
Korekiyo, please forgive me!
No can do.
There has to be some way!
Okay? I'm ready to do anything.
If I said no, it means no.
Korekiyo-sama, hey!
Pretty please, rub-rub.
If you're saying you wish to go that far...
Yes! Will you forgive me?
First, get on your knees and apologize.
What?
Oh? Just as I thought,
you weren't really gonna apologize, were you?
What's your answer, Honmaru-kun?
It's not like I'm the one who needs it.
Sorry, Korekiyo.
Not so fast. It's nowhere near enough
for me to forgive you.
Rub my shoulders.
Okay.
When you're done with that,
carry me on your back.
Okay.
And hand me that gum eraser.
And do the school lunch duty instead of me.
Okay.
Cleaning duty as well.
How about we continue tomorrow, Taru?
It's morning already, you know.
Me can't give up yet.
Me'll fight.
Me won't quit!
Taruru Double Kick!
Surrender, kanga...
You did it, Taru!
Yeah.
Look, look, look.
Hey, you're too slow!
Go faster, will you?
Korekiyo, can I ride it next?
Sure, have at it. Come on!
Do you need me to forgive you or not?
How did it come to this?
Me'll win and stamp him.
Me...
Will do my best for Honmaru!
Taru is doing his best for me now.
I should be able to do it too!
Hold fast, Korekiyo!
Clatter-clatter!
Isn't Korekiyo taking it a little too far?
Honmaru-kun...
Honmaru, lick my foot.
Why do you give me that look?
Didn't you say you'd do anything
to earn my forgiveness?
That's nasty!
You sure you wanna go that far, Ryoguchiya?
Korekiyo-kun...
Please don't interfere.
This is between me and Honmaru.
Taru...
Very well. That's enough.
Korekiyo?
If your remorse is that deep, I'll forgive you.
Condemn the offense, but not the offender.
Korekiyo!
It was my fault.
Well, let bygones be bygones.
Even when mended together with cellotape,
Shell-Coin is still Shell-Coin.
Besides...
That girl's smile will forever
remain unbroken in my heart.
Korekiyo...
Honmaru!
Korekiyo!
This - Return-to-how-it-walrus-kun!
You put broken thing in this cage
and it'll return to how it was!
Really?
That's it!
We'll return it to how it was, Korekiyo.
Is that true?
Alright. Let's put it in!
It worked!
It's mended!
Back to how it was!
It's mended, everyone!
Well done, Korekiyo.
Good for you.
As expected of the great Magician Taruruuto-sama!
Ahem! Leave that up to me!
Except my magic wears off in ten minutes.
My Shell-Coin...
Honmaru, you tricked me
into rejoicing prematurely...
What was that?
Didn't you say you'd forgive me earlier?
What?
You heard me!
Honmaru and Korekiyo quarrel again.
I'm still a dropout.
Need to train more.
That's 'cause you do nothing but annoy people,
always pulling trouble out of your ass!
When did I ever pull
any trouble out of my ass?
If I said always, it means always!
What? Name me the exact month, day,
hour, minute, day of the week when it happened!
They're back at it already.
Don't they like to pull trouble out of their asses?
What is the truth in reporting?
To unravel that mystery,
we summoned Taruru Newspaper.
What a petty newspaper this is!
Isn't there at least any kind of incident or scoop?!
Honmaru, scoop! Scoop!
Oh, I knew you could do it, Taru!
Hey, that's a spade!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Classified Scoop Battle!
Episode 80
Classified Scoop Battle
Spade, spade! Run, run, run.
That would be skiping!
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius