Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Alright! Taru, let's go get full on Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Yeah! Takoyaki, takoyaki!
I can't wait to eat Matsu-san's takoyaki again!
Hey, it's too early to be drooling, Taru!
Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Episode 67
Taru's Takoyaki Shop
Me fasteru-ru-ru!
Oh? Think I'll lose?
Oh! I can't quite keep up...
That's because your legs are too short!
Alright!
Grow like mushroo-roo-rooms!
If I become big, I can run fast!
Hey, Taruruuto!
It's fine. Me the Great Magician.
Everyone knows already.
Come on, Taru!
Here! Tako-tako, yaki-yaki, Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Eh?!
Taruruuto!
Matsu-san is squashed!
Matsu-san?
Matsu-san!
Ain't gettin' me!
Oh! Matsu-san, you're alive! Amazing!
Matsu-san!
Matsu-san?
Fancy. So Taru's been a magician all along, eh?
Sorry, Matsu-san!
It's nothing! Toldja already.
Sorry, Matsu-san.
It's fine.
More importantly, you'd better be more careful 'round!
'Specially when using magic!
Yes...
Matsu-san! Your hand slipped!
Matsu-san, are you sure you can handle it?
Matsu-san! Matsu-san, you go get rest!
I'll cover for you as takoyaki chef!
Doncha worry a'thing!
This ain't nothing Naniwa can't handle!
Matsu-san!
Oh, Matsugoro!
Boss!
Working hard, eh?
Yes!
The hell you've been up to?
These bandages and all.
About that... I just got burned here and there.
He's wrong! It was m—
I'm in a good mood today,
so I'll tolerate your stupid ass foolin' 'round like that.
Which reminds me, Matsugoro. You remember how you lost
100,000 yen playing mahjong with us the other day?
You'd better pay me your due...
This instant!
L-Like...
This instant?
You don't have it?
Don't have it?
Yes!
Well, ain't it alright?
He ain't got no 100,000 yen
to pay you so forgive him!
Apologies, boss!
I'll be sure to pay you back! If you give me just a tad bit more time, I'll get ya the dough!
Alright, then!
I'll wait for three more days.
You'd better have it by then!
Aight!
There!
I'm not done yet! Collecting 100,000
in three days is nothing special to me!
Looking good, Matsu-san!
In you go!
There, and in you go!
Matsu-san so good at it!
Turn around, you stupid... Come on. Turn around!
How 'bout that?
No good, no good! Matsu-san,
let me fry takoyaki instead!
'Preciate it, but I'm the one owing the boss.
Gotta bear with it somehow!
Not good. Matsu-san, me injured you!
Rosebind!
What?
Ah! Matsu-san!
Say, those magicians' instruments sure are a handy bunch!
Yeah! Matsu-san, you get a rest.
I'll get you your 100,000 cooking takoyaki.
Are you sure, Taru?
I'm fine! I can stre-re-retch my hand.
I also learned to be a takoyaki chef back in the day.
Leave it to me, alright!
You're pretty good at that.
Yeah! Me very skilled!
Smells delicious already, Taru.
You right... Looks delicious...
Looks so good with the crust...
Delicious...
But can't gobble myself!
Gobbling is unacceptable!
Don't you dare go gobbling them!
Ah, it'll be fine!
Ah! Me won't gobble.
Why you two look at me so scary?
Why me?
And it's done...
Yummy...
Can't gobble. Can't taste. No gobbling...
Fine, whatevs!
If you wanna eat them that bad, go ahead.
It's on the house.
I don't mind! It's a treat, ya hear?
Matsu-san!
Thank you so much!
I can have it too?
Thank you for the meal!
Matsu-san good person!
Me love Matsu-san!
Matsu-san! It's bad!
Head hot. So hot!
Misfortunes never come singly.
Seems I've also caught a cold now. Ain't I unfortunate?
Matsu-san, this is bad!
Need to return to room and sleep right now!
Leave the takoyaki stall to us!
H-He's right!
Idiots!
You think I can leave the shop to the two of you
and just go lie around?!
Matsu-san!
Matsu-san, hang on!
Matsu-san, bite this!
When you bite me, you can teleport in an instant!
Now, hurry up and bite me!
I'm the Telepotato!
What's this thing?
Will this cure my cold?
Bite! Bite!
Pretty good, actually.
Go to the room where Matsu-san lives!
What?
Are you sure it's safe, Taru?
I teleported Matsu-san to his room.
He can get some rest there.
Matsu-san didn't get angry at me.
Even though I gave in to my urges.
Matsu-san is always kind to us!
Oh, that's pretty handy, this magic thing.
Much obliged, Taru.
I hope I don't get spoiled by your infinite kindness...
Ah, it's useless!
Y'know, Taru, I'd appreciate it
if you untied me first.
Alright!
Welcome!
We'll be sure to get the business goin'!
Yeah! It's our thanks to Matsu-san.
Yeah!
Huh?
Hey, Taru, can the two of us
really handle it on our own?
It'll be okay.
Wassup! Business goin'?
Doin' a buck here and there!
What?
Everyone! Let's all work hard for Matsu-san.
Yeah!
Chef Matsu-san always cherishes us!
Ain't no way we won't pay him back!
Please do!
There we go!
Hey! Gonna stir and mix this real hard!
And then...
Into the small holes you go!
Go!
Put it in!
Put in more!
Pour!
Pour...
And then sprinkle the seasoning even and nice!
Ah, put in more!
Oh wow! And then, it's my turn!
We catch it by the edge and turn the takoyaki around!
Yes, turn them around!
We want them round and clean, so turn around!
Yes, like that! Turn around! Back and forth!
I'm round and fried, the yummiest Takoyaki-san!
Tako-tako, yaki-yaki!
You wouldn't believe how yummy we are!
I see! With Matsu-san's own tools,
we'll be able to replicate Matsu-san's taste!
Yeah! They work just the way Matsu-san taught them to.
Good thinking, Taru!
Yeah! Me good thinker!
Hey, whatcha doin'?
How business goin'?!
Wow! A moving takoyaki stall!
Yeah! The walking takoyaki stall is here!
There, there, there!
There, there, there, there!
There... Ow.
Ah! He fell flat!
Alright, set out! We're going to sell takoyaki!
Yeah!
Nice!
Sweet potatoes! Here!
Takoyaki shop here! Takoyaki shop here!
Got takoyaki! Very yummy!
What's that?
You guys go let everyone get a taste!
You'll see how tasty we are once you try us!
Takoyaki storm!
So good!
It's too delicious!
One box is 300 yen!
It's good!
Come on, get closer, closer, closer!
We've enough for everyone!
I'll take three boxes!
Here you go, here you go.
Here! Don't push others please!
Here, thank you!
They're goin' out, goin' out!
Everyone, keep working hard!
Yeah!
Alright! Let's keep selling them like this,
one after another, food stall!
Yeah! You can trust me for anything here!
Taru, let's go to school!
Everyone is probably having club time just about now!
Yeah!
Hey, we're here!
Alright! Let's sell at the school grounds!
Leave it to me!
Hey, Taru! We can't just enter without permission!
Everyone, please buy these takoyaki!
Buy these!
Hey, Taru!
Just try us and you'll see - we're delicious!
Takoyaki storm!
So delicious! Wow!
One box is 300 yen!
Come buy it!
Oh!
Yes, yes, yes! Line up, line up!
Yes! 300 yen a piece!
Yummy-yummy takoyaki for everyone! Yummy!
Taru! If the teacher sees us, we'll be in trouble!
No!
I've prepared these takoyaki especially for Iyona.
For Iyona-chan?
Right! Knowing Iyona-chan,
she's probably in the gym for volleyball practice!
Yeah!
Alright! Let's go to the gym!
Hey!
Give way!
Iyona-chan!
Mimora-chan...
I'm going through special trainings daily, all for you!
I'm starting, Rival!
Okay!
I'll do my best, Mimora-chan!
Here!
It's so round and plump, almost like...
Rival-sama!
Mimora-chan!
Hey, Iyona, buy some takoyaki from me!
What?
Right, buy it, buy it, buy it!
300 yen a box!
Buy from us!
Teacher!
Hey! Iyona, buy takoyaki from me!
Taru-chan?
Teacher, you buy takoyaki too!
Honmaru-kun!
Yes?
Do you think it's appropriate
for an elementary school student to run a takoyaki shop?
You're prohibited from doing any part time job,
even more so right in school!
Um, you see...
Oh, did I wake you up?
"Oh, did I wake you up?"
Mari-sensei!
Apologies. I've let myself in.
Well. Here you go.
No, no, no, no! That's unnecessary!
I'm honored...
Actually, Taru-chan asked me to do it.
T-Taru?
I'm so sorry! It's such a shame for me as a man
to make my former student work in my stead...
No, no! What happened to you was their fault anyway.
Or maybe it was my education's fault?
That absolutely can't be!
I'm glad to know those kids
have this good side to them.
Well, that's only natural.
Sensei!
Ignored...
Look, Matsugoro-san.
Looks like you can rest easy at least for today.
Delicious takoyaki here!
What the?!
Delicious takoyaki! Come closer!
I'll have three boxes!
Five boxes for me!
Alright! Thanks for your business!
I'm so sorry...
We even got you involved, Iyona-chan.
No. It's nothing. You should be proud of yourselves,
Honmaru-kun and Taru-chan!
No... After all, Matsu-san
got into all this trouble because of us.
Hey! Give me ten!
The business is getting better and better!
Everyone, keep doing your best!
Alright! Leave that to us!
Here, your ten yummy boxes.
Hey, Matsu-san! Business goin' alright!
Matsu-san, don't worry about anything and go to sleep!
We need you to get well soon!
Hey, Honmaru, Taru!
I won't forgive you if you ruin my takoyaki's reputation
with your cheap imitations!
Gotcha covered!
Honmaru!
Coming!
Ain't they two cheeky brats.
Taru and Honmaru, thank you!
The next time that the boss shows up
I'll be prepared, knowing I can rely on you,
the finest bastards around!
Taru-sama? Taru-sama!
Jeez... I wonder where Taru-sama could go. Seriously...
Buy it, buy it! Get full on takoyaki!
Takoyaki monster!
Caught ya!
Try some takoyaki!
Never!
I hate takoyaki!
Try it...
Mari-sensei!
Matsu-san!
Teacher!
Honmaru-kun!
I guess we gotta raise
even more dough now, Taru.
Dough rose...
Ach-dammit!
Good morning, Iyona-chan!
You're even more beautiful today.
Shining so brightly in the morning sun!
You are my goddess indeed!
Even 70 years from now, I'll still be loving you.
Let's get married!
Married, married!
Eeek! When did you attach Hearer to me?!
Taru, Iyona-chan hates me now!
It's fine. Iyona actually loves Honmaru!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Heated Skating!
Honmaru, back and forth!
Episode 68
Heated Skating
When expressing your feeling,
Being wishy-washy wishy-washy would get you nowhere
When saying "I like you, I love you,"
You do it in a loud voice from the bottom of your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Even if you...
Say that you love me, I won't mind it
If that's what you really feel in your heart
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Taruru, Taruru-Cataburaruru
Cast a spell on me!
I'll make your wish come true!
Taru's love is you
Love is you!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius