Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
I got a combo!
Caught this one!
A crayfish!
A watermelon!
Man, summer vacation is so much fun!
Much fun!
Delicious!
August 24th, Thursday
August 25th, Friday
Episode 51
Doing Homework With Magic?
Honmaru, it was so much fun in the pool, let's play more!
Sure. Wanna go catching insects in the park?
Iyona-chan should also join us if she'd like.
It's summer vacation, after all!
Playing more with Iyona too!
Sure, but...
Sounds interesting! I'm coming too!
I don't remember anyone inviting you!
What was that, Honmaru?
What's wrong, Iyona-san?
Is there something that worries you?
It doesn't exactly worry me per se,
but I still have some summer vacation homework left to do.
I mean, we've just a week left, remember?
What? Summer vacation homework?
Right. Now that I think of it, I've not done a bit of it.
Not trying to boast or anything,
but I've not even once thought of it yet.
Really? Homework?
What are you laughing at, Honmaru?
I bet you've not done any of it either.
Hey! Long time no see, friends.
Harako?
Ah? Hey, Harako-kun, someone like you
must've long done his summer vacation homework, I imagine.
Won't you let a friend copy it out of kindness?
Well, I didn't actually give much heed to it.
I was vacationing around the word after all.
I still have yet to open a couple of Dom Peri bottles
I drank with Parisiennes.
Such a burden!
Oh really? You haven't done it either?
This is bad. Anyone who forgets about homework
won't get away with it!
Is that clear, everyone? Do your homework bit by bit,
and make a daily habit of it so you don't forget.
Because if you forget about it...
Did I make myself clear? That said, I'm looking forward
to our meeting after your summer vacation ends.
What do we do now?
This trifle ain't worth freaking out over.
If you're so scared of summer vacation homework,
what are you even doing in elementary school?
Stool!
Honmaru, could it be that you've done your homework?
I didn't. I didn't do it, but it's as good as done.
What do you mean by that?
Honmaru, what is that unjustified confidence?
That's right, Harako.
I just outshone you before Iyona-chan's eyes.
Honmaru cool!
With Taruruuto's magic,
doing my homework should be a piece of piss.
Hey, everyone, how about we get together at my house
and hold a studying session?
If we all work hard together, I think,
we'll get the homework out of the way much sooner.
Together with Iyona-chan?
That's a splendidly good idea, Iyona-san.
Agreed!
Ugh, you can't be serious!
I wanna hang out with Iyona-chan too...
Iyona-san, in that case, please let me
give you a ride to your house.
No, I was already going with everyone,
so please go ahead without me.
Is that so?
Honmaru-kun?
Iyona-chan, Honmaru said he'd be just fine
on his own, so forget about him.
Precisely. Your attention is lost on him, Iyona-san.
Well, if you don't mind me going ahead...
Later!
Then, we're coming to the study session too!
Coming, coming!
If we all work together,
we'll be done in no time, Jabao-san.
Yeah! Let's get it out of the way fast and go play again!
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru, we go play too!
Quickly, quickly, quickly!
Yeah! In that case, we'll make sure
to enjoy playing around to the very end!
That'll show you!
Honmaru, we'll be playing in Iyona's house?
Should be fun.
Let's move, Taru.
Okay!
If I had been doing homework daily like the teacher said,
I'd be playing leisurely by now.
Honmaru-kun...
There!
Well, everyone, good job working so hard every day!
He's here again?
Let's all play together!
Hold it, we shouldn't distract them
from studying, Taruruuto-kun.
Aren't you the biggest distraction around?
Shit, what's even good about playing on your own?
Boy! Summer vacation sure is fun!
I'll get you!
Honmaru sure does seem happy.
How dare he come here to show off day after day...
There, get this, get this!
Oh! Hey, that's cold!
Hm! Snotty brat.
Hey! Get back here!
Summer vacation is almost over,
so let's try our best, everyone.
Ain't easy with that guy around!
Honmaru-kun, can you really pull it through
with your homework?
Iyona-chan would be in for a surprise!
Please make it true.
How about this? Perfectly filled out.
All that while Honmaru-kun was
playing around all day... Amazing!
This Honmaru is a genius after all!
Now then, what should we play today?
No way! Today's the last day of summer vacation?!
I gotta do my homework now!
Taru! Taru!
Do my... Do my homework with magic... Uh?
Honmaru!
I breathed life into water with magic to make Mi-chan!
Magical pool very fun!
Sister Ria is there too...
Alright, next is the whirlpool!
There, there...
There, there!
And now... jump!
Jump! Me so cool!
Not so fast, Taru.
Ria's swimsuit look is the best!
Here I go! Swinging punch!
What a nice breeze!
Here I go!
Stop it, you!
Taru!
Too tasty, me won't stop!
Why, you! Come on, it tickles!
Looks like so much fun!
It tickles!
Taru, let me join too!
Sure! Playing together with Honmaru!
Feels amazing!
Sister, sister! Let's send Mi-chan soaring!
Alright, I'll use a Lighterer.
Yes! A mid-air pool!
Goodbye to the filthy town!
There!
Yay! Friends with Mi-chan!
Best friends ever!
We're falling!
Got you covered! Yes!
Look at yourself, Taru!
You're a watery mess!
Honmaru, you got it all over yourself too.
SHIT!
September 1st
Friday
Stupid, stupid, stupid, yesterday me!
Right!
Taru! You gotta use some magic to do my homework! Fast!
Wake up, you! Please wake up, Taru!
Still sleeping...
Tarurururuuto!
Ah! Is that a huge serving of takoyaki?
Oh? Takoyaki? Where?
You're not falling asleep again!
My life is at stake!
Taru! Do something about my homework with your magic!
We could ask Tama-chan...
Not that, Taru.
Tama-chan would get mad at me for trying to cheat!
But Tama-chan doesn't get mad when she's in a good mood.
Tama-chan, how are you feeling today?
Perfectly splendid, Taru-chan.
What should we do about Honmaru's homework?
Always captivating, glamorous, and kind Tama-chan!
Come on, you heart-breaker!
Please, Tama-chan, do something...
Let's see...
On second thought, it's no good.
In the end, it was no good...
Though I really didn't want to do this...
Life is too precious, even to me!
It's a last resort.
I've no choice but to copy Iyona-chan's homework.
But dammit, how do I get inside unseen and unheard?
Honmaru, leave it to me.
I'll erase our bodies with Magic-kun.
Oh! You can even do that, Taru?
Perfect! Just when Iyona-chan is not here!
Not here!
Not here...
Here it is!
Alright, time to copy this.
Oh no!
It's this late already?
I gotta change fast.
Iyona-chan! She's deciding to change now, of all times?
Iyona, me help.
Will do undressing.
Huh?
For God's sake, Taru!
Not only am I copying Iyona-chan's homework,
but I'll also be peeping at her changing!
I'm the worst man ever!
I can't do something like that!
What happened, Honmaru?
I see everyone is in good spirits, so I'm glad too!
Let's start the new semester with doing our best!
Okay!
There's still hope.
They should be busy with entrance ceremony today,
so maybe she'll collect the homework tomorrow...
Everyone, I hope you've done your homework.
Yes!
Everyone did it!
And when did Taru...
I see, even Taru did his kindergarten homework.
Then, I'll collect them right now.
No way!
Taru, please do something!
Honmaru, you should be fine with this.
Oh? True Storing, huh?
What's wrong, Honmaru?
I don't think your raised your hand earlier.
After all the big claims you've made,
don't tell me you've not actually done your homework!
What about it, Honmaru-kun?
I've done... Done all of my homework!
But... you see... it may have slipped my mind a little
to bring it to school today. And... I'm sorry!
Is that really so, Honmaru?
Everything I say with True Storing becomes true.
Alright! Knowing our teacher,
you'd forgive me and let me bring homework tomorrow!
You're right.
Then, be sure to bring it tomorrow, Honmaru-kun.
What's going on?
The teacher is so unusually lenient today!
It's beyond doubt that Honmaru is making this up!
I'm also absolutely confident he's lying.
Of course he is! After Honmaru had been playing so much,
it'd be phenomenal if he actually did it.
It was going so well, if not for Jabao and others...
It's not a lie, Jabao!
Let my tongue become a thousand needles if it is!
Are you sure about that?
Yes it is!
That was dangerous!
Honmaru-kun...
Even Iyona-chan is looking at me distrustfully.
It wasn't supposed to come to this.
I was an idiot for showing off,
hoping to cheat with Taru's magic.
However... However, by tomorrow,
I'll definitely do the homework on my own!
So please don't give me that look, Iyona-chan.
Alright! Tonight I'm staying up all night
to finish my homework!
Yeah! Honmaru, you can do it!
Alright... Here I come, homework!
Charge!
There!
Taru and Ria are playing beetle battle with giant bugs!
Looks awfully fun!
No, no... It's not the time
to be thinking about that! I've gotta hold back.
How am I supposed to do this again...
Taru, Ria!
Don't you have homework, Honmaru?
Honmaru, do your homework.
I know that, alright!
But nothing would happen if I play around for just an hour!
It's been way longer than one hour, Honmaru.
Just one more hour, that's all!
Honmaru! Let's play tag in the sky!
Yeah! Sounds fun, Taru!
SHIIIIT!
Stupid, stupid, stupid, stupid, yesterday me!
What do I do now?!
Taru! Taru, Taru, Taru!
Taru, Taru, Taru, Taru, Taru!
Taru...
You've nothing to worry about, having done your homework!
And what am I supposed to do?
If I don't bring the homework today as well...
Teacher would absolutely destroy me!
And Iyona-chan would come to hate me!
I'd rather die than go through all that!
Help me, God!
Winter vacation, spring vacation,
the next summer vacation as well,
I'll be doing my homework in time!
Honmaru.
Ria?
I'll stop the time for you.
While it's stopped, you'll do it on your own.
But you'll only have three hours.
Thank you, Sister Ria.
But in just three hours...
You can do it if you try.
I'll look to it myself that you do.
I see! Ria's amazing magic would come to my rescue!
She's pretty, she'd kind, and she's the best ever!
Ria, thank you ever so much!
Miracle Star!
I don't understand this...
Hey!
No slacking off!
The charges of Goro the Thundercloud know no mercy!
Looks to me like a perfect tutor for Honmaru.
He really isn't, Sister Ria!
Isn't there some other magic for this?
No chatting during the class!
Get back to your homework!
Hang on! I'll help too, Honmaru.
Very well, Honmaru-kun.
Can't believe Honmaru actually did it!
He looks suspiciously exhausted.
Honmaru, drinking Power-Upple Juice should help.
Thank you, Taru...
I'm so glad, Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan...
Which reminds me,
only Taru-chan's forgotten homework remains now.
Yeah! I'll show teacher my homework!
It'll come soon enough.
Taru-chan, what is this...
My homework - collecting dung beetles.
Amn't I a good boy for doing my homework?
Good boy...
What?
Alright! I'm tingling with excitement,
because the sports season is finally starting, Taru!
Yeah, Honmaru! Let's return home sooner
for special training! Right?
As expected of you, Taru! You understand my feelings
without me saying anything.
Bastard, look as I squash you, Harako!
I'll be sure to break your nose for good!
Do your best, Honmaru!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Soccer Duel!
I'll do my best too!
Episode 52
Soccer Duel!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Translation checking by Aurelius