Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Here!
Iyona-chan!
Got it!
Heisei                 Nannosho
We're in the finals!
Episode 29
Iyona's Heated Battle
Amazing, aren't they, Taru?
For the first time in years,
we're in the prefectural final!
Yeah!
Even this sweat from playing volleyball
with all your might is beautiful!
You're spectacular, Iyona-chan!
Iyona waving to us!
Hey!
After making it this far,
ain't no way they'll lose the tournament, Taru.
Yeah! Should victori-ri-riously win!
Iyona-chan, at this rate,
the victory would be instantaneous!
Eh? You're setting your hopes too high.
Anyone making it to the finals
must be a mighty opponent.
There, we'll see it for ourselves there.
The match is about to start.
Fight!
Holy Moly! Hey...
Are they really still in elementary school?
Big! Big!
While still being in elementary school,
they're already 195cm tall, Emiko, Eiko, Ekiko -
triplets of the Kusuda family from the Higashinosho school.
In this tournament, they've not given
a single point to any opponent yet.
I'm sure those three
are going to advance to the finals as well.
I'm starting!
OK!
Impressive!
That Cannon Spike had countless elementary school students
sent to the hospital already.
It doesn't seem like a team such as ours, that barely made it
to the finals, has even a single chance of beating them.
Oh, look at you go, humbling yourself again!
Iyona-chan, a team with you in it is destined to win!
Right, Taru?
Yeah!
That's right!
We'll be fine, as long as we have me!
I'll show you how we win this!
Not like you'd change anything!
What now? I'm the one who's a regular
in the volleyball club here, mind you!
But of course, you probably know better
than the crowds of fans extolling me!
Oh, so you're agreeing with me?
Tsk! How could Honmaru, a guy with a mind lock,
ever appreciate my true abilities?
Still, I think it's going to be fun.
The match next week.
See, Taru?
It's exactly the way I said it'd be.
Iyona-chan is secretly super-motivated to fight.
She even picked up running so early in the morning!
Yeah! Iyona amazing.
Really, I so wish Iyona-chan would win this...
But I'll be damned if anyone manages
to receive that dreadful ball.
It'll be okay.
Iyona win with magic.
Now this is out of question!
A victory through magic
would never satisfy Iyona-chan!
I know! We could still conduct a special training,
the way we do it for myself!
Special training?
Yeah! Now, this is sorted out.
Let's commence the operation!
What's the matter, Honmaru-kun?
It's still so early in the morning,
but you're dragging me to the school gym, all of a sudden...
Alright, Taru. Let's do it.
Okay!
Iyona-chan, this might prove painful, but please bear with it.
You can't win without getting much stronger.
Hey, Honmaru-kun?
Silence! No irrelevant blabbing in the gym!
We're now starting your special practice
for the upcoming finals!
I'm starting, Iyona-chan!
Taru, ball!
Here!
Received!
Ouch! This ball is insane!
Don't get relaxed, Iyona-chan.
The real thing only starts now.
Taru!
Here!
Another one!
I like this. The result is apparent!
Just make sure to keep it up, Iyona-chan!
Got it!
Not yet!
It's not even close to the three Kusuda sisters' balls!
You need to get a grip on the ball like that!
More! More!
Her sparkling eyes...
Her nimble legs...
The sweat from receiving the balls...
Her waving hair...
Every part of you...
is twinkling,
Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan, that's the way.
Better already. Keep it up!
What now? No way such a short practice
was enough to wear you out!
Take a firmer stance!
Okay!
And keep going!
Impressive, Honmaru-kun!
I ain't no Honmaru-kun to you!
You can only call me Coach!
Okay, Coach!
Alright, keep going!
Honmaru, magic wears off in ten minutes.
Oh, right.
Iyona-chan, let's call it enough for today.
Okay, coach.
Ah! Meet me here tomorrow as well
for more special practice.
Got it?
Yes! Thanks for your concern, coach Honmaru.
Coach, huh?
This has some nice ring to it.
Okay, Iyona-chan!
We continue today! Get this!
Okay!
Henceforth, every day until the finals,
we've been going on with this special practice.
This won't do!
You can't lose your balance when receiving!
Get a grip on the ball with your eyes on it!
Okay!
I'm going in!
More!
Not there yet!
If you receive like that,
Higashinosho would mop the floor with you!
Got it!
You there!
Occupying the school gym so early in the morning?
What's going on here?
Answer, you three!
Teacher?
Oh-ho! I was just coaching Iyona-chan here, you see...
Iyona!
Iyona-chan!
Kawai-san!
School Infirmary
Honmaru-kun, why were you going on with this madness?
This special practice wore her out beyond belief!
Don't you know a girl's body is a lot more fragile?
I'm sorry.
I was so absorbed in it, I'd completely forgotten.
Iyona-chan is still an ordinary girl.
Sorry, Iyona.
What's wrong with you?
Don't apologize.
After all, I enjoyed it very much.
Honmaru-kun doesn't have to excuse himself,
because I enjoyed every second of it.
Kawai-san...
Teacher, Honmaru-kun's hitting is totally amazing.
Seeing a ball so amazing,
you just move out to receive it involuntarily.
I was so happy, so engrossed in it,
that I exhausted my body's resources without realizing it.
But hey...
It was thoroughly heart-warming.
Iyona-chan...
10th National Elementary School Volleyball Tournament
Prefectural finals among girls
Goin' in!
Higashinosho                     Nannosho
As predicted by the majority, the balance of strength
is clearly skewed to the Higashinosho side.
Up to now, they had no trouble wresting out
the first set from the Nannosho team.
And so, we're on the set point for Higashinosho.
Now serving - the eldest of three Kusuda sisters - Eiko.
Oh, and may I remind you - live coverage provided
by Ryoguchiya Korekiyo, from Nannosho's broadcasting club.
Now, what kind of serve will she hit now?
So far, by sending one Cannon Spike after another,
the enormously tall Kusuda sisters
managed to down six of Nannosho's players!
Die!
She did it! Kusuda Eiko's Cannon Spike!
What?!
Received! I can't believe my eyes!
The famous Cannon Spike, never before received by anyone -
today, for the first time in history,
successfully handled by Kawai Iyona!
Here!
Iyona-chan!
Got it!
Don't let it through!
And nevertheless... The Higashinosho wall is insurmountable!
Higashinosho conquer the first set for themselves!
Oh, they almost got it!
Just as she'd finally managed to receive!
But Iyona is still amazing.
Yeah! Our special training
yields immediate results!
Right!
That was great handling, Iyona-chan!
Kawai-san.
You put up a nice fight.
Thanks!
That Kawai girl
is the only one who can be dangerous.
True, receiving a spike from one of us is quite the feat.
'Tis was but a fluke.
Let's do our best, to the end!
We've nowhere else to retreat!
This next set - make it or break it!
Okay!
Nannosho, fight!
Yeah!
Get this!
Oh, just a little more!
They're this close to catching up!
Everyone's amazing!
What's this girl's deal?
Where did she get reflexes like that?
We're out of options -
we oughta target some another player first.
Iyona-chan is really fighting this match
like her life depends on it!
Then I should, too!
Rui-chan!
Ijigawa-san!
And there goes the final,
seventh outed player for Nannosho!
No more spare players on Nannosho's bench!
They're on the verge of pulling out!
Is this how Higashinosho's final victory will be decided?
Ijigawa incapacitated...
And they've nobody to replace her with!
Playing at a numerical disadvantage is suicidal!
Not even everyone's hard work can change anything!
Not even if you keep fighting till the very end!
This can't...
This can't be!
Ah! Iyona-chan!
Crap!
Taru!
I'll go there and take Ijigawa's place!
I must support Iyona-chan
in struggling till the very end!
Wait, Honmaru!
Don't try to stop me, Taru!
Honmaru... can't enter match!
Honmaru a guy!
Oh how could I've forgotten...
Taru! Can't you do anything?
Yeah! Anything is just what I have.
Honmaru, drink this.
What's this?
Just drink, it's good!
It's not even that tasty, to be frank!
This - Nature Switch Juice - Hormonger.
Drinking it makes guy a girl.
And makes girl a chap.
This is bad! My Willy is getting smaller already!
But in exchange, you will get big boobies!
What did you say?!
I've transformed into a girl!
This doesn't feel right...
Why did you do this to me, Taru?
Honmaru, as girl, you can enter the match.
It'll be fine. Magic wears off in ten minutes.
If you say so...
There's nothing we can do.
Continuing like this is too risky.
Wait, please!
Teacher, I...
am here, so please let me join the fight!
Are you one of my students?
Yes! I'm Emoto Marue.
Did we really have this girl before?
Still, the face looks vaguely familiar...
What's the matter, Nannosho team?
Do you wish to pull out?
Ah... We need just a minute more, please.
Teacher, please let me do it!
Alright. You're in, Emoto-san.
Got it!
Remember, Taru?
No use of magic while the match is underway.
Victory through magic would never do.
Okay!
Emoto-san.
Thank you! I'm so happy to see you here!
Let's do our best together.
Sure.
How's this?
It's out!
Kusuda Eiko's Cannon Spike is let loose!
Honmaru!
No country for amateurs!
Marue-chan, are you okay?
What?!
I'll be fine.
I barely felt that.
It's nothing, compared to Harako's punches,
or Taru's special practice.
Thank you, Marue-chan.
Let's keep going!
We're still in the game, people!
Got it!
Everyone so passionate!
Amazing.
Got it!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
Get this!
Nannosho are getting a grip on receiving.
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
Who could have foreseen that the number one
tournament favorite, Higashinosho
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
would suddenly meet such fierce resistance now?
Oh! Can you hear it, too?
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
Even the cheering squad for Nannosho is getting more excited!
It leaps and breaks away!
That's it! That's it!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
Keep going! Keep going!
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
There!
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Emiko!
Got it!
Your ride ends here!
Marue-chan! It's yours!
Got it!
Shoot!
Our rear is undefended!
Out!
We did it!
Honmaru couldn't do it...
It was still a fine match, wasn't it, everyone?
We lost after all, Kawai-san.
I'm sorry.
My clumsy play only hindered the team's performance.
Thank you...
We found this will to fight till the very end...
And it was all thanks to you...
Iyona-chan...
You should join my special practice, starting tomorrow.
This way, the next tournament will be ours, Marue-chan!
We'll try our best together!
Right, right! You'll totally love it
with a wonderful coach such as mine.
Let's ask him to coach us two together!
This wonderful coach - surely, you mean me?
So? Will you join me?
This won't do, girl! Receive like that
and you'll flunk the next match just like you did last time!
Let's try harder, Iyona-chan!
Okay!
Ready? Sorry dear, but my hand is firm this time!
Yes!
Honmaru so zealous!
But I think a girl's talking habits still show through sometimes.
I wonder what's happened to you, Honmaru-kun.
Suddenly, you have such a girlish manner of talking.
Marue-chan, I hope you come soon...
What's taking you so long?
Oh, what do you know -
this wonderful coach had been none other!
Alright, Taru! We'll go buy some takoyaki!
Yeah! Buy all the takoyaki!
Ah? Shoot! I completely forgot about Mimora-chan!
You never expect anything good coming from her.
Once she starts crying, it's a disaster!
Taru! I beg you, comfort Mimora-chan somehow!
Wow! Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Mimora's Great Rampage!
Episode 30
Don't miss, people!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius