Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 4
I Love Mama!
Honmaru?
If you don't wake up soon,
you'll be late again.
Wake up!
Honmaru, wake up!
Wake up now!
Give me a break, Taruruuto!
I must've crooked myself badly while sleeping.
My neck is rock-stiff.
Alright, let me take care of it.
Knead, knead, knead.
What are you doing...
You can't just toy with the human body like that!
It's unstiffened....
This is magic for softening things.
Can soften anything.
You could've told me this before,
not just attack without warning!
It's that late already?!
I gotta hurry.
We're friends to make meet ends.
I should hurry too!
I'm in a hurry, in a hurry!
Taruruuto.
I have to say...
the same thing as always.
When it's time for me to go to school,
you ought to keep it quiet.
It's best that dad and mom don't find out
you're actually freeloading at our house.
Magic should be kept a secret!
In our world, witchcraft is only exercised by fiends,
so everyone would think ill of you!
This is especially the case for my dad,
who is a picture book author and is a magic maven!
In other words:
if it leaks out, you can kiss living here goodbye!
Understood?
You have to promise me!
Promise you!
I'm off!
Honmaru goes to school.
I behave and be quiet.
Promise him... Promise...
Now you tell me, Iyona-chan,
what kind of boy
would you say you like?
A boy I'd say I like?
I think...
Hands down, that's Honmaru-kun.
No way!
After all, Honmaru-kun is so cool.
Oh, you're flattering me...
I think, it should be a buoyant boy.
Hands down, it's Taru-chan!
Can't shrug it off with a joke this time.
Just admit it. One who's light but steady on his feet -
your type's a sportsman.
So what about someone handsome and rich,
mature in manners and dependable as a man?
Hey...
What is it you're trying to do?
What's it to you?
What?!
Why, you...
You seem to be having some sweet chat about me.
This morning, your beauty
is once again even more refined,
Iyona-san.
Accept this.
Iyona-chan's type is defined
by Harako Tsutomu!
What?!
Um...
I'd still rather say Taru-chan.
Serves you right!
Losing even to Taruruuto!
To Taruruuto!
Taruruuto is at least popular with girls,
unlike someone else.
Honmaru studying at school.
Me here alone.
Me basking in the sun.
Mr. Sun warming gently, feeling pleasant.
Piglet cloud.
Octopus cloud.
Mama cloud!
You helped me out a great deal, Taru-chan.
Praised by mama!
Mama.
Wonder what she is doing now...
Please remain just as good a boy, Taru-chan.
Mama...
Honmaru's mama...
What is she doing?
Imagining things again.
Now this is odd.
Is someone there?
Oh?
My!
You're a cute little doll!
Now finish this.
Are you okay?
How pretty!
Mama...
Oh my?
You're smiling!
Honmaru's mama smells just like my mama.
I mistook you for a doll at first,
but turns out, it was Taruruuto-kun!
Honmaru my friend!
Mama's laps are the softest.
Nice to meet you too, Taru-chan.
Now, until your clothes dry out,
bask some more in the sun, will you?
Honmaru's mama bask in the sun together!
I still have chores to finish,
so maybe later?
I help doing chores!
That it, a way to mama's praise.
You helped me out a great deal, Taru-chan.
Thank you, but there's no need.
Mama can handle this by herself.
I decided!
I broom other rooms real clean!
Taru-chan?
Attractor
This - Attractor. It attracts and gathers
anything you command it to.
Rubbish.
Ru-rubbish!
Many rubbish!
Taru!
Wow!
I've never seen it that clean.
You did it all alone?
Thank you so much, Taru-chan!
Mama!
It's a little embarrassing.
It reminds me of when Honmaru was a baby, too.
Going out with mama! Going out!
I'm still not sure what I should make
as an appetizer for dinner.
Taru-chan, is there anything you'd like?
Me? Anything I like?
So, Taru-chan?
Oh...
He was here just a moment ago...
Takoyaki!
What are you trying to do with this thing?!
What is it? The kid from the other day again?
Takoyaki, give it, give it!
Make a lot for me!
Okay, coming!
Making-making takoyaki,
making lots for you.
But boy,
how much cash you have on you?
Me what?
How much can I have?
What? Not "can,"
but "how much cash you have?" Cash.
Cath...
Is this the most tasty kind of takoyaki?
The hell?!
If you're just window-shopping,
then off you go!
Get lost. Get lost!
Takoyaki...
Don't you know a disgruntled client
sticking to the store's front is detrimental to business?
Takoyaki...
Cut the crap and go pester someone else!
Look, everyone!
Huh?
Uh-oh.
He's bullying an adorable child!
How heartless. I'm not buying takoyaki
from that stall ever again.
Not at all! It's not like that at all!
Nobody is bullying anyone here.
Here you go, kid.
Here. Extra-flavored, just for you!
Now because you're such a good boy,
once you're done eating, you'll go home, right?
Yes, cause I'm good boy, I eat this!
Eat takoyaki together with mama!
You donkey!
How dare you!
Please spare me!
We've barely met eyes for just a second!
And yet, it was enough for you
to start laughing at my head's misfortune!
Knowing how delicate I am,
you're still hitting the sorest spot ever!
How dare you... How dare you. How dare you!
Roundhouse Kick!
Help me, someone!
Turning away?
Uh-oh...
Excuse me...
Won't you be so kind
to call this punishment enough?
Whaddya just say?
Mama!
Want to demonstrate your character,
interrupting my fun like that?
Huh, sis?
Mama! Eat takoyaki together!
Taru-chan!
Out of the way!
Nay... Nay!
Takoyaki! I save you.
So, sist...
Aaargh!
Nay! Where'd it go? Where'd it go?
Found!
Even bigger now!
But dirtier too.
Can't it eat like that.
You'll regret messing with me!
Take a good look at my dirk!
You messed takoyaki
I was to eat with mama.
Taru-chan!
Give your dirk here!
The hell are you saying!?
Little shit!
Dirk!
My dirk is not for a kid to play with!
You'll get hurt before you know it!
Bend, bend, re-render soft!
Mama, look, look.
Big bro also look.
Taru!
IT HURTS!
Old man runs away...
Taru-chan, what did you just...
Me the Great Magician!
Taruruuto!
Honmaru!
Magic should be kept a secret.
If it leaks, you can't live with me any longer!
Got it? Give me a promise!
What do now?
I'm no magician at all.
Besides, magic is secret,
so I can't be magician!
And, mama...
I totally not live in Honmaru's desk!
What do now?
Taruruuto! Where are you going?
Mom, take this home, too.
Taruruuto!
Hey, I'm hungry, mama!
Sure, sure. Going straight home now.
Honmaru?
Taruruuto.
I thought you returned to the Magic Realm already.
You had me worried there!
Honmaru.
I broke promise.
Sorry, Honmaru.
It was my fault, too,
for leaving you all alone when I'm going somewhere.
So drop that gloom of yours now!
It's not like your usual self, Taruruuto.
But can't go to Honmaru's home anymore...
Alright!
Since it came to this, I'll ask dad and mom openly
to let you stay with us.
Won't hurt to give it a try!
What are we to lose now?
That true, Honmaru?
Don't worry about it.
That's precisely what we became friends for.
Leave it to me.
We go there together as friends,
Honmaru!
Oh, for Lord's sake!
Taruruuto, it's too soon to rejoice yet.
Here we go...
Got it, Taruruuto?
Mom is more or less okay,
but my dad, despite his meek appearance,
can scold you THAT BADLY if he gets really mad!
Father! Mother! We need to talk.
Need to talk.
Ah!
Honmaru, Taru-chan, welcome home.
Me and your father
were already getting impatient.
Takoyaki? Takoyaki?
Eh?
A portion for Taru...
Well, Taruruuto-kun, I don't know how to thank you enough
for tidying my room up so shiningly clean.
A deed worthy of a Great Magician.
I hope you don't mind doing it again sometimes.
But that means...
You don't mind Taruruuto staying with us?
Dad! Mom!
I don't see why we'd have any problem with it.
Right, darling?
Having a Great Magician chosen our house for freeloading,
makes it the most distinguished in the neighborhood!
What's more important now, I don't want this little dish
I made for Taru-chan to go cold.
Hurry up and get to eat, both of you.
Taruruuto! We pulled it!
Together with Honmaru,
today to eternity!
Good job, Taru.
Finished.
And now, to commemorate Taruruuto's
introduction into the Edojo family,
the Great Magician Taruruuto-sensei
is putting his magic on display.
Sensei, your say!
Taru!
Yahoo!
Astounding, Taru-chan!
This means every day
will be a Magic Show now.
Amusing, amusing.
That was too much...
Taruruuto, revert this guy to how he used to be!
Hear my command...
Taruru... Order you...
Hey! Don't tell me you've forgotten the spell!
Taruruuto!
This and that, that and this,
magic, rinse!
Disappear to somewhere else!
Danger behind.
Be quicker next time, Taruruuto...
Spectacular.
What a magnanimous display!
Japan's #1!
Impressive, Taru-chan!
Eh? Any idea about the ruckus outside, Taruruuto?
Taru!
Just your imagination, imagination!
That's what I thought, too.
What should I do?
I'm not ready for tomorrow's test at all!
Say, Taruruuto,
why don't we pay a visit to teacher's house?
I like our teacher, too!
Let's hurry there!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Preparing for the Test with Magic!
Make su-ru-rure to watch!
Episode 5
Preparing for the Test with Magic
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume