Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
It's February 13th today.
Which means...
Don't tell me tomorrow is...
Ah! It is, goddammit!
Tomorrow, it's February 14th!
Valentine's Day!
The one day in a year,
when nightmares come true!
Episode 23
Valentine Declaration
Last year I had zero chocolate
The year before that - zero chocolate
So what of that?
Should I be bothered?
"Valentine's Day" - more like "nobody cares!"
Last year I had zero chocolate
The year before that - zero chocolate
So what of that?
Should I be bothered?
"Valentine's Day" - more like "nobody cares!"
Some get three, four,
five, even six
Some sleek snob gets 25 at once
I sneer at his "conquests"
That's just unsightly!
Petty numbers don't reflect
a true man's worth!
Va-Va-Va-Valentine
Ain't worth a dime-dime, ain't worth a dime
The chocolate hustle is a waste of time!
Va-Va-Va-Valentine
Ain't worth a dime-dime, ain't worth a dime!
The chocolate hustle!
The chocolate hustle...
I still goddamn want it!
Valentine, you cretin!
Cretin! Cretin!
Oh, Honmaru-kun?
Iyona-chan...
What happened?
It was as though you were shouting something.
Ah, about that?
I was just testing my vocal cords.
Ah, is that so?
Ooh! Here, here.
Cute thing! Here, here.
Me and Iyona's doggie - friends, friends!
Well then, I'll see you tomorrow at school, okay?
See you again sometime, doggie!
You seem to have been into it quite a lot.
Back in the Magic Realm,
hadn't your family ever kept a pet?
Pet?
Well, you know...
Say dogs, or cats.
Some animal that lives in your house, get it?
I had Niruru!
A friend Niruru.
A long time ago...
Draw, draw, draw, draw, draw, draw.
Hey, what are you up to?
Niruru, Niruru!
Niruru!
Do you know what you're doing, Taru?
I summon theeeee!
What's that?
Finally! Niruru!
Taru, is that thing Niruru?
Niruru, my friend.
Summoned from the Magic Realm.
Hey, Niruru.
Honmaru here, nice to meet you.
It tickles, Niruru!
Niruru seems to be into Honmaru quite a lot.
You sure know how to make cute friends, Taru.
Niruru doesn't know how to speak.
But instead, Niruru can shapeshift into anything.
Just need to sque-ue-ueeze Niruru's tail.
Here.
Niruru takes form of anything he's looking at
when you clutch his tail.
Now that's impressive!
I see... So he's exactly like me?
I just licked myself.
I mean, I just got licked by myself.
This all is too convoluted!
Honmaru!
But how? Does that mean, I...
Hey! What's the meaning of this?!
Hey, you need to stop! Hey, sit.
You can't let him impersonate me
on a whim like that!
Hurry up and revert him to normal.
Niruru returns to normal
when you make him sneeze.
This - sneeze-inducing, Achooweed!
It can give a sneeze to anyone.
Achooooo!
I know!
Niruru!
Try shapeshifting into this!
Yeah!
Niruru becoming a full-scale Iyona...
He'll lick me to his heart's content...
Maybe even...
No, even more than that!
He must have her tits, too!
Honmaru, he finished transforming.
Iyona-chan!
Why'd you say that?
Honmaru, why did you turn Niruru into a picture?
Damn it!
No way it can ever make up for the actual one!
Alright, tomorrow you're coming to school with me!
We're confronting Iyona-chan in person!
Let's see...
Apparently, Mimora-chan is not here yet.
Taruruuto!
Today's the day you're finally
getting gagged for good!
Let's hurry!
Yeah!
You'll regret this, Taruruuto...
Alright, I just need to lie in ambush here,
and when Iyona-chan comes, we'll know right away!
She's here!
Niruru, take a good look
at the girl over there.
It worked!
EEEH?!
Oh, for crying out loud!
Why did he change into this?!
Giving up that easily would mean
throwing my man's honor out the window.
We'll make another attempt!
There you are, Iyona-chan!
The hell?
Iyona-chan, what is it you want with Harako?
Don't tell me...
Here, some chocolate.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona-chan is giving her love to Harako?!
So that's what we came to...
Iyona-chan feels that way towards him.
Honmaru?
Say, say, who are you giving your chocolate to?
Um, me? To Harako-kun!
Eh? Me too!
No way, for real?
Why... Why does Harako get everything?!
The world must have gone completely nuts!
Honmaru regained vigor!
Unforgivable, Harako!
Someone has to teach you the maddening experience
of not receiving any chocolate!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
Just you wait, Taruruuto!
With my cunning plan,
I'm making you gorge on that Magical Itch-Itchocolate!
This chocolate attacks you from the inside!
Itch-itch-itch...
Belly itch! Belly itch!
Hope you like it, 'cause you're bound to spend
the rest of your life laughing!
In that case, Mimora-chan will have no choice,
but to abandon Taruruuto's eternally cackling ass!
Harako-kun!
Please accept this.
My, what do we have here?
Harako-kun, here.
This is for you!
Harako-kun!
Please!
Damn it... Harako, you bastard!
This is the last time you get to grin so nonchalantly!
Niruru, take a good look at him.
It worked!
Alright, with this, we'll gag Harako once and for all!
Yeah!
Ah! Harako-kun!
Please accept ​​this!
Alright, the chance presents itself.
Let's do it, Taru.
Okay!
Niruru! Repeat after me!
Harako-kun...
Harako-kun?
After this, Harako's reputation will flop beyond repair.
Harako-kun, great!
So light on your feet!
Please accept this!
Take, take!
Crap...
Stop it now, you!
Hey, hey, did you hear about Harako-kun?
Eh? With Honmaru-kun?
That's what I'm told, Harako-kun did it!
He was tonguing him ardently!
Oh no!
He's a pervert!
Am I imagining things?
Anyone there?
I see now, you have the urge to give me that chocolate,
but too bashful to approach me?
You needn't not feel embarrassed!
Come out now!
I'm ready to accept
all the chocolate you have prepared for me!
Must be my imagination, after all.
No, I can definitely sense it.
But what's going on?
What is this cold gaze?
For the first time ever, I'm getting this kind of gaze -
the one you give to a hopeless pervert!
Right! In addition,
the supply of chocolate presents
have run completely dry in an instant!
What in the world could have caused this?
Ha! Harako!
Everyone knows bringing sweets to school is prohibited!
What?
Right, Oaya-sensei?
Teacher?!
The teacher is giving me that eerie smile, too!
I am so screwed!
Oh my god!
Have you seen it, Taru?
Harako's face just now.
Seen it all!
Honmaru-kun...
Do you think that it being Valentine's Day today
is an excuse for eating chocolate during school hours?
Moreover, you even brought along your pet!
It's the real one!
Hold it!
This is it, Taruruuto.
Turn
Turn with Transformation Belt!
Transformation!
What's he doing?
So weird...
Transformation!
Turning Mimora-chan!
Stop right there!
Taru-chan?
I need to know where Honmaru-kun went.
You'll tell me, won't you?
Thanks!
Now's the last time
you get to smile so nonchalantly, Taruruuto!
'Cause after this, you'll only be laughing nervously
till the end of your days.
Taru-sama!
Here, Valentine's Day chocolate from me!
Please make sure to eat it all, okay? Here.
Achoo!
Niruru!
Niruru...
Where could he have gotten lost here?
Taru-sama!
Where are you hiding?
Mimora-chan...
I could have sworn
I heard Mimora-chan's voice just now.
Mimora-chan!
Could that be Mimora-chan's Valentine chocolate?
Mimora-chan...
That chocolate...
It must be for Taruruuto, isn't it?
Life takes a turn for the better
It's for me!
It's the sweetest ever!
Take that, Taruruuto!
Niruru!
Where Ni-are you?
There you are!
Got lost, didn't you?
Honmaru-kun!
Ah, Iyona-chan?
What's going on?
Honmaru-kun is cuddling me!
I'm right here,
but I'm also there!
How can that ever be...
Iyona-chan!
Are you okay, Iyona-chan?
What was going on with me just now?
You fainted and collapsed on the ground.
Is that so? But I'm sure
I saw another me just now... What was that?
That must have been a dream!
Iyona-chan, you saw it in a dream!
Right, Taru?
Yeah! Dream, dream.
Iyona, this is Niruru.
My friend.
I see. Nice to meet you.
That's right...
The package may have gotten a bit crumpled, but...
Here. Honmaru-kun, your chocolate.
And this is...
I made it yesterday.
I wanted to treat everyone in the class.
I see...
You've been giving one of these to everyone?
Which means... Harako, too!
I see!
Oh, I see!
I see it clearly now!
Thank you, Iyona-chan!
Taru-sama!
Taru-sama, Taru-sama!
I got you a lot of Valentine's Day chocolate,
brimming with my love!
Sorry, but could it be that you're
Taru-chan's girlfriend?
I wouldn't say "girlfriend" is the right word here...
But you can just call me Mimora for now.
I knew it - my bond with Taru-sama is so strong,
even people I meet for the first time can see right through it!
That must be the magical power of love.
Now, now! Now! Now, now...
Taru-sama, make sure you get full on those.
Here, here!
Turns out, I very much like Valentine's Day!
Honmaru, Jabao's grandpa is a nice guy.
That's perfectly normal,
just as grandpas and grandmas go.
I wish I also had a nice grandpa,
buying all sorts of stuff for me.
Wanna go see our grandpa, Honmaru?
I guess...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Dreadful Grandpa.
Honmaru's grandpa is a funny guy!
Episode 24:
Dreadful Grandpa
You should never be saying something like that, Taru!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius