Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 22
Primal Rage Runs Amok
It's time for homeroom session.
Can we have some silence, everyone?
Okay!
And now, I give the floor
to today's class monitor, Ryoguchiya-kun.
Okay.
What I'd like to discuss today is the question of money,
raised during the latest school bazaar.
Or rather, how we should possibly spend it.
The significance of this money cannot be overstated,
so we need to spend it in a way that'd benefit everyone.
Well, do we have any propositions?
Yeah!
Taru-chan?
We're all ears, Taruruuto-kun!
I know you won't let your best friend down!
Go for it, Taru!
Yeah!
With significant money,
we buy a takoyaki suru-ru-rufeit!
Taru!
What's wrong?
We buy takoyaki with significant money.
Me happy. Honmaru happy, too!
Everybody benefits.
Will you ever shut up?
Stupid thing, your head is too dense
to have any good ideas in it!
Jabao!
Here!
Then, Jabao-san, your call.
Pfft! All that just to add a stupid idea
from your own dense head!
How Jabao of you!
Well, I believe, we would all benefit
from keeping an animal in the classroom.
Through communicating with the animal,
we would be able to relieve, or even enrich our hearts!
Support!
I support!
I also would like to support it.
Iyona-chan?
Damn you, Jabao...
Even a broken clock is correct twice a day.
Can't be helped...
You've been beaten flat, Taru.
Me love animals, too!
Cute animals most of all!
So we've settled on buying a squirrel,
as well as naming it Primal Rage.
The feeding expenses would be shared equally.
That's right! Agreed!
A squirrel?
How childish.
Personally, I'd prefer a Siberian Tiger.
And name him Special Thunder the Great Godar.
Harako! Do you mean to say
you'd look after it all by yourself?
What? You've gotta be kidding!
This has been everyone's decision.
By assuming a collective stewardship over it,
you'll learn a lot about responsibility.
Animals are not playthings.
They are sentient creatures,
just like all of us, and we should respect this.
Is that clear?
Without a doubt, teacher.
Right, people?
Yeah!
Taru, let's chip in for the food expenses, too.
Yeah.
Getting my savings out, too.
He's cute!
I want to see him, too!
I'll look after him every single day!
You adorable thing!
He squeaked!
He looked this way!
Look, look!
Ah? It's eating, eating!
Eh? So cute!
See now?
My idea was so excellent, you can rate it 50 out of 10.
Iyona-chan, let's feed it together.
Sure!
Hold it!
It was me who came up with an idea
of keeping a pet.
Without my permission,
I ain't gonna let nobody get too buddy-buddy with it.
What did you just say?
Jabao, do you think it's fair to have it all to yourself?
Right, right!
What?!
Not so fast, Jabao-kun.
That squirrel was bought with money
belonging to the class as a whole.
I don't suppose you want to be charged
with embezzlement?
Harako!
A broken clock really is correct twice a day!
In that case, why don't we make a roster
for looking after the squirrel?
I support Iyona-chan's initiative.
Fine. But only if the first turn is mine!
Then second's mine!
Third turn here!
He squeaked, squeaked!
So cute! I wish I could look after you every single day!
Right?
Good one...
Went to buy takoyaki.
Got some for you, too.
Don't want any? Your loss!
Will eat it myself.
Refusing something tasting that good -
your big loss!
Oh, come on!
To forget it here on a day like this!
Huh? Someone's still there.
Iyona-chan!
See? It's so nice and tidy now,
Primal Rage-kun.
Ah, right. Our class keeps a squirrel as a pet.
We've been feverish over it at first,
but now, when it's our turn to look after it,
we're just looking to pass the buck!
So now Iyona-chan has been looking after it all by herself!
You're such a hapless creature.
Always confined to that tiny cage.
But in reality, you'd prefer to roam the woods freely,
make new friends and find your love, wouldn't you?
I'm sorry.
Jabao! Isn't it your turn on Primal Rage today?
If you don't clean the cage, it'll start to stink!
Why am I also supposed to deal with his disgusting turd?!
Honmaru, Touch!
Huh? Why is it always me?
Hey, Ryoguchiya!
Eh? Come to think of it, yesterday was actually my turn.
But I completely forgot to feed it!
Iyona-chan.
Honmaru-kun?
Our squirrel sure is cute.
Still, these days,
he's being less and less lively.
He doesn't eat a thing,
and barely touches his water.
You think this cage may be too small for him?
I know! What if we release him in the nearby forest?
If a pet has been raised by people,
can it really sustain itself in the wild?
I'm not sure he'll be able to forage for food
if he's left all alone.
Is there really something we can do?
At this rate, after Primal Rage,
Iyona-chan would lose her cheer as well!
I have to think of something!
Alright, I have to cheer you up somehow.
Iyona-chan!
I swear by my name of Edojo Honmaru
that I'll figure this out, somehow!
Be it a squirrel, or be it a willow,
I can cheer anyone up in a blink of an eye!
Really?
Why, of course! Truth be told, there was even a time,
when I was dubbed Dr. Pet of the 3rd Avenue.
Please help him, Honmaru-kun.
If the reward is Iyona-chan's smile,
I can move mountains!
Get it, Taruruuto?
And that's why, whatever the cost may be,
I need to make Primal Rage lively again.
Yeah! Primal Rage my friend, too.
Drinking this Power-Upple Juice should help.
That's right! Indispensable for power-upping
your wits, muscles and guts, Power-Upple Juice!
Thank you, Taru!
Are you sure it'll help, Honmaru-kun?
Here, Iyona-chan, your pleas were heard!
Brewed by the so-called Dr. Pet,
the great sensei Honmaru himself, a nutrition drink!
Try it, Primal Rage-kun.
He liked it! Liked it! I'm so glad!
That's it! He looks mighty cheerful already!
Alright, let's give him some more.
Amazing!
It worked perfectly, Honmaru-kun,
or should I rather say, Dr. Pet? Thank you!
If I was able to brighten your day,
I'm already happy!
Honmaru-kun, is it just me,
or has he grown somewhat bigger?
Strong stuff!
Honmaru-kun, did you say something?
Don't tell me it was the squirrel talking!
Huh?
What... in the world?!
The squirrel went giant!
Taru's magic has been too effective!
After all, he downed the whole flask
of Power-Upple Juice in one gulp!
Iyona-chan, it's dangerous here!
Slap
Honmaru-kun!
Damn pervert!
Don't you get handsy with my girl!
Pervert?
Iyona-chan is going to marry me and only me.
Honmaru-kun!
What's this all about?!
He's making plans to marry Iyona-chan already?!
This damn squirrel!
Who do you think you are?!
Damn you...
You guys had your share of fun,
toying with me carelessly up until now.
How about I get my share
by toying with you this time?
I don't feel very playful...
Let's see who'll survive a game of tag!
Mercy! No... I beg your mercy!
Primal Rage-sama,
I've been inexcusably disrespectful up until now!
I beg your forgiveness!
Tsk. No fun messing with a faint of heart.
I know!
We can go play outside, Iyona-chan.
Look!
What?!
As if I'm ever letting you do that!
Wait, Primal Rage!
Huh? There's no place for someone like you
in my and Iyona-chan's happy family life.
I slept through the morning.
Drowsy, drowsy.
But I'm still sleepy.
Taru-chan, this is urgent.
Tama-chan, what is it?
It's getting perilous for your friends at school.
Oh! Primal Rage feeling better already! I'm so glad!
It's not the time to look
at the bright side of things, Taru-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan!
Iyona, Honmaru!
I'm destined to be the one who'll save Iyona-san!
No runaway squirrel is able to outrun me, the Absolute
World Champion of Sprinting at 100m among kids!
Then try to follow me into here.
I fear nothing!
Like this!
Eeeeh?!
Try to tag me, this way!
Damn it!
Stop!
Cold...
Taru is never around when you really need him!
You bastard...
You'll regret making fun of Harako Tsutomu-sama!
Harako, didn't he go that way?!
Not there!
Not there either?
Where could he have run off to?!
That voice... It's the voice of the lunchroom granny!
Honmaru...
Good stuff! You people always
leave good stuff like that for yourself! That's just unfair.
It was supposed to be our curry!
I was so looking forward to lunch today!
Some cheap curry is not worth all that ruckus.
Shove it!
What'd you say!?
Lord, Lord, Lord, Lord...
Iyona-chan, I have my appetite with me again.
Please be glad.
I'm happy to know it!
Still, Primal Rage-kun, would you be so kind
as to not give everyone any more trouble?
They're my friends, you see.
Forget about them!
You'll never need anyone else if you have me!
Iyona-chan!
Eat this!
Animals are powerless against fire!
Animals are also not supposed to be that cocky!
Let Iyona-chan go now!
Well said, Honmaru!
I beg you to stop, oh, my omnipotent master!
Whatever it takes, I'm willing to obey any command!
First, let Iyona-chan go!
Na-ah.
What?
No! No...
You ass! How dare you piss on me?!
In the wild, you defend with what you have!
What are you talking about?
Just admit it that you have no sense of honor!
Primal Rage, please get down from there!
Iyona-chan...
Come down here, Primal Rage!
Come down and fight me fair and square!
Better yet, you come up here yourself!
Finally!
Ten minutes have passed.
Taru's magic loses its effect.
Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan, I will protect you...
It's no use, Primal Rage! With your body that small,
Iyona-chan will get hurt even if she lands on you!
Honmaru, trust me with this!
Taruruuto!
What are you waiting for?!
You did it!
Iyona-chan, are you alright?
Show me where it hurts, Iyona-san!
Get this villain!
Yeah!
Not running away now!
This is for covering me in squirrel piss!
Stop it!
Still, you lost with dignity, Primal Rage.
You risked your own life
in order to to save Iyona-chan.
By cushioning my fall, you saved my life.
Thank you, Primal Rage-kun.
Oh, I see now, Taru!
You used that magic again
to make a squirrel cushion!
In a single sneeze,
this magic softens anything into a cushion.
"A-kushi-choo" is the spell.
Even when I think you're just sneezing,
you're actually casting a spell!
Which means Primal Rage will also be fine
when he comes to his senses!
Good thinking, Taru!
We're sorry, Primal Rage.
From now on, we won't be ignoring our duties.
After all, you're our classmate, too.
I'm so glad you're safe, Primal Rage-kun.
Still, that sure was one mysterious phenomenon.
It must be that his grievance,
when we stopped looking after him, gained enough power
to even make Primal Rage's body grow in size.
The adrenaline produced by anger,
affecting the growth hormone in one way or another,
sounds a lot more like a scientific explanation.
From now on,
let's look after him with all due diligence.
We don't need a second giant squirrel incident, do we?
Besides, it turns out,
there are good sides to this guy, too.
Jabao-kun...
But I was the one heroically trying
to save Iyona-chan all that time!
And yet, all the eyes are on that rogue!
I would have preferred
to be some cute little animal, too!
Honmaru!
Pork-Bonk can make you into animal!
Pork!
What'd you do this for, Taru?!
Honmaru pretty.
I was, until you did this to my face!
But you said you'd prefer to be a cute animal.
Which part of this spells "cute" to you?!
Cute! Cute!
Hold it!
Give me back my normal face, Taru!
Cute! Oink, oink!
Honmaru, what are you looking at?
Taruruuto, this - take a look at this.
This prick Harako is receiving all that chocolate!
And I still haven't received a single one
since the day I was born!
Damn it...
Oh, you've done it. Prepare to witness the wrath
of a man who never receives chocolate!
Honmaru, looking boiling!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Valentine Declaration.
Episode 23
Valentine Declaration
Ah! And Iyona gives it to Harako!
OH MY GOD!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius