Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Good morning!
Morning.
Honmaru.
What now?
Say...
Did you do your arithmetic homework?
More or less.
Please!
Lemme copy it real quick!
Alright.
Still though, can't say if I didn't screw it up.
What are you talking about, Honmaru-chan?
Shouldn't be humbling yourself!
No, sir!
As we know, a friend is someone
you can always count on!
Would you look at this ladykiller.
Yo! Broken many hearts today, you scoundrel?
Be it more or be it less -
better to have this than none at all!
After all, the teacher's temper is damn short
for those without their homework.
Episode 10
Conscientious Use of Oppoositer
Now then, let's check how much change
Tomoko-san was supposed to receive.
I am, of course,
talking about yesterday's homework.
Well then, formula and answer...
I know.
Jabao-kun.
Sure.
Judging by the picture, one might conclude
Tomoko is drawn here with a face,
suggesting a certain degree of stupidity.
Formula - Tomoko forgot to take the change.
The answer thus is 0 yen!
BRAVO!
A genuine, unique case
of thinking outside the box.
Right, beautiful teacher?
So true!
Once again, Jabao-san outwits his nemeses!
You idiot!
Why did you also copy the gibberish
that I scribbled on the margins?
I'm so sorry, teacher!!
Honmaru....
What now?
I was made into a laughingstock and got my butt spanked -
all this is your bloody fault!
You'll pay for it!
You were the one asking to look at my homework!
And that's what I get in return?
Jabao Punch!
Honmaru's Cross-Counter!
Jabao, you schmuck!
That piece of trash ain't even human!
You're listening to me, right, Taruruuto?
Mom used to say, back in the day...
Remember, Maru-chan.
The good that you do for others
is bound to return to you.
Our world connects together
all sorts of people with its invisible threads.
Maru-chan, as long as you show compassion for others,
you'll always keep growing happier.
Too bad it was nothing but a lip service.
A beating was all I got
In return for being compassionate!
What's the point then, Taruruuto?
Do good deeds for others -
that goodness returns to you!
Do harmful deeds for other -
expect the same to befall you as well!
That's how the world is supposed to work!
How can I be that hapless?
Found it, found it.
Taru!
How frustrating.
As if I wasn't hapless enough already,
Taruruuto adds his two cents with a poo on my head!
I'm such a friendless loser!
Taru!
Quit it!
Taruruuto! Enough is enough!
Taru. This is no poop.
This - Oppoositer Minus Mk-3,
you wear it on head.
Come, Honmaru!
Wait for me, Taruruuto!
You're trying my patience!
Dad seems particularly bent out of shape today.
A smidgen of mischief!
Stop, you idiot!
Hey, dolt!
Damn it!
Don't you look down on me!
You're a goner!
Inspired!
Why'd you do that, Taru?!
A thousand pardons, dear father!
We were practicing pro-wrestling, and we got carried away!
Honmaru...
He'll kill me...
Thank you, Taruruuto-kun.
Thanks to you kicking me, a superb idea for a cover
of my new fairy tale struck my mind.
Professional wrestling, what a grande diversion!
Now...
Go get yourself a treat, kid.
You helped me a great deal just now!
Alright!
Will get to drawing it right away!
Got praised!
I guess I could give Oppoositer-kun a chance.
Wear on the head...
A smidgen of mischief.
'Tis no dream!
I can eat a pile of takoyaki!
Thank you for pinching my cheek to make sure!
Grateful...
I get it! With this magical item, when you do people harm,
they do the opposite and praise you!
So hey, what do you say?
What a prick!
Courting ladies in broad daylight!
Honmaru!
Don't you like it? C'mon, babe.
Did I go a bit overboard?
Thanks a lot!
You saved me.
I was starting to worry because he was so headstrong.
Here's your reward.
See you, my boy.
You've outdone yourself, Taru!
I should definitely test this out more!
How showy.
Pile of scrap!
Hey.
D'you just kick it?
Yes or no?
Yes...
Saved me there!
The engine stalled suddenly
and the damn thing wouldn't start!
But through your deed, it recovered!
Here are some tickets to the cinema.
Feel free to use them whenever.
It worked!
So far, this item is the most promising one, Taru!
Jabao! What's cooking?
I lost the wallet mom gave me
for grocery shopping!
If I don't find it quick,
mom's gonna work me over!
Serves you damn good!
Truth be told, his mom is mighty frightening.
'Kay, Jabao!
I'll help you look for it!
Taru, we could use your help, too.
Honmaru, Taruruuto! Thank you both!
Don't mention it!
Right, Taru?
Don't, Honmaru!
Why are you stopping me, Taru?
Honmaru, don't!
Found it!
You're the savior, Honmaru!
Jabao!
Mom!
Ma'am! The wallet that Jabao-kun dropped.
Honmaru!
You don't happen to have pocketed
anything from inside it?
Jabao! Whatever your excuse is,
you don't hand our important wallet over to anyone else!
Your mom sure is never taking it easy.
Honmaru! It was your fault again!
Honmaru.
Forgot to tell you something important.
Folk flip out when you do them favors
with Oppoositer on.
Consider mentioning such things
before it's too late!
Hurts...
I told you, later than I had to though.
Honmaru, slow down a bit!
I swear!
With or without Oppoositer,
doing favors brings you nothing but more trouble!
I'm a doofus, too.
Should have just ditched him on the spot!
Oh?
Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan!
I know!
Alright...
Iyona-chan!
What is it?
Like this!
Saw it!
Panties so white that they dazzle!
Honmaru-kun, you brute!
Wait, Iyona-chan!
I mistreated her and still got the beating.
Why so, Taru?
My magic wears out in ten minutes.
Folk now react the natural way
to Honmaru's mistreatment.
Taru!
Taru,
it's just as mom said, after all.
By mistreating others,
you're bringing about your own misfortune.
Honmaru's mama is the kindest!
Makes sense.
She is my mom, after all.
Now Iyona-chan hates me too!
A crippling cost for just seeing
some lousy snow-white panties!
Honmaru, apologize to Iyona!
Life is not that simple!
Trust me to make amends!
Tama-chan, show us.
But no peeking!
Iyona, where is she now?
In the park.
Alright... On our way, Honmaru!
Hey, hold it!
What's this about, Taruruuto?
Taru!
Iyona!
Oh?
Taru-chan!
Where did you run off to, Taru?
Iyona-chan is smiling again!
That must be it.
I have nothing more to worry about.
Taru kept his word!
Just gotta apologize!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru!
Iyona bought me some takoyaki!
Let's eat it with Honmaru, too!
Iyona-chan, sorry for what I...
Honmaru-kun, you're...
despicable!
Despicable!
Let's go elsewhere, Taru-chan.
Come on.
Honmaru!
Iyona.
Iyona...
Honmaru?
Taru-chan? Wanna play something else?
Me like Iyona!
Glad to hear!
I also love Taru-chan the most!
Me like Honmaru, too!
Honmaru my friend,
so Honmaru likes Iyona, too!
Who is that person?
Take care, Iyona!
Taru-chan...
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun, you're despicable!
Iyona-chaaaan!
Honmaru, you alright?
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru?
Honmaru?!
What now? You again?
Didn't you just walk away together with Iyona-chan?
This - Yahook up with me-kun.
Honmaru, if you pierce Iyona's heart with this arrow,
Iyona will start liking Honmaru again!
Are you sure, Taru?
I see, so this is a Cupid's Arrow kinda thing?
With this in my arsenal,
Iyona-chan's mine!
You're a real deal, Taruruuto!
However, I might have a hard time
trying to hit the heart.
You can use Magical Goggles, too!
Alright... My steady aim is going to win
Iyona-chan's heart spectacularly!
Honmaru, Iyona this way.
Honmaru, into position.
Honmaru, take good aim. Heart. Heart!
Sneak Peek!~
Those are called H-Filtering for a reason!
Honmaru, get it over with.
Relax, I know!
~Sneak Peek!~
Lewdy thoughts are tabooed.
'Kay.
Well then.
Fire!
I'm screwed!
Pulled it!
Seems a bull's eye!
Honmaru, Iyona is off to somewhere.
Okay...
Honmaru-kun...
I wanted to see you...
What is it?
Well...
I was acting so rude, earlier.
Please forgive me!
It's just that you took me by surprise
while you were merely bantering with me.
And yet, I took it to heart.
Right, right! Casually bantering. Casually bantering.
It worked, Taru!
I was on the brink of losing a friend so dear to me
in such a reckless way!
Honmaru-kun.
Forgive me.
A trifle like this is not even worth mentioning!
You're so understanding...
Honmaru! Go for it! Go!
Alright.
Iyona-chan...
I like you.
Honmaru, so double-minded.
Limpy-kun.
And...
Honmaru-kun, I...
Honmaru, go for lips!
Lips!
Honmaru-kun, you're...
I was just an inch away!
Taru, it was nowhere near ten minutes yet.
What happened?
Still, kissing Iyona-chan while under a spell
would have proven futile anyway.
Of course, because Iyona-chan would still
have no real crush on me. Neither with Yahook up-kun...
I err'd!
Honmaru, pardon!
The arrow that hit Iyona was no Yahook up-kun!
It was Yahoonest feelings-kun.
This arrow makes heart face its true feelings!
What does it matter which magic arrow...
You mean to say...
Forgive me.
Those were Iyona-chan's honest feelings.
It was rude. Honmaru-kun, I...
Can it be...
Iyona-chan has it for me...
Iyona-chan!
Wait for me!
Honmaru, you can do it!
Taruru!
Honmaru! You scarred my perfect face
with a mechanical pencil!
You've damaged more than just skin!
Cut the crap! No one ever liked your face
in the first place! Swallow it!
What did you say?!
Wanna go?
Stop right there! If you need to settle it with fisticuffs,
do it the civilized way with boxing.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Unyielding Boxing
Honmaru, I'll give you special magical training!
Episode 11
Unyielding Boxing
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume