Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Milk
Here.
Thanks for the meal!
Sure, thanks for appreciating it.
Ah, I'm so full...
Honmaru's mama superb at cooking!
Mama!
So nice of you to do that as well.
Today's mama looks especially happy.
I don't really see why you'd think so.
Got it. Not think so.
She is acting odd, though.
Episode 19
Papa's Punishment!
Definitely odd.
Odd?
Hearer.
Honey, you remember, don't you?
It's our wedding anniversary today.
That happened when I was 15...
We're screwed!
This unsolicited peek into her mind
will cost us dearly!
Mama, happy marriage!
Thank you, Taru-chan!
Really-yo?! Molesteruuto-kun
- Unzip!
- Huh? For real?
- Real, real!
Honmaru!
Surprise change of sight!
What? What's going on? For real?! For real?! What...
Say, Honmaru?
Who is mama going to marry?
What are you talking about?
She's been married to dad for years already.
Papa, then?
They're a good couple.
Now, please...
Alright, I'll go ask papa if he is marrying too.
You'll what?
Honmaru, let's go and ask him now!
Taruruuto...
I'm off!
Hold it right there!
Hold it, I said!
I wouldn't have been here
if they weren't married.
Going out, honey?
Yeah...
Well...
Can't you ask for a day off just for today?
No.
I'm going out.
Take care, then.
Now I'm totally asking papa, too!
Which way did papa go?
Don't be so rash, Taru.
If you misword it even a bit,
dad would never give you a second chance!
Papa's footprints.
Remember, our dad is actually
a hardline materialist!
Materialist?
Right! It's been years since,
but I still can't forget that one time.
Today, it's exactly one year since we first met.
At Cecil's cafe?
Thank you.
My reflection is unworthy
of the eyes as beautiful as yours.
I'm sick of your
coquettish jaw-jawing all day long!
This is our farewell.
Honmaru, make sure you don't become
this kind of bathetic excuse for a man,
only using his mouth for kowtowing to women.
Uh-huh.
Excuse me?!
Yeah!
Nothing rubs dad the wrong way
as much as relationship and marriage-related jabber.
Which is all the more bizarre
if you consider the fact he's a picture book writer.
I'm nevertheless intrigued,
where would dad go on a day like this?
Alright, I'll run after him!
One moment there, Taru!
Taru!
We'll go where papa goes before he does!
Papa!
Honmaru, why are we hiding?
Hush it!
Dad might still hear you!
Honmaru, he acts strange. Sneaky. Uh-huh.
Honmaru, what did papa do?
Why sneaky-like?
He entered a coffee shop...
There he is!
Is he ordering something?
Who could that be?
No clue!
He gave her something?!
She's looking inside...
What's that?
She's giving dad such a flustered look!
Today is his own wedding anniversary!
Yet he spends it dating another woman!
Huh? She's giving him a present, too!
What's with that embarrassed giggle?
How would you explain that?!
Taruruuto, you're giving the game away, you...
Honmaru!
Oops.
Honmaru...
Dad!
Unforgivable...
This is unforgivable, you filthy gramps!
Taru, we'll punish him!
Somehow repulsing.
Papa is happier with another woman.
Papa and mama go sour.
Taruruuto...
Somehow repulsing.
Exactly! That's why we should punish him!
If we punish him, repulsing will be gone, Honmaru?
Most certainly!
Great!
Dad, just you wait!
Counting on you, Taru!
Taru!
With Limpy-kun, we'll manipulate him.
Even now, he's only concerned
with that woman's present!
Damn it...
And make a splash now!
Harder!
Why are you clinging to that present for dear life?
Crap...
Taru, wrestle that present out of his hands!
If I wrestle, repulsing will be gone?
Yeah!
Yeah.
Attractor, then.
The present that papa is holding on to!
What's going on?
The present is trying to break away by itself!
This is bad! He's heading straight for here!
Right, let's run!
Crap...
Papa incredibly strong! A normal guy
would have released it long ago!
It's just a present from some woman!
Why won't he release it?
Make it stop! Present!
Not working, Taru!
He's catching up with us!
'Kay, Snow Cloud Taro!
Hey!
Snow Cloud Taro here!
Aight, bestow a blizzard upon papa.
Okay!
Authentic North Pole Winter Rush!
What the heck?!
A blizzard out of the blue?!
Won't release it still.
Papa super-determined!
Damn you! Release it!
Release it already!
Crap! No way I'm releasing it!
I'll release it when hell freezes over!
Honmaru's papa perv.
Come back here, you!
You ain't getting away!
That's all? Try harder!
Present! Your determination to break away
is no match for my determination to keep you in check!
Papa coming.
Honmaru, gotta run!
Present!
Papa very strong-willed!
Taru, make it stop!
You'll get dad ran over!
Now, run more!
Dad?
Look over there!
I hope dad made it out alright.
When hell freezes over!
You bloody thing!
Amazing!
Dad...
Honmaru! Taru!
Have you two been behind this all?!
Dear father, what's in the package?!
Nothing special.
Come on, Taru, let it go!
Okay!
Taru!
Papa very impressive!
Great willpower! Great looks!
Let's go home.
Okay!
Papa...
So much for our punitive mission!
Honmaru, tea!
Now, I need to serve the feast.
Wait here quietly, will you?
Sure!
Taru, is repulsing gone already?
Maybe repulses a bit...
Huh?
Who could have left this package here?
My...
It sure has been through some places.
Mom!
Ah! Right on our wedding anniversary,
what's the meaning of this!?
You can't be seeing this!
Honmaru!
We wait quietly!
How did that woman's present
end up here, of all places?
Princess and the Demon
It's over...
This scatterbrained dad!
Thank you...
Honey...
You didn't forget, after all...
About our wedding anniversary.
Demon and the Princess
Hey, what is it?
Let me see, let me see!
To me too, to me too!
Sure, sure.
This is your dad's picture book
that'll be put in print, starting today.
"Demon-kun and Princess-sama."
Author - Big Edo Fireman.
Mama, why crying?
That's right, what's so special about that title?
This story is just like that
preceding your dad and mom's marriage!
Once upon a time,
a demon sneaked into the castle.
While nobody was watching,
he snatched the princess away.
The king was so livid,
he aimed his revolver at demon and fired 6 shots.
Your dad portrayed himself as a devil,
and me as the princess!
Still, even I was a bit startled with your grandpa
shooting actual firearms at him back then.
Papa cool!
This sure was quite the adventure for him!
Hey!
Instead of all this jabbering,
you could've served dinner already!
Sure, already there!
Well, well. So the woman turned out to be
nothing more than a publisher?
Honmaru, looking happy somehow.
Look who's talking!
Right, Honmaru, what about our presents?
I completely forgot!
I need help!
Bring the dishes over, will you?
Sure!
Here, your beer.
Here, sorry for the wait!
Mama's cooking wonderful.
Really?
Thank you for the wonderful present.
Honmaru, we too!
Yay, going skiing, skiing!
Skiing?
That, you can trust me with! People around these places
call me Edojo Skimaru for my amazing skiills!
I'm proud to know you, Honmaru!
Well, at least that's what I told everyone,
while in reality I can't ski for toffee!
You have to help me somehow, Taru!
Taru?
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Skimaru of the Silver-white Slope!
Episode 20
Watch it, everyone!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius