Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Maybe it's a little early, but let's have a Christmas party
in class the day after tomorrow.
We will all come up with ideas for presents on our own,
and won't share them with anyone until the designated date.
Okay!
What do I choose for a present?
Something hand-made and fancy should do.
But I'll also have no way of knowing who gets it.
So worrisome...
Hey, Taru, what are you bringing for a present?
Bright idea came to mind!
What is it?
She-ki-ret!
A se-cret, huh? What is it?
Come on, whisper it on my ear!
Teacher said...
We come up with ideas for presents on our own,
and don't share them until the designated date!
Honmaru should also
come up with a present of his own!
Episode 16
Takoyaki Christmas
Later, Honmaru!
Me go for a bit of detour,
you return home without me!
I'm off!
That weird Taru, what's on his mind?
Take you in as an apprentice?
Yeah. Here's Takoyaki taste the best.
If I received takoyaki for Christmas,
I'd be the happiest ever!
My Christmas present - takoyaki!
Got a bright idea in that head of yours, didn't you?
I cook takoyaki as old lad's apprentice,
anyone eating it becomes carefree!
Aye, I know! You figured you'd send them to others,
cause it's such a delight to receive those yourself?
Yourself, yourself.
Alright, kid! I'll cram my trade thoroughly
in that little head of yours!
Yeah, yeah!
That's the spirit!
Then, we'll first learn how to knead the flour!
Now I know what Taru's up to.
A rather dandy idea, if I do say so myself.
Big Bargains
Damn...
What should I ever choose as a present?
There, even higher!
Christmas tree, huh?
I know!
I should make a miniature Christmas tree!
Something this small but fancy
is certain to become an eye-catcher!
I'm home!
Don't you know how to knock?
Whatcha doing?
Nothing that damn special!
Hiding things not polite.
Let me see!
Go away, will you?
Instead of being mean,
you could just show me!
Taru!
She-ki-ret!
Okay!
Balls-up!
Still raw inside!
Yes!
Start over once again!
Did it!
Quite the progress you've made.
Taru, we ain't eating it!
Sorry.
Did it!
Maybe a little rough here and there,
but still a fairly good job, I daresay.
If I try, I can do anything, too!
Alright! Just gotta find a transparent case
that fits it perfectly.
I so want to find out what Honmaru's present is.
Can't stand anymore!
That me!
Cute...
Fell apart!
Taru... You broke it!
What now, what now, what now?
I was losing my goddamn sleep making it!
This... This is my tree! This!
Sorry, Honmaru.
Taru...
You've crossed the line...
What is it?
Honmaru, Christmas is not the time
to make enemies.
Say what? Say what? Say what?
It's not your present that just got smashed!
What am I supposed to bring tomorrow?
There's no time to make a new one!
Christmas, what kind of day is that?
What kind of day, you ask?
With "Jingle Bells" playing,
dad and mom put presents in the socks.
And we eat one big cake...
And well...
Sister Ria?
Do you at least remember
whose birthday is on Christmas?
Yes! Jesus Christ's birthday.
Bingo.
Still, even if it's his birthday,
how is it related to making enemies?
Jeez...
On Christmas, one should avoid
arguing or quarreling with others.
It's the time for getting along.
Okay!
I will make up for your tree, somehow.
But you should forgive Taru.
Okay!
Taru!
Sister Ria?
Don't mind it.
Just wait here for a moment.
What on earth is that huge fir?!
Just something fancy
I found on a mountain side.
Now, let's hurry up and decorate it.
Honmaru, I help too!
Let's do, let's do!
But I can't bring along a thing this big!
It's fine, it's fine.
Honmaru, let's do, let's do!
Did it, did it splendidly!
It's nice we decorated it,
but how am I supposed to bring it?
Trunsform!
I see!
It's all fine if you shrink it with magic!
Trunsform.
This miniature's a lot more elaborate!
Thank you, sister Ria!
This would do perfectly for tomorrow's Christmas party.
Honmaru, remember that sister Ria's magic
wears off in ten days.
Sure, I'll make an inscription "big enough"
for anyone to understand.
Imagine if I'm lucky enough
to have Iyona-chan receive this tree!
One, and a-two, and...
A sleigh is like the wind,
dashing through the snow
Merry Christmas 1990
Look how light can it be,
look how fast can it go!
Our laughter is the seed,
sow it in the snow
So buds of glitter and delight
sprout up before you know!
Hey!
Jingle bells, jingle bells
Bells keep on jingling
Getting Iyona-chan's present would be nice, too...
Light is dancing in circles
while the bells are marking rhythm
Jingle bells, jingle bells
Bells keep on jingling
Through the forests, through the groves
you can hear them echoing
My present is nearing Iyona-chan!
Stop!
OH MY GOD!
Why did it have to end up in Jabao's claws?
Now, everyone, let's open it.
It's takoyaki!
Iyona! My tasty present! Eat it, eat it!
Thank you, Taru-chan.
Hurry! Hurry up and bite!
Delicious!
I learned that at old lad's takoyaki shop!
It's ultimate takoyaki!
Somehow, eating Taru-chan's takoyaki
makes me suddenly oh-so happy!
Oh-so happy...
This here is one badass tree!
It's precise down to the smallest details!
It even has working lights!
Who in the world could have done that?
It appears that I would be the one who did it.
Honmaru did?
Fine craftsmanship, Honmaru-kun!
But now this tree is mine.
Not even those begging me with their "Please let me see it,"
will get to actually see it!
Please let me see it, Jabao-kun!
Sure, you can look at it all you want.
This douche!
Why is my tree bringing closer
Iyona-chan and Jabao instead?!
I got a toy Santa-san!
From Iyona!
Aren't you lucky, Taru?
Then there's this thing I got -
a botched clay toad that Jabao pasted together. Damn it.
Shit!
Please let me see it, Jabao-sama.
Jabao, that prick!...
Christmas is not the time to make enemies.
Honmaru, you can have my present, too. Cheer up.
It's fine. One should not
hold any grudges on Christmas.
Delicious indeed!
That's right! When it's actually Christmas eve,
I'll give Iyona-chan another hand-made present!
A brooch, maybe?
Think I can make it in time?
Honmaru, sounds great!
Make Iyona happy!
Just don't spill it to anyone else!
Yeah!
'Kay!
Honmaru busy all day.
I have nothing to do.
It's Santa Claus!
Wanna-wanna-wanna!
Santa Claus, give-give-give! Lemme touch it!
Hey! What are you trying to do?
Stop this at once, or I'm handing you over to the police!
Don't you know when to stop, you brat?!
Reminder: in 10 days, it grows mighty big, fella!
Iyona-chan!
Ah?
Honmaru-kun?
I couldn't give it to you during the school party.
Here, your Christmas present.
Jabao...!
Honmaru, you schmuck!
The tree was a trap!
Thanks to your freaking tree,
mom gave me the hardest beating ever!
I bet you didn't even try to read the inscription!
It said "big again after ten days" pretty damn clearly!
Shut up!
Or what?
You shouldn't be fighting, both of you!
After all, it's Christmas eve!
Christmas?
What does it freaking matter?
Christmas?!
Jesus Christ's birthday? Christ's?
I don't know any chump by that name!
What the hell does Christ know about it?
He's not the one getting the beating every time!
Jabao-kun! Please stop throwing your fists!
You're my friend, aren't you?
Thy neighbor shalt be loved and cared for!
That's what Jesus taught us!
Time neighbor shelled by love and carrot?
Whatcha trying to say, Iyona-chan?
The person next to you, the one near you -
you should be forgiving and loving towards everyone, he said!
And that thou shall love thy enemy the dearest!
Whaaa?
Then, does he mean to say this cockroach Jabao
roughing me up right now deserves to be loved, too?
This Christ buddy
must have been goddamn insane!
Besides, if two guys start loving each other,
it's as though they're homos!
Jabao-kun, stop beating him!
You shut up too!
Iyona-chan!
You ass...
Stop it, already!
Fighting won't solve anything!
When two guys fight, you don't butt in!
Someone I'd call a friend
would've never hit anyone!
Shut the hell up!
Iyona-chan...
Christmas is not the time to make enemies.
Jabao... You schmuck!
Look who's talking!
I love thou!!
What?!
Jabao!
You gross thing...
I love you,
Jabao!
What's on his sicko mind?
Alright, just gotta mimic Taru's antics now.
Jabao! Jabao...
I love you!
Jabao... Rub-rub. Jabao...
I got it.
I got it, alright? Get away from me!
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan, are you happier this way?
It's probably beyond repair now.
Great! Not even a scratch!
Iyona-chan,
an extra Christmas present.
Thank you, Honmaru-kun.
It's the most gorgeous.
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru-kun...
It's snowing!
True!
Beautiful...
A White Christmas for us.
Honmaru!
My, Taru-chan!
What's with that garb, Taru?
Lookin' fancy.
Me Santa Claus!
Santa Claus, you say?
If you claim to be Santa,
where's your magical reindeer-drawn sleigh?
Throne sleigh?
This what? Sleigh?
What we call sleigh is...
Is this for real?
Honmaru, you displayed your forbearance in the fight.
Accept this as a Christmas present from me.
Pretty!
What's going on?
It's like a dream!
Speaking of which, Taru,
what do you have inside that bag?
Almost forgot! Me Santa Claus!
Handing out the presents!
Eating this takoyaki
makes you suddenly oh-so happy.
Iyona said so.
Honmaru try and see, too!
Lemme have it...
Delicious! There's something incredibly uplifting in it!
Alright, I'll share it with everyone else!
Merry Christmas!
Heavily snowing, this night sky,
of mama's kisses and papa's gru-ru-rumbling
I love takoyaki, I also love everyone,
here is my big present to all of you
Tatattatakoyaki tru-ru-runsform!
Even Santa-san looking through the window
most surprised
So no need to be shy, not even for you
You!
Come along with us, too
Together, we gobble them up
Lucky Happy Christmas
Dancin' our hearts out,
till morning comes
Do it with us and you'll never be short of friends
Stars give us light and moon is a disco ball,
so let's dance our time out, enjoy it all!
Tatattatakoyaki tru-ru-runsform!
Idling again?
Look at this, even Santa-san is grinning wide,
he is one of us now!
So don't you be shy, come along now,
we've waited for long enough
Merry Christmas!
Everyone comes along
Lucky Happy Christmas
Lucky Happy Christmas!
Suspicious.
Kinda very suspicious!
I could swear we've never had this guy in our class before!
And yet, he's already acting
so brazen towards Iyona-chan! Taru...
Honmaru, sorry.
My magic doesn't take any effect.
How did that happen?!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Friends from the Magic Realm.
Taru's Rival, what kind of cloth are you cut from?!
Episode 17
Friends from the Magic Realm
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius