Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
So cold!
Episode 25
Dangerous Snowball Fight!?
Finished!
Mr. Snowman!
Are you out of your mind?!
You can't build a snowman on my head!
Honmaru, all's covered in snow!
Hey, look, look! Hurry up! Honmaru!
The window has been wide open!
No wonder I felt so cold all this time.
Honmaru, not like the snow?
The snow can stay, but the cold has to go!
Yeah!
Honmaru, I got you covered.
Hi!
Honmaru, you rub this pocket heater.
Thank you, Taru!
Huh?
It suddenly reddened.
What's with that pocket heater?
This - Beater-Heater-kun.
Wherever Heater-kun hits you,
this place trunsforms into source of warmth!
Hey! I'm warmer already!
Yeah!
Whew! Wait! My whole body is burning!
The heat is unbearable!
Mom! Bring out my summer garb again!
It's snowing!
Look at all this snow!
Honmaru, are you quite okay?
What happened, Honmaru?
Children are as free as the wind!
As three as thirteen! As three as thirteen!
Aren't you even a bit cold, Honmaru-kun?
Just bearing it out of vanity!
It's all okay, all okay!
Cake, cake!
Impressive, Honmaru-kun!
Life is thriving in you!
We'll see about that bragging,
once you catch a cold!
I'll be alright.
After all, I train all the time!
Fiddle.
Spittle.
Your confidence is inspiring.
Make sure to live up to it by not catching a cold.
Or perhaps the winter clothes
are just too pricey for you?
Hey, people!
Let's have a snowball fight instead!
Yeah! Let's do it! Let's do it!
Snowball fight!
Right!
Count me in!
An exquisite diversion.
Today I'm giving you a lesson you won't forget.
You're ignorant of the fact I'm the commander-in-chief
of the Junior World Snowball Fighting cabinet.
Okay, here we go!
Alright! Let's split into teams now!
Yeah!
And now...
My hand decides my band!
Egh?
I'm on the same team as Jabao?!
Ah, whatever. All that matters is that Iyona-chan
is on my team, and Harako isn't!
We can do it, right?
Alright!
Let's smack 'em, Honmaru!
Sure!
Do your best!
Okay!
Iyona-chan!
We'll do our best, won't we?
With Honmaru-kun's energy,
we can do anything.
Nothing here to be "eheheheing" about! I swear...
People! Let's hurry and prepare the snowballs!
Yeah!
Right, keep it up.
Why don't you prepare some yourself?
Why don't you do?
Huh?
Anybody knows where Harako is?
How are combat preparations, comrades?
Harako! Why the full-blown military uniform
for a snowball fight?
Lookin' cool!
From now on, this unit is placed
under my full command.
My orders have absolute power!
Alright...
Unit Red-Con five minutes!
We start at 8:25!
Roger!
Eck?!
Honestly, just learn to be easygoing sometimes.
Young Master.
Alright! You have five minutes to build a pillbox!
Get to work!
Roger!
What's going on... What?
Good.
The sooner you master modern warfare, the better. Got it?
You pull the trigger here to shoot snowballs.
Jabao-san.
What is it?
A whole battalion of adults
is helping Harako build a fort in his camp.
What?!
See?
I see!
Alright, we can't lose this!
Let's build a fort, too!
Yeah! With all our might!
We made a lot!
True.
This way, push!
I'm pushing.
You sure?
I'm pushing, I swear!
Taru! Bring over our banner!
Got it!
Honmaru!
That's right!
Ah-ah. Test, test. One, two.
Attention, enemy army!
What's going on?
Playing big! Wow! So cool!
We are thus commencing
the first wave of attack!
Hey, Taru! Hide!
Whew, I like this thing already.
Fire!
Roger!
Pause to reload!
Eat that! Annihilated!
Screw you...
Using machinery ain't fair!
Damn right! That's just cowardly, Harako!
Throw snowballs with your own hands,
like normal children do!
You fools!
All's fair in love and snowball fights!
In modern warfare, superior technology
is what tells a winner from a loser!
You ass!
Why, you...
Fire!
Taru-chan!
Iyona-chan...
Damn you...
Hey!
I'm not impressed, Harako!
I'm not impressed!
Taru-chan. Taru-chan!
Harako!
We have girls here, too!
It's ungentlemanly warfare!
A precise one just for you!
In an age of nuclear and chemical weapons
being deployed on actual battlefields,
such relicts as ethics, rules, and so on
aren't worth a zilch!
Damn it! Harako lost it completely
and is preaching some malarkey!
Now's our turn, Ryoguchiya Korekiyo!
Roger, Jaba Jabao-san!
This won't work!
Stop, Jabao, Korekiyo!
Now!
We shine today!
Yes!
If a snowball barrage hits you point-blank...
You'll lose your balance!
Korekiyo, if we go down, we go down together!
You alright, Jabao, Korekiyo?
Been friggin better.
Jabao, don't give up!
Honmaru…
Counting on you to finish this...
Jabao...
Jabao was the most repulsive kind of guy,
but still a lesser of evils,
compared to Harako!
I must take care of Harako myself,
whatever the cost may be!
Direct fire at Honmaru!
All-or-nothing attack!
Me attack too!
Alright then...
Watch out, Taru!
It's dangerous here!
Damn it!
Alright. This way, Honmaru is pinned down securely.
Harako-kun is outside!
What?
Alright...
Hit him with everything you've got!
Very well!
There!
You're too weak!
You'll never get me with a throw that clumsy!
Iyona-san, are you done sending the prayer?
Move it, move it!
I'm only doing this to seal Honmaru's utter defeat,
so you'll have to forgive me, Iyona-san.
You brute! Harassing Iyona-chan for the fun of it?!
How dare you—
Honmaru!
Taruruuto!
Taruruuto! Don't try to shield me!
You shouldn't be shielding me!
Look at all the snowballs I caught!
A snow shower!
Feels so refreshing.
I swear, Taru! We don't have time for games,
just discharge it at the enemy already!
Okay, help me aim.
Ready!
Full ready!
Vertical angle at plus 201 degrees!
Fire!
We did it!
Alright, now just to discharge at Harako, too!
Wait, Taruruuto!
Harako, where are you?
Where you hiding at?
Enough! Not a step more!
Okay! Me not stepping!
That's good, for if you come any closer,
Kawai Iyona-san's delicate white skin
will become even more white with a snowball.
Sounds fun! Do it, do it!
Cut it out, you!
Taru, I need you to go play elsewhere now.
Okay!
That's just cowardly, Harako!
Doesn't matter if it's cowardly or whatnot.
What matters is you lost, Honmaru!
How should I handle this?
You've got me this time.
It pains me to do so, but I must surrender.
Another victory for me.
Honmaru-kun...
Come on! You've got my surrender.
Now hurry up and untie Iyona-chan!
You utter dope!
The surrender is merely where the fun starts!
The defeated party
is then subjected to the war reparations!
What?!
As a punishment, the losing side must make 10 laps
around the schoolyard in his birthday suit!
Why should I embarrass myself like that?!
Need I remind you why?
Look.
The snowball will surely do a number
on a skin that delicate.
I heard you! Stop! No more!
Hurry up and bare that tiny Cockmaru!
Come what may.
Nothing I can't do for Iyona-chan!
Honmaru, look.
Iyona-san is about to witness your grand humiliation!
Wait, Honmaru-kun!
You don't have to make a fool of yourself
just to help me!
My back is thoroughly soaked already
with cold water, constantly dripping
from Harako-kun's muzzle.
Iyona-chan...
Even a snowball on top of that
would change nothing now.
Go ahead, Harako-kun.
Feel free to pull the trigger.
Stop this at once!
The hell?! An earthquake?
Iyona-chan!
That's right!
Iyona-chan, I'll bring you to safety no matter what!
This thing...
What the hell is going on?!
I used Sword-Pen Magic-kun
to bring snow to life!
Honmaru, he will trample Harako for you!
Screw you!
This doesn't look good.
He lacks thickness and is easy to tatter!
See now? That's the superior technology
of the Harako Conglomerate for you!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru?
Honmaru!
Are you okay, Iyona-chan?
All's good with me.
It's just getting a bit cold here.
Give me a moment.
I told you I'd bring you to safety no matter what.
I can't do it.
It's cold.
And I'm so tired from all this running...
No way!
Iyona-chan, don't fall asleep!
Don't fall asleep!
Right, I still have this thing.
To save you, to warm you up,
getting beaten is nothing!
Iyona-chan!
That's good, make sure to smack me everywhere!
This way, with my body...
With my body...
Iyona-chan...
Honmaru! Honmaru! Honmaru!
Young Master! Hurry up and dig him up!
Roger!
Honmaru-kun is so warm!
Honmaru happy enough as it is.
Honmaru, wanna do sumo with me?
Sumo? Ahhh, this just brought up
so many deplorable memories!
What's wrong, Honmaru?
Ah, why was I born so feeble?
I wanna win! Whatever it takes against an opponent
such as him, I should definitely win, Taru!
Sure! Leave this to me.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
To Battle, Honmaru!
Alright, I'm having special
sumo training with magic!
Episode 26
To Battle, Honmaru!
To battle!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius