Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Episode 7
I am Ijigawa Rui
I'm late, so late! I should have asked Taruruuto
to stop time for me!
Cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle!
She's also running late,
why is she so casual about it?
Hey, Ijigawa! If you don't hurry,
our teacher will have you spanked!
God, you're annoying!
Quit commenting on my every move, you bed-wetter!
Be late then, if that suits you!
Honmaru seems to have left in a hurry.
What he's up to?
I want to see, Tama-chan!
It's too embarrassing to show!
However, if it's just a quick glance...
Slap
I came late after all...
This testifies to the fact your devotion is insincere!
Another latecomer?
Ijigawa! Get your butt battered, too!
What's the matter, Ijigawa-san?
You see... I'm not feeling quite well, teacher.
Will you be okay?
I'll manage...
If you don't feel well enough,
maybe you should rest in the infirmary?
No, I...
Won't forgive myself for missing your lesson...
Ijigawa-san!
Ijigawa-san.
Then, we should all not let Ijigawa-san down.
Let's study productively today.
Teacher, when everyone depends on me,
I just have to get better soon.
Feigning illness to escape punishment?
That's just cheap, Ijigawa!
Taru-chan, you promised to only take a quick glance.
Hey, look! Look!
Only 10 points!
Who could possibly flunk so miserably?
Can tell you one thing - it ain't me!
Can you believe our class
has such a disgraceful stain on it?
Knew it! It is Edojo Honmaru's!
Not here?
Really Honmaru's, after all!
Ijigawa!
Give back my test!
Wait though. The law allows for the finder
to retain one tenth of the finding's worth.
Hey! Look, look, look!
Why, you!
This is my rightful property.
You have no legal grounds to press charges.
How low can you get, Ijigawa?
Didn't you just steal the test from my desk?
How mean!
To call me a thief, even!
Honmaru brought a girl to tears.
She's tricking you!
GOD DAMMIT!
How much of a brute must you be
to bring an innocent girl to tears?
I'm struggling to believe my eyes!
Right, Iyona-san?
Iyona-chan, you are misled!
Don't give me that look!
I got carried away. Sorry.
What is it?
Making me come all the way here...
You have a thing for Kawai Iyona, don't you?
N-n-no...
Alright. Then I'm razing your love to the ground.
Why are you so obsessed with that?
Because I have a thing for Honmaru-kun myself.
Lies!
Throb
No lies, just love.
Hey...
You can even touch my butt as proof.
kyaaa
What's going on!?
Can't take my hand off!
Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun just said "Hey, I like you, lemme feel that butt,
HE-HE!" and wouldn't let go of it ever since! Look! Look!
That's a bunch of bullcrap!
Iyona-chan, you shouldn't believe a word of it!
Honmaru-kun, why won't you take your hand away?
That's what I'm telling you!
My hand just won't go away! There, there, see?
Huh?
Iyona-chan!
Ijigawa must have glued it, I swear!
Honmaru-kun is a devil, don't you think?
And that's not nearly it, what he also said was...
Stupid idiot!
Screw you, Ijigawa!
Now even Iyona-chan despises me...
Honmaru!
Playing pranks on each other?
I partake, too!
Right, a culprit that heinous,
should be the first one in the spanking queue!
But there's no way! Because she's a girl,
the whole class would side with her!
In the end... In the end,
only I would be made into a villain!
She manipulates others like a seasoned actor,
that'd lie without batting an eye!
Means you need to stay in shadows?
Got it, Honmaru!
Meet Limpy-kun.
I stick Honmaru's photo like this and... Taru!
What's the deal with that creepy laugh?
But I can't stand on just one...
This is doll for operating people, Limpy-kun.
With it, you take your revenge on Ijigawa.
That's it, Taru!
And then...
'Kay...
Here!
What did you do that for?
My hand just moved by itself!
Oh, it must be hard to believe!
Why are you also making up impossible excuses?
If you fool around,
just admit it and apologize!
I let my guard down with that one,
but as a 3rd dan in karate, 4th dan in judo
and 3rd dan in kendo, I won't let you land a single blow more.
Cheeky child...
This time, it's Ijigawa Kick!
Stop it right now!
While putting on a face of docility,
your true intent has been a rebellion against teacher?!
You're mistaken, teacher!
Whatever it is, I must come up with some explanation.
Well then, what's all that dancing about?
Well, I figured I could show you
this thinking dance of mine.
Dancing, dancing, dancing!
Hop, hop, hop, and twist!
What do you say?
Isn't that cool?
Honmaru! Let me too! Me too!
Ijigawa-san...
Now go for the boobs!
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze, squeeze.
I help too, like this!
What's the meaning of this?!
Rui-chan...
Taruruuto, we didn't go a bit too far
with this one, did we?
Saw it? Saw it? Saw it?
You get it now?
No teacher is a match for me!
It's like your daily humiliation has been avenged!
How about thanking me, huh?
Turns out, we didn't go far enough, Taru.
Cheer up, Honmaru!
Our pranks on Ijigawa are off to a good start!
Iyona-chan despises me nevertheless!
Why am I, as a man, so unfortunate?
All my trials and tribulations arise because of just one girl,
the meanest in all of Japan!
Next time you're playing meanie on me,
you're not getting away with it, Ijigawa Rui!
Honmaru-kun.
Iyona-chan?
Rui-chan is not as bad a girl as you think.
But still...
I really like Rui-chan.
And that's why we're friends.
Iyona-chan...
Iyona's friend - my friend!
Taru-chan.
Smile...
What is it, Taru?
And my's friend - Honmaru's friend!
Ijigawa and Honmaru.
F-ri-en-ds!
That's right.
Just like Taru-chan said.
Right? Isn't that true, Honmaru-kun?
Uh-huh!
Then, will you and Rui-chan start getting along now?
Like friends would.
Can you promise me?
Most naturally!
I promise too!
Splendid, splendid!
Iyona-chan's not one bit disgusted with me!
Right. We're lucky, Honmaru.
Here, it's yummy.
There! There, there, there, there.
Now, come here.
Isn't it dangerous to live in a place like this?
It tickles!
Did someone throw you out?
Or did you just lose your way?
Mi-chan! Where are you?
Mi-chan!
Meal time!
Hey, what is more important now
than getting home, Taru?
This is bad...
Freeze!
Uh-oh...
Honmaru, you promised to Iyona.
Now that I think about it, Iyona-chan probably wouldn't
make friends with someone who's actually that rotten.
Alright! What am I? Not a man?
Hey! Ijigawa!
So, what is it?
About that...
In what way could I put it
that we have to start getting along?
Well, you see, the matter is...
Just learn to enunciate
whatever it is you want to say, you bed-wetter!
Just making yourself even more of a fool
with how gutless you are!
Damn it all! Ijigawa remains Ijigawa, after all! A demon!
Stick.
Honmaru is a bungler in getting along.
I help out.
You miserable, bed-wetting, 10-point scoring brat!
I can't take it anymore!
Ijigawa!
Are you trying to...
You're wrong!
My hand's moving by itself!
I see, it's Taruruuto again!
How can I be getting it wrong
after everything you just did?
But that's exactly why you're wrong!
Make it stop!
Make it stop...
Somebody!
Is it you? The molester.
He's still just a dirty brat, but already
he's become an elementary school pervert!
But I'm not in the slightest a pervert!
Get lost.
I bet Honmaru is getting along with Ijigawa.
I'd really wish to!
Don't get hung up on it! Think of this
as a stray dog's bite. Or rather, just forget it.
Honmaru!
You alright?
Hang in there.
That was inconsiderate of you.
After admitting you actually like Iyona-chan,
suddenly approaching me like that...
I don't mind...
...if you kiss me.
Ijigawa...
Go for it, Honmaru!
Are you kidding me?
I'm not playing into your hands again!
I'm only here because Iyona-chan
pleaded me to start getting along with you!
Who'd ever be interested in you otherwise?
You're not pulling another one on me, Ijigawa!
Man, almost let myself fall for another one.
Ijigawa...
You fell for it, you scatterbrain!
What do you mean?
Iyona-chan, what a story I got for you!
About this elementary school pervert Honmaru
that molested me in the park!
But I didn't!
Well, what do I call this hand, then?
Looks like a mighty piece of evidence to me.
Can't take away...
Look at this, Iyona-chan!
It's Honmaru again!
Now I'm definitely not buying it for the third time!
Iyona-chan!
Please help me, Taruruuto!
Honmaru's failure is my failure.
What do you know,
we're playing baseball, Taru!
In the next inter-school match,
our team certainly wins!
We win!
Enough fooling around, Honmaru.
Naturally, you're ignorant of the fact
I played a key role in the Junior Major League.
Episode 8
Magic Ball Baseball!!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Magic Ball Baseball!
See you all there!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume