Those stars are on a strange march today...
Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
My! What a pretty flower!
And a spiky one...
Smells good.
Patience, patience.
Patience...
Thanks for the meal!
Takoyaki!
Whoa! Delicious takoyaki!
You decided to return to me, after all!
Takoyaki, you can't run away!
It's been a while, Taruruuto-kun.
You're still as mischievous as ever, Taruruuto-kun.
Our school teach! Doing good?
Don't you act so casual!
Not after skipping Magical Kindergarten classes!
Lest I, Tabanba-sama, will serve
as an agent of teacher Oshiru's punishment!
Tabanba!
Serves you right!
Now then, Taruruuto-kun,
how about we return to the Magic Realm together?
I can't return.
What was that, you shrimp?
Mind you, teacher Oshiru came all the way here
just to fetch some witless dropout!
I'm talking about you, little prick! Yes, you!
Tabanba!
Ah... Yes, I'm Mute-banba...
With you dropping out from the kindergarten,
both Mimora-chan and Rival reflected on their ways
and fully devoted themselves to their studies.
Taruruuto-kun, you too need to study hard in the Magic Realm,
in order to catch up with them
and become a fine magician. You see?
Me like this world...
Me go to school with Honmaru...
Honmaru a bit pervert.
But me really love Honmaru!
We're going back.
Never.
Taruruuto-kun!
Never!
Never, never, never!
Ha! Think you can run away?
Taru-Taru-Taru-Taruruuto-kun!
Teach Oshiru!
Banba-Tabanba!
Taru-Taru-Taru...
Our te-te-teach!
Taru-Taru-Taru!
Te-te-te-te-teach!
Taru-Taru-Taru-Taru-Taru!
Me love this world!
Honmaru too. Iyona too, me love everyone!
Love them...
Banba-Banba-Tabanba!
Me not wanna!
Give up now!
Not wanna!
Oh, my!
Why?!
Not wanna return!
Mom, we're off!
Honmaru's mama, we're-ru-ru-ru off!
Honmaru, Taru-chan, take care!
Let's hurry, Taru!
I hurru-ru-ry!
Just this once, I'm letting you be!
Counting on you, Soccer Ball-kun!
Yeah! Ain't nothing I can't do!
There!
Move it, move it, move it!
What'd you do that for, Taru?
Soccer Ball-kun, what's wrong?!
Honmaru, going where to?!
What was that for, Taru...
Banba!
So far, so good! Soon, all your friends in this world
will come to disgust you, Taruruuto!
The heck?
Are you alright, Honmaru-kun?
I'm very much alright now. Have no fear!
Taru's mischief caused this as well.
Thank you, Taru!
It feels like I have a fever.
Did I catch a cold somehow?
Oh, how caring Iyona-chan is...
Honmaru-kun, what's the matter?
And cute, too!
It's nothing!
My bad, Iyona-chan!
And if I say I love her now?
Hey, Iyona-chan!
Did you know I'm actually a soccer prodigy?
I can hit the ball with any part of my body!
Limpy-kun, Honmaru's photo stuck.
Honmaru, me and Limpy-kun help out, too!
Kick!
What is it, Honmaru-kun?
Just wanted to say my thanks.
Must be Taru's doing, too!
Honmaru, cuddle-cuddle more!
Huh?
Limpy-kun! Where you going? Where...
Good!
Thank you, Taru.
I'll take it from here!
Alright, that's it. The time is ripe to confess my love!
Tabanba! There!
Iyona-chan, I sort of...
Sort of...
Love...
Pristine whites, whoa!
Honmaru-kun, you...
Honmaru-kun, you're...
Taruruuto, what was the point of that?
Honmaru, Don't be a pervert now!
Lemme fix it for you.
As if I'd let you, Taruruuto!
Your miserable magic is nothing like...
What?
No you won't, I said!
There!
Look, me and Tabanba play tag!
Stop right there this instant!
Tabanba, watch this!
No you don't!
Yes I do!
There!
I said you won't!
Didn't you hear me?
Watch this!
Wait!
Tabanba!
Here, here!
No, here!
There!
Huh? Who turned off the lights?
Come out to play, Tabanba!
Honmaru-kun, you're disgusting!
But I...
Tabanba!
Me? No, it wasn't me... Look, it was...
Tabanba! Cock-a-doodle-doo!
No...
No. No, you sick bird!
Huh?!
Why...
Iyona-chan...
Why did I just do that?
I blamed you, instead...
Oh, never mind that.
I'm sorry, Honmaru-kun...
Thank you, Taru!
Yeah!
Why, you... No...
Don't... Yeah, you, just... don't...
I beg of you! Just one more chance, Oshiru-sensei!
This time, I'll bring Taruruuto back
to the Magic Realm for sure!
I hope Honmaru's mama likes this!
Oshiru-sensei, the Magic Realm considers you a super-elite.
If the word gets out that one dropout pupil
is leading you a merry dance,
your peerless career would be tarnished forever!
Pretty...
But I'd sooner lose my life than fail you,
you can be sure of that!
Please trust me to take care of everything!
Tabanba.
Yes?
You need to learn how to be quiet now and then.
Huh?! Ack, no way...
Why?!
That was quite the superb
home-run on your part, Jabao-san.
Oh, it wasn't that good...
Tabanba, here!
Hey! Taru, y—
You...
You jerk!
Doncha dare gambol so carelessly, you lousy turkey!
Takoyaki. Takoyaki! Takoyaki, takoyaki.
Tabanba-babanba! Scram!
This for me!
Why?
Me noticed first!
Who's the smart-ass who put this lousy cage here?!
Did I not make it clear enough
that I want you to stay out of this?
Tabanba, it appears that ultimately,
a third-rate wizard like you
would never suit me as a right-hand man.
It's time for you to return to the Magic Realm!
Eh? You can't be serious...
Let it be known that I don't wish to see you
meddling in my affairs ever again.
Is that clear?
Teacher Oshiru!
Why...
Why, oh, why? Why me?!
Mom, is my snack...
Mom!
Hang on, mom!
What's wrong with Honmaru's mama?
We need a doctor!
No... Only the ambulance would do!
But what now? What now? What now?
What to do? What to do? What to do?
Mom...
Honmaru's mama...
It's not something a human doctor can alleviate.
Sister!
I had reaped the disgust of Teacher Oshiru!
It all came to Oshiru-sensei disowning me...
And it's all Taruruuto and Honmaru's fault!
You're not getting away with it.
Just you watch as I turn upside down
this sweet little world you've grown used to living in...
It's as if I'm being beckoned...
Wait a minute...
With a touch of black magic on this old piece of scrap...
Hah! It's strictly forbidden in the Magic Realm,
but what does it matter now?
Mom...
Honmaru's mama, stay strong.
Ah! Ria, is there really no way whatsoever
to help cure mom's illness? Really?
Sis...
Taru, it's not in my power...
Taru...
Wait!
Big sister!
Sister Ria...
In the Magic Realm, I've heard about the "Fruit of Life,"
that can do anything, including curing this kind of disease.
Once a million years,
a single flower blooms, and the fruit is born.
But as for where to look for it...
Alas, I haven't a clue.
I'll be fine without it...
There ain't no way you're fine...
Mom!
Honmaru's mama won't get better!
Taru-chan, you're a big boy now...
So you shouldn't cry, no matter what happens to me.
Honmaru's mama...
Mom!
Taruruuto-kun...
Let me escort you home, Taruruuto-kun.
Teach...
If you return to the Magic Realm with me now,
we'll go look for the Fruit of Life together,
to help cure your friend's mama.
You wish to save your friend's mama, don't you?
Me... Me...
Yes.
But in return, I'll have your promise
to not show up in this world ever again.
Honmaru...
Alka-gilka, alka-gilka!
Show yourself, Hogeru-ru-ru-ru!
Alka-gilka! Show yourself, Hogeru-ru-ru-ru!
Taru!
I promised to Teach...
We return to the Magic Realm together...
Taru!
Me love Honmaru's mama...
Honmaru's mama mustn't die!
Taru...
Alka-gilka!
Show yourself, Hogeru-ru-ru-ru!
Honmaru!
Me definitely find the Fruit of Life!
Taru!
Honmaru's mama said that -
boys can't cry. Me not cry, too!
Taru...
Honmaru...
Show yourself! Hogeru-ru-ru-ru!
What?
Go forth! Let nothing stop you
from razing this world to the ground!
Foolish bird...
Bam-bam-crush everything! Bam-boom-pound it!
Tabanba!
But why...?
This robot is a piece of scrap, after all.
It completely came to a halt.
The spring finally went unwound, I bet.
But what if it starts moving again...
We'll be a-okay now, Iyona-chan.
Oh! Honmaru! Taru! Over here!
Honmaru-kun...
Iyona-chan!
Iyona!
Oh, Honmaru? Where were you hiding?
Have you seen this robot, raging with great power?
Well, it's certainly but a great piece of scrap now.
Even though I recalled the effect of Tabanba's magic,
the robot won't return to its original size...
Oshiru-sensei!
What're y'all so spooked by?
My magic has no effect?
Are you okay, everyone?
Oaya-sensei!
Eh? Isn't that Taru-chan?
Huh? Taru-chan is missing?
That was naughty of you.
Aren't you a good kid?
Taru!
Taruruuto-kun?
Taruruuto's got a darn handy pair of toy wings, I reckon.
Rub. Rub!
That's a good kid.
Good kid, are you not?
Taru Taru! Taru!
Honmaru! My life saver!
This aid isn't meant for you!
The duty of protecting peace in the world is mine to fulfill!
Great Special Thunder Squadron,
commence the attack!
Harako Great Special Bomber!
Are you kidding me...
Don't you fuss over such trifles!
You're the best, Dad!
Honmaru's papa, banzai!
I've got something important to tell you both.
Listen closely.
The stars were moving ominously recently,
so I investigated whether or not they foretold a great calamity
that would unleash itself upon our world. And indeed...
Dad...?
Honmaru, this world of ours
is closely intertwined with the Magic Realm.
Therefore, both are constantly threatened
by hellish powers.
It's quite possible that this robot
is powered by hellish powers, too.
It must have been generated
from the enormous energy of someone's rancor.
There's no doubt about it.
This is something that is said
to only exist within the Magic Realm.
A fruit amazingly born here, in our very garden.
Dad, this fruit can do anything,
including curing mom's illness!
What?
The Fruit of Life appeared once again -
something that only happens once per million years.
Sister Ria...
When or where it will appear the next time...
Is a mystery to anyone.
But that means we'll only ever have one chance to use it,
to cure mom's illness!
It's up to you to decide
how to dispose of this fruit, Honmaru.
Dad...
Honmaru?
Embrace the world!
☢️ Harako Conglomerate
Build a brighter tomorrow!
☢️ Harako Engineering
Embrace the world!
☢️ Harako Conglomerate
Build a brighter tomorrow!
☢️ Harako Engineering
Embrace the world!
☢️ Harako Conglomerate
My mission is to protect our world's peace!
Nobody gets away with ruining my city!
Dad, what should I do with it?
If I use it now, mom will never...
Ain't no one but us is gonna unwind this thing!
Well said, Jabao-san!
Sister Ria...
See for yourself.
You stay here, while I avenge you.
Iyona-chan... Everyone...
Honmaru, in our world, one lives to help another.
Only when everyone around is happy,
can you truly be happy yourself.
Right, Honmaru?
Mom...
Therefore, you should never place your own good
above the good of many.
Mom...
Taru, we'll fix this pile of scrap for good!
Yeah!
Honmaru, I'll buff you up with Inflatable Muscles-kun.
I can do it, Taru!
Banzai!
Eh? Where are my pants going...
Banba!
Tabanba?
He might still be too strong for me, Taru...
What are you up to?
Honmaru, Power-Upple Juice. Drink this, too!
Honmaru, drinking this will make you
thousands by thousands stronger.
That'd be...
Yeah! The power is overflowing me!
Me go there-re, too!
Now's my chance!
Honmaru! Honmaru, wait for me!
Honmaru-kun...!
Crap! It won't let me get closer!
Eh? Eh! Taru's magic wore out already!
Honmaru, need this!
Honmaru, do it now!
Honmaru, don't stop!
Mom...
Is it defeated?
I could have used it to cure mom's illness...
But this chance is gone now!
I can no longer save her...
Not without a fruit only appearing once every million years!
When and where will the next one be born...
not a soul knows.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, mom.
Honmaru-kun! Taru-kun!
Iyona-chan!
What's wrong?
We saved everyone else, didn't we?
Honmaru! The fruit! The light!
It showed up! It's right here!
A Mysterious Giant Robot Appears!!
Raws & encoding by Renascent
With VHS audio & trailer captured by WOWmd
Original Portuguese translation by Armagedonfansubs
English translation by Cavery210 of Saiko no Fansub
Translation checked by Perevodildo & Aurelius
Quality checked by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser) & Izma
Bye-bye!
FIN