Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Takoyaki, takoyaki!
Together with Honmaru!
Gonna crunch! Gonna cru-ru-runch!
Ah! Takoyaki!
Not so fast!
Little One, gotta be more careful with such things.
Takoyaki rewards those who treat it with respect.
Episode 28
A One-in-a-Kind Guy Comes From Osaka
Where'd Taru run off to again?
Just as I was about to treat him
to some takoyaki with my allowance...
Come on...
Honmaru! Honmaru!
What is it, Taru?
What's all this hurry-scurry about?
I found takoyaki oh, so yummy!
Go there right away!
You did what?
Super-yummy, this way ru-ru-run!
Honmaru, here! Here.
Eh? Here, huh?
That's your super-yummy takoyaki shop?
Famous Osakan Takoyaki
Little One? Dropping by my place again?
Yo! Again. What's cooking?
This and that - things...
Ah, this - Honmaru. My friend!
Welcome to my stall. How's it goin'?
Fine, thanks. Name's Edojo Honmaru. Nice to meet you.
Honmaru. Matsu's takoyaki is a holy yumster!
Japan's bestest takoyaki!
Well said. My Famous Osakan Takoyaki ain't nothing like the other stalls, 'cause those swindlers put no guts in it.
Honmaru, buy sooner!
Okay...
Matsu-san, we'll have one serving.
Aight! A-coming!
Are they really that yummy?
Yes! Yummy. Yummy-yummy!
This is...
YUMSTER!
How can there be takoyaki that's this yummy?!
This takoyaki is worth breaking a neck over!
They really are... Japan's bestest!
No, no...
The world's best... takoyaki!
Honmaru, not so fast!
My share will be gone, too!
Matsu-san!
Another box of takoyaki!
Sure, coming.
Hey, Taru!
Don't eat with your hands!
Matsu-san!
Takoyaki!
Sure, coming.
Taru...
Matsu-san!
Another box!
Aight, coming.
A giant takoyaki right there!
Now's my chance!
Crap... There goes my month's allowance.
Ah! Was yummy!
Taru! Mind you, I haven't eaten
even a boxful of those "yumster" takoyaki!
Sorry!
Oh? Honmaru-kun and Taru-chan?
Oaya-sensei?
I see, it's about takoyaki?
Is it really that delicious?
Yeah! Unworldly delicious!
Then, how about we get some
to eat them together as friends?
You wish to try them, too? That's a win!
Hey, partner!
Can we have three servings, please?
Aye! Be it three servings, or thirty servings,
I'll fix it for you in a blink of an eye!
Huh?
Please eat, while it's still hot!
Fabulous!
More takoyaki, takoyaki, takoyaki...
Excuse me, how much do I owe you?
This one's on the house.
Service, right? Service.
This doesn't feel right...
Don't worry, those were leftovers anyway...
On the house, I say!
They're really good...
Aight, aight?
I got more!
Thank you! I'm full already!
You can come anytime.
I'll always have plenty more for you!
Aye. Aye. Aye!
Say, pal, whatcha this lass happens to be to ya?
C'mon, spill it! The one I gave service to!
Boss!
C'mere for a sec.
Matsu-san!
This ain't no kids business!
You absolute moron! You're being excessively generous again!
Even if it's leftovers, you don't just let anyone eat it!
We can't afford keepin' softies like you!
Matsu-san!
Don't die, Matsu-san...
Sorry. It's because of us...
Don't mention it.
Boss is just habitually grumpy.
Now then, I've got a business to run.
That woman is our homeroom teacher.
Her name is Oaya Mari.
Mari-sensei, then?
A fine name for a lass...
I'm off!
Hurry up, Taru!
We're late again!
Okay!
What is it now, Taru?
Smell of Matsu-san's takoyaki!
Matsu-san opens his stall that early in the morning?
Oaya-sensei!
Good morning!
Yes, good morning.
Matsu-san!
Business goin'?
Doing' a buck here 'n there.
It seems takoyaki is growing on you as well, Sensei.
Well, they were so irresistibly delicious yesterday.
I just couldn't get my mind off it, so I went here to see
if Matsugoro-san's shop was open.
And then, before I knew it, I started crunching on them.
'Tis an honor...
My decision to wait here paid off in plenty...
No denying it - Matsugoro-san's takoyaki is delightful.
Matsu-san is totally crunching on Oaya-sensei himself.
Just look at how he's flushing to the tip of his nose!
Thanks for the meal.
Also, Honmaru-kun, you should quit buying snacks on your way to school.
Tsk! Talk about hypocrisy,
teaching others not to after eating 'em herself!
Right, Matsu-san?
Mari-sensei...
Honmaru! Say, if it ain't spring already?
It's still winter!
I swear, what's gotten into you, Matsu-san?
Tsk. Not like I expected any answer.
Come on, Taru. If we don't hurry, we'll be late again.
Okay!
What a lucky bunch.
You'll get to spend this whole day with Mari-sensei...
Now then,
can anyone solve this problem for us?
YEEEEEEES!
Yes, Sensei!
Matsu-san!
Matsugoro-san?
But we're on the third floor now.
How did you climb up here?
Ya see, I used to work as a steeplejack
before running the takoyaki shop.
I just followed your water pipe to climb,
so please never mind it!
You know that man?
Yeah! Takoyaki cook Matsu-san!
He's making Japan's best takoyaki.
Naniwa of the Matsugoro clan. Fifth dan in karate
and speaking the thickest Osaka dialect, a jolly funny fella!
Naniwa of the Matsugoro clan?
Matsugoro-san, you see, at the moment...
Mari-sensei, I got a favor!
Please lemme attend your classes, too!
But still...
I beg ya!
For the first and last time!
Very well.
I guess, when duty calls, there's nothing a teacher can't do.
Let's all make sure Matsugoro-san
receives the best possible education.
Much obliged, Sensei!
She's also not taking her teacher's job lightly!
Oh, I just keep falling even more madly in love!
Well then, Naniwa-kun.
Why don't you get to the blackboard and try solving it?
Yes!
Lookin' good, Matsu-san!
I won 'em over.
That's my Mari-sensei, after all.
Ain't no way she'd be easily impressed.
Very well, then. 'Cus I ain't slowing down
in demonstrating my great gutsy to everyone!
Now! Let's-a crack this bad boy!
You managed it so well, Matsugoro-san!
O-o-obliged...
Eh-whaaa? Why's it so difficult?
Are these fellas really in elementary school?
No clue. Not a measly bloody hint!
I'm one hundred percent in deep
with this life-or-death ordeal!
Busted! Ain't nothing but guessing can do.
And my guess would be...
Ya'd better be correct!
Answer
Whatcha say?
Like my answer, y’all?
Whatcha mean?
Y'all don't mean to say
ya got any answer that's better than mine?
Say it, then!
34!
Ain't no way...
Sensei, and your answer would be..?
What if my number is still closer?
34.
Elementary school kids could solve it and I couldn't!
With this, the ultimate humiliation
is brought upon the whole Matsugoro clan!
Naniwa-kun, this problem is simple...
I am... I am...
Naniwa, the absolute moron!
Matsu-san! Don't do anything rash!
Matsu-san...
Matsu-san.
Matsu-san?
Matsu-san!
What is it, Honmaru?
Want something of me?
Are you quite alright, Matsu-san?
We asked for some takoyaki like half an hour ago.
Quickly, give some! Some!
Just as I was so eager to get Matsu-san's yummiest takoyaki!
Yummiest!
Ye, thanks for your business...
Excuse me? The hell is this takoyaki?
Matsu-san! There's no guts to these takoyaki!
They're like snot!
Guts, you say?
This word has such a nostalgic ring to it...
Taru, we ought to come up with some way
to restore Matsu-san's reputation.
Yeah...
I know! Taru, hear this out.
You're getting it, Taru?
Yeah!
Matsu-san, need you to put these on.
What's this for?
Never mind it, never mind!
Those are a surefire way to restore your guts.
Here! Now it's Board Pen Magic-kun's turn to act.
Wrap this up quickly, Taru.
The teacher is already near!
Okay. Done!
Oh! With a face that rough, he outta do the job!
Let's hope he runs amok right away!
Honmaru! Teacher coming!
Alright...
Alright, almost here...
Do it now!
Taruru!
Oh, it's been ages since I could roam about on my own!
Today, my only mode is full throttle!
Eh? Who's there?
What's going on?!
You'd better not resist, Oaya-sensei!
My bike is suddenly moving on its own!
Alright, that's Matsu-san's surefire way for restoring honor -
by rescuing our teacher!
We need your help, Matsu-san!
Oaya-sensei is in big trouble!
Whatcha saying?!
It's Oaya-sensei's bike!
Her bike is moving on its own!
Our teacher is in danger, unless someone saves her!
She in what?
Sensei! I'm coming to your rescue already!
Attaway! Matsu-san will catch up with her in no time!
What's wrong with this bike?
Mari-sensei!
Matsugoro-san?
Mari-sensei! Gimme just a moment!
I'm here to save you!
Don't be absurd!
Matsugoro-san!
Witness Naniwa's great gutsy!
Tama-chan, show us how Matsu-san and teacher are doing.
Sure thing, Taru-chan.
Give me just a moment.
Lookin' good, Matsu-san!
Do youru-ru-ru best!
Say, Honmaru, what's coming after this?
It's a little wonder!
Matsu-san successfully saves our teacher!
I've come to your rescue!
How's that?!
Bike only got more excited.
How do you think Matsu-san will save teacher?
I didn't think it through that far...
Honmaru.
The canal's this way!
But the bridge is still disassembled!
Naniwa stops at damn nothing...
to save our Sensei!
Ain't you safe, Mari-sensei?
Matsugoro-san...
Thank you, Matsugoro-san...
Truly, I'm so grateful.
Don't ya even mention it.
I'd do that for ya anytime, y'know...
But please...
As soon as your traumas are better,
make sure to come to class again, will you?
That ended well, Taru.
Yeah.
Iyona! Don't lose! Keep trying! Keep trying!
Honmaru, Iyona's team is struggling.
We have to do something!
I know! Honmaru joins the game, too.
On Iyona's side!
What are you talking about, Taru? I'm a guy, remember?
They won't let me into the game.
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Iyona's Heated Battle.
Episode 29
Iyona's Heated Battle
I got this! We'll be fine.
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius