Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Despite being a complete ski layman,
I claimed solemnly before the whole class,
"My amazing skiills earned me
the nickname of Edojo Skimaru!" - like that.
I was putting on airs, really.
And yet, with Taruruuto's magic at my disposal,
I managed to live up to the legend
of being a skiing prodigy!
You got carried away
and carried us all the way to the Sea of Japan!
It's the sea, the sea!
Episode 21
Hot Springs Give Rise to Love Divination
Some amazing aptitude is hidden in everyone,
where you least expect it to be.
Today, I have personally discovered,
right here, in our school, we have a promising skiing genius!
Gosh, it's tiresome... Right, Taru?
On such occasions,
I like to gaze at Iyona-chan to kill time.
So cute, Iyona-chan...
Still an elementary school student,
he has all it takes to become a gold medalist already.
She turned to me, too!
So cute, Iyona-chan...
That would be Edojo Honmaru-kun!
Yes?
What's that?
The teacher's grinning so ominously...
I'm so sorry!
I didn't listen to the question!
Ha-ha-ha
You could at least try to listen carefully
when you're the one being praised here, Honmaru-kun.
And that's why you should appreciate it, too.
Honmaru-kun's skiing.
Was it really that breathtaking?
This whole Honmaru's skiing thing.
Even more than that!
Yo! Edojo Skimaru!
Honmaru, we did well!
Thank you, Taru.
If it weren't for your magic, I'd never become a hero!
He's such a hero now...
Hey, you alright there?
I'm the one supposed to be standing there,
basking in that hero's fame!
Damn you...
Well, it's true what they say:
being a hero sure is an invigorating experience!
Right, Taru?
Heeey!
Skimaru-sensei!
Skimaru-sensei, you should definitely
come play cards with us!
Pretty please, Honmaru-kun!
Oh, you guys are so insistent!
Then I guess I've no choice!
And that's how it was, Iyona-chan!
Say, Iyona-chan, won't you play cards with us, too?
Not happening. Iyona-chan and I have already planned
to do some love divination after this!
Love divination?
Rui-chan is famed
for having the most accurate divinations.
You just need a developed sixth sense.
Like I do, per se...
Then, Honmaru-kun, see you later.
Wee you bedder!
This seems like fun!
I go take a sneak peek at divination!
Me too!
I need to concentrate,
so nobody else is permitted into here!
But why...
Skimaru-sensei, we need to hurry!
Found one.
Passing one.
Diamond? Anybody got a diamond?
Iyona-chan...
If they're doing love divination,
maybe they're talking about the guys they like...
It's getting under my skin!
There's a veranda, right?
I know!
Secretly checking on Iyona-chan
from outside the window sounds like a solution.
Oh hey, gonna go to the toilet real quick! Okay?
Got it, toilet.
Jabao-san, this is the "Sevens" row.
I know, alright?
Stage one of operation -
complete success!
Phew, it's cold!
But I'm here on a mission!
Behind that window is Iyona-chan!
But it's also so damn high out here!
How come this tiny curb is all I have?
No, it doesn't matter!
Anything for Iyona-chan!
Off I go!
The door is wide open!
Hey, Korekiyo.
Yeah, yeah...
I swear...
Who in their right mind would leave it open?
Thought I'd die there.
No way I can pull off something like this.
I'm also freezing!
Jabao-san, still nothing?
Shut it, you!
I'm trying to think my next moves through!
Someone locked the door!
If I stay outside even a bit longer...
Hey! Hey!!
Jabao-san, still nothing?
Told you I'm thinking it through, you dimwit!
I can't get through...
Is this how I'll meet my end - on this veranda?
I know!
I can still count on Iyona-chan!
Alright... This time, I'll get firm footing first.
Damn it! How come a blizzard
also starts at a moment like this?!
Say, Iyona-chan,
what kind of divination are you looking for?
Well, I'm a little curious
about the man I'm going to marry, so...
OK! Now, if you just let me...
Hey...
Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle!
Bang
There's a snowman!
What? A snowman?
Are you quite sure?
More than sure! I've seen him with my own eyes,
outside the window!
He must be still somewhere around here!
Alright, he's not getting away!
Honmaru? What are you doing?
Help me please, Taruruuto...
Honmaru!
I'm sure we can still catch him.
Hey, snowman!
If you really are a man, show yourself now!
I was already sure that was the end of me.
You alright, Honmaru?
Rui-chan, are you sure your eyes
didn't play a trick on you?
This is bad!
They're coming back already!
Taruruuto! We can't let Iyona-chan see me here!
Right now, right here,
I need a magic for staying in this room!
I certainly shouldn't think so.
And I still remember seeing it so vividly!
I beg you, Taru!
Do something, anything to save me now!
Well, at least I cooled my head a bit.
Shall we resume with the divination, Iyona-chan?
Oh?
Did we have a cushion like that before?
Honmaru, this is Concushion Magic.
It turns anyone into a cushion.
Thank you!
Lucky!
You are, well and truly,
the Great Magician Taruruuto-sama!
Well, whatever.
Where were we...
Ijigawa...
I resume from where we left off, right?
Iyona-chan is sitting on Taru's cushion.
I'm so jealous, Taru!
Iyona-chan's future husband
would be really tall and hefty, it seems.
Are you sure?
I'm sure I'll have yet to grow
much taller than this!
Maybe I'll even grow tall enough
to become a basketball pro!
One and two, and three, and go!
Moreover, it seems, the guy would be mighty rich!
I'm sure, I'll have yet to discover a new oilfield!
I wonder who it'll be.
Maybe even Harako?
Oh no, Rui-chan, you're going too far...
Ain't no way it can be Harako!
'Cause it's me! Right here!
And also handsome.
So he is tall, with deep pockets and handsome!
Yeah!
And he is right here.
Well, from what I can tell,
he is not a boy from our class, that's for sure.
Ijigawa!
With this next card,
we'll find out what this guy's initials are.
I'm actually a bit scared to know...
Have no doubt, it's H for Honmaru.
All right, then I'm flipping!
Wait though. If it's E for Edojo,
that would be cool, too... Right?
Ready, Iyona-chan?
Bang~
Honmaru-kun?
No, I mean... divination!
Pero?
Honmaru, cheer up.
There's nothing to be cheerful about.
Hold up! Honmaru-kun!
What are you doing here, of all places?
No, that's not... well...
Actually, I know!
You hid in the room
so you could spy on later while we change!
Not like that! It's not like that at all!
Not a word of truth!
I can explain, Iyona-chan!
What is it, Honmaru?
I...
Finally realized it.
Be it after changing or after divination,
peeping is still peeping. An unworthy misdeed.
Not something a hero would do.
Honmaru...
I'll go ask Iyona-chan to forgive me once more.
Yeah! You can do it, Honmaru!
Iyona-chan.
I'm sorry about what happened.
I'm convinced that peeping into a girl's room
is something only the most unworthy man would do.
Honmaru-kun...
And yet, when I learned
you'd be doing a love divination...
I just couldn't help it.
It's alright.
But I turned your divination
into a hullabaloo!
Didn't I say it's fine?
Besides, I had already found out
who the man is that I'll be marrying.
I used to be constantly worried
about whether or not this person would love me back.
But now I feel so relieved and refreshed!
Iyona-chan...
Look! This starry sky is beautiful!
It really is!
Slither, slither. Almost there. Slither, slither.
Men              Oiwa Hot Springs           Women
Isn't that Harako?
What's cooking?
Harako want to get in the hot springs, too?
Who do you worms think you are?
I'm the son to the president
of the Harako Conglomerate.
Your kind is in no position
to address me in a manner that familiar!
"Harako-sama" is the only way
you can address me. "Harako-sama!"
Cretins!
Main Room Hot Springs
Pero~
We're the first ones here today!
Boy, I love me some good hot springs!
Honmaru!
Oh, really? Taru!
There, get this!
Oh, must be Jabao and the rest of the guys.
What a magnificent tub!
Come see this too, Iyona-chan!
Wait for me, I'm almost there!
Keep it down!
The water is clean!
True!
How did this happen?
I'm quite certain we entered the one
with "Men's side" on it!
It's that guy!
What else could he have been doing
in a place like that?
He must've switched around
the "Men's" and "Women's" signs!
Change!
Honmaru, this is disgraceful!
Oh, how the mighty have fallen -
from "hero" to "sicko" in a single slide!
Cr-r-r-rap...
Get this, Rui-chan!
Now you've done it!
Here!
Sorry, teacher!
Iyona and others having fun...
We go play all togetheruru!
Cretin! If we're found here,
we're bearing a "sicko" stigma for the rest of our days!
Pervert here!
Peeping after me again?
Honmaru-kun, you're disgusting!
How the mighty have fallen -
from "hero" to "sicko" in a single slide!
I went through fire and brimstone to become a skiing hero,
just to end up earning Iyona-chan's disgust?
Iyona-chan, Mari-sensei,
how about a more secluded corner?
Sure.
Sounds good.
Taruruuto! Use the Time-Freezing Magic now.
We can sneak away from the springs while time is frozen!
Okay!
So? What's wrong now?
Magic-kun is...
Right! Magic-kun is in the changing room!
We can't freeze time without Magic-kun!
They're almost here!
So much space!
Can even swim here, like in a pool!
True.
Ah, I'm gonna die.
There's no way out!
I only have enough air for a minute or two.
Iyona-chan will be disgusted,
and the teacher will tatter my butt when I'm found!
Ijigawa will tell everyone I'm a pervert!
Disso-so-solve!
What was that, just now?
What was what?
It was as though
I heard Taru-chan's voice just now.
But there's no one here.
Must be your imagination.
Huh? What just happened?
I'm in Iyona-chan's plain sight,
but she doesn't seem to notice!
Honmaru!
Taru! Did you make us invisible or something like that?
Wrong, wrong.
This - magic for dissolving into hot water.
So you turned us into liquid instead!
Iyona-chan! Whaddya thinking of?
The stars are beautiful tonight!
This magic is pleasant, too.
Makes whole body warm and nice.
That sure is one pleasant magic!
Actually...
This way, I can approach
without anyone finding out.
I can admire Iyona-chan's body all I want,
maybe even taste it here and there!
From hero to pervert in a single slide!
No, I'm still a hero!
Magic is a necessity,
not an excuse for becoming a pervert!
Abstaining from any illicit peeks at naked ladies,
this dignified man Honmaru
endured the temptation once more...
Taru, we'll have our leave now!
Taru, you idiot!
He lost it completely and mistook Oaya-sensei's breast
for his mama's breast once again!
The hot springs here are the most soothing.
Damn it, Taruruuto!
How can one ever be so self-absorbed?
I also...
I also crave to get a taste of Iyona-chan!
At times like this,
maintaining a hero profile is beside the point!
Even swimming is a big deal when you're in a hurry!
Come on! Ijigawa, you're in my goddamn way!
Heavenly sensation!
Ijigawa just barely grazed my Willy,
but it feels so great already!
I'm struggling to even imagine how much better it will get
after I get a proper taste of Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan!
Hey!
Huh? Taru's magic fizzled out already?
Crap!
Ten minutes ran out
while I was floundering my way here!
I'm so done!
My goddamn life is over!
Taruru!
Eh?
But it's...
While a liquid, I went to fetch
Magic-kun from changing room.
Then froze the time with it
and switched Honmaru places with Harako.
Taruru~
Taru!
I became a pervert in a single slide!
Wow, Honmaru!
Squirrels sure are cute!
They called it Primal Rage?
Who'd think our class
would decide to keep a squirrel as a pet!
But this guy has been feeling down lately.
I know! He should drink this!
Power-Upple Juice?
Alright, this way, not just the squirrel, but even Iyona-chan will surely cheer up!
Yeah!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Primal Rage Runs Amok.
Episode 22
Primal Rage Runs Amok
Watch out, Iyona-chan!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius