Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Iyona-chan...
Well, my feelings for Iyona-chan...
What are you doing?
If you don't hurry,
you'll be late for school.
Got it.
Iyona-chan...
Episode 2
Reaching out to Iyona
A pencil box...
The guy clearly has a freeloader's mindset.
Honmaru, so early in the morning!
Wait a bit, I gotta get ready.
It's good to be carefree, isn't it, Taruruuto?
What the matter, Honmaru?
Don't look much cheerful.
No, nothing in particular.
Honmaru, hiding some secret?
Don't have to. We friends!
It's nothing at all.
Never mind it. Never mind.
All right then, will just hear it myself.
Taruru!
This will let me hear.
What's this?
Taruru!
I LOVE Y💛NA-CHAN MORE THAN LIFE ITSELF!~
Heard it?
Behold, a Hearer.
It puts thoughts or anything inside your head into voice.
With this, I can hear
anything and whenever I want.
I love Iyona-chan! I love Iyona-chan!
Make it stop!
How come falling in love with someone
always brings such suffering?
What should I ever do about that feeling?
Honmaru, you suffer?
Alright...
I help deliver this message to Iyona.
Wait a minute!
Stop right there, Taruruuto!
I love Iyona-chan! I love...
No way I'll ever tell her anything directly!
Alright!
But I can compose a love letter!
Finished!
Taru?
Here it is. I'm gonna also put it in a cute envelope.
And give it to Iyona-chan! Attaway!
Upfront: I love Iyona-chan
Very-very-veeeery much! Honmaru.
To Iyona-chan♥
But how do I give it to her?
Iyona-chan...
She is beautiful. She is bright.
She is the pride of the class.
How should I pass it over to someone like that?
I should chuck it away like a man.
Here!
Honmaru is giving her a love letter!
But this way, everyone finds out at once.
Then, maybe in the shoe rack?
We can see!
We can see everything!
Crap... In the desk, then?
Look, it's Honmaru!
Trying to sneak a love letter in the desk!
A dead end!
How in the world should I solve it?!
How would you solve it,
Honmaru-kun?
The problem that I just picked from the book.
The answer is Regent Shotoku.
The answer is Regent Shotoku!
How come the answer to a division problem
is the Regent Shotoku?
You... Jabao!
Just how should I hand it over?
Honmaru!
Taruruuto?
Honmaru, did you give her letter?
How should I hand it over
without absolutely anyone noticing?
Honmaru, you let me handle this.
Board Pen Magic!
Honmaru, got the time?
There's one.
Taru!
What are you doing?
Honmaru, stop fidgeting.
But how can I when you're doing this? It tickles!
Done.
Taruru!
Taruruuto!
And what exactly did you do this for?
He frooze!
The birds too.
People too.
Water too.
The light too!
Everyone is frozen!
This way, no one would notice me
giving the love letter to Iyona-chan!
It's Jabao!
Let me return the favor!
The teacher's skirt slips into his hand.
Splendid! Just splendid!
Next is the physical education section.
Oh
The girls' changing room.
What do I do? No guy should ever enter
the girls' changing room...
No! I don't have a choice, do I?
Anything to pass over the love letter.
Pardon the intrusion...
Iyona-chan... Iyona-chan.
Good stuff!
Ijigawa!
What is that look?
Just for the record, I merely came here
to pass over a love letter.
I've no interest in your nude forms!
Alright!
Did it! Without batting an eye, Honmaru!
Hey, Taruruuto!
You really are The Great Magician! Hey!
Now, feel free to unfreeze everyone again.
Yo. Quit keeping silent already.
Can't play me.
Enough, you hear me?
Taruruuto, you hear me?
Hey...
Frozen...
Hey.
Hello?
Anyone?
Anyone here? Hey!
Anyone! Is there anyone not frozen? Anyone!
The time has stopped!
I'm the only one in the world still moving!
This can't be true!
"If you got a problem,
you should share it with me."
Teacher! Say something, please!
At least spank my butt with all your might,
like you usually do!
Teacher...
Why aren't you saying anything?
Out of the way!
What's the point of a love letter now?
There's no use in such things any longer!
If that's the way things are...
If that's the way...
Might as well look at the nude Iyona-chan!
What?
Unfrozen...
Whites!
Why is Honmaru-kun
in such a place?
Iyona-chan can speak...
Hurry up and beat up that molester!
Honmaru!
Honmaru, I forgot to say.
My magic wears off in ten minutes.
Should have told me that sooner.
Still, I regret nothing.
I'm just glad the world returned to normal.
Honmaru, you look happy now.
Then I'm happy, too!
After today, Iyona-chan is probably
not speaking to me ever again.
Of course she isn't!
Of course she won't...
She'll hate me till the end of times,
no two ways about it.
What's that?
Honmaru, cheer up!
Easy for you to say.
If only I knew your magic wears off after ten minutes
in the first place, all this... All that happened...
Honmaru is friend.
Enough already! It tickles!
Hey, Taruruuto!
Peck, peck, peck.
Taru!
What is your concept of a friend?
You find it amusing to be a distress-monger?
Is that a friend's thing to do?!
But I'm not. I saw it in the park today.
Everyone looked so happy.
I thought I'd cheer Honmaru up with it.
Taruruuto...
I see, you just tried your best to encourage me?
I'm already twice as cheerful!
Honmaru cheerful!
Honmaru,
are you really?
I really am.
Even getting dumped by a girl or two
is not something worth fretting over.
Are you saying the truth?
There are so many other girls in the world
I've yet to meet.
Taru!
WAAAAAH!
Scared the life out of me there!
Heart is jumping out, out! Now...
I don't believe you,
so I engraved your true feeling on a stamp.
But my heart!...
The heck you did this for, Taruruuto?
Paper.
Stamp.
Just as I thought, Honmaru.
You're still restless because of Iyona.
Honmaru is still in love with Iyona.
But this time, also as a bit of a pervert.
You there...
My heart is not some potato stamp!
Potato stamp! Potato stamp!
Give my heart back this instant!
Wait, Taruruuto!
Potato stamp!
Taruruuto!
I'm choking!
Just returned to its place.
What?
It really did.
I call this magic
"Waaah, you scared the life out of me!
My heart jumped clearly out of my chest,
so you cut it away into a potato stamp!"
Hey! So in the end,
it was all just to mock me, Taruruuto?
My magic is just starting to work.
What?
This magical figure
serves to attract Iyona to this room.
Don't try to lie your way out
when cornered!
Now you won't even answer anything,
yet expect me to believe you can do it?
Me the Great Magician.
I can't tell lies.
Just ask Tama-chan.
Fine, I'll ask once!
You! Show me what Iyona-chan is up to right now!
What a boor!
Honmaru, I told you before.
When asking favors from Tama-chan,
you do it in a polite and well-behaved tone.
Always Captivating Tama-chan,
please let us see.
Should have asked this way in the first place.
Honmaru, a friend of yours is at the door.
Coming!
Here, please make yourself at home.
Pardon my unexpected visit.
For some reason, I felt the urge to come.
Iyona-chan...
Is actually here!
Well, I guess you really managed it, Taruruuto!
My, what's gotten into him?
He's such a weird child...
Now, come on, let's go up.
If you excuse me.
Please, please. My place is a little unkempt,
but you're always welcome here.
This is the stairway.
Be careful when climbing it.
Iyona-chan is coming to my room!
Taruruuto's magic is a real deal, after all!
This here is my room!
Please.
If you excuse me.
Oh crap.
What is all this?
I can explain...
I should have guessed you were so corrupt!
Good bye.
Iyona-chan!
Imbecile! Thanks to your perverted potato stamp,
Iyona-chan was so mad she just ran out!
Potato stamp not to blame.
Honmaru being pervert to blame!
It's because Honmaru had perverted things in mind,
that my potato stamp ended up perverted.
This may be true as well.
I was also the one who asked you
to stop the time in the first place.
I'm sorry, Taruruuto.
Honmaru.
Don't lose heart, Honmaru.
Not all is lost yet.
Not with my magic.
Thanks. But we've had enough of magic.
I'll come up with something on my own.
Honmaru is cool.
I caused this mess myself,
I must fix it myself, somehow.
Iyona-chan!
Iyona-chan, wait!
Iyona-chan, I'm sorry.
I just want you to hear me out.
I've no need for listening to excuses.
Not excuses! You see, there's a funny story
about that potato stamp. The thing is...
My heart - Taruruuto made me "Wah, you scared
the life out of me!" - heart jumped out, so he cut it away...
How low of you!
Trying to shift the blame onto Taru-chan!
Here they are!
What is even wrong with you?
Imprinting your room with so many indecent...
pictures of Taru-chan?
I wonder what exactly
I'd been so mad about a moment ago.
Iyona-chan, but what about the potato stamp?
The potato stamp?
Huh?
Nevermind, nevermind.
Honmaru-kun! I'm so sorry
for being that rude, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
With magic, I rewrote Iyona's memory.
Honmaru, for friends
you spare no magic.
This will make the pain go away sooner.
You're so caring, after all.
Say, can I ask you just one thing?
Honmaru-kun, in the girls' changing room,
why did you touch me like that?
You remember things from that time?
Can't get it out of my mind.
The thing is, you see...
Honmaru-kun?
Well, this and that...
I had a love letter and...
Honmaru-kun!
Wah
Iyona-chan, you will never forgive me
for that as well!
Honmaru-kun, wait!
Honmaru's heart has become just a little purer today.
Taru?
Hey, what are you doing to my Iyona-chan?
What's the matter, Honmaru?
A very arrogant heir to a nuclear power corporation,
Harako Tsutomu, has taken Iyona-chan out for a drive against her will!
I have to do something, lest at this rate...
It'll be alright!
Leave this to me!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Dangerous Transfer Student.
Everyone, don't miss!
Episode 3
Dangerous Transfer Student
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
A study in .srt by Perevodildo
RAW by Renascent
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Yume