Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Taru!
Dad, mom! I'm home!
Welcome back, Honmaru.
Taruruuto!
I see! He must be taking an afternoon nap!
Let's go play outside, Taru!
Ah? He's not in the living room?
Not in his bedroom either.
Not even in Japanese room?
I know!
Taking a bath?
Hey, Taru!
There you are.
What was that just now...?!
Episode 14
Sister Ria Makes an Appearance
What did I just see?
Good afternoon.
Good afternoon!
I totally didn't mean to peep at you.
I'm really sorry!
I was just looking for Taruruuto.
You know, this fellow...
Speaking of which, who might you be, babe?
Eh? Limpy-kun?
Your punishment...
For peeping.
That's one intense punishment.
Wait though.
Oh, I see!
Taru!
Whew, you sure chose a sizzling hot lady to impersonate!
You even had my heart pounding there!
Too bad, but your pranks won't ever trick me!
Good job with those boobies!
They even feel like the real thing!
Alright! Let's see if there's any worth to those boobies
you like sucking so much.
Boobie suck...
Just don't overdrink.
Help me...
Were those boobies that good?
You broad!
You ain't no Taruruuto!
Who the hell are you?
Honmaru!
Taru, is that your friend?
Sister...
What? This woman is... Taru's sister?!
Bollocks!
Taru can't have a sister that pretty.
Do you have any idea
how long you've been playing in this world?
Taru.
Taru...
Mama is growing so worried.
What a truly...
naughty little rugrat!
Promise to behave?
Slam!
Come on, we're going home.
Honmaru, not returning our home!
Look, miss big sister.
Can't Taru stay where he is now
for just a little longer?
Not listening to what your big sister wants you to do?
Taru.
Big sis!
Big sis! Big sis!
Big sis!!
Taru! Taru! Taru! Taru!
Taruruuto's using his Repeller to counteract the pull
that his sister's exerting with her Attractor!
Big sis!
Taru!
Taruru!
Out of here!
Taru!
Sorry, are you taking Taruruuto home
even if through force?
As conventional wisdom has it,
a child should grow up with family, don't you think?
I guess...
I take it I can count on your help?
What are you staring at?
Come, we need to have a talk!
Just as I thought, Taru's big sister
is captivating every guy around.
No wonder even my heart is pounding!
When his sister asks for a favor, you enter this odd state,
when you just can't refuse her anything!
Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan?
What's the matter?
You look so panic-stricken.
Hey, what's up with you as well?
May I ask who that is?
Ah... Well... You see...
Taru's sister!
Good afternoon.
Pleased to meet you...
Let's go, Honmaru.
See you, Iyona-chan!
Honmaru-kun!
Doing good?
Why wouldn't I?
See you.
She's a good girl.
This is the place.
Takoyaki!
It's real Takoyaki!
Now, let's lie in ambush.
Okay...
You really expect him to get caught that easy?
Not even Taru can be that simpleminded.
He came.
Takoyaki!
Let's have a meal!
Now!
Taru won this one, admit it!
Think so?
Taruruuto!
You're coming home now!
Honmaru!
Honmaru-kun.
There is my family...
And there is Taru's family.
Taru! It's best that you grow up
with your own family!
Honmaru...
See?
Taru.
Even if our ways part,
we'll still be friends.
Honmaru...
Promise to write me letters!
Let's go.
Pinky swear, Honmaru!
Taru!
How could I say such a thing?
After all,
we have a mom and a dad in our house, too.
We can provide a family for Taru just fine!
But instead, he's taken away by an implacable sister!
Oh, how could I be that foolish?
But now, all's lost and we'll never meet again, Taruruuto!
Yes, that is very true!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
What's with that gloomy look?
You see, Taru has...
Honmaru, Taruruuto-kun's sister
is paying us a visit.
Sup, Honmaru!
I am The Great Magician Ria Kinakãmo.
And I am The Great-Great Magician Taruruuto-kun!
I meant to say,
I'm The Great-Great-Great Magician Ria...
And I'm Great-Great-Great-Great-Great-Great-Great Ma...
But sis, weren't you on your way
to the Magic Realm?
I figured I could also give this world a chance.
Meaning...
Please feel free to come play at our house
whenever you feel like it.
Taruruuto-kun must also be glad,
since he got to see his sister again.
Honmaru! Living together again!
Taru! I'm so glad!
So glad, I'll join, too!
Honmaru.
Honmaru!
Morning came! Wake up!
Honmaru sleepyhead!
Honmaru won't wake up.
Rousing Egg.
Cock-a-doodle-doo wakes anyone. Here.
Honmaru still not awake.
Then, one more will do.
Awake awake awake!
I'm awake, alright?
Honmaru finally awake!
Taru, quit waking me up for no good reason at all.
Don't you know it's Sunday?
Gimme a break!
Sorry. Keep sleeping then.
Damn right I will.
Honmaru sleeping.
Me together with Iyona go bowling.
That's right!
I was so tired this week, this one very important
promise to Iyona-chan almost slipped my mind!
Like that!
Let's do it, Taru.
Bowling with Iyona-chan!
Yeah!
Where are you off to?
Say, up to some fun, are you?
Say...
Sister, wanna go together?
Sounds good, going together.
Long as it doesn't bother you.
No, no, not in the slightest!
Now, now, let's be on our way.
On way, on way!
Both with Iyona-chan
and Taru's sister!
That's what I call playing on two lanes at once!
Bowling with everyone!
See those holes?
You put your fingers in, like that.
She's pretty... Taru-chan's sister.
And then?
To put it simply,
you send this ball rolling.
Aim at those 10 pins
and try to knock as many as you can.
Iyona...
Now, the form.
First, try to feel it.
Hold the ball like that.
Like that?
I Touched her boobies!
Iyona weird.
Hearer!
Like this!
What's going on?
Honmaru-kun is so absorbed in sucking up to her!
Flattened!
Do those two enjoy each other's
company for bowling that much?
Then I'll enjoy Taru-chan's company, too!
Huh?
No! You're getting it wrong, Iyona-chan!
What just happened?
I involuntarily let odd thoughts slip.
Taru...
Honmaru.
Iyona, why you mad at him?
But I'm not mad or something.
Not at all, Taru-chan!
That was close.
Say, why don't we split in two teams
for a competitive game?
Sister and Honmaru-kun's team
against my and Taru-chan's team.
Bring it on!
Honmaru-kun, would you kindly
mentor the big sister?
I knew you'd understand, Iyona-chan!
Don't need to ask me twice.
Sis!
Taru-chan, we'll make sure to have lots of fun.
Right, Taru-chan?
Everyone around smiling, and yet...
Something's off.
But we won't let them have all the fun to themselves, right?
Beating Taru should be a walk in the park, right?
Honmaru, is this fine by you?
What is?
What's that sudden smile, big sis?
Alright, Honmaru.
We need to beat them.
Sister, please trust me to do that for you!
Hold it like this.
Then send it rolling.
Alright!
I'm about to demonstrate my prowess
to both Iyona-chan and to Taru's sister!
None here plan to lose to sister or Honmaru, either!
Let's do out best, Taru-chan.
Good. This one's from me.
Speeding good...
Speeding good!..
Don't give up, my ball!
Looks like a gutter!
Gutter?
Iyona! I did amazing gutter throw!
Alas, gutter throw is 0 points.
Zero points...?
Taru doesn't know the first thing about bowling!
Now, it's your turn, sis!
Well, look closely.
Inflatable
Muscles!
She can inflate her own muscles
by just casting the spell once!
She really is Taru's big sis!
So? Was this about right?
Only "Amazing" would do it justice!
That's the way! That's the way!
Do your best, Iyona!
Okay...
There!
Perfect! Iyona knocked them all, too!
Same way she swept me off my feet,
she sweeps away all the pins!
It's Taru-chan's turn now.
I can try again?
Heard this, Honmaru?
Just gonna lose again.
Fine. This time, taking no chances.
Won't let go of ball till the end!..
Won't let go of ball till the end...
Taru-chan!
Taru!
Knocked all of them!
Taru-chan!
Taru, that was a foul.
Alright! What I get for a foul?
Zero points.
There!
It's a Strike!
Knocked them all again!
Looking good, Iyona! Love!
Taru-chan!
Iyona.
Oh, my!
Taru-chan so mischievous!
Iyona-chan's first kiss!!!
Iyona-chan's first kiss . . .
Huh?
A Seething Kettle.
You put it on top of an incensed person's head,
you get the water instantly boiled
and the person's head cooled down.
Care for a drink?
Thanks...
Yummy!
It's Honmaru-kun's turn.
Go ahead and throw it.
Sorry, Iyona-chan.
Huh? My body suddenly feels very light!
Alright. I'll do my best too,
and steal Taru's sister's first kiss!
Go!
Well done, Honmaru.
Got it, sis!
Just like Taru did, I'll go pe-e-e-eck~
Honmaru.
You alright, Honmaru-kun?
Sister, when you treated him to drink,
you used a Power-Upple Tea.
Me won't hold back either!
Sister used magic.
Then I use, too!
Help me, will you?
Just you watch!
Ball to pins!
Great, Taru-chan!
This one is bound to be a strike!
Yeah, a great curve!
Taru is in the gutter again!
Did that ball... just return back onto the lane?!
Told ya it's a gutter!
My, is that the definition of a great ball for you guys?
Shall I go next?
Sure, sure, this way.
Playing dirty, sister!
You drove if off course with TVkinesis!
Taru, try better.
Ball that sister threw.
Was that a hook bowl just now?
Alright, gonna knock all of them!
Taru-chan, where are you going?
Really wanna win that badly?
Won't let you use magic.
Know sister's weakness.
Pero!
Sister?
Now's our turn to win, friends!
That's it!
Knocked every single one!
Guess I lost, Taru. In this long time away from home,
you've grown to find your way around magic.
Sis!
You there! Are you those ruffians
that turned everyone's bowling lanes into a pandemonium?!
Doing bowling seems fun, right sis?
We'll come again.
Don't ever come here again!
Honmaru, I'll leave you alone with Iyona-chan now
to let you finish what you started.
Big sis, let's take a bath together,
first time in ages.
One thing that never changes
is how spoiled you are.
But say, Taru, aren't you glad
to have made such good friends?
Honmaru my friend!
Sister is friends with Honmaru, too!
I guess it fits my liking too, this world.
Crap! I forgot to do homework!
But if my teacher finds out, my butt is going under!
Taru, can't you do something with magic?
Honmaru, lying for cowards.
Easy for you to say.
I so much don't wanna go to school!
At least induce a cold or something!
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Cold Outbreak in Honmaru's Family.
Episode 15
Cold Outbreak in Honmaru's Family
Everyone, wear a face mask for next episode!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius