Taruruuto-kun
Magical★
Magi
cal★
Magica
l★
Taruruuto-kun
★
I love your licks more than anyone else's on my lips
A friendly magician is sending you his best regards
Always grinning wide
His head is very light
And with an appetite like his,
no takoyaki crumb can hide
Till forever "me, Taruruuto"
stays unshaken by you side as friend
With a breeze, "me, Taruruuto"
can do anything that you can't
Because the one true magic is me meeting you!
So we can now go play around together
and never feel the blue
Fired up "me, Taruruuto"
will remain your friend all the way through
"Leave it to me, Taruruuto"
I'm sure all our dreams come true
Because only after meeting you,
my smile truly broadens!
To stay forever with you, mayhaps...
Ahh, how do I...
Honmaru-kun, do you mind if I distract you
from your studies?
Wah!
Nah...
What's that?
No...
Nevermind it, Iyona-chan.
Tomorrow, we're holding a birthday party at my house.
Honmaru-kun, please come.
To Edojo Honmaru-kun
Birthday party invitation
23rd of November, at my house
Kawai Iyona
That true, Iyona-chan?
Lies.
...is what I'd say, if I were joking.
Make sure to show up, okay?
Sure.
Eh?
To Taruruuto-kun 🖤
My birthday is on 23rd of November
Come for a fun party at my house
Kawai Iyona
I made an invitation for Taru-chan, too.
Episode 13
Unruly Birthday Party
This screams danger.
Taruruuto tagging along means the magnificent party
for me and Iyona-chan will turn into a hullabaloo again.
I love Iyona-chan so much!
Poop-hat!
I'm screwed. A magnificent party for me and Iyona-chan
is bound to become a hullabaloo.
And besides...
Taru-chan's cute!
I'm only getting more and more screwed!
Too screwed.
Totally screwed! What do I do now?
Guess there's no choice.
For now, I should best turn my heart to stone,
so that tomorrow...
is safe from Taru's prying!
So sorry, Iyona-chan!
Although you went to such pains to invite him,
unfortunately, Taru ate too much takoyaki the day before
and now he is suffering a terrible belly bloat!
That's a no-way to show up at a party!
My genius for contriving compelling lies
is almost frightening.
As for Taru...
Honmaru!
Whats the matter?
Something cheered you up, Honmaru?
I guess you can say that...
Must be because of the weather!
Honmaru lies!
Tama-chan not letting lies slide!
But I have nothing to hide!
What are you up to? Hey...
Sneak Peek. Sneak Peek! Sneak Peek.
The heck?!
Tomorrow... Iyona's birthday party!
HONMARU!
Whaddya want?
Honmaru!
Me tag along!
Rub, rub.
Honmaru!
My bad.
There isn't a secret
H-Filters can't expose, after all.
My bad, Taruruuto.
Here you go.
There's an invitation for you as well.
For me too!
Go together with Honmaru!
Yeah, Taruruuto!
Honmaru, not sleeping yet?
Honmaru, sooner go to bed...
Ah, dozing off...
Taru!
You okay?
Taru... My bad, my bad.
Sweet dreams, Taru.
BIrthday Party Venue
Taru, Iyona-chan lives here.
Jabao and Korekiyo, too?!
Honmaru, Iyona-chan even invited scum like you?!
Look who's talking!
Came to attend our party
merely as part-time waiters, didn't you?
Suits you, actually.
Why, that...
He's on his way to outstrip us!
Ah... Ah! No way you'd come first!
Get lost, peasant!
What everyone doing?
Hurry up!
Thank you very much for coming.
I am Iyona's mother.
Kawai Ina.
Everyone! We got things to do here.
We can't just stand in awe all day.
Let's get full!
Not that!
Iyona-chan, best wishes for happy birthday!
I am Kawai Iyona.
Born in November, Sagittarius.
Blood type - B group.
Type of boy I like...
not tel-ling!
Best wishes from us!
Iyona-chan, accept the bestest of wishes!
Tarururuu!
On this delightful day,
one more candle
Is added to to the bunch
Just a bit of Champagne, just a bit of cake,
and a bit of smiling, too,
But also a bit of happy tears!
Taruru!
Made a bit of memories, too
Here, Iyona-chan. Made this myself.
And started hoping a bit more
Congratulations!
Sure is cute, this fellow.
He can even crunch a carrot.
I carved it out of North Pole's perpetual ice.
A captivating ice sculpture of Iyona-san as a present.
Well, in my mind, he looked rather more intimidating.
But I suppose he's not doing the greatest job as a monster...
I like him.
Thank you for such a great
hand-made present.
Iyona-chan...
Everyone's silently listening
to Iyona-chan playing the piano, Taru.
Hearing to hearable hearings with Hearer.
Finished.
BRAVO! Iyona-san, splendid!
This was Mozart, mind you.
What are they talking about?
That's quite plainly just a piano.
Right, Taru?
It's just a little something I wrote on my own.
But since I like Mozart so much,
I guess, I just ended up mimicking him.
Pardon my clumsy playing...
No, no. For something composed at home
and allegedly amateur-written, that sounded phenomenal.
Compost?
Mozart's works are divine, after all.
I can but to arrange them with some alterations.
Clearly, we're lucky to have this last five years' winner
of World Children Composing Concours here with us.
In my book, his gift is to be reckoned with
on the highest level.
I'd go as far as saying that this lovely melody is well and truly
the pinnacle of humanity's cultural advancement!
Don't you know, Harako-kun?
What makes Mozart so great
is that he hides "passion"
within the "beauty" of his works.
For me personally,
it's the Piano Concerto No. 21 in C major.
I'm amazed at the development
of the melody line in its Second Movement.
You're so knowledgeable! Impressive!
It's because Amadeus Mozart
is a peerless composer.
But isn't it extraordinary how my pastime preferences
align so well with Iyona-san's?
Ryoguchiya Korekiyo.
That's another sly bastard on my radar.
I'm quite fond of Mozart myself!
My, even Jabao-san?
How most unusual.
Talking cards, right?
Napoleon is a cool one, too.
But Mozart is the best, doncha think, Iyona-chan?
Good idea!
Let's do it!
Even Jabao is playing along now?
Everyone flips two cards per turn.
If you find matching cards, you flip again.
Whoever gets the most pairs wins!
That's Mozart for you!
Nothing is new under the sun. You managed to mistake it
for the Concentration game, somehow.
In France, they call it Mozart, don't they?
Yes.
Mozart, sir...
This is bad. I'm finally hanging out with Iyona-chan,
but I'm not standing out at all!
As luck would have it,
I'm also a Mozart ace!
Taru, lend me this.
Shall we start?
Well. Well...
"Mozart," isn't it, Iyona?
Alright, then...
Softy-softy.
Hey, Taru!
On Iyona's most beautiful dress,
I take my special seat here.
You're too heavy for Iyona-chan! Stop it!
That's right!
Isn't that right?
GET OUT!
It's okay, Honmaru-kun.
Taru-chan is pretty light. And because he's
such a cute little tot, I don't mind it. Not in the slightest!
Honmaru, I'm allowed!
Iyona...
That was unexpected!
Birthday present: peck!
My, Taru-chan is so inventive.
Thank you for the wonderful present.
I have a peck as a birthday present, too!
We came here to play Mozart, didn't we?!
Yes...
I know how to solve this, Iyona. Only the one
who wins in "Mozart" will earn your kiss as a prize.
But mother...
You are a daughter of the Kawai family.
Showing that much concern is a basic rule of hospitality.
Alright!
Not exactly some fancy cards, but in Pogs,
they call me the unstoppable Jabao.
I am Ryoguchiya Korekiyo
and that says enough.
With five consecutive World Children's
"Concentration" Championships under my belt,
I don't expect anyone
to pose a real threat for me.
But what do we do if I win?
Ah, whatever...
Honmaru!
You'll have the first turn of flipping.
Yeah!
Honmaru, do your best!
Cretin! He doesn't even realize the first turn
in "Concentration" is the most disadvantageous one!
Okay...
Sneak Peek.
What is it you're mumbling?
This matches...
This!
Look!
And this one!
This one!
Keep it up, Honmaru!
Splendid, Honmaru-kun!
Iyona-chan...
To tell you the truth,
I have always been a clairvoyant.
Wonderful result, Honmaru-kun.
Thisandthisandthisandthisandthisandthisandthis!
He flipped all of them...
From now on, I expect you
to call me The Last Cardbender.
Wondrous performance, Honmaru-kun!
I wonder if Iyona-chan
will award the victor in the lips...
Honmaru, those goggles look hella fishy!
Keep it to yourself!
Those are my special goggles for concentrating!
Give them!
The more the fishier!
Totally has some trick to it!
What do we have here?
Nothing's out of order.
Give them back now!
Not a single thing!
What did I tell you...?
Even if those goggles have a trick to it,
constructing a device that can see through cards
is a marvelous feat, Honmaru-kun.
Thank you, Iyona-chan's mama!
The way Honmaru-kun spectacularly flipped all the cards
was as though he peeked under them.
Yes!
As though I took a sneak peek under!
Oh no!
Sneak Peek's also the spell!
I remove a layer for each time
I mention sneak peeking!
Oh my lord!
Iyona? What about the kiss
promised to the winner?
Iyona-chan...
I'd have to kiss her while she looks so brazen!
Honmaru-kun...
What's worse, if I let the spell slip even one more time,
I'll end up peeking at a nude Iyona-chan! And then...
Just did...
What's up with Honmaru?
Are you alright, Honmaru-kun?
Honmaru-kun, hang on!
Honmaru-kun is weird.
It's great to be young...
Rendered unconscious from just the thought of getting kissed.
How most unexpectedly chaste of Honmaru.
I must be one authentic doofus.
I screwed everything up, after all.
Honmaru-kun.
Thank god, you're awake.
Iyona-chan?
Does this mean...
Does this mean you've been here this whole time?
Feeling better, Honmaru-kun?
No need, Iyona-chan...
I see!
Iyona-chan, I'm full of life again!
Not a trace of fainting!
There! See? See?
Honmaru-kun, a lovely new star just appeared.
Beautiful...
Certainly, all the stars popping up on this sky tonight
are here to wish Iyona-chan a happy birthday, too.
Honmaru, mood's perfect.
Thank you, Taru.
Honmaru, keep trying.
I'll be trying harder, too.
Taru-Taru-Taru!
What a beautiful shooting star!
Honmaru's there... with Iyona-chan!
The hell?!
They slipped out!
No way!
That should totally be me!
Honmaru, I'll keep trying my best for you
no matter what!
This starry sky can become infinitely beautiful,
but it's still nowhere near as dazzling as Iyona-chan!
Got you covered,
Honmaru.
Taruruuto! You've turned yourself into a hot lady today!
Making my heart pound!
Honmaru! Wrong, wrong!
'Tis my older sis!
The mysterious lady?
Taruruuto's big sis?
But why is she here?
Oh no...
Magical Taruruuto-kun:
Sister Ria Makes an Appearance.
Episode 14
Sister Ria Makes an Appearance
Honmaru, help me!
I wish to stay in this world!
Always sitting there, like a proper woman should
In a serious mood
My seat in the classroom is the one next to the window
I stare at the endless sky that had always been there
Soon enough, the dream grows its own wings
It leaps and breaks away!
Though it's personal, I'll tell you the truth
The thing I'm secretly striving for...
is to conquer the world!
I made up my mind,
I'm not playing around
My fancy flies off to unreachable, it's unbound!
Though it's private,
I'll speak up my mind
If there is something I truly want,
it's to conquer the world!
If I'm honest,
I speak my mind:
Being frank with yourself is paramount!
Raws by Renascent
Translation by Perevodildo
QC by MartyMcflies (LonelyChaser)
Translation checking by Aurelius