Come on!
My bike is perfect!
Keizou, what about Zenba?
He'll be here soon.
Get over here, Linda!
Alright! What's our course?
We takin' the usual route to Hakone's turnpike and back?
Haruma, you're riding
in my sidecar.
Get in already!
Look... He can slide his bike like that to turn it around.
Awesome!
It's like he's skating!
It really is awesome...
Yeah, Linda!
You're the greatest!
Keizou, blow them away!
That's right...
I used to sneak out all the time to watch this back when I was a kid.
But now I'm in the thick of it!
Alright, let's go!
Come on, come on!
Zenba, let me
ride sometime!
Write down your
favorite position...
and how much foreplay and afterplay you like.
H-Hey, what did you come back for?!
You're going to lose the race!
Don't you worry!
Those biker punks...
New Shounan Bombers
WILD NIGHT
Grim Reapers' Street Race
Listen up, Haruma.
So far, none of us
have ever beaten Zenba.
Kinda sucks, don't it?
But since you're on my bike, it's heavier than usual,
so hold on tight, you're in for a bumpy ride!
Wh-What are
you trying to say?
Let's go!
Hey, watch it!
I-It's not what you think, Zenba!
It wasn't me who bumped into you!
It was Noro!
Hey, watch it!
Zenba, it wasn't me!
Noro's the one driving!
Die! You bastard!
Stop it, seriously!
Seriously, someone's gonna die! Please, be careful!
Die, Norosuke!
Haruma, what's with you?
You're not lookin' too good.
That tanker trying to block us?
Bingo. Whenever I try to slip past 'em, he cuts me off.
Look the other lane is open.
It's not open! A car is headed straight for us!
It looks like a bike, but it's actually a car with a broken headlight!
Ah... You're right.
Zenba, you've let your guard down now that you're out of danger,
so I'm taking that slipstream!
Here I come! Here I come!
A-A toll gate?!
Zenba, stop!
My nerves are shot,
I think I'm gonna die!
Why's that?
Aren't you having fun?
Don't you worry.
I always get a bad feeling
right before I wipe out.
A bad feeling?
Yeah, and the funny thing is...
Let's say you feel like you're gonna run over an empty can in the next corner,
I get this kinda "oh shit" feeling,
but by the time I realize, it's usually too late.
It ain't worth a damn if it kicks in just before a turn.
Seriously!
The first time me and Hinako did it,
I had the same "oh shit" feeling.
But, hey, what happens
happens, I guess.
No way. That was Linda.
Are they completely nuts?
What? I thought that was the bullet train for a second there.
Damn it. How far ahead did Maki get anyway?
Zenba, to tell
you the truth...
I'm still a virgin!
I was kinda hoping to live a little longer.
If we wipe out, I'll be right there with you. You won't be alone then.
Hey! Why so slow, Maki?!
By my calculations, I should've stayed in the lead for another minute or two.
That's Zenba for you.
It's no good! Today's no good, Kurata! The crosswinds, they're—
Are you shittin' me?!
We'll show those beach boy bastards what the Demons are made of!
Come on, let's show 'em what we're made of!
I-It's Cobra! Cobra ambushed
us from behind!
Don't let them overtake us!
Kill 'em!
Eat this!
You thought you could come all the way out here? Huh?
You fucking shitsnakes!
You thought we'd be stuck behind shitty riders like you all day long?
Alright, bring it on!
You'll all be six-feet under before the cops even show up!
You really wanna mess
with us?! Huh?!
Out of my way, dipshits!
Yeah, that's right, shitbags!
Linda rules!
Damn it!
We let another one through!
Cobra? More like Slowbra!
You ain't got shit on us!
We were having a good time chasing after the boss,
but you bastards are blocking the middle of the road.
What was that?
Maki, you motherfucker!
K-Kill 'im!
L-Let's focus on Linda first!
Maki! Start with Maki!
Wow! Zenba, we're way out ahead!
They don't stand a chance!
So, don't you think it's time we slowed down a little?
Haruma, let's see what you're made of. I'm gonna open her up a little.
Cobra's boss should
still be up ahead.
That's him!
Zenba, we've found him!
About 50 meters ahead!
H-He's fast.
He's insanely fast, Zenba.
Then we'll go even faster!
I... can't breathe... Zenba.
Let's take a break.
I'm sorry, the wind is makin' it hard to breathe...
'Sup!
I was wondering what kinda idiot it would be.
If it ain't Linda's very
own Zenba Naito.
I thought something
smelled like shit,
so I knew you were around here somewhere, Ibu.
You never change,
eh, Zenba?
No matter how you see it, Cobra and Linda have been at it for ages.
But it's about time we found out who's the fastest on the coast road.
And who's got
the biggest balls.
How 'bout we
finally settle things?
Now you're talkin'!
Haruma, you're weighing me down, so hop on that one instead!
T-The fuck are you doing?!
Get off, damn it!
Get off!
Are you fuckin' kidding me?!
I don't take orders from you!
Here, take him back!
H-Hey, watch it!
It's on, Zenba!
Can you hear that, family-man punk biker boy?
Mind your own
damn business!
You middle-aged high schooler!
Credit where it's due, we both drive an RS Z2, so at least you've got taste.
But you lose on specs and guts.
I'll prove it so hard you're gonna choke on it!
Starting today, the undisputed star of the Hakkotsu Highway...
will be me, Ibu Koijirou, the third head of Cobra!
Pleasure to meet ya!
Zenba... for an idiot, your blocking is perfect.
You bastard! You got eyes in the back of your skull or what?!
And in crosswinds like this?! You've gotta be some kind of monster freak!
One fuck up and you're goin' straight to hell.
And I can't afford to lose this.
Zenba!
What is it?
Huh? Why's there a naked woman with a doll over there?
Are you serious?! Don't take your eyes off the road!
Zenba, eyes on
the road or we die!
Come on, bossman!
Snap out of it!
Why would a naked woman with a doll be wandering around the bypass at midnight?!
What an idiot! This race is as good as mine!
See ya! And maybe
die while you're at it!
So where's that
lady with the doll?
Z-Zenba, eyes on the road!
I'm Haruma Yuuki.
You'd better remember it.
For starters, full marks in guts! Other school stuff, not so hot.
And I'm a member of a gang I admire,
Linda, Winds of Cemetery!
And this is the apartment where the leader of Linda, Zenba, lives.
Good morning!
Zenba, hope you're well!
I've come to escort
you this morning!
Ah, Yuuki?
Good morning.
Good morning!
Have you recovered already?
Yeah, nothin' to worry about!
You shouldn't force yourself.
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
Good morning!
That's right.
That daddy is our leader.
Honey, he burped.
My, good boy!
Well then, Yuuki,
I'm counting on you.
No matter what happens, make sure he actually gets to work, okay?
Right...
Oh, it's not that.
It's not that I don't trust him, but it's just in case.
You got it! I, Haruma, will see to it personally!
He's all yours.
Sorry about this, but you know I did a real number on my bike the other night.
No problem. I'll drive
you around anytime.
You're a real stand-up guy, Haruma.
Didn't your brother go to school with my Hinako?
Sorry, but that was the only way I could join you guys.
But now that I'm part of Linda, I'm really stoked! I mean it!
Hi, Zenba!
Oh, hey there, kitty-cat!
What's up? You got any cash on you?
Wanna go grab a drink?
L-Leader, you need
to get to work!
I first saw Linda when I was back in middle school, and, well, I dunno, I just...
Hi, Zenba!
Heya! You got any cash on you?
Wanna go grab a drink?
Zenba!
So I decided that I'd do whatever it took to get into Linda.
So, where we goin'?
Hey, "Daddy!"
What about work?!
Wait a minute.
Is that your son, Zenba?
I'm training under the leader to become a real man!
Training, eh? Come to think of it, I'm just one short.
The first 98 were easy.
But since I hooked up and settled down with Hinako,
for some reason, I just can't score that last one.
Gimme a fuckin' break!
I'm only one off hitting 100!
Well, Zenba, all the more reason for us to take care of you!
Alright, you got it!
Haruma, lend me some money!
Wait a minute.
You're broke?
Uh? Yeah.
You can't even
pay the hotel fee?
I don't think so, mister!
What's even going through that head?
Wait... Wait a minute,
baby! Hey! Hey!
This guy...
He's only a year older than me,
he's got a babe for a wife and a kid...
but he's like an
animal in heat...
He really is somethin' else.
They're alike.
Are you sure, Chihiro?
So are his eyebrows thick?
No, I wouldn't say that.
Then, is he stupid, stubborn, and inflexible?
I wouldn't say that either...
What, really? In that case, you should be glad they're not like each other.
There aren't many
people like him.
If there were, everyone would be in trouble.
He even brags about his energy being his redeeming feature.
He's got a one-track mind and is totally oblivious.
Hey, Haruma, how are you?
Good. After all, I'm full of energy if nothing else.
Aihara.
You change your hair? Looks pretty good on you.
The nerve of that guy.
When I cut mine shorter, he didn't say a thing.
Hey, Koume,
let's give it our all.
Chihiro, you're the only one giving it your all here.
It's not like I've got anything to do with Haruma or anything.
I never would've thought that my first boyfriend would be the bad-boy type.
Yeah, I heard you already.
Still, they're so alike!
But you're not going out with him because he acts like Haruma, are you?
Haruma knows that guy called Zenba, doesn't he?
Yeah.
Didn't Haruma say he admired him?
That's how I feel
about my boyfriend.
Haruma...
Got a minute?
What is it?
He's in the year below.
Well, I'll be waiting outside.
Hey, what kind of
person is Zenba?
He's the best.
But then again, he's the leader,
so he's also the scariest.
Everyone around him is easier to read, though.
Like Noro, he swings
first and asks later.
No, he sounds scary!
I get a little
overwhelmed sometimes too.
I wonder what it would take for me to be like those guys.
So anyway,
my boyfriend...
Oh, shut up already,
not him again.
I'm sick of hearing
about him, you idiot.
He said he wants to meet Zenba.
What's stopping him?
Just tell him to join the team.
But isn't Zenba really scary?
He's the kindest
out of all of us.
You've gotta be kidding me.
Didn't you just say that
he was the scariest?
He's the kindest
and the scariest.
Then, is it difficult
to join the group?
He really is a lot like you,
I swear.
I'm sorry. I hope you didn't take that the wrong way.
No offense taken.
Really?
When I say I mean it,
I really mean it!
It's a no go, isn't it?
You don't have that
kind of pull yet.
I'm the closest thing he's got to a brother, and even I'm not part of the family.
Besides, you only got in by luck and connections anyway.
Even if he is similar,
it'll be even more difficult.
I hope you didn't take
that the wrong way.
Yeah, big time.
I've got my ultimate weapon!
I'm always full of energy, you idiot!
Our goal is to be like Zenba Naito!
Let's go!
One!
They local nutjobs or something?
Two!
You don't see men doing that nowadays, huh?
One!
That's true.
Two!
One!
You change your hair?
Yeah.
It's been rainy and humid lately, so it feels much better.
Does it suit me?
By the way, did you ask him about that thing?
About Linda.
Of course I asked him! You might just be able to meet him.
If you asked, they might even make you part of the team!
You idiot!
Since when did I want to do that?!
You thought I wanted to join Linda?!
You've gotta be kidding me!
You'd get me killed in a place like that!
But, Kacchan, you're always talking about how amazing Zenba is.
So I thought I was being considerate by asking Haruma about him...
Well, I guess you're right.
Chihiro, you're a woman, so you probably don't get it.
I guess you could call it my dream, so even if I don't end up like him,
if the bad crowds gave
me some respect,
it'd be nice to feel that, even if it all ended tomorrow.
That's why I live every
day covered in scars.
I don't really think I get it, but...
That part of you that gets carried away and gets into trouble...
It really is a lot like Haruma.
That's why I want him to lend me his Linda jacket for a while.
Please...
That jacket gives you
some serious status.
Just once I'd like to walk outside wearing that.
Then why don't you ask Haruma or Zenba for that jacket to their face?
Did you take that
the wrong way?
Of course not.
Thank god.
Chihiro, you like me, don't you?
If you really did, you'd quit fussing and go get it for me.
Why are you so hung up on it?
I need it.
Come on, Chihiro.
If I had that, I could get money or anything else I want.
And I've got a great idea in mind.
No, if you did that, you'd be—
What's that got to do with you?!
If your boyfriend asks for it, then just shut up and bring it!
Relax, I got this.
Don't worry, I'll make her do as I say.
Aihara? What are you doing out here?
Haruma?
What are you doing here?
The thing is... I...
I'm thinking of breaking up with my boyfriend.
Breaking up?
Yeah, or maybe just a break for a little while.
Things have been kinda rough lately.
I'm sorry. After I said how alike you two were.
What are you talking about?
You idiot.
I really did hope I'd run into you.
I think I've finally got the courage to tell him.
If it was your own decision,
then that's fine.
Just take better care of yourself, okay?
Haruma, the thing is, Kacchan...
He doesn't want to talk to you or your leader, he just wanted that jacket.
Your face is bright red!
You running a fever or something?
The leather is thick,
so it feels a little heavy.
But for me, it's heavy in a whole other way.
It'll keep you warm.
But isn't this really important to you?
Forget about it. You can take it in place of me walking you home.
There might be a race tonight,
but you can return it tomorrow.
Thank you!
Cheer up, Chihiro!
Don't go catching a cold!
Hey, Katsuhiko?
It's already fallen into our lap.
No, that's not it...
It's not for you! It's not!
Hello?
Chihiro?
What happened?
What should I do?
Koume, I...
Chihiro, what happened?
Kacchan and his friends...
I was so excited I tore up the pages
of my diary and now I cry alone
Took Haruma's jacket...
Yeah, he was only after the jacket from the start!
I'd rather be hated by him than
endure kindness that isn't love.
Haruma...
I'm sorry, guys...
I'm not worthy of Linda's name!
The cold tears falling on my small chest
are trembling in the moonlight.
What's your problem?!
Hey, lend us some money.
Who the fuck do
you think you are, huh?!
We're part of Linda, that's who.
Linda...
Hurry up and give us your money.
I-I'm in Cobra!
Ain't that just perfect?
Oh, God, take me somewhere
far away and hold me tight.
Linda!
Scared shitless or what?
What? Linda did?
What the hell is going on?
You bastard... What do you think you're doing with that?!
I don't care if you're Aihara's boyfriend or whatever!
But we're gonna settle this!
You motherfucker!
Come on!
Take him.
Noro was attacked by Cobra?
We taught them a lesson and then asked what happened.
But they said we're
the ones who started it.
The hell is that
supposed to mean?
Something doesn't sit right.
Oh well, what can we do?
You damn biker punks...
You're nothing but a nuisance!
Y-You motherfucker...
An idiot like you...
is just gonna get himself killed by the rest of Linda.
Maybe you should've kept quiet about the jacket.
Hey, you listenin' to me?!
Don't fuck with me,
you bastard...
You're one tough son of a bitch.
Idiot!
Y-You'll pay for this...
I swear it...
Why don't you just...
fuckin' die already!
Dumbass!
Let's go.
That was great.
They all went white as a sheet and forked over their money, huh?
We can make even more off 'em.
Yeah, but we should stick to guys that look shady.
If they haven't heard of Linda, it won't mean shit.
Don't freak out!
There's just the one guy!
Look how many of us there are! Get him! I said get him!
W-We're in shit now...
It's just one guy!
He's not alone!
P-Please forgive me... I'm sorry...
W-Wait, please!
Motherfucker...
You're a dead man!
Z-Zenba?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Before I make excuses,
hit me as much as you want!
I'm just dead weight to everyone.
I'll never be as cool as Maki...
Never be as tough as Noro...
I can't think on
my feet like Keizou...
And I'm nothing like you!
Don't lend it to someone that doesn't suit it.
Don't go collapsing
before I hear the story.
I used to pull that same stunt on
my seniors when I first joined Linda.
Even Noro once got into trouble when
he beat up one of our founding members.
And don't let Maki know I told you.
But he couldn't even ride a bicycle until middle school.
It's a bit tattered and there's some blood on it, but fix it up yourself.
Come on, we're going home.
What happened to your scooter?
I was in a hurry to get here, and I fell off and wrecked it.
I thought your energy was your saving grace.
So quit cryin' on me.
What the hell? You're getting in the way of our race!
Quit fucking with us.
We still haven't settled things with Linda.
You wanna settle it?
Well, ain't that just perfect, dumbass?
What was that, you bastard?
W-Wait! Wait just a minute!
That mess the other
day was all my fault.
It was my fault! So, I'll be the one dealing with you.
Hey! What're you scared of?! Let's get this over with already!
Wh-What's so funny?
Zenba, looks like you've got yourself another idiot.
What was that?
Alright, we'll settle this whole thing with a race!
Quit trying to act cool, you idiot.
Haruma!
Don't crash this time!
Think there's a boy like Haruma out there?
Hey, Chihiro.
Be honest with me. Don't you actually have a thing for Haruma?
Maybe.
come to a stop and yield at intersections
Just kidding. But you should've seen the look on your face.
What's with you?!
come to a stop and yield at intersections
A blue crescent moon, an emergency stairwell,
worn-out clothes, the sound of silence.
Tiptoeing forward,
I don't know where tomorrow will be but...
Rhythms we can't ride, an old manual,
our time is inversely proportional.
I feel like getting into a dangerous story,
like something from a twisted comic.
We're past the time of dreaming,
like naked DNA without a map.
A dropped earring, a fickle wind,
a streetlight gone out, a tall building.
At the tip of my outstretched fingers,
the one certain thing is the warmth of you.
We're past the time of dreaming,
like naked DNA without a map.
End of Chapter 2
@InkaSubs