Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
The person I most respect—
that is today’s theme.
Shakespeare, Churchill, Schweitzer—
history is full of such figures.
But I wish to speak of someone nearer,
someone far greater to me.
That person is my father.
My father is but a humble schoolmaster.
Yet he built a school for the blind.
In arts, mathematics, and even sports,
he drew out the hidden gifts of his pupils,
and strove with all his strength to show them
the joy of learning and the joy of living.
He has taught me how noble a calling
the profession of teacher truly is.
Hilary, congratulations
on winning the special prize!
Your speech outshone those of the fourth
and sixth forms many times over!
Thank you.
Hilary, you’ll help me
with homework later, won’t you?
Doris! That's sort of impudent, you know.
Not at all! Let’s work hard
in the prep room later.
Hurrah!
Top of the form in studies...
Gentle as the head girl of the class...
Truly, Hilary is our greatest pride.
Episode 19
Don’t Leave, Hilary!
What’s the matter?
Not sleepy?
I was thinking of Dad.
About your father?
When I leave St. Clare’s,
I should like to be a teacher, like him.
Ah! Hilary—a teacher?
Why, your father will be overjoyed!
I’ve not told him yet, not after what happened to my brother.
Your brother?
Two years ago, he died in an accident.
Jeff was outstanding,
the true pride of Father’s heart.
Father used to say every day:
“My school, my dream that I spent
my entire life creating, shall be Jeff’s to carry on.”
Without a doubt, Dad doted on him.
I scarcely recall him ever playing with me.
Since Jeff died, it was as if Dad’s dream
collapsed at once.
He was heartbroken.
And I, I could do nothing.
Hilary...
If there’s aught we can do,
jay say the word.
Thank you, twins.
Hilary, are you awake?
Yes.
Then go straight to the Headmistress.
Hilary, steel yourself and listen carefully.
Y-Yes?
A message came from your mother:
your father has collapsed.
Eh? Dad?
Hilary.
Mum!
How's dad?
Undergoing surgery.
Il y a quatre saisons dans l'année: le printemps,
l'été, l'automne et l'hiver.
What's the matter with you all?
Forgive us, we're too worried
for Hilary’s father.
As well you might.
I wonder how Hilary feels right about now.
He’ll pull through.
Won't you agree, Mam'zelle?
Let’s dismiss lessons for today.
There are times when friendship and a human life
matter more than any study.
Let us pray, with all our hearts.
Girls, I heard from Hilary just now.
How is he?
The operation was a success.
Her father’s life is saved!
Thank God! He was saved!
I'm so happy for Hilary!
Our prayers have been answered.
Jeff, where are you?
Jeff... Where is my Jeff?
Father...
The doctor says he is making
a miraculous recovery.
Ah! Thank Heaven!
Hilary.
Mother, what is it?
Since the start of this year, you know
your father’s school has been struggling.
Y-Yes…
One cannot charge the blind
a great deal of money.
That was your father’s principle.
Your father has at last had
to give up the school.
Eh?!
Hilary...
We can no longer pay your tuition fees.
You will have to leave your school.
Eh? Hilary...
is leaving St. Clare’s?
That can’t be true!
No, I’m afraid it’s confirmed.
O-Oh no...
Just now, her mother called…
Ah, Hilary...
Headmistress!
Please,
do something for Hilary.
We’ve all leaned on Hilary in our hearts.
She’s not only a good learner;
she’s calm and kind...
and always thinking of helping her friends before herself!
If it’s money that’s needed,
please grant Hilary a scholarship.
I’m sorry.
The rules say only the students who've reached at least the third form are eligible for a scholarship.
So Hilary cannot receive one?
Must she really go, then?
Headmistress!
Enough, girls.
Lessons are about to begin.
Back to your classroom at once.
That's right!
Hilary said she wanted
to become a teacher herself,
so surely St. Clare's could lend her
an advance payment​?
Did you really both
come up with the same idea?
Still, all things considered, it's a big stretch...
It's possible!
Isn't it, Headmistress?
Isabel, Patricia, financial matters
are not for you children to solve;
these are problems of the grown-up world.
Now, run along to your lessons.
How cold-hearted of Headmistress!
I thought better of her.
But perhaps, for once, it's truly beyond
what we children can do?
That can't be! We've overcome so much
by friendship and teamwork before.
Then we shall now as well!
I know!
Hey, Pat, Isabel, you two
might just be the ones who can help.
Eh?
Your father is a solicitor, isn't he?
Perhaps he can help Hilary’s father stay afloat?
Certainly! Your father got to work at once.
Really, Mum?
Hilary's father is a distinguished educator.
So he's going to explore whether some emergency funds could be raised by legal means.
I don’t know if it will succeed yet,
but I’ll do whatever I can.
Thank you, Father!
Hurrah!
For once, I feel obliged to join this plea.
A pupil brimming with appetite for learning
must be protected come what may.
That is the duty of us who teach.
Headmistress, might there be some way?
Ah... The twins' idea had some merit indeed.
If only we could advance her salary
as a future teacher…
I know not what can be done,
but we will try every avenue.
As you say, pure-hearted children
are powerless against
the large machinery of society.
To shelter such children
is our obligation as grown-ups.
Hallo, Hilary?
Whatever comes, we are on your side.
Thank you.
And if ever you feel
you cannot go on, think of us.
I will.
Please don’t feel ashamed
that you can’t come to school any more.
Your father has done
the most wonderful work for the blind.
Okay.
When we have a vacation,
we’ll come to see him too.
Do come back to visit us at St. Clare’s.
Promise us!
Thank you.
Thank you all.
The Twins at St. Clare's
I tried only to hold fast to what I believed in.
And yet my dream is over now.
Ah, Jeff...
If only he were still here…
Come on, dear.
Get yourself together.
Think of the future rather than the past.
Consider how we can overcome this trouble.
Dear...
You're right. Forgive me.
We must keep our spirits up,
for Hilary’s sake.
I have suffered enough;
you all need not do so too.
Hilary.
Father, should you be getting up yet?
Yes, I am all right.
That's a relief.
You mustn’t fret about me.
You're a girl, after all.
And you shall be happy, that I vow.
So, did the doctor say how he is?
If he remains a fortnight in hospital,
he should make a good recovery.
That is a comfort.
But losing the school
has weighed upon him most of all.
Please, Miss Roberts, do not tell my father
that I must leave St. Clare’s.
He blames himself for everything.
I cannot bear to wound his pride further.
Very well.
When they're on vacation,
Pat and the others will come here.
I shall let him know of that.
We're home!
Welcome back.
Mum!
Thank you!
We're grateful—to you and Dad,
from the bottom of our hearts!
What is it with you two?
Because of what happened to Hilary,
we’ve realised how blessed we truly are.
We used to take going to school for granted.
We never considered that we owed being able to study at St. Clare’s to our parents.
From now on...
we shall cherish every day at St. Clare’s!
It's our last hope.
If your Father can help Hilary,
we shall learn the result today.
Welcome home!
I’m back.
Dad...
How did it go?
I did everything in my power.
Th-Then, what of Hilary...
How... How can such a cruel thing happen?
Our Hilary should have
to leave school—how dreadful!
So cruel!
God is too cruel.
Listen, Pat, Isabel,
many things befall folk in life.
One may strive hard,
but trials and pain will come all the same.
Yet the word “hope” never dies
from the human heart.
Hope?
You two, do endeavour
to kindle the flame of hope in Hilary’s heart.
Okay...
Hilary!
Ah! So you came?
Even if you are absent from our classroom,
and in another city...
you shall always be
our head girl in our hearts.
Thank you.
Hilary!
We've missed you!
These are get well soon gifts!
And from me!
Cookies from me!
Just like Joan.
Thank you...
Girls...
If only a dunce like me
could leave school in Hilary’s place...
Why must Hilary be the one to leave St. Clare’s?
Hush! You mustn’t say such things!
Hilary is leaving St. Clare’s?
Father!
Wait!
Hilary!
Oh dear, what shall we do?
Is something wrong?
Ah! Headmistress!
It’s dreadful! Hilary’s father...
Dear...
Mum! Where's Dad?
I don’t want it...
Father!
Father... Father, don’t be upset!
Even if I leave St. Clare’s,
I’ll still have Pat and Isabel and all the others.
And I’ll still be able to go on
studying as hard as I can.
It is my fault.
I poured my whole heart into my work,
without much care for anything else...
I have left my dearest daughter with nothing.
Dear...
I could do nothing for you.
No! That is not true.
You have left me something—
a wonderful way of living, in my heart.
Please, let me say what I truly feel.
I’ve kept it back all this time.
Hilary...
Since I was small, you only ever
spoke of your dreams to Jeff.
Because I was a girl, you told me nothing
of your work or your school.
I was so dreadfully lonely.
No matter how hard I tried to talk, you always looked so busy and showed me only your back.
But I loved your back, Father.
For I saw how hard you worked, pouring the light
of hope upon the people who can't see on their own.
Your back was strong and broad,
and so I always thought—
I want to be a teacher like you.
Father, I want to carry on your dream.
I’ll take up Jeff’s books in his place.
Hilary...
I always thought you were still a little girl...
I was blind to everything—
both how lonely you were,
and how strong
and grown-up you had become.
Hilary, you will one day be able
to rebuild your father’s school.
You shall be a fine teacher.
Until then, St. Clare’s will guide and nurture you.
Eh?
Headmistress,
what do you mean?
Today I gained the approval
of the board of governors.
For any girl who wishes to be a teacher,
St. Clare’s will provide a special scholarship.
Such special scholarships only exist in a few selected schools, and in a very small number.
At St. Clare’s, it was once proposed
in the former headmistress’s time,
but the board vetoed it
and it came to nothing.
But today, our Headmistress overcame
their strong resistance with her splendid spirit!
Well, Hilary Wentworth, what say you?
If you are firmly resolved to become a teacher,
and your parents give their consent,
then you may go on
with your studies at St. Clare’s.
As for repayment, when you are a teacher,
you may return the sum little by little each month.
Thank you.
I shall repay this kindness one day,
by becoming a fine teacher
and rebuilding Father’s school,
together with Father and Mother.
Dear, we can achieve anything
if we put our strength together.
For your dream is our dream too.
Yes...
Thank you, everyone! Thank you!
Pat, Isabel, it is all thanks to you two.
Eh?
Had you not come out
with that outlandish idea,
I should never have thought
of that special scholarship.
Outlandish idea?
Why, that Hilary might borrow
against her future teacher’s salary.
Ah!
You two have lit a flame of hope
in Hilary’s family’s future.
Splendid, both of you.
Indeed, indeed.
My, what’s the matter?
You’d usually be rushing about
like a rocket telling everyone.
Well...
It wasn’t our doing at all.
Eh?
It was Hilary who was splendid.
And everyone else besides her.
Oho, listen to that!
Putting on such airs!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Did you hear, Isabel?
To celebrate the opening of the new pool,
there’s to be a grand relay between the forms.
And our anchor in the first form
will be Miss Roberts, our form mistress.
They say Miss Roberts is a splendid swimmer.
But the fifth form
have some strong opponents.
Belinda, Pamela—and Miss Lewis too.
A powerful line-up!
We shan’t lose!
We’ll fight for the championship!
Yeah!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
“Bonjour in Bathing Suits.”
Episode 20
Bonjour in Bathing Suits
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End