Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
We're twins. The younger one is Pat.
The older one is Isabel.
Our parents plotted to transfer us
from our beloved Redroofs School
to St. Clare's School.
We put up as much of a fight as we could,
but it was no use.
So eventually, we resigned ourselves to it.
Our homeroom teacher, Miss Roberts,
is quite a stylish lady.
Matron is very scary!
And it seems the headmistress is veiling
her kindness with strictness.
Now that we're here,
we'll have to give it our all.
Episode 2
Look at my Lacrosse!
Good morning!
Morning!
So it begins.
Yes, it's now or never.
Don't forget last night's vow.
How could I?
This school building is not bad either.
The breakfast is decent as well.
The dinner yesterday was up there too.
True.
Remember our vow last night?
Put the athletic and academic abilities of the O'Sullivan twins on display to blow everyone away.
Unleash a twin shock on St. Clare's.
This isn't a drill anymore.
Yes, this time, it's for real.
What's the matter, Patricia and Isabel?
Can't you solve this problem?
They never taught us this stuff back at Redroofs.
Shouldn't this come later in the curriculum?
Then it's obvious we can't solve
something we've never been taught!
They're so awfully behind!
Yeah, that's Redroofs for you.
Very well. However, you two
cannot rely on that excuse here.
To grow up to be dignified ladies,
you must learn to be more cooperative.
C-Cooperative?
This is St. Clare's School,
not Redroofs School.
Now that you’re part of this school, make sure you put in the effort to keep up with our curriculum.
If there’s something you don’t know, just ask your classmates. I’ll be glad to help anytime too.
Do you understand?
Yes!
Y-Yes!
What the heck!
Why did you say "Yes" so readily?
What's that?
Didn't you say it yourself too?
I only parroted you without thinking.
It sure shook me to the core.
Yeah, the standard of education here is pretty high.
Don't let your guard down!
But we need to rethink our strategy a bit.
Next period is gym class.
Just leave it all to your sis.
But we'll be playing lacrosse.
Isn't that just hockey in the air?
There's no sport that I can't handle.
Fair enough.
The honor of the O'Sullivan twins is on the line!
That looks doable.
We just have to do it, Isabel.
Isabel, pass to me!
Nice goal, Pat!
Is this really their first time playing?
No way! They're too good at it!
Belinda Towers is one really intimidating senior.
You should watch yourself around her.
Go for it, Pat!
Belinda Towers? She's a fifth former
and the captain of the lacrosse club.
Being intimidating is what she's famous for.
I doubt any underclassman
has ever escaped Belinda’s wrath.
Well, she can bring it on for all I care!
Even if she forbids you to go outside?
Huh?!
Wh-What's that about?
Aren’t we free to go outside whenever we like after school?
That's what you'd think.
But in reality, it's impossible without permission from our seniors.
No way!
Can we talk, Janet?
Yes, what is it?
Kay Longden, the fifth former, wants you.
You’re to light the stove and make some toast for her.
Okay.
Don't make her wait.
Janet!
Wait, Janet!
Why must you go help that arrogant person?
That's right!
I'd never agree to it if I were you.
How come you have to light
someone else's stove?
That's what maids are for.
If she doesn't have one,
Kay should do it herself!
Something tells me you're next in line.
Watch yourselves, our little twins.
Janet...
Hey, you two. You know seniors get their own study rooms for just one or two people, right?
There, they can drink tea and eat cakes,
and do whatever they want, freely.
All while the juniors are helping them out.
Juniors do what they're told to,
without objections.
That's the custom of our school.
Nobody here is complaining about it.
Once we become seniors,
we'll also be able to give orders to our juniors.
My parents didn't send me to this school
to cater to lazy seniors!
Why should we listen to their orders?
Geez, you're a fool, you know that?
Being obstinate like this all the time
will make you the public enemy of the school.
Yeah!
I hope you get an order from Belinda.
When Belinda calls, she’ll keep piling errands on you without end.
The worst people are those who think they are somebodies, like you two,
when so often they are just nobodies.
If my parents heard of it,
they'd probably tell me to stay away from you.
What was that?!
Humph!
Come off your high horse, Sheila.
The twins aren’t that bad.
Of course we aren't!
Ah... I'm sure they'd be getting along with everyone just fine if someone knocked them down a peg.
We should give them a chance.
Oh, I'm mad now!
I need to blow off some steam.
Got it.
One more!
Have you received a letter from them?
No, not yet.
I did ask them to write,
but it hasn’t even been a week yet.
Right... They must have enough
to worry about as it is.
That's right.
Either way, I'm sure those two are doing just fine.
It’s the third day since we came to St. Clare’s.
So far, the customs of this school
have given Pat and me nothing but shocks.
Hey, Pat, do you think the seniors are going to call on us too one day?
Even if they do, we can just feign ignorance.
Right...
Um, has anyone seen the O'Sullivan twins?
We're here.
Belinda Towers wants one of you
to come to her room.
Huh?!
Pat!
So it begins.
What for?
How would I know?
But Belinda’s been out on the field all afternoon,
so she probably wants a shoe-cleaning.
Either way, you'd better hurry it up. Bye.
Are you not going?
You need to stop with this silly protest.
One of you should go
and find out what Belinda needs.
For your own good,
don't make Belinda wait.
If you make her come here, Pat...
No, it’s all of us who’ll catch her wrath, not just Pat.
Now, hurry up and go.
If you don't, she'll make a huge scene.
I'll go!
No way! It's beneath the O'Sullivan family
to clean other people's boots!
But if I just go and see what she needs...
That's right!
Either way, someone needs to go soon.
Maybe it's actually for something
completely different.
What's the matter?
Get going already!
Belinda has a very short temper.
You'll be in a world of trouble if you don't hurry.
All right. Isabel, let's go together.
Yes.
But we're only going there to ask what she needs.
Yeah.
Not to clean her boots or light her stove!
Yeah!
Knock, can’t you?
Barging like that into someone else's room!
And I should jolly well like to know
what took you so long!
Hold on, I only sent for one of you.
And now you just stand there speechless—
haven’t you a tongue between you?
I can't believe these girls, Pamela!
That's true.
Well, as you’ve both come,
you can both do a spot of work for me.
Light up that stove for us.
Put the kettle on to boil
and clean our boots.
We're going out to collect our prep,
and we need it done by the time we get back.
Well, let's go, Pamela.
Please hold on a minute!
We didn't come to St. Clare's
to babysit seniors!
Huh?
We refuse to clean your boots
or boil water for you!
I can’t believe my ears!
Where’d they dig up girls this full of themselves?
Well, here's a kicker, young ladies.
You can say goodbye
to going outside any time soon!
You got that?
No! We won't accept it!
Seniors or not,
you're in no position to forbid us that!
Are you hearing what I'm hearing, Pamela?
I've never heard an underclassman talk like that.
Not once in the history of St. Clare's!
This is going to be a huge problem!
A huge problem?
You can start by going to Winifred James,
the head-girl, and ask her to arbitrate for us!
We'll see how you sing then!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Hey, Pat, wouldn't it be better to just
do as they say and not escalate this any further?
You can't be serious!
I'm gonna fight my way through!
Come in.
W-We're this year's newcomers.
I'm Pat.
I'm Isabel.
I'm Winifred.
If you also had the same hairstyle,
it'd be impossible to tell you two apart.
You get this study room all to yourself?
Yes, that's correct.
Anyway, did you want something?
Y-Yes.
Belinda, the fifth former,
says we have to clean her boots,
light her stove, and boil her kettle—
and if we refuse, we’re banned from going outside.
How can that be acceptable?!
Did you really come to ask me about that?
Well, in this school, the juniors
are to wait on the seniors within reason.
Is that another custom of St. Clare's?
Since you know that, do as you're told
and help them with their errands.
You know what they say?
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
This is the way St. Clare's does it.
We don’t want to follow silly customs of that sort!
I think you should wait a little while
before calling our customs silly.
Can’t you girls clean boots?
Don’t you know how to light a stove?
Have you never put a kettle on to boil?
No. We never had to back at Redroofs.
Even if we were at home, I don’t think
we’d know how to clean muddy boots!
Why, that is just sad!
To think you don’t know
how to clean boots at your age!
All the more reason
why you should learn at once.
Go back to Belinda’s study
and try to do what she tells you.
Ugh...
I don't care if it means
not going to town once this whole term,
who'd want to clean Belinda's beastly dirty boots?!
That's true, but I did want
to get a new set of hairgrips...
Well, of course I wanna go to the town too!
If so, haven't we resisted enough?
If we just suck it up now and help Belinda...
Then feel free to do it on your own!
Isabel, I'm definitely not going to do anything for them!
Oh... Pat, you stick in the mud...
What's wrong, Pat?
Is something troubling you?
No, not at all.
Good.
Miss Matron...
What is it?
I'm Isabel, not Pat.
Oh, my bad, then.
You two are so awfully alike!
Well, Isabel, see you later.
Yes, that's a great plan!
Excuse me?
They left already?
Now how do I clean these?
Would you like a bit of help?
Kathleen!
First, scrap them and get all the clay off.
Like this, see?
Next you rinse them with water.
Okay, now to light the stove
and put the kettle on to boil.
I'll start the fire,
meanwhile you fill the kettle.
Thanks!
Kathleen, I'm really grateful—
you're a lifesaver!
Oh no...
I'm just glad I could help.
It was fun today.
Yeah.
Even though you got lost.
Right, sorry.
Oh my, Isabel?
So you decided to be sensible, I see.
But where’s your twin?
She didn't help, did she?
Then tell her that there’ll be no going
down to town for her!
I won’t have new girls
behaving as if they own the place!
Word-for-word!
Y-Yes!
Is the kettle boiling yet?
My goodness, it's still cold!
I’ve only put it on just now.
It didn’t occur to you to put the kettle on first,
before you did the boots?
How is something like that not obvious to you?
I had a lot more common sense
when I was your age.
Well, you can clear out now. And see that you come running next time I send a message!
Y-Yes, I understand.
Isabel, one more thing.
Make sure you tell that obstinate
twin of yours what I said.
If she keeps disobeying us,
I’ll report her to the headmistress.
She can report me all she wants!
I know I did nothing wrong.
More importantly,
why did you obey that brute Belinda?
I thought it’d just be easier
to set everything right that way.
No way!
What do you mean set everything right?
I wasn't there with you,
so I still can't leave the campus.
I'm sure you can.
What makes you think so?
Just copy my hairstyle and you can pass for me.
I see, that's a good idea!
So, how about it?
It suits you well, Isabel.
Likewise, Pat.
All right, I'll show that Belinda.
Let's go, Isabel.
Yeah.
I absolutely love going out.
Don't you think its important to unwind every once in a while, Isabel?
Yeah, that's true.
I wonder what Pat
is doing in town right now.
We'll switch back tomorrow
and I'll go to town.
Patricia!
Patricia O'Sullivan?
Aren't you Patricia O'Sullivan?
Yes, that's me.
Belinda sent for you, come at once.
Belinda did?
I... I hope she doesn't see through it.
Patricia O'Sullivan.
Y-Yes!
You’re a silly, obstinate kid, but I’m not holding that against you where lacrosse is concerned.
I was watching the last few practices,
and I can't deny that you're good at lacrosse.
So I’m putting you down
for the match on Saturday.
As the captain of the team,
I have to leave my personal feelings out.
Pat!
Pat, hear this!
Hey, Pat!
Hey, come on now, what's all the rush?
Pat! Belinda's signed you up
for the next lacrosse match!
This upcoming Saturday!
What? She'd let me play in the match already?
That's right, Pat!
Pat...? But isn't she Isabel?
Pat, you did it!
Isabel...
If she was really as mean as we thought her to be,
she’d have left me out for months.
Belinda must actually be very forgiving.
Really, Pat, what is...
Pat, I know exactly what you're thinking!
I'm going to Belinda's study now!
What's the matter, Isabel?
I didn't send for you.
I'm Pat. It's about Saturday's game.
Pat? If you're just here to pull my leg...
No, it's true!
The one you talked to earlier was Isabel.
I was down in town,
pretending to be Isabel.
At first, I thought it was
a rather smart trick to pay you out.
But now I realize it was a sly
and cowardly thing to do.
And I feel embarrassed for resorting to it!
I’ve come to say thank you
for putting me in the match,
but of course, now that I've done this,
I don’t expect to actually play.
I was wrong.
I’ll take my share of the work with Isabel now,
no matter what kind of task it is.
Really, I was foolish, sly, and mean before.
I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
I have something to say too.
You’ve done something rather mean,
but you’ve been big enough to make it right.
Our opponent in Saturday's match is strong.
Do your best.
Belinda...
Indeed, you're full of yourself and stubborn,
so I want you to throw all
of that fighting spirit into lacrosse.
Lacrosse is the kind of sport
that requires that fighting spirit you have.
Okay!
That's it, Pat!
Nice shot!
Hooray!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
JmePenseBon
Next time
I'm Pat.
I'm Isabel.
I hate conjugating French verbs,
they’re such a pain in the neck!
Why must we learn French at all?
True! And our French teacher is so strict too!
Mam’zelle, huh?
"Ah, abominable!"
Exactly!
Hey, Isabel, let's call that teacher "Mam’zelle Abominable" from now on.
Yeah!
Next time on Twins of St. Clare's:
"Mam’zelle Abominable."
Episode 3
Mam’zelle Abominable
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End