Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Hey, let's go around the farm on our way back.
Yeah, sounds good!
Hey, sheep!
Kathleen!
Are you okay?
Ugh... I fell on my butt.
That sounds like gunshots.
Maybe someone's hunting?
Maybe they're shooting wild dogs?
Wild dogs?
The sheep should be lambing soon.
It’s a crucial time, so the farmers shoot any dogs that come near, lest they frighten the sheep.
Let's just hurry home.
Yeah.
Episode 10
Breaking the School Rules Together!
Is that a wild dog?
The farmer shot it by mistake!
See? It must still have a bullet in its leg.
Poor thing!
Hey, if we leave it here, it'll die, won't it?
We've got to take it
to the vet as soon as we can!
There's no vet in this area.
I'll heal it myself!
Huh? How?
I'll take it with me to the school.
Huh? To the school?
Why don't we try calling the police?
The owner might be looking for it.
Later.
Right now it needs its wounds seen to at once.
But you're not allowed
to bring pets to school!
So are you saying we leave it here to die?
Absolutely not!
It’s all right now.
We’ll have you mended in no time.
Aren't you tired?
I'll manage. More importantly,
where should we take it next?
The bicycle shed is frequented by a lot of people.
How about the gym storage shed?
That also has a lot of people
coming in and out.
Hey, how about the dorm closet?
Good idea! We'll be able
to check on it often enough in there, too.
I just hope none of the mistresses find it there...
So far so good.
How's the puppy?
It's fine.
What's fine?
Janet!
C'mon, don't scare us like that!
Oh! What's that, a dog?
It's injured.
I'll look after it until it recovers.
Janet, are you going to town now?
I was going to...
But I wanna help too!
No, you go to town and ask the police
if there's anyone looking for it.
Want me to go to the police?
Please!
We need your help!
Come on, please!
A-All right, all right.
I know Kathleen can quite lose herself
when it comes to animals.
Isabel, there's an old wooden box
in the storage shed. Could you bring it?
Sure.
We should be safe after making it this far.
This way...
No way!
Quick!
Huh? Oh, Pat?
Y-Yes!
Did you make that sound?
I thought I heard a dog's bark.
Huh? N-No, that was...
You're not hiding any cats here, are you?
N-No, none, madam.
What are you doing, Pat?
R-Right, I was tying my shoe...
What was that?
What was what?
I heard some whimper.
Sniff-sniff...
Pat?
Ah, I wonder if I caught a cold...
Goodness!
Looks like you don't have a fever.
There’s an epidemic raging, so do take care.
Okay.
Geez...
Ready? Hold it down real tight now.
Bear with it.
Just a little more.
Finally! I did it!
Thank god!
Don't let go yet!
I have to apply the medicine too.
Okay.
You're great at this, Kathleen!
I want to be a veterinarian when I grow up.
Good to know.
You're lucky that wound wasn't deep,
so you should recover in no time.
You did well bearing with it!
There, you can sleep undisturbed here.
Shouldn't we feed it at least something?
Better to do that after a nap.
My, it's starting to doze off already!
It’s been through so much today—
frightened and shot at, hurt and in pain.
Is this a terrier?
Yes, that's right.
But terriers are ten a penny
among themselves too.
The Medium Airedale Terrier is a police dog.
Small Scottish Terriers
and Yorkshire Terriers are lapdogs.
Bull Terriers, crossed with Bulldogs,
make excellent guard dogs.
Wow, you know so much about it!
Have you already started studying to be a vet?
Sort of.
I still haven’t the slightest idea
what I want to do in the future.
We should be more like you.
So what's this puppy?
Yorkshire Terrier.
As it matures, its fur grows
increasingly long and fluffy.
Ah, it's asleep already!
You're right!
It's adorable!
There's no one looking for a dog?
That's what they said.
What a relief!
Huh?
No, I just...
They asked the name and address of the person
who found it, so I gave them Kathleen's.
But if the police call the school,
the mistresses will find out at once!
But I couldn’t very well leave
without telling them that.
Ah, by the way, I bought this!
Dog food! Clever!
That gusto is amazing!
It seems it was really hungry, huh?
If it had developed such a strong appetite already,
that must mean its wound is healing up nicely.
Already?
Yes, dogs heal quickly.
Now, we must take it out for a walk
before going to sleep.
Huh? You mean outside?
It’s got to relieve itself somewhere.
Ah, I wonder if there's a shovel somewhere here.
We need to make sure to clean up after it...
Don't worry, I'll go look for it.
We don't have to worry
about being spotted out here.
Look how delighted it is!
Still, Isabel, this shovel
is way too big for what we need!
We’re not here to plough fields, you know.
I know, all right.
I'll try to find a smaller one later.
Shh! Someone's coming.
It's me!
Girls!
That's the one!
So cute!
You told them?
Isn't it best to let everyone know
about this sort of thing?
That's right! He belongs
to all of the first form now.
I told them you're only going to keep it
until its leg heals.
Th-Thanks...
But Hillary...
I protest it!
The school rules make it perfectly clear that you can’t bring pets to school, let alone keep them here!
Are you going to report it to the mistresses, then?
If we let it go now, its leg will worsen
and the puppy will die!
Is that what you want?!
I get it, all right.
But in return, if something happens to it,
you will all take responsibility.
The Twins at St. Clare's
A small announcement before we start the class.
A student was caught secretly keeping a bird
at St. Christopher's the other day,
and was consequently expelled.
I have no doubts in our own students,
but would still ask you to be careful.
Let us start the class now.
Do you think Miss Roberts knows already?
No way!
It's a coincidence.
But being expelled would really sting.
What are you, scared?
No...
But what are we gonna do if it's discovered?
Then you make absolutely sure
it never gets discovered. Got it?
Yeah.
What is that sound?
It's a dog! A dog is whimpering.
You hear it too, don't you?
Mam'zelle! You must be mistaken.
Mistaken?
There's no way there's a dog in the school!
Th-That's right!
There aren't any dogs here!
We can't hear a thing!
Yeah! I don't hear anything!
Quiet now! Silence!
I know there are no dogs at St. Clare's.
Only the kitchen cats to catch the mice.
Still...
Écoute!
Huh?
Ah, it must be something wrong
with my ears, then.
I have dogs barking
and whining in my head.
C’est sûrement!
Take down a dictée!
That was close.
The puppy must be feeling better today,
that's why it started barking out loud.
What are we gonna do?
What if we soundproof the room
by hanging blankets on the walls?
That's our Hillary!
One, two, three, four...
Exercising in a place like this?
Yes! To work up an appetite before dinner.
To work up an appetite?
Why don't you stop saying nonsense
and step away for a moment?
I need to leave this in the room.
Ah! Please let me put it away for you!
Huh?
More importantly, Matron,
I think our roof is leaking! Please take a look!
All clear. We got rid of her.
It seems its leg has already fully recovered.
True. That was fast!
I wonder if we'll be able to keep it forever.
I was just thinking that same thing too!
Me too.
Me too!
Ah, no...
I mean, you're responsible forever
for what you have tamed, but...
Our soundproofing worked so well too!
Only for now, okay?
Mam'zelle will have another class tomorrow.
And she has such good hearing...
Oh, I can't ever let it go!
The mistresses will hear you!
Quel jour sommes-nous?
On divise l'année en 12 mois.
Ce sont: janvier...
Oh?
mars, avril, mai, juin...
Get back here!
Hey! I said stop!
Somebody!
Headmistress! Catch that dog!
Dog?
G-Goodness me...
Get back!
What's going on here?
Quick! Somebody!
This is getting out of hand!
What's all that racket outside?
Q-Quiet, please!
What's the meaning of this?
Oh-la-la!
So when I heard a dog whimper the other day,
it wasn’t my ears after all? What a relief!
Kathleen, Isabel, Pat,
I believe you all owe us an explanation.
I'll be waiting in my room.
Of course we knew
you can't keep a dog at school.
But I simply couldn't bring myself to leave that dog to its fate, injured and in pain!
S-So we decided to only take care of it
until it's injury heals.
We have also notified the police
in hopes of locating the owner.
Get back, all of you!
How abominable!
What's the matter, everyone?
Those three weren’t looking after that dog
by themselves. We all helped!
G-Girls...
That's right!
So you'll have to expel all of us!
Hallo, police?
This is Miss Theobald,
the headmistress of St. Clare's school for girls.
It's about one of my students finding a dog...
Yes.
Indeed.
I see.
I see no reason to blame you
for taking care of a puppy in distress.
No, on the contrary, as the headmistress
of this school, I am proud
that you did not abandon that suffering puppy
and instead saved its life.
No matter how small a life is,
it is irreplaceable.
To cherish and value that life
is the most important thing.
Well then, it doesn't seem likely
that this puppy's owner will be found.
The police also said
we can keep it for all they care.
As such, you are allowed to keep it here
until you go on vacation.
Headmistress!
Hooray!
Now, now...
Headmistress, but what are we
going to do after vacation?
Let's see now...
How about taking it to Kathleen’s aunt
or the O’Sullivans’ place, if either of them agrees?
It pains me, but you deserve it.
Yeah. After all, you're the lifesaver
who healed the puppy's injury, Kathleen.
Thank you!
By the way, what is the name of this puppy?
Ah... We haven't given it one yet.
How about "Binks"?
Binks?
I don't know why, but I've been wanting
to name him that for a while.
That's such a classy name!
Wait, let me ask him.
Hey, Binks, do you like it?
Well, that sounds like a "yes!"
Wait, Binks!
Wait!
Binks!
I’ve never seen our first form students so united.
It was the students
who taught us something this time.
Excusez-moi?
A true education is impossible if you constantly
restrict students with school rules.
Yes...
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Pat, just imagine for a moment.
If we show the best possible result on the next exam, how happy do you think Dad and Mum would be?
Mum would throw a huge party as if it were both a birthday and Christmas at once!
Dad never praises us,
but I'm sure he'll brag about us this time.
"Well, it turns out my naughty twins
can be quite capable too!"
Exactly like that, Pat!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Isabelle is Cheating?!"
Episode 11
Isabelle is Cheating?!
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End