Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
King Arthur was a legendary Celtic hero,
and some say he really lived between the fifth and sixth centuries.
His kingdom was called Logres,
and most of it was what we now call England,
but the tales also spread to Scotland, Wales, Cornwall, Ireland, and even Brittany in France.
The main stories tell of Arthur’s stormy life
as the conqueror of England and Gaul,
and of course, of the wizard Merlin...
Say, you all know the Knights
of the Round Table, don’t you?
Yes, we do!
They were the brave knights
who served King Arthur.
And the greatest of them all was Lancelot.
Quite right, Lancelot’s gallant exploits
and his secret romance with Queen Guinevere.
It’s all so romantic, isn’t it?
Wish I could meet them!
By the way, a castle has been discovered
up in the hills just beyond Rensing,
and they say it may well
have some link to King Arthur.
Is that really true, Miss Lewis?
Tomorrow, Saturday afternoon,
we’ll go there to visit the ruins.
Who wants to come?
I do!
Me too!
I absolutely must come!
Episode 23
What! History Might be Changed?!
Now don’t forget,
you’re not coming just for a picnic.
But you did say we could
bring along some sweets, so...
Yes, I did grant permission,
But you never thought
it would be on such a scale!
That’s right.
Besides, we did restrain ourselves, you know.
I think this castle ruin we’re going to see now may be closely connected to Lancelot.
Ah! I simply adore Lancelot!
So do I!
Me too.
What sort of connection is it?
You’ve heard of Sir Meliagrance, haven’t you?
Of course.
Well, one day when Queen Guinevere
was out in the woods picking flowers,
Sir Meliagrance, one of the Round Table knights,
suddenly attacked her and carried her off to his castle.
How could he do such a horrid thing?
Because in secret Meliagrance
was in love with her.
Oh? Fancy that, Queen Guinevere
was as popular as me!
You’ll go a long way,
saying things like that.
And the one who rode straight to her rescue
was none other than Sir Lancelot.
Exactly so. Lancelot charged in all alone,
cutting down wave after wave of foes,
until at last Meliagrance grew frightened
and begged Queen Guinevere to spare his life.
Isn’t Lancelot marvellous!
I’d love to meet him.
Some even say it wasn’t Meliagrance’s castle at all,
but the very one we’re going to visit
where Guinevere was taken prisoner.
And I’m inclined to believe it.
Really?
How thrilling!
There it is.
Surely, Miss Lewis,
you don’t mean that’s all there is?
Yes, that’s all.
Eh?
Only this?
I thought we’d find a proper castle standing.
True! I’m dreadfully disappointed.
Even so, from these few remains
we can tell it was a castle of Arthur’s time,
and it does fit the idea that Queen Guinevere might once have been held prisoner here.
We’ve learnt quite a lot already.
Now, what I’d like you to do
is stand here a while and see what you feel.
Look up, for example,
at this moss-covered tower.
Think of Lancelot, Queen Guinevere, and Sir Meliagrance.
Don’t you feel something stirring?
Or perhaps the view itself—
the sky, the hills, the lake.
Doesn’t it give you a sense of something?
It may not come at once, but keep it in mind
as you wander about the place in your own way.
Just walk about, Miss?
Yes. You never know, you might stumble upon something linked to the castle.
I see.
Hey, Isabel, did you feel anything?
Nothing at all.
Me neither.
But just once, I wish I could meet him.
Lancelot, right?
Yeah.
I was thinking the very same thing just now!
Princess Pat, I have come to rescue you!
Lancelot! Thank you.
Isabel, over here!
Where are we?
It feels as if we’ve strayed
into some strange place.
Listen! A sound.
Eh?
A horse!
Let’s follow it.
Yeah.
This way!
Wh-What are those people?
H-How odd!
Odd? They look exactly like folk
from King Arthur’s time!
I know!
Know what?
It must be a film shoot!
Oh, of course!
Who’s starring, I wonder?
But wait...
Eh?
There’s no director,
no cameras, no crew anywhere.
You’re right.
Then what could it be?
Perhaps a Shakespearean troupe rehearsing?
Out of doors?
I’ve never heard of such a thing.
Queen Guinevere!
What is it, Sir Meliagrance?
Eh?!
In the depths of the forest,
there blooms a field of beautiful flowers.
My! Pray guide me there.
D-Did you hear that?
He called her Queen Guinevere,
and himself Meliagrance!
We’ve slipped back
into King Arthur’s time!
S-Surely not...
Whatever it is, let’s follow and see!
Yeah.
Hide there!
Wh-What is the meaning of this?
You must come with me, Queen Guinevere.
I love you. Be my wife!
Meliagrance!
That is no way to speak to the Queen!
S-Silence!
They are slaughtering them for real!
Queen Guinevere!
Flee at once!
Otherwise you’ll be shut up inside the castle.
Hold your tongue!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Stop this, Meliagrance.
Put down your sword.
Then you will come with me, will you not?
Who are you two?
Y-Yes, Queen. We’re from St. Clare's School,
Pat,
and Isabel.
We’re twins.
Oh, my, twins?
Take care of your lives.
Okay!
Lead the way.
What shall we do?
Isn’t Lancelot of the Round Table
supposed to come to the rescue?
That's right!
Then we must warn him at once!
Yeah.
Are you hurt?
N-No...
Ah?
Sir Lancelot, knight of King Arthur’s Round Table!
That is me...
And you are?
I’m Pat.
And I’m Isabel.
Queen Guinevere...
has been carried off by Meliagrance!
Wh-What? Where to?
We’ll show you.
You have my thanks.
Come then!
Come on.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Go!
Isabel, isn’t this the very place
Miss Lewis brought us to?
Yes, I’m sure of it.
So a castle...
once stood here after all.
Thank you, both of you.
From here on it will be dangerous,
so you must get down.
You mean we must part here?
Oh, we can’t bear it!
We want to stay with you always!
I would take you with me,
but a battle is about to begin.
You will get down, won’t you?
Yes.
Take care, Lancelot.
I will.
Go!
What shall we do?
That should be obvious!
Yeah.
Meliagrance!
What business have you with me, Lancelot?
You traitor!
How dare you carry off the Queen!
Hand her over quietly,
or I shall strike you down!
Fool!
What can you hope to do alone?
Get him!
You came here all by yourself?
What folly!
He really rode in all alone.
How gallant!
What are we gonna do?
You know the answer!
Yeah.
Ho there, Guinevere!
Where are you?
Ho, Guinevere!
Ho, where can she be?
Let’s try over there!
Yeah!
Ho, Guinevere!
Ho, Guinevere! Come forth!
What’s happening here?
W-Wait!
Oi! You shan’t escape!
Ho, this way!
You two!
Miss Lewis!
Janet, Kathleen, Hilary, Alison!
Oh, wait for me!
And Joan!
Wh-What’s going on?
Ah!
There they are, over here!
Right!
You're not getting anywhere.
Lancelot! Help!
Impossible!
He couldn’t have come this far alone.
We'll see about that!
What?
Lancelot!
Thou wretch...
Attack!
Get the queen to safety!
Aye!
Don’t let them get away!
Perish, Lancelot!
Curse you…
Pat!
Wh-What was that?
An exit!
Are all three of you unhurt?
Lancelot!
Ah!
Pat, Isabel—thank you.
I shall never forget you.
Nor shall we ever forget you two.
Ah! They opened their eyes!
Thank goodness!
They're alive!
We are!
You bet we are!
We’re coming down now.
Where have Lancelot
and Queen Guinevere gone?
Eh?
What are you talking about, twins?
What do you mean,
what are we talking about?
There really was a castle here.
Yes! And we truly spoke
with Lancelot and Queen Guinevere.
Didn’t we?
You’ve banged your heads and gone daft,
haven’t you, twins?
Nothing of the sort,
we really did see them!
The Queen thanked us.
And Lancelot said he’d never forget us.
It would be marvellous if it were true...
But I can’t believe it.
I believe you, though.
Miss Lewis!
Do you think they slipped back in time?
I’m certain of it.
Well, I don’t know
if such a thing is truly possible,
but at any rate, you two seem to have had
a mysterious experience.
Mysterious indeed—to think you both
had the very same dream.
That’s twin magic for you.
In any case, it’s something you could never do
without using all your imagination.
Try not to think of people of long ago
as merely figures from the past,
but imagine them as if they were alive.
Then the smallest detail may become a clue,
and suddenly it all takes shape.
In other words, history is not simply learning dates by rote.
The harder you try to understand it,
the more history itself seems to speak to you.
Queen Guinevere was truly gracious
and kind at heart.
Radiantly beautiful!
And Sir Lancelot of the Round Table
was noble, brave, strong,
and the most splendid of all!
Wow, I’m envious!
Ah... I wish I’d tumbled over that cliff too.
Perhaps you'd only have fainted then, that’s all.
Janet!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
I say, Pat, Alison’s gone on a diet.
She says unless she’s pretty,
boys won’t even glance at her.
What nonsense!
Who needs a diet? I can't believe my ears.
But the others have started too.
Surely not you as well, Isabel?
Yes, just a little.
Oh, this is dreadful!
Whatever shall we do
about the lacrosse match?
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"A Dieting Craze!"
Don’t miss it!
Episode 24
A Dieting Craze!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End