Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
Isabel, we finally held
a great midnight feast.
It was fun! And the food tastes better
in the middle of the night!
Doris' clown dance was a sight to behold too.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
I panicked, wondering what would happen
when Miss Kennedy came.
I was relieved when she said she won't report it.
But Pat...
Something is worrying me about Kathleen.
Oh, she's doing jolly well.
She's a lot more cheerful now.
And she was put on the lacrosse team with you!
That's right. As the school's representatives,
we've gotta do our best!
Episode 6
Poor Kathleen
Kathleen.
Remember that feeling earlier, and use it during the match to stop St. Christopher’s shots.
Huh?
I'm putting you out as our goalkeeper. Got it?
Huh? There's no way I'm fit for that yet.
If you picked a second-former...
Don’t worry. Of all our players, you’re the quickest to intercept a ball, as long as you stay calm.
Exactly! Be more confident, Kathleen.
Okay.
Oh geez, I'm exhausted...
Hey, Isabel.
Let's get up early tomorrow and practice.
There are only three days to the match.
Early in the morning?
I don't know if I'll be able to...
I'll wake you up.
We're the only first-formers on the team.
We can't afford an embarrassing match, can we?
You're right.
We must do our best.
That's the spirit!
Hm?
We’ll all be there to cheer you on,
so give them a proper hiding!
Sure. But St. Christopher’s has a strong team.
If only, only I could shoot
two or three goals on Saturday...
What? What happened?
You said it again, Isabel!
I wonder who it was who turned her nose up
at lacrosse just a few weeks ago,
saying it’s nothing but hockey in the air?
Who vowed and declared she would never try
to be any good at a silly game like lacrosse?
I must have seemed rather an idiot...
You were a bit of a goof.
Do you know what we used to call you back then?
The stuck-up twins!
Oh! What a dreadful name...
What's wrong, Isabel?
What dreadful name?
Nothing!
All right...
I'm going to shine in that match!
If I become the pride of our form,
they'll surely forget that silly nickname sooner.
Dad, Mum, we're doing more or less fine so far.
Isabel is giving her all
at lacrosse practice right now.
She was picked for a guest match.
It stings, but she even beat me!
"There will be a match on Saturday.
Please pray that we win.
Isabel will write to you soon with the results.
Until then, that's all.
—Pat."
Really, that's all?
Yes. That sounds like Pat.
But I'm glad they're doing well.
They've finally managed to adjust, it seems.
They must've realized
why St. Clare's is the best for them.
We don't need to worry anymore.
That's what I want to believe...
The match is today.
Isabel must be working hard right now.
Okay, let's prepare for the welcoming luncheon!
And make haste, the St. Christopher’s players will be arriving soon!
Hey, what's on the menu today?
Sausages, mashed potatoes, and pudding.
Wow! I wonder if there’ll be seconds.
Overeating won't do!
You too, Kathleen.
I want both of you to give it your best
and become the pride of the first form.
Yep. Instead, we ought to make sure
the other team eats so much they can’t stand.
There's only one pudding, though.
But if you win, the whole form
will stand you cream-buns at tea-time!
Wow, you had a midnight feast?
I'm jealous!
If you commute from home,
you don't get to have that kind of fun.
More sausages, anyone?
Thanks.
By the way, what's your
lacrosse team like this year?
We’ve beaten you each time
we’ve played you so far.
Don't mind if we allow ourselves
to beat you again today.
Kathleen! Make sure to catch their shots,
for a cream-buns treat!
One bun per shot stopped!
M-My heart is pounding...
What should I do?
Don't you worry.
Just do what we always do.
Kathleen is completely untroubled by this.
She’s like a completely different person
from when we first met her.
Kathleen, Isabel, don't hold back!
New goalkeeper?
Huh? She seems rather small.
She's a first-former.
I wonder if she'll manage.
Kathleen, don't mind the seniors!
Just give it your all!
Looking good, Isabel!
Nicely done, Kathleen!
Keep that up!
Don't worry, we're still in good shape.
I'm sure you can turn it around in the second half.
Everyone on the other team is so fast,
it's almost impossible to keep up!
Isabel, why don't you try
shooting some goals now?
Huh?
When you see an opening,
shoot with all your might—just like in practice.
Okay!
I'm sorry, I missed three goals already...
We could use those three extra points,
but you also saved four, didn't you?
Yes...
Let's go!
Yay!
Amazing, Isabel!
Keep that up and we'll turn it around!
That’s it! You’ve levelled the score!
C'mon, hurry!
Why, you...
What do you want?!
Isabel, you can do it!
We need this one extra point!
Isabel! Shoot now!
She did it!
Nicely done, Isabel!
Cream-buns are yours!
Isabel!
Really, you both did extremely well.
You're the pride of our first form!
Janet went to buy the cream-buns for you.
Look forward to it!
What's wrong?
We thought you went to town.
I couldn't buy the cream-buns.
My money is gone.
What do you mean?
I definitely had five shillings on me
just this morning.
But when I went to buy the cream-buns,
I couldn't find them!
That's weird.
I also lost my ten shillings the other day...
And now it's Janet?
What's the matter?
Hurry up, we've gotta prepare the tea.
The day-girls of St. Christopher’s are waiting.
Ah... I was so looking forward
to those cream-buns....
Janet, take this.
Oh, no! We wanted to buy them for you and Isabel
because you did so well in the match.
Please do use this.
We're also grateful to you all.
Your support is what kept us going—
it's what allowed us to win! Right, Isabel?
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Janet, Kathleen is doing it with all her heart,
so you should accept it.
Okay. Thank you, Kathleen!
I'll be on my way, then!
How jolly generous our Kathleen is!
Kathleen... Please tell me I'm wrong.
The Twins at St. Clare's
When Janet couldn’t find her money,
we gave up on trying those cream-buns.
But thanks to Kathleen,
she was able to buy enough for everyone!
We had a great time chatting with the day-girls
from St. Christopher's, and we sent them off
saying we look forward to playing them again.
Well done, both of you.
Your early morning practice paid off.
You ought to make that into a habit.
Okay.
Isabel, come here for a second.
What?
Huh? Really?
That's what I heard.
Isabel, you lost money too?
Uh? Yeah... Two shillings,
right before our midnight feast.
Where did you leave it?
In my wallet, in the top drawer of my nightstand.
So someone really did steal them!
Just like the ten shillings from my drawer,
and the five shillings from Janet's coat.
Um... Belinda Towers told me
some of her money was gone too.
Then there can be no doubt—we have a thief!
One of the girls?
Of course not!
How could one of us do it?
It would've been plausible
if we had any outsiders wandering around.
The culprit is right here, in our school!
Hey, let's tell Headmistress.
Let's not be hasty!
Besides, the money that I lost
may have been simply misplaced.
But mine was definitely stolen!
I'm sure I still had those ten shillings on me.
Next time something like this happens,
let's report it to Headmistress.
Until then, everyone,
be careful with your money.
Take every precaution so it doesn’t get stolen.
What's the matter, Isabel?
It's almost dinner time.
It's important, and it won't take long!
Something about Kathleen?
What? It can't be!
I didn't want to believe it either.
But when you think about it,
it was when everyone’s money
began disappearing that Kathleen became
so generous and extravagant.
Didn't she just receive
pocket money from her dad?
That's what I also thought at first...
I really fancy Kathleen as she is these days—
so kind to everyone, always going about
with that can-do attitude.
So do I! That's why I haven't told you before.
I hate to doubt others—I really do!
If... If that's true, we ought
to tell Kathleen to stop doing that.
But we can't just make such an outrageous claim...
I really hope I'm just wrong.
Yeah... Let's not discuss it with the others for now.
Yes. And also keep an eye on Kathleen.
Isabel! Gym class is starting.
You'll be late if you don't go now.
Huh?! It's that late already?
We've only five minutes left. Hurry up!
Oh no! But what should I do?
Kathleen hasn't come back yet.
Where did she go?
To the room of Rita George,
head of the Nature Club in sixth form.
Let's go remind her!
Oh, please forgive me!
Oh, please don’t tell anyone!
It's Kathleen!
To think that a student of St. Clare's
would stoop to this!
I must report this to Headmistress.
Dismissed. Leave now!
Kathleen...
Kathleen! What happened?
We can talk if you want to...
Go away!
Don’t come prying after me.
We can't leave you.
We're your friends, you know.
You’d be horrified to be friends with me
if I told you what had happened.
Kathleen, you were the very first friend
we made when we came to St. Clare’s.
And you'll be our friend forever,
no matter what.
Whatever’s happened? Tell us!
Well, I’ll tell you—and you can go
and spread it all round the school if you like—
and everyone can laugh and jeer at me—
but I’ll not be here by then!
Kathleen, please don't talk like that.
We won’t turn on you, I promise.
Yes, you will!
What I’ve done is so dreadful!
You won’t believe it!
I hardly believe it myself.
I’m a thief!
I took all the money that’s been missing!
Even your two shillings, Isabel.
Hillary's, Janet's, and Belinda's money—all of it!
Why?
You wouldn't understand.
I don't have a mother.
I haven’t anyone to send me money and sweets
all the time like you and the other girls have.
But didn't you say before...
That was all a lie.
The only truth is that my father is away abroad.
But he’s so busy that he had to leave me
in the care of my old aunt.
My...
Aunt only gives me about a penny a week!
One penny?! That's all?
She says you don't need money
to live in the common dorm.
But what can you do with just a single penny—
buy a friend a present, give at church,
or get your everyday little things?!
Poor Kathleen...
It hurt so much to pretend I didn’t notice
everyone calling me stingy.
I really wanted to be generous to everyone.
I wanted to have friends.
Then one day, I found a shilling
in the school yard.
The one shilling I needed to contribute
to the present for Headmistress.
It was such a relief!
It even made Janet see me differently!
So now I felt like I had to gift Janet
something nice for her birthday.
I still don't know why I did that...
But it made me so happy to see her delighted face...
And then I could no longer stop...
I thought that'd make everyone happy,
but I was just fooling myself.
A theft is a theft!
In the end, I just wanted
to force everyone to like me...
What a blithering idiot I've been!
So today, in Rita's room too...
Yes!
So she’s going to tell Headmistress now,
and I shall be known all over the school as a thief,
and I’ll be expelled and...
Kathleen...
Please go!
Leave me alone.
I need to pack up my things.
Wait, Kathleen!
Don't bother! I know that in your heart of hearts
you despise me too. Just leave me alone!
That's not true, and never will be!
Just leave... Please!
Let’s go and find Rita if we can!
Ask her not to report it.
She's probably in Headmistress's office.
Hurry!
Did she report it already?
Yes, come in.
What's the matter, Patricia and Isabel?
We'd like to ask you for a favor—
it's about Kathleen!
Of course, what Kathleen did was awful.
But she's terribly upset about it now!
But oh, Headmistress,
Kathleen didn’t spend a penny on herself.
She took our money,
but we got it back in gifts and things.
Kathleen isn’t an ordinary,
contemptible kind of thief.
But if she gets sent away now, she may really
become one, and be spoilt for always!
Please give her a chance!
I’m quite sure Kathleen would apologise to everyone,
and try to repay every penny to set it right.
And we would help her in any way we could!
Please, Headmistress!
If I hadn’t heard your story,
I’d have had to judge based solely on Rita’s.
I might have written to her aunt
to take her away.
And then I dread what might have happened
to her, poor, sensitive child!
Headmistress!
Do you mean that you will let Kathleen stay?
Of course, I must talk to her first.
I shall know how to deal with her, don’t worry.
Where is she now?
In her dormitory, packing.
Kathleen slipped up,
it can happen to anyone.
Especially when you're young.
What matters is what she does next.
You have been watching over her warmly—
I am proud of you both.
You are kind and understanding,
two things that matter a great deal.
Now, off to your lesson, and tell your teacher to excuse you for being late, since you’ve been with me.
I will also ask Rita not to let this story get around.
You two will keep it secret too, won’t you?
Yes!
Thank you, Headmistress.
The sky is stunning!
It's just like my feelings right now!
Isn't it great that everything ended well?
Everyone was kind enough to forgive you.
It's all thanks to you two.
And Headmistress too!
She's a wonderful person,
just like our mum said!
She’s going to write to my aunt and ask for a proper amount of pocket money to be paid to me.
Isn't that great?
You’ll be able to pay back all the money
and soon be generous again.
And if you can’t, just admit it frankly—
don’t try to force yourself.
I will!
I'm so glad they didn't send you away!
You're our dear friend, after all.
And you're mine! I'm a really lucky girl
to have wonderful friends like you two!
Will you be able to trust me again?
Of course we will!
Because then we'll be able to store our fortunes with you—not the bank.
Pat, you silly-billy!
I'm so lucky to be at St. Clare's!
I love this school!
Me too!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
I'm Pat!
I'm Isabel.
Hey, listen, Isabel.
Miss Kennedy might soon resign.
What? Why? First time I'm hearing of that!
She says she's just not good at teaching.
That's not true!
Miss Kennedy is a wonderful teacher.
She's, kind, sympathetic, and excellent!
And yet...
But if Miss Kennedy really quits,
what are we going to do?!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
Stay Strong, Miss Kennedy!
Episode 7
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End