Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Finished!
Look! I’ve done it!
Whew! So fast!
Ah! We’d better wrap this up quickly
or it’ll be tea-time.
Oh, how very pretty!
Are you throwing that away?
Yes, it’s only scraps.
What a waste. May I have it?
Eh? Sure... Go ahead, it’s nothing much.
Thank you!
Well then.
What a queer girl.
By the way, who is she?
She’s the one who’s been
working in the dining hall lately.
Gladys, I think that's her name.
Episode 22
Run, Gladys!
Is that so?
Anyway...
Watch out!
What the heck!
Perfect!
Careful!
Oh, bother!
Just as we were about to go out.
What are you gonna do about it?
I’m so sorry, I’ll wash it straight away.
Oh, you'd better make sure it's real clean!
Come and take it from my room.
I am very sorry.
Watch where you’re going next time!
Are you all right, Gladys?
You're not hurt, are you?
No.
I can't believe her! It was Pam who wasn’t watching where she's going!
Whatever shall I do?
This was meant for Headmistress and her visitor.
I’ll fetch Pam's skirt for you.
But then...
Never mind, off you go, quickly.
Thank you, I’ll be back in a moment.
She looks about our age, doesn’t she?
Yes, I think so.
Ah, I’ll do it, sorry for the delay!
Gosh! Your hands...
Yes... They’re terrible, aren’t they?
They always get rough no matter what.
Poor thing, don’t they hurt?
I can’t help it, washing hundreds of plates every day.
Goodness... I know, Kathleen has some ointment for chapped hands. Wait here.
Phew, thank God,
the stain has come off.
This ointment works wonders.
I’ve always had trouble with rough hands myself,
and my father sent me this from abroad.
Thank you. My father was a kind man too.
"Was?" Then...
Yes, he passed away three years ago.
Oh... So that’s why you’re working
instead of going to school?
Yes, I’ve younger brothers and sisters,
so Mother and I must manage.
My, that must be hard on you.
Not at all, I like working.
Ah... I must go now!
Gladys, take this ointment.
Use it every time after washing
and your hands will soon be better.
Thank you.
Right... So that’s what it was.
Hm? What do you mean?
I’d been wondering for a while,
and now I know.
Without a father,
it must be hard for that family.
Gladys, with that slight little body,
is supporting them all.
How splendid of her.
She’s quite different from us,
who only need think of our studies.
Gladys is a brave girl, working so hard
in spite of poverty and hardship.
Kathleen, you do exaggerate.
Oh, but I’m sure it’s so.
But she doesn’t look
all that miserable, does she?
Yes, she’s so very cheerful.
That’s what’s splendid about Gladys.
Is it, though?
Perhaps it’s just Kathleen imagining it?
Janet, you’re too much
of a young lady to understand.
Hm...
If she really is in trouble,
I’d like to help her somehow.
Yes.
That was a splendid play today.
Yeah... If only it hadn’t been in French, I’d have understood it far better.
I did understand some of it.
“Je t’aime” and “Adieu.”
Joan! Even I knew that much.
But listen, did you notice?
Mam’zelle was in tears right through the end.
Yeah, I saw it! She’s more of a romantic than we’d thought, and such a soft-hearted one too.
I heard that, you know. You needn’t have said “more than we’d thought.”
Wh-What, what is it?
It's Gladys!
Is she running all the way to town?
She does it every day, you know.
Really?
Of course, she must be saving her bus fare.
You’re joking!
Let’s form a Gladys Support Club.
Yes, I want to help her,
working so hard as she does.
All right, I’m in.
What shall we do, though?
How about giving her brothers some books?
Yes, I’ve still got plenty I read when I was little.
I’ll give her some clothes,
the sort in her size.
Then I’ll get Mother to send me
some sweets to pass on.
Settled!
Let’s begin at once.
But why give these things to me?
Because we want to support you, Gladys!
Don’t we!
We do!
Watching you work so hard gives us courage too!
It’s our way of saying thank you.
We’d be glad to know
you liked and accepted them.
May I really?
You may!
Thank you, then I will!
Splendid!
Goodbye!
Bye!
See you!
That was well done!
The first operation of the
Gladys Support Club was a success!
Let’s carry it on!
Agreed!
Ah, wait, just a moment!
Gladys!
Here.
Use it for your bus fare.
Janet!
I cannot take that.
Ah... With this rain,
there can be no going to town.
Oh? There’s Gladys.
She’s on the late shift today.
Ah! She’s soaking wet.
She didn’t take the bus again.
I do hope she doesn’t catch cold.
We'll go first!
Gladys.
You look so pale.
Are you all right?
Yes, I’m fine.
Okay, then. Bye.
G-Gladys!
Matron, will Gladys be all right?
No need to worry, it’s only a mild cold.
She was already tired,
then she went into the rain too.
I gave her my medicine,
a little sleep will put her right.
Thank you very much, Matron.
I... gotta hurry...
She’s fretting about her work.
That’s it!
Come along.
What is it, Pat?
I’m calling a meeting of the Gladys Support Club.
What are we going to do?
Operation Two:
we’ll do Gladys’s work for her.
Put them on that counter.
Oi, we can stand in for her,
but do you know how it’s done?
So long as they’re clean,
it doesn’t matter.
Leave it to me, I’m an expert washer-up.
We’ll make them shine
and give Gladys a real surprise.
Don’t you think we’re terribly efficient?
Indeed, we’d make fine housewives one day.
But is this really the only drying cloth?
It’s sopping wet and won’t dry a thing.
Give it a good wring-out,
that should do i— Ah!
Janet!
Sorry.
It’s all right, missing one plate
won’t make any difference.
I only hope Gladys doesn’t get scolded.
The Twins at St. Clare's
Right, that’s it.
Tomorrow’s Sunday, so Gladys has the day off.
A whole day’s rest will put her right.
Thank goodness!
Ah! Gladys!
Are you really better already?
You need to take it easy now.
Er... Is this...?
Aren't they real clean?
We did it for you.
Go on, hurry home and get some rest.
Th-Thank you...
No, think nothing of it.
That went well, didn’t it?
Yes, I feel jolly pleased.
Sorry. I appreciate it, but…
Oh... Gladys?
Isabel?
Are you re-doing it?
I’m sorry.
I was touched by your kindness, but...
there’s a set procedure,
and it has to be followed.
For instance, the plates aren’t to be wiped at all,
only scalded in boiling water and stacked in the rack.
There are other rules too…
I see.
Then let me help.
No, please. It’s past bedtime.
You’d best go back to your dormitory.
But...
This is my job.
I’m paid to do it.
So we only gave you extra work?
Not at all. Thanks to you I feel better
and I’ll be finished sooner.
I’m grateful.
But please—don’t breathe
a word of this to anyone.
Will Gladys really run
all the way home this late?
Oh, Pat.
Yes?
Gladys dropped this yesterday.
Take it to town for her, will you?
Okay.
Eh? How come? Good gracious!
Say, what?
Gladys is entering the marathon?
That’s right. But unless this form is handed in
by 10:30, she can’t compete.
But she had a fever yesterday—
she can’t possibly run!
That’s not all. In fact, last night...
Eh? Really?
They refused?
What bad luck.
You're also not well today,
so let's pack it in.
Gladys!
Excuse me!
Can you still make it in time?
Come on, Gladys!
Cheer up!
Gladys still looks a bit pale.
I wonder if she’s all right.
She was working late into the night.
Honestly!
She never tells anyone a word.
Shouldn’t we stop her?
No, Gladys must absolutely run today.
Headmistress?
So you knew about this all too?
Of course. She’s a born runner.
There’s even talk of a scholarship.
But she chose to keep working while she runs,
so she runs to and from St. Clare’s every day.
Ah, so that's why...
She wasn’t just saving her bus fare?
Today is a special day.
If she finishes in the top three,
she’ll qualify for a bigger competition.
And if she shines there,
she may be chosen as an Olympic hopeful.
The Olympics?
Yes.
Gladys has staked everything on this race.
If it’s so important, she ought
to have taken a day off yesterday.
That’s just what makes her so splendid.
Yes.
Ready!
Hey, this is the moment
for the Support Club to prove itself.
Okay! Let’s cheer her on with all we’ve got.
Gladys, steady now!
Keep going!
Fight, fight!
Pat, don’t shake us,
the handlebars are unsteady!
Keep your eyes straight ahead, won't you?
Look, you...
Gladys is in the lead!
Brilliant!
Come on, Gladys, you can do it!
That’s it, Gladys, keep it up!
If I let her break away,
it’ll be all over.
I must stick close...
My body feels heavy…
my legs won’t lift any more.
I mustn’t fall behind...
Gladys!
No... I can’t run any longer.
Gladys, don’t give in!
You must run right to the finish.
Your mother is waiting for you.
And your father in heaven is cheering too!
Yes… Father!
Father, run with me.
Thanks!
Gladys, don’t push yourself too hard.
Ah! Mum, sis is not leading!
There she is!
Mum, she's right there!
Gladys!
Sister!
You did it!
Ain't that great?
Thank you, Mother...
Headmistress, Gladys has come third!
Now the dream of the Olympics is within reach.
Thank you for your cheering.
If you’d like, do come to my house.
I should love to give you tea.
Sure!
Oh?
That tea cosy...
Ah, I made it from the scraps
you gave Gladys.
What lovely patchwork!
Mother is so clever with her hands.
I take after Father, so I’m no good.
But instead, you can run fast.
Your father was a sprinter, after all.
Had he not hurt his leg in an accident when young,
he might have run in the Olympics himself.
Mother, I’ll go to the Olympics in his place!
Who was it who called Gladys
a poor, unfortunate girl?
We really had it all wrong, didn’t we?
Gladys’s family may have no father,
and they don’t live in luxury,
but don’t you think they live richly?
Yes. Warmly and happily,
with hearts full of wealth.
She never needed our meddlesome charity at all.
Yes, and I feel a bit ashamed.
Where does all that power
come from in such a slight body?
I can’t help admiring her!
Say, what about turning the Gladys Support Club
into the Send Gladys to the Olympics Club?
Sounds great, let’s!
But do promise not to say
we must run with her every day!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
On our history outing, we went to see
the site linked with the legend of King Arthur.
It was ever so romantic, wasn’t it, Isabel?
Indeed, for we lived through history itself
and met the gallant knight Sir Lancelot.
Everyone may think it’s a tall story,
but it’s the truth.
Absolutely, isn’t it, Pat?
Was it a dream, or an illusion?
Only we shall ever know!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"What! History Might be Changed?!"
Episode 23
What! History Might be Changed?!
Look forward to it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End