Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Ah... So the semester is finally ending?
Tomorrow evening, we'll already be in London,
dining with Dad and Mum.
Come on, give way!
Old Janet will fluff all the blankets
in Room Seven for you!
There we go!
Geez!
Come on!
Huh? What's that?
Ah! My paper flowers!
I've been looking for them since last year!
Ah! My notebook too!
General cleanup brings out all sorts of stuff.
My precious history notebook.
Ah! Is that Miss Kennedy's handwriting?
When I submitted my homework,
she even wrote this to praise me!
It was about the life of Cleopatra.
Miss Kennedy is really
fond of me as her student!
Oh, but it's not just you!
Huh?
My Greek mythology notebook
also looks like this.
Incredible! So many notes!
And she lent me Da Vinci's art book.
Miss Kennedy cares for each student
as if they were her only one.
Ah! Speak of the devil,
there's Miss Kennedy!
Teacher!
Miss Kennedy!
She couldn't hear us.
I bet she was up all night
writing her paper again.
Episode 13
Goodbye, Miss Kennedy
Hey, did you hear
about Miss Kennedy, Belinda?
I did. Miss Kennedy
was only meant to stand in for Miss Lewis,
who was on sick leave for a long time, right?
Um... What is it about Miss Kennedy?
This is bad!
Very bad!
It seems Miss Kennedy
will have to leave St. Clare's!
No matter how many times I read it,
it's a great thesis.
Miss Kennedy, you must guard this with your life.
Headmistress, can we talk?
Come in
Headmistress!
How come you're letting Miss Kennedy go?!
Miss Kennedy!
Quiet, girls!
I'm having a guest, mind you.
B-But...
Aaaah
Watch out!
Are you trying to ruin the thesis Miss Kennedy
spent five years writing in just five seconds?
Ah... W-We're sorry.
I'm glad you understand.
This is Professor Sydney of Oxford University.
The professor came here today from London
to accompany Miss Kennedy.
May I?
This thesis was met with great praise.
Miss Kennedy has been officially invited
to be a female professor at Oxford University.
At Oxford?
So that rumour that you're letting her go...
Of course I am letting her go.
With honours and my gratitude.
Miss Kennedy did a wonderful job
replacing Miss Lewis for us.
It's time for her to nourish
her own talents too.
If she carries on her research at Oxford,
Miss Kennedy will gain international recognition in no time.
So you really have to leave...?
Make the time you spent with Miss Kennedy
a lifelong source of pride.
Oh, no...
No, it’s they who shaped me,
a clumsy novice teacher, into who I am now…
Pat,
Isabel,
Janet, Kathleen,
and each and every one of you,
who opened your heart to me.
Knowing you...
will be my lifelong source of pride.
Miss Kennedy!
Miss Kennedy...
Headmistress, would you please
grant me this final request?
I wish to give a lesson just one more time.
Everything I can teach them now... No!
Even if it's just a fraction,
I want to share it with them once more.
Very well.
Isn't the weather wonderful?
A lesson that'll become your heart's memento?
I know! Give it in our rose garden.
Please tell all the first formers that the final lesson
will be held there after school today.
Thank you...
"If she carries on her research at Oxford,
Miss Kennedy will
gain international recognition in no time!"
How wonderful!
Miss Kennedy!
She's so amazing!
Let's get her autograph!
So we'll have something to show to our relatives when we get home!
Yes, an autograph!
Huh?
Excuse me.
Yes, what is it?
A Rolls-Royce!
They're loading Miss Kennedy's
luggage in it already.
It feels as if Miss Kennedy has suddenly become
so distant from us somehow.
It's heavy, so be careful.
Oh, crumbs!
It’s too painful to think
that we’ll never see Miss Kennedy again!
I won't be coming to that final class...
lest I burst into tears!
Pat!
Pat...
Ah... Miss Kennedy!
I...
Pat.
Miss Kennedy...
I've invited you over for tea
several times, haven't I?
Our secret.
But our secret meetings are no more.
No, not before we do it once more.
Huh?
Miss Patricia, are you free now?
Yes!
Pat!
Where in the world did she go?
Pat...
You're not the only one feeling lonely, you know.
Hands up!
Why, you...
Hey! Didn't I tell you to behave yourselves?!
We need to stay in this school's good graces
to get what we came for!
Huh? Really?
Attention!
Yes, sir!
Apologise now.
We're sorry!
Good.
Um, who might you be?
We need to ask you something.
How do we get to the headmistress's room?
Huh? Ah, well, if you go around that building...
Thank you.
We're leaving!
Thank you very much!
Ah... Hey, wait a second!
Who are those kids?
Wow, what an adorable girl!
That's just me.
Huh?
I must be about your age in that photo.
Next to me is Miss Marple.
She was like a big tree of wisdom
with big boughs branching in all directions.
As a student, I was a very docile girl.
Many teachers even struggled
to remember my name.
But one day, Miss Marple called out to me,
alone as usual, and lent me a book.
She'd talk about history and literature for hours,
losing all sense of time.
When she saw how much it made my eyes shine,
she'd do it every day since then.
She taught me the joy of learning and made me want to learn more and more about all sorts of things.
I could never get enough.
Not a day goes by that I don’t thank God
for that wonderful encounter with Miss Marple.
If Miss Marple hadn’t been there for me,
I might never have developed a passion for research
or ended up in this delightful job.
She was the one who gently opened
the door to a passion for knowledge
that lay dormant in my young heart.
Passion for knowledge?
Hell's bells! This school is huge!
Not at all like the one we go to.
And it's just as labyrinthine!
What do they need all these stairs for?
You again?
Here it is, the headmistress's room.
Huh?
Remember? Our destiny is at stake!
Here we go!
Yeah!
But that room is...
Excuse me!
Hallo!
We've come from St. Mary's Island.
We have a favour.
Please help us find our teacher, Headmistress!
The Twins at St. Clare's
We're looking for our teacher.
Our old teacher has died.
She's in heaven now.
So we came here on a ship.
You guys came here all on your own?
Please!
We left early this morning
and it took us half a day to get here!
We’re starving like wolves now!
N-Now stop for a second!
One way or another,
this isn't the headmistress.
There's one thing I understood from this—
you kids are seriously in distress
and you've been through a lot.
Really?
Here it is.
St. Mary's Island.
That's pretty far...
I think it only has ninety people.
Ninety-two.
My younger brothers were born the other day.
And they're twins, just like these two!
There is one school on the island,
with only eighteen students studying there,
and only one teacher.
And now that one teacher died of illness?
We've sent letters to all the nearby schools,
asking them to recommend a teacher to us.
Dozens of them, I tell ya!
So, did you get an answer?
They all refused.
We couldn't bear it, couldn't sit still,
so we came to ask personally.
We were told that the headmistress
of St. Clare's is a person of great compassion.
Indeed, we've received a letter
from St. Mary's Island.
So?
Unfortunately, we at St. Clare's
don't have a teacher that'd fit the bill.
That's how I replied to it.
Headmistress!
Can't you do something about it?
Headmistress.
We've received a call
from the mayor of St. Mary's Island.
He wanted to know if any of the children from their island had ended up here.
Hallo?
Ah, Mary... I finally found you!
How could you sneak out like that?
F-Father?
We were all deathly worried!
But we must find a new teacher no matter what...
You return to the island this instant!
I'll come to the mainland to pick you up.
O-Okay.
Have no worries.
I'll watch over the children
and see to it that they return safely.
Now, you kids must go home now.
Headmistress!
I'll ask Matron to walk you to the station.
I’ll also ask around through my contacts
and other schools once more.
I will put in my best effort
to come back to you with good news.
Miss Kennedy, everyone has gathered
at the Rose Garden.
O-Okay...
No one else will ever come to our island!
Never... Never again!
That teacher we saw earlier...
I'm going to ask...
Ask that lady once more!
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Now, let us begin...
the final lesson.
Miss Kennedy!
What are we gonna do?
This must be something important.
Gimme!
It's you again!
what are you doing here?
And that's Miss Kennedy's precious thesis!
I-It's a disaster, Miss Kennedy!
Your thesis...
Huh?
What?
Stop! I'm not going to scold you!
She'll scold us for sure!
She totally will!
Miss Kennedy will probably be beside herself.
Open! Open up now!
What are we gonna do?
Open up already!
Ah! Jim, it's dangerous!
Jim!
It's dangerous!
Oh no!
Miss Kennedy!
H-He's gonna fall!
Quick, call the police
and ask for help!
Jim's mother...
Please, protect Jim from heaven above.
Jim's mother?
She fell ill and died.
I-Is she that teacher from the island?
Mum, what should I do?
Don't move!
Stay still! I'm going now!
Miss Kennedy!
Don't get mad!
I'm not mad!
I only... Only...
Wanted a teacher for the island.
With a teacher, I might be able to learn to read.
Because right now
there are so many letters from mother
that I can't read.
That's why...
Mother's letters?
Don't come!
Ah! The world-acclaimed thesis!
Miss Kennedy?
I can write that thesis again.
But you only have one letter from your mother.
Hey, if you want,
I can read this for you.
Huh?
As a sign that I'm not mad.
Jim has never shown it to anyone else.
"My Jim, it pains my heart,
but I'll have to leave you alone.
Mum has to go to heaven.
As the only teacher on a small island,
I had many more things yet to teach you,
Mary, Tom, and everyone else.
The history of our country,
the workings of life on our planet,
and the preciousness of life.
Even without me,
I'm sure your new teacher will..."
Mum!
Jim!
I... I...
Mum!
Jim, it's all right now.
Mum...
I...
Hey, Jim, let me tell you something good.
I have to leave this school tomorrow.
And then I'll go to the island with you all!
Huh?
M-Miss Kennedy...!
No way!
It's true! Would you approve
of me becoming your new teacher?
What was that?
Surely, that can't be true!
Miss Kennedy already agreed to go to Oxford!
Once Miss Kennedy makes a promise,
she never takes it back.
She picked up that terrifying stubbornness from me.
No, that's just...
Thank you!
Passing through!
Miss Kennedy!
Thank God...
So you're really going to that remote place?
It's kind of sad.
If you went to Oxford, you could become a world-famous researcher.
It occurred to me the moment I saw these children:
this is my chance to open the door to the passion for knowledge, lying dormant in their hearts.
Just like Miss Marple did for me.
I'm grateful for all the wonderful acquaintances I've made.
Miss Kennedy!
Be well.
Good bye!
In the end, the final lesson got cancelled.
No, the lesson did take place.
Before she left, Miss Kennedy
taught us this amazing way of life.
Let's go home now.
Dad and Mum are waiting.
We'll tell them about the wonderful Miss Kennedy.
From what point?
From the beginning!
All of it!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Our cousin Alison will be enrolling at St. Clare's for the new semester.
Alison is still as dry as ever
and only thinks about herself.
And that gets to her head.
Why did she have to follow in our footsteps?
A fun new semester...
is about to turn messy because of Alison,
but will we stand for it?!
But when a senior girl sent for her,
she did the unthinkable.
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Homework is Burned!"
Episode 14
The Homework is Burned!
Look forward to it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End