Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
Yumeiro Patissiere: every Monday at 6:30pm.
Stay tuned!
That silly Pat caused another big fuss.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Yeah... But I share the blame for that with Janet.
You two are made for each other.
Good-natured humour is one thing,
but hurtful pranks are quite another.
That's true.
I feel really bad for what I did to Miss Kennedy.
I didn't know she was such a devoted teacher.
But thanks to that incident, we came together
as a class with Miss Kennedy!
Yeah.
But that's at the cost of Miss Roberts
getting even more impatient with us.
Episode 5
The Great Midnight Feast
You forgot your textbook?
Y-Yes, although I'd prepared yesterday,
it just slipped my mind...
I don't want any excuses!
You forgot your textbook, and that's that.
I'm sorry...
Not bringing your textbook means you have no intention of taking the class.
I didn't mean to...
But that’s how it comes across—
like it or lump it!
Next time something like this happens
I won't let you in.
Hurry up and fetch it now.
Okay!
Wasting our precious time on such nonsense...
Please pay attention, everyone.
Okay...
Ah... Miss Roberts is so unfeeling.
The way she scolded me...
She thinks I'm a kindergartener or what?
She hasn’t tolerated any nonsense in class
since the fire-cracks incident.
But I can't really hate her,
I respect her too much for what she's done.
Neither do I, but if she was a bit more charitable,
I'd enjoy learning math a great deal more.
Don't lose your heart like that, Isabel.
We have a lacrosse match in the afternoon,
let's give it our all as usual.
You're right, we won't lose today!
Naturally!
We did it, Isabel! Hooray!
You're getting the hang of it, Isabel.
Once you learn the tricks,
the rest comes to you naturally.
Yes, you’ve got it. But stay on your guard—
we shan’t lose next time!
Oh, but the rest of our team is strong too.
Even that girl Kathleen is doing her best now!
Janet! Kathleen has always
been good at lacrosse.
Yeah... Right.
And that's why I'm praising her, don't I?
Hey, Headmistress's birthday is coming up, so...
Ah, the present money?
Yeah. We've decided
to chip in one shilling each.
Please prepare it, everyone!
Okay!
What'll it be this year?
How about a photo frame?
I know it's a bit banal, but...
Oh? But where's Kathleen?
Maybe taking a walk?
Really? I'll find her later, then.
Kathleen is just stingy.
She didn’t even put in an offering
when we went to church the other day.
Janet! Don't smear others like that with rumors.
But it's true!
Maybe she heard it?
Janet, you idiot...
One shilling?
So they sent me a boxful
of cakes and tinned food from home!
How wonderful! So you'll be throwing a great birthday party, right?
Yeah, I'll treat everyone during tea time.
Wow!
Can't wait!
Are there any chocolates too?
Of course!
There are cookies, biscuits, and whatnot.
Yay!
Um, Hillary.
Oh, Kathleen? Where were you?
I was looking for you.
I just left a little early.
Here, for the Headmistress's gift.
Y-Yeah, right. Thanks.
Are you going to give her a photo frame?
I hope you find a nice one.
Kathleen, we were just talking about how we'll celebrate my birthday this Thursday.
I'll be treating everyone,
so look forward to it.
Ah, really?
Thank you, Janet.
We gotta buy a present for Janet too!
Wanna go pick one tomorrow?
Sounds good.
Let's do that!
Good timing!
My granddad just sent me ten shillings.
We'll buy a present for Janet,
and then also get my lacrosse stick mended.
Hey, Pat. I'm worried about Kathleen.
What?
She seems downcast, somewhat.
Isn't she always like that?
She’s just upset by Janet’s remarks.
Yeah...
I wish she was more confident
and knew how to held her head high.
But as long as she keeps slumping,
Janet will keep teasing her.
When we're alone, she's always in good spirits...
I wonder what's causing this.
Good timing!
My granddad just sent me ten shillings.
This isn't right.
What's going on?!
They really are gone!
My ten shillings!
I'm sure I've put it in the top drawer...
The same your granddad sent you?
Sure you didn't leave it elsewhere?
I've searched everywhere.
To think I'd lose ten shillings like that...
We can each lend you a shilling or two.
We have to leave soon, we'll be late!
Yeah, you're right.
There's no time, so I'll have to ask you.
Hey, maybe this?
It's lovely!
I know, right?
So pretty!
Here! She's here!
All right, it's finally here!
The feast you've been looking forward to!
Huh?
Where did everyone go?
Happy Birthday, Janet!
Congratulations!
Thanks!
But it seems to me you’re happier
to see what’s in this basket than to see me.
Well, that certainly is a factor.
Here, for you.
Our simple gifts.
Yes! This one's from me.
I hope you like it.
Here.
Thanks, everyone!
Congratulations, Janet.
This is from me.
Thanks, Kathleen.
Hey, come on, let's open it already!
Yeah!
Next is from Kathleen.
What could it be?
Kathleen... I can't accept this.
It's too luxurious!
But you're the only one who can use it.
Turn it around.
That's amazing... Thank you!
I'll get to opening this, then.
Wow! Take a look at this abundance!
Cakes with butter, biscuits,
and condensed milk!
Some sardines too!
And peppermint creams!
All the things I love!
The next tea time will be fun!
Hey, let's have a midnight feast!
Midnight feast?
We used to do it at our previous school.
It's thrilling, and all food tastes better
in the middle of the night.
That sounds fun.
I heard some third formers did it before.
Really?
How about we all bring
a bit of everything to the table?
Sounds good! That'd almost make it
a proper feast. But when?
Tomorrow's good time.
Well, I overheard Miss Roberts talking about it.
She’s off to a concert tomorrow evening,
and she’ll be staying at a friend’s house.
Yahoo!
Perfect timing!
Hey, let's go and tell Sheila's room too.
We'll get the whole class together!
I'm in! The more—the merrier!
Not so loud.
Let's start preparing at once!
Make sure the others don't catch on to this.
Operation Midnight Feast begins!
Yeah!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Isabel, I'm off!
Go on ahead.
I’ll just fetch my purse and catch up.
Huh? Aren't you going to town, Kathleen?
Everyone else left already.
Y-Yes, I was just leaving.
Excuse me.
Oh?
Weird, I thought I still had two shillings left.
That's strange. I'm sure I still had them
when I paid the cleaning fee this morning...
Don't tell me...
Oh no...
It's not nice to suspect others like that.
I'm sure it's my mistake.
Ah... But what do I do now?
I'll just have to borrow from Pat.
Hey, did you see the cake?
Yeah, that was crazy!
Okay, that should be all.
That's quite a lot we've gathered here.
Can't wait!
Miss Roberts left.
Great! I was terribly worried when she
so nearly scolded me in maths class today.
That's true!
"Hey, you two. What are you fidgeting about?"
Come on, wrap it up now.
The preparations are finished.
Joan! Joan, wake up!
Ah? Is it time already?
Did you forget already?
We’re changing shifts.
Isabel will take over from you in half an hour.
Ugh... I'm so sleepy.
Think about all the tasty stuff in the cupboard.
That'll help you stay up.
Isabel, it's time! Wake up!
Hilary!
Janet, Joan, Doris, it's time!
Kathleen, Vera, you wake up too!
Feast time!
Sorry...
At least try not to drop the cake!
This bread is heavenly!
Impressive! It's the great feast, all right!
I’m sure it’s even grander and more splendid
than the third form’s feast was.
Ta-da! Tonight's special is here.
Behold!
Looks delicious!
Provided by Kathleen Gregory.
There's not much of it,
so first come, first served!
That almond icing is gorgeous!
Those sugar roses are something.
Oh? There wasn't enough for Kathleen?
Huh?
Oh no, I'm good.
It's my own fault for not bringing a bigger one.
By no means!
It already looks awfully expensive.
It must've cost you a fortune.
Oh, that's nothing.
I’m most awfully glad you liked it.
I’m sorry for doubting you,
when you so love to bring joy to others.
Ladies and gentlemen...
There aren't any gentlemen here.
We present to you the clown dance
of genius girl Doris Elward.
Doris learnt it during the holidays
at some special classes. It's great fun!
Yes, she has a talent!
Bother! Someone’s bound to have heard that!
Quick! Clear everything up!
Get into your beds!
Kathleen!
It's Miss Kennedy.
Who's hiding there?
What are you doing at this hour of the night?!
Well...
Miss Kennedy, a mouse!
Ah! A mouse?!
Kathleen, was that noise I heard
from this room just now also down to a mouse?
Yes. I think so, Miss Kennedy.
Very well.
If that's the case, I don’t see that there’s anything to report to Miss Roberts.
But you might want to see that it’s tidy
before Matron does her rounds tomorrow morning.
Good night.
Good night!
Wow! That was scary!
She saw those awful ginger-beer bottles all right—
fancy agreeing that it might have been mice!
My goodness! Kenny’s a sport!
She's the best teacher one could have!
"Kathleen, was that noise I heard
from this room just now also down to a mouse?"
Anyway, it seems that Miss Roberts
won't find out this time.
That was fun!
And delicious!
The midnight feast was a great success!
All five of you are unwell?!
My stomach feels queasy...
I know these symptoms very well.
You are suffering from Midnight Feast Illness!
You needn’t pretend to me!
Who told you?!
Nobody.
But I haven’t been Matron of a girls’ school
for twenty-five years for nothing!
One glance at your faces
is enough for me to know!
But don't you worry—I shan’t tell tales.
I always say there’s no need to punish girls
for having a midnight feast,
for the way they feel the next day—the bitter medicine
they must swallow—is punishment enough!
Ah... I love sardines, but I don’t think
I’ll ever be able to look a sardine in the face again.
Same here.
Although Kathleen's cake was something else.
I wanna try it again once.
Speaking of Kathleen,
don't you think she's altered a lot recently?
Yes. She seems much more active and happy now.
That's true. The old Kathleen was always so jumpy, you couldn't help teasing her.
Turns out she was always a cheerful and kind girl.
Yeah. I've come to view Kathleen differently now.
Ah, there you are!
Isabel, Belinda Towers sent for you.
For me?
I wonder why.
I know about your midnight feast.
Kathleen told me everything.
I laughed so hard my stomach hurts now!
Right...
By the way, our next lacrosse match
will be with the St. Christopher's School.
The full-day school in town?
I want to put two first form players on the field. One of them is Kathleen.
Even though I used to think her
too weak-willed to play before.
What do you think, Isabel?
You absolutely must choose Kathleen!
She's been acting a lot more confident lately.
I'm sure she'll do her best!
And the other one is you.
Huh? Me? Not Pat?
Pat is a perfect defender, but right now
I need a player who can score goals.
I'm impressed by the sharpness of your shots.
Thank you very much!
I'll do my best!
Sorry I'm late.
I bought the biscuits.
Thanks.
Kathleen's treating us.
I was going to buy something to celebrate myself,
but I couldn't find my money.
Yeah. Those biscuits are great!
I’ve found a delightful little sweet shop.
It happened again! Don't tell me...
Kathleen...
Huh? Isabel and Kathleen are gonna play?
I tried to tell her that Pat or Janet
were much better players...
What are you talking about?
If you hesitate, I'll start teasing you again!
Go there and show them all!
I'll come to cheer for you.
Attagirl!
Pat, I'll do my best!
Of course! I won't forgive you if you lose
to the likes of St. Christopher’s.
That’s right, I shouldn’t trouble myself
with any extra worries just now.
Just give it my all
preparing for that lacrosse match!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
I'm Pat!
I'm Isabel.
Hey, Pat, I need to tell you something important. It's about Kathleen!
Are you serious?
No, I can't believe it...
I didn't want to believe it either.
But when you think about it, it was when everyone’s money began disappearing
that Kathleen became
so generous and extravagant.
I really love Kathleen
the way she is recently.
But if that's true, we'll have to give up on her!
I really want to think I'm wrong...
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Poor Kathleen."
Episode 6
Poor Kathleen
Stay tuned!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End