Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
What is it?
An in-school lacrosse tournament.
A form-on-form?
That's all for today.
Also, start practising for the lacrosse
tournament from today.
Hilary, please go sort out
the field schedule at lunchtime.
Okay.
Miss Roberts!
What is it, Patricia?
Why is the lacrosse tournament
between the forms?
Obviously, the seniors are bound to win.
That’s what I think too.
Unless there’s some sort of handicap...
we’ll never stand a chance!
It’s not always the seniors who win, you know.
Huh?
Besides, this tournament is meant
to bring pupils together and foster teamwork.
Winning and losing isn’t everything.
That’s why everyone is required to take part.
Anyway, it’s only a week away.
Practise hard and enjoy yourselves.
Hey, twins.
It seems you just can’t rest easy
without grumbling about something.
But sport is only fun if you play to win!
Exactly! If you give up
from the start it’s no fun at all.
Right then, we’ll just have to win no matter what!
Right, Janet?
Okay!
Episode 15
The Lovely Miss Roberts
Joan! Sheila’s running for you!
Pass it!
What are you doing,
putting it in our own goal?
Sorry.
Come on, Joan, get a grip!
Your passing still isn’t good enough.
We’ll work on that from tomorrow.
Anyone who isn’t handy
with their stick had better practise.
Okay!
Joan, I don’t ask you to score,
but at least don’t help the other side score!
I’m not playing.
Everyone must take part—it’s the rule.
Oh, never mind who wins or loses.
Let’s just take it easy.
I’m more looking forward
to the tea party afterwards.
Hey, hey!
Did you see? I managed a pass!
I saw it. Well done!
See? Even I can do it when I try.
Joan?
Honestly, Joan!
We've barely started,
but she's already given up trying.
And the others don’t seem to be trying either.
We’ll never win at this rate.
How can you give up already?
Fine, I’ll train Joan myself.
Huh? Train me?
That's right.
If you practise every day,
you’ll improve before the match, right?
But I...
I’ll help too, with Kathleen.
Hold your stick higher!
Ready?
Y-Yeah!
There!
Joan! The ball won’t bite.
Keep your eyes on it.
Like this.
See?
Here we go! There!
Joan! Shoot!
That’s enough, I’m just no good at sports.
Not that it’s anything to boast of,
but I always come in last in P.T.
Joan, they're still offering refills.
I'll pass.
Oh, really? That’s unusual.
I always make a mess of it when it really matters.
I hate matches.
Why must I play no matter what?
Is your leg quite all right now?
Yes, I can run and jump again.
When I fell off the stage set, it hurt dreadfully—
I thought for certain I’d broken a bone.
That must have been awful.
Still, I’m glad it was nothing serious.
I wish all our P.T. lessons were lacrosse just now.
Yeah! With only three days left,
we ought to practise more.
I should really like that.
Oh, that's a rare sight—
Joan's climbed onto the balance beam!
Ouch...
Joan!
Ugh... My leg!
It hurts too badly!
Joan!
Let's get her to Matron, quickly!
How is it?
No need to fret; a poultice
and she’ll be better by tomorrow, no doubt.
Huh? But I... Ow-ow-ow!
Does it hurt so badly?
Yes!
Why, that’s serious! You might need to go into the town infirmary, then.
Huh? Oh no, it’s not such dreadful pain,
but I don’t think I can walk for a while.
In that case I’ll give you some special medicine.
It reminds me—I once gave this same drug
to another pupil often enough.
Her name was Felicia, if I remember aright.
Right, Miss Roberts?
Uh? Yes...
She was a plumpish girl, rather like Joan,
and not keen on games.
She particularly detested lacrosse.
Before P.T. she would often complain of stomach-aches,
and so I dosed her with this medicine.
Felicia’s great friend was Judy.
Judy had a weak leg,
so she never played games, only watched.
The two of them were thick as thieves.
But one day Felicia...
caught sight of Judy secretly practising lacrosse.
With her bad leg?
Yes.
Correct. But of course Judy couldn’t manage it,
and she was bitterly vexed.
“If only my leg were sound,
I’d prove myself good at it!” she cried.
When Felicia heard that,
it struck her like a blow.
She realised how shameful it was
to have a sound body and not use it.
From that very day,
Felicia began daily practice.
It was hard labour, indeed.
But thanks to it, she grew skilful—
not only at lacrosse but at other sports too.
How splendid!
And there was another benefit to it as well.
What was that?
Felicia soon became quite slim.
Well, the situation is settled now.
Go back to class.
I’ll see to the rest.
Okay!
What do you say, Joan?
Want to sit out P.T.?
Yes, Miss.
Do you suppose I could ever
grow good at lacrosse too?
Joan, human beings are curious creatures.
With effort and practice,
one improves little by little at anything.
Even at things one dislikes?
Of course, talent and disposition
do have their place,
but until you try, you can't know.
Maybe you just convinced yourself
you're no good?
Still, I think... I'd rather...
No pianist, however great,
began by playing Mozart or Chopin.
Not to test your own powers is sheer loss.
Don't you think, Joan?
To possess a sound body
and never use it—that is shameful.
Human beings are curious creatures.
With effort and practice,
one improves little by little at anything.
Not to test your own powers is sheer loss.
One, two, one, two, one, two, one, two!
U-Um...
Good morning, Joan.
Is your leg better?
Miss Roberts?
Yes! A-And, er...
I'm practising as well. We mistresses will have a match too. Want to do it together?
Yes!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Nearly there, Joan.
Release the ball a touch earlier
and try your shot again.
Okay.
See? Told you, it's Joan!
Oh? And Miss Roberts too.
Huh?
Yes! That timing's just right, Joan!
Hooray!
Miss Roberts!
Now, next, receive the pass and take your shot.
Yes, miss.
Miss Roberts rose early
just for Joan, didn’t she?
I daresay so.
I always thought Miss Roberts was too strict,
but she’s more complex than that.
She can be quite a considerate person too.
Yeah.
Here I go, Joan!
Catch!
So close! Once more!
Okay!
I hope we have a good match
the day after tomorrow.
We shall now decide the match-ups.
Representatives of each form, please gather.
Are you all ready?
Yes!
Never fear, Joan.
You today are not the Joan of a few days ago.
Have confidence.
O-Okay...
This is bad!
Our first match is against the Fifth Form.
Eh? Belinda's form?
To be drawn against the favourites, of all things!
Lousy luck!
We shan’t stand a chance!
What are you saying, all of you?
We do not yet know we shall lose.
That's right. One must never
throw a match from the start.
It is by playing the strong teams
that one gains skill.
Even if we lose, there is much to learn
if we apply ourselves.
Quite so!
Anyway, let’s do our best
and have a good game.
That’s the spirit!
And one never knows
what may happen in a match.
Indeed.
Let us all show them our overwhelming vigour!
Well said!
Yay!
Let’s do it!
Let’s give it our all.
The starting members and positions
are as decided yesterday.
First Home, Patricia.
Okay!
Second Home, Isabel.
Third Home, Vera.
Okay!
Right Attack Wing, Janet!
The first round
is Fifth Form against First Form.
Don't you dare lose to the freshmen!
Good luck!
Are you all right, Kathleen?
Yes. But what a shot!
As expected of Belinda.
Alison! Pass!
C'mon, Tess!
Belinda!
Got it!
Belinda is just too formidable.
Whenever the ball comes her way,
she always intercepts it.
Don't let Belinda run freely!
Try to get in her way!
Substitution!
Janet, get on the field.
Okay!
Now’s our chance!
Miss Roberts says, while Belinda’s absent,
go in and intercept everything!
Yeah. Everyone, let’s do our best!
Yeah!
Get this!
Halftime!
Delightful!
As expected of the twins,
you’re so well-coordinated!
Keep up that spirit and stay sharp.
We're already sharp!
We’re finding our stride now.
Turn the match around in the second half.
Okay!
The problem is Belinda.
We must mark her closely
and keep their goals to a minimum.
I wish I could just stay here
and not have to go out to play.
Attagirl, Isabel!
It's thanks to Alison!
All right, four minutes remaining!
Let’s give it our all!
Joan, switch with Vera.
Eh? M-Me?
Th-That's hopeless.
What are you saying?!
Just follow the practice—
receive the pass, then shoot.
Pat, Isabel, go get them!
Okay!
As practised...
As practised, when the ball comes...
Here it comes!
Shoot!
As practised...
She did it!
Joan!
Amazing, Joan!
Did it go in?
Of course! It’s all square.
Really?
Okay, now we take the lead!
Help!
No time left!
Just one more point!
Just one more!
Fifth Form versus First Form, 18 to 17, Fifth Form victorious.
'Twas a splendid match.
Thank you.
A fine shot! I never knew we had
such a strong point-getter in our school.
That was a close call—we almost lost!
Fifth Form! Keep going!
We shan’t forgive you if you lose!
Belinda, shoot!
As expected, the Fifth Form are champions!
After matching the champions blow for blow,
don't you think we deserve second place?
As always, Janet is only here
for the accolades!
The champions: Fifth Form.
We may not have won,
but it was a match of far greater value.
Isn't that right, Joan?
Yes, quite so.
Next, an exhibition match between
the victorious Fifth Form and the staff team.
Everyone, please cheer them on.
Headmistress is playing too?
It may be hard to tell now,
but I was once lacrosse captain. Watch and see.
Joan, I was watching it closely.
You were fabulous.
Thank you. I finally gained confidence,
thanks to you and all the other mistresses.
And most of all, I wish I could thank Felicia
for showing me what I am truly capable of.
But you can.
Look, there she is—Felicia Roberts!
I can scarcely believe strict Miss Roberts
had such a childhood.
She truly wished to share
her own experiences with Joan and us.
To teach us the importance of effort!
Felicia, fight!
Miss Roberts, do your best!
Miss Roberts!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Oh dear, Binks has run away
from Kathleen’s house!
That Binks... He ran all the way
to St. Clare's to see Kathleen.
But the rules forbid you to keep pets here!
Rules this, rules that—
it’s seriously tiresome!
No one may keep Binks but Kathleen.
And so a grand debate
on the subject of rules was held in class.
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"All-Night Debate!"
Episode 16
All-Night Debate!
Do look forward to it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End