Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Eyes, look your last.
Arms, take your last embrace.
And, lips, O, you
The doors of breath,
seal with a righteous kiss...
Um...
A dateless bargain.
A dateless bargain to engrossing death.
Ah, I'm no good!
Can I have the script for a moment?
Pat! Come on, get a grip!
Pat! You must stop dawdling and learn your lines—
we’ve only ten days left until the concert!
Sorry, I really...
This is the crucial point of the whole play!
It’s meant to be a heartbreaking scene of lovers dying,
torn apart by a feud between their families!
You have to feel it!
I understand, Madam Director.
I promise I'll memorize it all by tomorrow.
Hey, first form? Time's up.
Please vacate the stage.
Okay.
Ah, I really want more rehearsal time.
True. We have to compete for the gym.
Sheila?
I wonder what's up with Sheila?
Isabel, what's the hold-up?
Let's go have tea!
O-Okay!
Episode 12
A Disaster! Who Will Take the Role?
Ah... I'm bored.
The other roses are alive and well,
but this one's just like me.
Not like I can do anything about it.
A dateless bargain to engrossing...
Pat, why don't you stop memorizing lines
at least when you're having tea?
But I'm really strapped for time.
It must be hard.
I’m sure I’d fall flat at learning lines.
But learning the dance steps
is jolly hard too, isn’t it?
Y-Yes, but at least in dance, you learn it with your body rather than your head.
Really, I wish I had two heads sometimes.
Ol' Shakespeare's lines are a pain to learn.
That's true.
Hey, Pat, hasn't Sheila's been
rather gloomy lately?
Sheila’s taking part
in a French play, isn’t she?
Mam’zelle must be working her to the bone.
Abominable! That is not French.
So-so. Pat's impression was much more believable.
Huh? What's so-so?
Wait, really? Sheila won't be
in the French play either?
Yes, that's right.
And I thought she was going to be
in Romeo and Juliet.
Is she not?
No. That's weird, though.
I was sure Sheila was to play
the role of Monsieur Triomphal...
No, that role was assigned
to Mary from the beginning.
Goodness! Could it be that Sheila
didn't get a role at all, then?
Why?
No one invited me, that's why.
You should've told us.
We were just sure you were going to appear in that French play.
That's fine, I don't have
any special talent for it anyway, do I?
Sheila, we never said that.
If you didn't get a role, you should've affirmed it clearly with everyone present.
It's a school concert that we all create together,
so everyone must be a part of it.
There's no crying over spilt milk, is there?!
Everyone has their roles assigned
and is already busy rehearsing.
Who cares if I'm not a part of it?
Sheila, that sulky attitude
is almost downright foolish.
Because I am a fool, all right?!
So stop distracting me and leave me alone!
Huh? Really?
Yeah...
That Sheila...
I wonder why she kept quiet
about it up to now?
She felt left out.
Fancy that!
What is she, a little baby?
We can't babysit her all the time.
But we can't just leave her be
like this either, can we?
That's true.
It must be hard, being the only one
who doesn’t get to perform in the school concert.
Oh? What's that I'm hearing?
Now you suddenly care about Sheila?
Because I do sympathize with her!
In the past, I’ve also been pulled
from a lacrosse match I was meant to play in.
Why?
The captain made a mistake
and we had too many people on the field.
But the whole school was buzzing with rumours about why I was pulled,
and it’s been weighing on me a lot.
Incredible!
Look, you two!
I can be pretty sensitive too.
You two are lucky to have each other.
You can talk about anything,
support one another, and comfort one another.
When you’re like Sheila
and can’t share your troubles with anyone,
even the smallest thing feels like a huge deal.
But what can we do?
Maybe ask Miss Kennedy
to include an extra role?
Forget it. She’d struggle to memorize the lines on such short notice.
Her lines, right...
Right! I've got an idea!
Huh? What?
Prompter?
Yes, if someone forgets a line onstage,
you can prompt them by glancing at the script.
There's no way I can do that well.
Of course you can!
Just having you watch their backs
would give everyone confidence. Please.
All right.
O Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name,
Or, if thou wilt not, be but sworn my love,
and I'll no longer be a Capulet.
Shall I hear more, or shall I speak at this?
'Tis but thy name that is my enemy.
A-And...
Thou art thyself, though not a Montague...
Ah... Thou art thyself, though not a Montague.
Hey! News! I got news!
What is it, Pat?
It's about Sheila.
Sheila?
Old Sheila is still reading the script,
even this hour!
Wow, impressive!
She might just memorize it in full.
Asking Sheila to be a prompter
was the right call.
Yeah. Even if she looked disinterested at first.
Sheila really is a sport!
If I was given such a boring role,
I'd stop caring halfway through.
True! For Pat, it'd be impossible!
You didn't have to say it so clearly!
O Romeo, Romeo,
wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father...
Vera sure is lucky.
She gets to play Juliet.
Dad,
Mum,
The school concert is almost here.
I’ve memorized Romeo’s long speeches perfectly,
and our rehearsals run smoothly.
The performance preparations
are also in full swing.
We made everything ourselves—
the costumes and the props!
It's a shame you can't see it.
Once the school concert is over,
it's the long-awaited holiday!
We'll be bringing back lots of stories to tell,
so look forward to it!
Some shall be pardoned, and some punished.
For never was a story of more woe
Than this of Juliet and her Romeo.
Bravo!
You've all done a wonderful job.
It must be hard to tell such a long story
in just two episodes.
Juliet is only fourteen in the play.
About the same age as you.
I think you gave a convincing portrayal
of two young lovers’ devotion.
What do you think, Miss Roberts?
That's true.
For the short time you had to rehearse,
I think it turned out really well.
Oui, vraiment!
We’ll have to put in double the effort
if we want our French play to be just as good.
If I had to rate it,
I'd give you 85 out of 100.
Then, I'll be looking forward
to the actual performance.
This concludes the stage rehearsals.
Yes! Thank you very much!
Tomorrow's the day.
Ah, my heart is racing!
Let's do our best and bring it to 100/100!
Yay!
Hurry up, everyone!
The performances start in only two hours!
Okay! We'll be done soon!
All ready here, Pat.
O Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
You're so good at it, Vera!
Just keep this up
and carry it into the real thing.
We won't accept anything
less, you hear?!
Yeah, I know.
Then, let's move the costumes now.
Okay!
Vera!
It... hurts...
Are you okay, Vera?
Vera...
The Twins at St. Clare's
Ouch!
Ah, it looks to me
like you've badly hurt your ankle.
No fracture, most likely, but it’s better
to get an X-ray at the hospital just to be sure.
Got it, I'll call a car.
Are you okay, Vera?
I'm sorry, girls. I'm making you all worry.
And the school concert...
Vera...
It's a shame, but it doesn't seem
that Vera will be able to perform.
What are we gonna do?
We can’t very well stage a play without Juliet.
That's true.
I guess we'll just have to give up for today
and try to perform it some other time.
Ah... It was coming together so nicely...
That's true.
I’ve been trying so hard to memorize my lines,
but if I relax now, I’ll forget the lot.
It’d be such bad luck if we couldn’t stage the final performance after coming this far.
Girls.
Not everything in life
always goes according to plan.
Things that throw a spanner in the works
happen all the time.
That's when your true value is put to test.
Do your best to see if there’s a way
to get yourselves out of this crisis.
Why don't we try to salvage this?
Yes! As long as you're doing your best,
it's okay to fail.
Yeah! If you just give up,
nothing will come out of it.
But who's going to play Juliet?
We have her. We have a Juliet!
Huh?
We have a girl who can play Juliet!
Who?
Someone who remembers all the lines
and movements. Right, Sheila?
Huh?
I see!
That’s right! How come it didn’t
occur to me right away?
What, me?
Don't be unreasonable.
I can't do it. I don't have the confidence.
Yes you can!
Please Sheila, help us out!
We'll all be supporting you!
It'll be fine.
Let's do it, Sheila!
B-But...
You ought to try.
Huh?
Yes. I'm sure Vera would be happy
to know you agreed to do it.
I'll try my best.
Sheila...
Nice!
What a relief!
Hilary, speak to the head girl and ask her to rearrange
the program so that our play comes last.
Okay.
We'll rehearse at once!
I'll get the costumes!
The script!
And the props!
There have been changes to the program.
Due to unforeseen circumstances, the Romeo and Juliet play, which was supposed to be first,
will now be the final performance of the night.
Thank you for understanding.
O Romeo, Romeo,
wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name...
Or, if thou...
Or, if thou wilt not, b-be...
Be but sworn my love.
N-No...
I forgot everything!
I can't do it!
Sheila!
No, it really is impossible for me.
I'm just gonna ruin the play for everyone!
It's not impossible!
Vera!
Are you okay, Vera?
Yes, the bones are intact;
she just got a sprain—a bad one.
Thank God!
Sheila, Miss Kennedy told me what happened.
I'll be a prompter for you.
Good luck!
But if I mess up...
Doesn’t matter! We can all attest that you’ve been
giving your very best despite all the odds.
Right! Let’s just enjoy ourselves and give it our all, come what may!
Please, Sheila. Let's try our best, okay?
Okay, Sheila?
Let's do it!
I'll do it.
With Vera's help!
Sure! Leave it to me.
Wow, what a relief!
It suits you just right!
I'm sorry, it was meant to be worn by Vera.
What are you saying?
I'm the one who must apologize
for letting everyone down like that.
In truth, I was jealous of Vera.
I wanted to play Juliet myself.
But I never imagined
it would turn out like this...
Sheila I'm happy that you agreed to understudy me. I mean it!
The first half’s over, and everyone’s heading to the cafeteria. Want to come?
I don't feel like eating right now.
I need to rehearse!
We'll help!
Me too.
R-Really?
I'll bring sandwiches for everyone. Wait here!
I-I'm coming too!
Hey, are you madly excited too?
I feel unstoppable right now.
Same here!
Okay, no time to waste.
Let's do one more.
I don't see Hilary and the others from her form.
They must still be rehearsing.
They're awfully agitated.
They'll be starved afterwards, then.
Please set their meals aside for later.
Okay.
Binks!
Sorry I'm late!
There!
Who's a good dog?
Binks, I gotta run now, so see you later.
She's almost about done.
Get ready.
Ah, good Lord...
Are you all set?
Yes.
It's torn!
Don’t worry, we can fasten it with a safety pin.
Kathleen, tell Doris to buy us some time.
Got it!
Binks!
It's done.
Thank God...
We present to you today a sad story of love
between young Romeo and Juliet.
In fair Verona our scene is set,
where an ancient grudge has bound the noble families
of Montague and Capulet in endless strife.
First, let us look at the sacrifice of love
made by two pure souls,
as they strive to melt the icy walls
that separate the two families.
And the selfless tears
of the unfortunate couple.
He jests at scars that never felt a wound.
But soft, what light through yonder window breaks?
It is the East, and Juliet is the sun.
Arise, fair sun,
and kill the envious moon!
O Romeo, Romeo, wherefore art thou Romeo?
Deny thy father and refuse thy name...
Looking good, Sheila.
Or, if thou wilt not, be but sworn my love,
And I'll no longer be a Capulet.
Shall I hear more, or shall I speak at this?
O churl, thee drunk it all, my love?
Haply some poison yet doth hang on thy lips.
Enough to make me die with a restorative.
Thy lips are warm still!
Thy lips are warm still...
Lead, boy! Which way?
Yea, noise?
Then I'll be brief.
O, happy dagger,
This body is thy new sheath.
My Romeo... My Romeo!
There rust, and let me die.
Some shall be pardoned,
and some punished.
For never was a story of more woe Than this of Juliet and her Romeo.
We did it!
Sheila, you were incredible!
Well done! You got us through this crisis!
Thank you, everyone.
Sheila, you did great.
Prepare for a curtain call.
Okay!
Today, Sheila Naylor saved us
in our hour of need by urgently stepping in
for Vera Johns, the actress playing Juliet, who was injured.
Please give another
round of applause to Sheila
and her classmates
for their outstanding performance.
Sheila, you were the best.
Everyone... Everyone was amazing.
So much has happened these past few days.
The theatre is wonderful!
I've never felt so connected to everyone before.
Friendship is wonderful!
I don't think I'll ever forget this day.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Pat, we're in trouble!
What is it, Isabel?
It seems Miss Kennedy
will have to leave St. Clare's.
Huh?
The history teacher, Miss Lewis, who’s been on sick leave for a long time,
is coming back, so Miss Kennedy
will have to step down!
No way!
Pat, I've decided not to attend her final class.
I'll probably burst into tears!
That's right! I won't be able to live
without seeing Old Kenny!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Goodbye, Miss Kennedy."
Episode 13
Goodbye, Miss Kennedy
Look forward to it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End