Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Nice! I'm done!
Ready for half-term holiday?
Quiet, please!
You girls are so restless!
It seems the half-term holiday
is the only thing on your minds.
We'll have a test after the break to see how well you grasped today's material.
Not again!
By the way, is there anyone here whose parents
won’t be visiting her over the next
two days of the holidays?
Yes!
Yes...
Got it. Those of you in that category
will come with me to a play tomorrow afternoon.
Nice!
That is all I have to say.
Let's all have a fun half-term holiday.
Episode 9
Sheila's Secret
Oh, but it is true!
We have five bathrooms at home—
all in different colours!
Pink, blue, green, cream,
and even violet!
Oh? It sounds like a fairyland!
We also have three cars.
Did I ever tell you about that?
You did, Sheila. We've heard that more times than we can count.
And eight servants, right?
Yes!
I bet your mother will turn up
to collect you in a Rolls-Royce tomorrow.
Yes, the Rolls.
But my mother won't be coming here herself.
She's staying at the best hotel in town!
And I'll stay there too!
Yes, come to think of it, we’ve never actually seen your mother in person, Sheila.
She's too busy! Even tomorrow she's got another meeting lined up with the town's top brass.
Hey, everyone, if you've ever fancied a ride in a Rolls, I can take you for a quick spin.
We bought a new horse the other day!
It's a terribly costly thoroughbred,
descended from a Derby winner!
"We have five bathrooms..." Humph!
I wonder if she thinks baths are only for games,
since she doesn't even wash the back of her neck.
Hey, why do you think Sheila is bragging so much about being rich?
It was especially bad today, Janet was about to tell her everything she thinks of her!
She was properly getting on my nerves too!
She knows full well that Doris and Kathleen have no visitors,
yet she keeps on with all that
"My mother… Rolls-Royce…" nonsense.
How insensitive can she be?!
Yes...
But while I feel bad for Kathleen and the others,
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow!
It's been so long since we last saw Mum!
A car!
It's Mum's car!
Mum!
Hello!
Hello there! You two look lively.
Yes! We very much are!
You're the first to come today, Mum!
I couldn't wait to see you two.
Hey, Mum, you should've heard
how the art teacher praised me the other day!
And I've knitted a sweater
in home economics class!
Hold on a minute.
We'll have plenty of time to talk later.
Right now, I must meet Headmistress.
Right.
We'll take you to the headmistress's office!
This way!
Hurry!
I wonder if she'll give us out completely.
That French assignment we submitted in the middle of the night and all...
And the fire-cracks incident...
Ah! What are we gonna do?
What's the matter?
D-Did Headmistress tell you anything?
Only that you are wonderful students,
always attentive to your friends.
Thank God...
Well, how how about I drive you two out now?
I'm sure you have a lot to tell me about.
Yeah!
Wow! Pat's and Isabel's Mum is so gorgeous!
She's elegant and she's kind.
I'm jealous!
Nice to meet you, Madame O'Sullivan.
My name is Sheila Naylor.
Pat, Isabel, and I are always socializing together.
The pleasure is mine, Sheila.
It's a Rolls-Royce!
It must be Sheila's family car!
Would you children happen to know my Sheila?
Y-Yes, she's in the same class as us.
Oh? Why, that's capital!
Thank you ever so much for looking after my Sheila—
you truly are such lovely and splendid ladies.
Ah, Sheila?
Why won't you become
a little more ladylike yourself?
Wh-What's the matter with you?
Didn't I tell you to stay in town?!
B-But I just had to say hello to your teachers...
Oh, for goodness's sake!
Just drive already!
It seems to me you’ve taken quite a liking to St. Clare’s, even though you were so against it at first.
It's not a bad school.
Yes, quite decent indeed.
I wouldn’t mind moving you
to another school now, if you’d like.
Come on, Mum!
We're just fine here.
Just as you told us, the headmistress here is a wonderful person!
We admire Miss Roberts too.
And all our seniors and friends
are such good girls!
We love it here at St. Clare's!
Your father is eager as well to see you,
to know in what ways you two have changed.
We miss him too.
We'll be the best in everything—
even studying by then!
Tell him I'll do my very best at the next finals!
I look forward to it.
Oh, look...
Sheila… how much longer are you going to sulk?
It's natural for parents
to come to their child's school.
Not for all of them.
Huh? Did you say something?
It's nothing!
I'll be happy to go shopping with you.
I can shop on my own just fine!
I can help pick the most elegant and fine clothes
to make you look like a proper lady.
I get it, all right?
Um... Are you Sheila's mother?
Yes.
I'm Patricia O'Sullivan.
I'm Isabel O'Sullivan.
We are Sheila's classmates.
Oh, is that so?
I'm delighted to see you!
For some reason, Sheila hates it
when I come to her school.
When I ask her to introduce me to her friends,
she doesn't even listen!
Is my Sheila studying the ways of the school as she should?
Huh? Yeah...
Um... You know, Sheila really likes to tell us about her family. Right?
Yeah, all the time.
That's a relief!
I want my Sheila to learn
everything good she can from St. Clare's.
Please get along well, won't you?
Okay.
Who was that?
Sheila's mother.
She looks like a very amicable and kind mother.
If Sheila were more like that,
she'd be a lot easier to get along with.
That's true.
Isabel...
Pat...
Let's do our best!
The suite where my mother and I stayed had five rooms!
We stayed at the most
expensive suite of that hotel...
Give it a rest, Sheila!
I'm worried you forgot
your holiday is already over!
Goodness, but why oughtn't I,
if I'm just talking about it?
"But why oughtn't I?"
Where did you say
you were brought up again?
Haven’t you learnt by now that true
decent people don’t say "why oughtn't I?"
I've been meaning to say this for a while...
I'm all out of patience for your haughty bragging!
You always talk about your life of opulence—
and then you talk like the daughter of the dustman!
I can see right through you!
I-If only my people knew that St. Clare's
has girls like you with no notion of manners...
Manners? Oh, what is it I'm hearing?
What about your own manners?
You can begin to talk about other people’s when you know how to wash your neck
and brush your hair, and how to eat decently!
Janet, don't you think
you went too far this time?
It's Sheila's fault...
I thought you people were just as fed up
with her bravado as I am!
That's just how Janet is.
She finally lost her temper.
But it's understandable.
Sheila's attitude can be ridiculous indeed.
I really don't understand Sheila.
Why does she need to conduct herself that way?
Her mother hasn’t a trace
of pretence about her.
But Sheila is the complete opposite...
Something must be wrong with Sheila.
I'm quite tired of her nonsense.
The Twins at St. Clare's
Sheila isn't here, even though it's the evening preparation time...
Come to think of it, I haven't seen her
during tea time either.
Sheila...
Isn't your name Pat?
It's the evening preparation time
for the first formers.
Did something happen to Sheila?
Yes. You see...
I see. It's a good thing you told me.
I know Sheila very well.
Huh?
We come from the same village—
her mother is the daughter of our gardener.
The Naylors were once terribly poor.
But in the end her father opened a shop, made a great success of it, and was soon comfortably off.
I met Sheila's mother the other day.
She said she wanted Sheila to learn
everything good she can from St. Clare's.
Is that so?
She must really want her only daughter to grow up into a graceful lady.
But you know, there are always those who envy the successful.
They called the Naylors the upstart bumpkins.
Oh...
Being poor must be awfully embarrassing to Sheila,
so that's what she feared the most.
What she wanted the least was
her St. Clare's friends seeing her as an upstart.
So that's why she's so reluctant
to introduce us to her mother?
She put on this absurd, high-handed front,
like a wall to keep her secrets safe.
But her manners and language
stem from the time when she was little.
So Janet broke through that wall,
hitting where it hurts the most?
I wish Sheila just stayed the same as before...
She lacks confidence in herself,
so please spare a thought for her.
Yes, of course!
Sheila! I was looking for you.
Are you unwell?
It's nothing.
Let's go, then!
Isn't it cold here?
I'm not going.
I can't face you all ever again.
Why?
Because of what Janet said!
Fancy taking any notice that!
You know Janet always says things she doesn’t mean when she...
We both know she said things she did mean!
Oh, I hate Janet!
Y-You're right, she’s dreadfully quick-tempered and impatient, but she’s very kind too.
I met your mother
in town the other day.
You've such a lovely mother!
Lovely? Spare me your sarcasm.
But how can I not call her lovely
when she's so amicable, warm, and kind?
She was very worried about you,
asked if you're studying the ways of St. Clare's...
You bet I do!
And I'm learning how to be a lady, all right?
Sheila, I'm sure you just got
a wrong impression.
Wrong impression?
Ah, here you are, Sheila.
Good timing. I need a favour from you.
Would you help me out?
Yes.
Wow, it's beautiful!
As expected of Charles's granddaughter.
Please don't talk about my granddad!
But why not?
I don't want to be reminded
that I'm the grandchild of a gardener.
Please...
What a lovely scent.
Charles really was a great gardener.
Hey, Sheila, do you remember it?
Our rose garden.
This way, Sheila!
Wait! Wait for me, Winnie!
Charles took care of the roses with all his heart.
I'm sure the roses understood it too,
and so they always bloomed beautifully.
You'd think Charles was a magician.
He was always such a serene
and dignified person.
Is he doing well?
Y-Yes.
He moved to the countryside
and is taking it easy.
Your parents resemble Charles too.
Huh?
They’re friendly and approachable,
and can understand others’ feelings so well
that I can’t help but admire them.
Y-You can't be serious!
It isn’t appearance, wealth,
or family background that defines a person.
It's your character that matters.
Sheila, I really think you should be proud
of Charles and your parents.
If you excuse me...
Sheila...
Just being who you really are
is the best thing to do.
I'm not going to apologise!
We're not asking you to apologise!
Just try to be a little more understanding towards Sheila.
You really did strike Sheila
where it hurts most—with all your might!
Someone had to knock her down a peg!
Maybe you're right, but you also
have to avoid hurting her.
That's what it means to be friends!
Winifred, the head-girl,
already tried talking to Sheila.
We should give her a chance too.
That's true. If Sheila has any common sense in her,
she would try to refine her ridiculous attitude.
Wouldn't it be infinitely better if we made Sheila change instead? Right, Janet?
All right.
She's here!
Janet!
Y-Yeah...
Sheila, how about some candies?
Thank you, Janet.
Pat and Isabel told me your mother seemed to them a really jolly, cordial person.
Huh? Right...
She must be a wonderful person,
truly the epitome of motherhood!
Why didn't you ever introduce us?
I'm sure I'd have loved her!
I was under the impression
she must be an outstanding cook.
That's right, Sheila!
Yes, though she can manage
only plain country fare…
Just like my grandma!
Now I wanna try her cooking
next time she's here.
That's right, Sheila.
Could you please ask your mother?
Ah, the food for the miserable
starving young ladies...
Mum's speciality is pies.
She also likes making sweets.
I'll write her to send something over next time.
Wow!
Oh, I’m certain I’ll be a marvellous cook too
when I have kids!
Oh, I wouldn't have any doubts about you, Joan!
If you become a mum, at least your kids will eat well.
Janet!
They're all so loveable people.
In comparison, I've been so...
It's your character that matters.
But what can I do to be more like them?
Such a nice scent!
I wonder who put those here.
They're wonderful!
Flowers are known to soothe the heart.
Now then, let's all study in high spirits.
Ah, here too!
Sheila, was it you?
Uh? Yes...
Wow, that must've cost you!
U-Um...
The true worth of these roses
isn't in the price.
Only when tended with love
do roses repay it by blooming beautifully.
I just wanted to show you
how grateful I am to all of you.
Thank you, Sheila.
They are wonderful roses.
You have great taste!
Yeah, they're a fancy addition to our school!
Is that so?
But that was to be expected.
After all, I'm the granddaughter
of Charles, the supreme gardener!
Sheila has really begun to change.
Not a hint of her usual swagger now!
Perhaps too quiet now—
I sometimes forget she’s there!
That's true. She could definitely do
with a bit more of self-assertion.
But it's still a huge improvement.
I hope she becomes
even nicer a person from now on!
I'm glad we decided to give Sheila a chance.
Yes. I guess that means
we made another great friend today.
Wh-What?
You two are talking about giving someone a chance now, huh?
This reminds me of the time we once gave a chance
to a certain pair of stuck-up twins before.
My word, you were quite unbearable back then!
Well, at least they're
a lot more agreeable these days.
Janet!
Don't hurt me!
Get back, you!
Like hell we'll give any chance to you!
That's right! You don't deserve that!
I don't need it!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
When we went out to town with Kathleen,
we picked up an injured puppy.
We wanted to take him to the vet,
but there's no vet practice around here.
So Kathleen proposed taking it to school.
Even though pets are a big no-no at our school!
But Katherine just loves animals too much.
Will she be able to take good care of it?
More importantly,
if someone finds out about it...
she'll be expelled!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Breaking the School Rules Together!"
Episode 10
Breaking the School Rules Together!
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End