Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
You've not much time!
Okay!
Quick!
Sure you don't want me to see you off?
It's okay!
Give my regards to Miss Roberts.
Write to us soon.
Okay! We're off!
Hi! Isabel, Pat!
Alison?
How are you, my dear twin cousins?
I came to pick you up.
Came to pick us up?
Don't you know?
I'll be going to St. Clare's with you now.
What?!
Oh? So my mum didn't tell yours?
Speaking of which, recently...
she's been asking me all sorts of things about St. Clare's on the phone.
And starting this semester,
she decided to send me there too.
Why is this happening to us?!
Alison, you'd really be better off
going to Ringmere!
Why is that you must come where we go?
Isabel, Pat, take good care of your cousin.
Yes, you'll be reliable guides
through St. Clare's for her.
Oh, you mustn't be concerned, uncle and aunt.
I know how to take care of myself,
no special babysitting needed.
Let's go now!
Our fun new semester...
is getting messed up because of her?
Like we'll stand for it!
Episode 14
The Homework is Burned!
Alison.
Change into your uniform
as soon as you arrive at the station.
Why?
Miss Roberts is going to get mad.
Really? Over something like this?
Don't underestimate Miss Roberts's strictness.
I should be fine changing
when I get to school.
Girls!
Hallo, twins!
Kathleen! Has Binks been behaving well since you brought him to your aunt's house?
Yes. He may have been a little too energetic, though—he gave auntie a shock!
Didn't you feel sad when it was time to leave?
Yes, sort of.
Goodness me, twins! Did you become even prettier while I wasn't watching?
Oh, but shouldn't we be saying that?
You're all so much prettier now!
St. Clare's students bloom more
with every break they take.
But the only real progress we have
is with words, it seems.
Oi, girls, we brought someone along!
Our cousin Alison.
Huh? Where did she go now?
Your cousin will be changing schools?
That's right...
Good morning, everyone.
Ah! Miss Roberts!
Good morning!
You all seem jolly well together.
Yes!
Isabel, Pat, where is your cousin, Alison?
About that...
She was with us just a moment ago...
Who?
Alison!
Where have you been?!
I went to buy this.
Geez...
What's the matter, Isabel, Pat?
Won't you introduce me to the class?
And who's this old trout?
Old trout?!
It's Miss Roberts!
Introduce yourself properly!
This pretty lady is our teacher?
Golly, that's a delight!
I've heard a lot about you from Isabel and Pat.
Huh?!
I'm Alison O'Sullivan.
Mighty pleased to meet you.
I'm counting on you.
However, Alison...
Yes?
What is that outfit?
Golly! You like my outfit too?
I was also considering a green jacket,
but decided to go with this.
The new semester begins now.
Change into your uniform at once.
Huh? O-Okay...
I was actually planning to change on the train.
Be prepared: St. Clare’s is well ahead of Ringmere School in their curriculum.
I'm sure I'll manage, so rest easy.
Cleaning, laundry, mending our clothes—
we do everything ourselves!
Huh?
No way!
It's true!
It really is!
How can I do that?!
Don't we have maids for that kind of thing?
A girl your age should be able
to do that at least!
One should be embarrassed if she's not!
Why are you laughing?
Because not so long ago,
you two talked the same way Alison does now.
Yes, that sounds about right!
Ah, I'm still hungry...
Ah, right! That's what I brought a cake for.
It won't be cheap for you, though.
Just kidding!
Are you okay?
So-so.
Hey you, the girl in the isle!
Me?
Yes. You're a newcomer, aren't you?
What's your name?
Alison O'Sullivan.
Alison? Can't you keep it quiet?
Me? But I wasn't particularly loud already.
Look, we’ve got a shovelful of French homework to get through, so we’re cramming like mad right now.
So what?
So what...?
Your loud bawling is both distracting
and a thorough nuisance!
I want you to stay quiet.
You shouldn't have been slacking off
during vacations.
Huh?
What was that?!
We've no time for that!
We need to finish our homework!
That person is Rita George.
She's so scary even most of the seniors
prefer not to get in her way.
Ooh, I'm scared!
You should be more careful.
She might even summon you later.
Summon?
Okay, look...
If that’s all there is to being summoned,
it’s a piece of cake!
What do you mean?
Because even if I wanted to, I haven’t the faintest idea how to light the stove or polish the shoes.
It’d be no use asking me to do it.
And that's also exactly the kind of thing
Isabel and Pat used to say!
Because everyone at Redroofs is like that.
But you're not at Redroofs any more.
You'll also have to work hard now.
Work hard?
To think I'd hear such a thing
from the O'Sullivan twins, of all people!
Not quite how I expected this place to be.
Seems fine so far.
Naturally!
Try to understand, Alison.
If you don't start taking seriously what we say,
we won't be able to help you!
Ah, that's Matron!
Isabel, Pat, how was it?
Did you enjoy your vacation?
Yes!
This time, we brought our cousin along.
Ah, Alison, right?
Ah! Matron!
You look like such a hearty person,
just as my cousins described you!
Goodness, did you really say that?
We still need to check in your luggage,
so come to the dorm later.
Okay!
Gee, Alison, are you really going
to talk to everyone like that?
Don't give others such obvious compliments!
Flattery will get you everywhere.
Headmistress, this is our cousin Alison!
Pleased to meet you.
You girls are certainly cousins.
I can already see a resemblance to Isabel and Pat.
You think so?
I always thought we aren't much alike.
She said we're alike, didn't you hear?
Regardless, you're just like I imagined you to be, Headmistress!
No, you're probably
even more virtuous than that.
I'm glad I came to St. Clare's.
If that feeling is sincere,
please do your best.
Okay...
Alison is still as dry as ever
and only thinks about herself.
Yet she's already thinking a lot of herself.
It was a relief when they didn't put us in the same room today.
Keeping an eye on her around the clock
would've been a pain.
I just hope it all goes well, that's all.
Vous savez, en France il y a beacoup d'artists.
Par exemple: poète,
écrivain, peintre. Alors...
My!
Alison!
Oh, to hell with it!
The first day of classes came to a close without any serious incidents, it seems.
If only we manage to keep this up...
Where is Alison, the newcomer?
Alison!
What?
You're Alison, right?
Rita and Katie from the sixth form sent for you.
Go there at once.
The Twins at St. Clare's
I'm never gonna clean someone's boots!
It’ll make my hands dirty,
and soap always irritates my skin.
But you can't leave the campus
without a senior's permission.
You can't go down to town!
It's that town we passed through yesterday?
Why would I want to go
to such a rural town anyway?
Suit yourself, then!
Ah... Pat!
I see Pat is still as short-tempered as ever.
And you're still as hell-bent as ever.
I'm just a very ordinary girl.
One way or another, listening to your seniors
is the rule of this school, got it?
I've read the school rules,
it doesn't say that anywhere.
It doesn't have to—
it's been agreed on since forever!
And who agreed on it?
Oh, you...
Alison, if that's your final word,
I wash my hands of it.
No need to get so overly serious about it.
Just let me handle this.
Off I go now.
You've finally finished it?
Yeah!
Come in.
Alison, right?
Yes!
Wow! Those cakes look delicious!
Can I have one too?
Who said they were for you?
They are for us—the sixth formers—to eat!
We’re celebrating finishing our homework.
Ah, but... What if you leave some over?
Even if we do, that has nothing to do with you!
Now go—light up the stove,
boil some water, and clean our boots!
Um...
What?
I don't know how to light the stove.
Seriously?
Yep.
You've never done it at home?
Oh, I would sure like to see what kind of parent
doesn't even teach their daughter that!
Are you saying everyone else can do it?
Of course!
Then what's stopping you
from doing it yourself?
What was that?!
And here I was, thinking
it was actually something important.
Excuse me!
Wait a minute.
I'm Winifred, the head girl.
Head girl? So that's why you look
so reasonable and smart!
What's the big idea—
disregarding your seniors?
You see, it doesn't bother me
that I can't leave the campus.
But that's not all!
You might get kicked out of the school
for breaking our long-standing tradition.
That's quite all right.
I'll just come right back in.
You really don't understand, do you?
That means expulsion!
Expulsion?
U-Understood!
I'll light the stove at once.
The fire still hasn’t caught?
Yeah. Not at all.
What are you doing?
Of course you can't start a fire out of nothing!
First you put in some paper
and set fire to that!
Ah, is that so?
Goodness, that Alison...
Let's see...
Um... Where can I find some paper?
Can't you see it on that desk?
I wonder what's even in her head...
That's true!
My word, where was she brought up, really?
But weren't we like that at first too?
That's also true, actually.
It's burning!
It burned well!
That's only natural.
What's wrong, Rita?
My homework...
My homework is on fire!
Step back!
Um... Your homework?
The French homework we're supposed
to submit to Mam'zelle tomorrow.
Huh?
H-How come...?
Why did you burn it?!
B-But you told me
the paper was on the desk.
I told you to take the newspapers
that were on it!
Couldn't you open your eyes for once
and check if it was in French or not?!
Alison! Apologise!
We're sorry!
She didn't do it on purpose!
What's it to me if it was on purpose or not?!
It took me several days
to finally finish that homework...
This is no joke.
Um... And what if we go to Mam'zelle
and explain the situation?
Let's do that!
Forget it.
Why?
It is Mam'zelle's policy that you must turn in
your homework by the appointed date,
no matter the circumstances.
But... it wouldn't hurt to try!
Alison, you're coming with us!
I understand the situation.
But I can't just tell Rita that it's okay for her
not to turn in her homework.
I expect her homework
on my desk tomorrow, as arranged.
So it's hopeless...
What's hopeless?
We had hoped that you
wouldn't be quite as strict today...
But if it took Rita days to finish that homework,
there's no way she can redo it all by tomorrow!
That's right! It wouldn't be possible!
Um... What would happen
if she doesn't submit it?
Then Rita wouldn't be able to graduate.
Huh?
Wouldn't be able to graduate?
However, I don't believe it would come to that.
Wh-What do you mean?
She can't finish it by tomorrow, can she?
Our school has something we call
"The Spirit of St. Clare's."
The Spirit of St. Clare's?
You'll understand soon.
I say, just sit back and watch.
I can't believe what Alison has done.
True. That won't just blow off.
What do you think that Spirit of St. Clare's that Mam'zelle told us about could be?
I wonder...
Wanna go and see how it goes?
Right now?
All right.
They're all helping Rita with her homework!
Should we bring them a midnight snack?
Yes, let's do that.
It's Matron!
It's us!
A snack for you.
Please help yourselves.
While the tea is still hot.
I'll take you up on that.
Thank you.
That snack was great.
You girls can return to your dorm now.
But...
Please let me stay here.
Me too.
It's hopeless!
Why do you say that?
We still have three hours left.
It's not that.
We can't possibly finish this without a map
of 19th century downtown Paris at hand!
Huh?
On that, I wrote down all the cafes
and avenues that Musset frequented.
They are essential for a thorough study
of Musset’s youth.
Musset... You mean the French poet?
The subject of Rita’s homework
is the life of Musset,
one of the four great Romantic poets
and the author of the play No Trifling with Love.
We could recover everything else from memory,
but without that map with Rita’s markings…
Just as we're so close to finishing it...
Hey, sure you can't recall it?
I've also included a couple
of Musset's unique private poems,
but that's now lost too.
If we don't find that...
Alison!
What are you doing here?
This is all I could recover...
Isn't that just some burned scraps?
Yes, of the homework.
But maybe you can still read something
that was written on it.
I thought that maybe
it could be of use to you.
I-It's here!
The map I used!
Is that true?!
Yes, it's true.
Thank you, Alison.
Finished it
Thank God!
Well now, Rita.
It seems you've done it, after all.
If anyone's in trouble,
everyone will help her out.
That's the Spirit of St. Clare's!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
The school lacrosse tournament
will be held in a week.
But Joan says she won't come out on the field!
Everyone must participate!
It's not just Joan—it doesn't seem like anyone is taking it seriously.
I guess we can kiss victory goodbye.
We've never given up before,
so to hell with starting now!
Here's the plan: I'll give personal
special training to Joan.
But then a terrible incident struck!
Joan fell off the balance beam
and got hurt badly.
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Lovely Miss Roberts."
Episode 15
The Lovely Miss Roberts
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End