Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
I wonder what's causing this.
Whenever I’m working out these equations,
my eyelids simply drop.
It’s the eighth wonder of the world.
Oh?
What's the matter?
Ah...
This young, love-struck Janet
kisses you in her dreams every night.
Maybe a trifle too forward?
Well, never mind.
Janet!
Wh-What's your deal, sneaking up on me?!
Is that a love letter?
To whom on earth?
It's S-Secret!
It's Jimmy...
From the circus!
Hiya!
Episode 18
The Great Tarot Fortune-Telling Craze!
I never guessed Janet would...
write...
to Jimmy!
Have you been sending him
dozens upon dozens of letters?
S-So what if I have?
And has he ever answered?
An answer? How rude to ask!
To expect an answer would be indelicate.
Ah... Jimmy being lodged
in my heart is enough for me.
Whoa!
Have you got any letters for me today?
That answers it.
I’ve already sent a dozen.
He could've written at least once in return.
Jimmy does travel a lot, doesn’t he?
Perhaps the letters never reached him.
Or perchance...
he was taken ill?!
Hey, Janet!
If you’re anxious, you should have Margot of the fifth form read your fortune.
Eh?
They say she’s a dab hand at the tarot.
Her divining is frightfully accurate.
It's all the rage in the fifth form just now!
Tarot fortune-telling?
Tarot cards harbour a curious magic.
That magic,
and the reader’s gift,
may pierce present, past, and future.
Margot even foretold
Pamela’s sister’s marriage to the letter.
Now then, Janet, I will divine whether a reply will come from this youth called Jimmy.
Y-Yes, please do.
This card represents his present.
The present?
Rest easy; he is hale and hearty.
Ah... How relieving!
And...
Oh? He's a gentle sort of lad, is he not?
I-Indeed he is!
Blimey! How did you know that?
I see...
D-Did you understand something?
Janet, you have waited so long for his reply, have you not?
It must have been hard for you.
Yes! It really has.
So... will an answer come?
Do not be impatient.
Wh-What does it mean?
Alas, the cards show no reply will come.
Eh?
They tell me the letters have not been received.
O-Oh no...
Janet...
But do not be downcast, Janet.
Look here.
I see a token of good fortune very near at hand.
A token of good fortune?
Some small windfall
may all at once befall you.
I... I see...
A sudden windfall?
Sounds a tad suspicious, doesn’t it?
I don’t much trust these fortunes, to tell you the truth.
Why so?
Because whatever they say to you
is always the fancy stuff you want to believe.
"He's a gentle sort of lad, is he not?"
"Yes! Indeed he is."
"He is hale and hearty."
"How relieving!"
But it did indeed seem
like things worked out well today.
Did it, really?
Janet, what's wrong?
A sudden windfall!
What, really?
Janet, do you seriously believe it?
Is Janet here?
Oh... Yes!
I checked the lending card, you see.
Didn’t you borrow this book half a year ago?
Inside it, with your report,
you forgot your pocket-money.
I thought it was lost for good!
Whoa! Ten shillings!
Hurrah! What luck!
See? It came true...
My sudden windfall!
No mistake—
the fortune was right!
Extraordinary!
I’m bound to believe it now!
Margot, please!
Do teach me how to read the tarot!
I long to work miracles
with fortune-telling too.
I beg you, please!
Hey, what do you make of it, Pat?
Eh?
Could Janet’s ten-shilling miracle be genuine?
Codswallop! She only blundered six months ago.
Where’s the miracle in that?
Right...
Hm?
What?
Janet’s begun telling fortunes?
Ugh, bother!
I ought to have charged a shilling a head,
seeing how it’s thriving.
They’re only in it for the lark.
It’ll never prove true anyway...
Not with our blundering Janet!
Behold the powers of Janet the Great Seeress!
Now then, Sheila Naylor,
your present is...
Oh?
Wh-What is it?
Sheila, you’ve a bit of a cold
just now, haven’t you?
Eh...
How did you know?
Why, you were coughing this morning.
Anyone could tell.
And...
Oh!
No way!
Wh-What is it?
Someone’s in love with Sheila!
T...
Truly?
Madly.
Wh-Who?
Come now... Isn’t it John of the stationer’s?
Yesterday, when you bought an eraser,
he gave you such a smile.
Eh, John? Oh no...
You don’t mean it!
That handsome John...
Whatever shall I do!
A yellow ribbon will be
your lucky token in love.
A yellow ribbon?
I... I see.
Thank you, Janet!
Oh my! Whatever shall I do!
Look at her after saying it'll never prove true!
Why, it does look rather fun.
Divine for me next!
Me too!
Good morning—
What’s the matter?
It’s dreadful!
According to Janet’s divination,
something unexpected is to befall us today!
From early this morning I’ve had the feeling—
an unexpected happening is certain!
If it comes true, I may begin to believe
in Janet’s divination.
So shall I.
An unexpected happening...
It’s bound to come!
Nonsense.
Oh!
I see you're having a busy morning, girls.
M-Miss Roberts!
G-Good morning!
Of late I’ve had the impression
that your minds have been curiously unsettled.
Is it only my fancy?
To sharpen your wits,
I shall set you a surprise test.
Janet!
No way...
It’s happened!
The sudden unexpected thing!
The Twins at St. Clare's
According to Janet’s cards, I’m “Red.”
And I’m “A.”
"A?" Really?
Yeah.
Say, shall we all go to the pictures?
That new one everyone’s talking about.
Pictures?
Pass.
I’m too busy with my knitting.
Janet’s divination says
a red jumper will bring me luck!
Yes! I’d rather read.
She said any book with a title beginning with “A” will improve my marks in tests this month!
Hold up! Are you people serious?!
Do you mean to say everyone’s taken in
by Janet’s divining?
But she did hit the nail on the head!
That surprise maths test.
Right? It was incredible!
Pure chance!
Anyway, I’m far too busy.
Janet!
Extraordinary!
Someone’s in love with Sheila!
Could it be John, the stationer’s son?
A yellow ribbon is your lucky token in love.
Young lady, what a pretty ribbon you have!
Oh, don’t! It’s far too embarrassing!
I swear... This fortune-telling craze...
Everyone’s gone clean daft!
Janet says I mustn’t marry
till I’m twenty-eight. I’m shattered!
She says I’ll never be a nurse!
It was my dream,
but I suppose I must give it up.
Give it up? Nonsense!
If you long to be a nurse, then work for it!
Pat!
Kathleen, marry at twenty
if you please, and be happy!
You mustn’t let fortunes rule you—never!
Anyway, we O’Sullivan twins
won’t be taken in by such rubbish!
Isabel!
Let’s go to the pictures.
Ah... But, Pat, listen.
I’ve just been told—the destiny of twins
is governed by the same star.
Nonsense!
You don’t mean to say even you think people’s fates
are settled by a pack of cards now?
But... I do feel there’s something to it.
Perhaps people’s lives are mapped out
from the moment they’re born?
Exactly!
The fates of St. Clare’s first-formers
are all revealed by Janet’s cards!
Janet! You're seriously getting ahead of yourself!
Playing the oracle
and leading everyone a dance!
How dare you!
You braggart!
You stubborn mule!
That settles it—our friendship’s over!
So it is!
Y-You two...
You’ll bring a terrible punishment on yourselves.
Very well! Try it, then.
Punishment or whatever you please!
Tell my fortune, if you dare.
And if it proves false,
then it shows you’re an impostor.
But if it comes true?
Then I’ll obey you all my life.
Pray, tell us Patricia O’Sullivan’s fate.
What shall befall her within three days?
Wh-What's wrong?
Wh-What is it?
S-Something dreadful!
Oh, no! What is it?
A misfortune is to come upon Pat.
Within three days.
Wh-What kind of misfortune?
I can’t tell...
A sinister accident...
A curse!
Eh? A curse?
Yes, within three days.
Shh! No need to remind Pat.
Pat, are you okay?
What do you mean?
Well, with all the...
What curse? It’s nonsense!
Ah! Delicious!
But the whole school’s buzzing with it!
Poor Patricia O’Sullivan.
They say she may die!
Really, why do they need to say things like that?
“Misfortune” my butt!
But... Suppose...
Wh-Who’s there?
O-Oh... It’s just you, Binks!
Today...
is the third day.
Oh, if only she could be safe past twelve o’clock!
One more hour and Janet’s prophecy
will be done with.
To the lavatory, I suppose.
She’d be safer if she stayed still.
N-Not that we're tagging after you
out of worry, mind you!
I know that.
L-Look there!
Wh-What?
Heavens! The stables!
Binks!
It was me who brought the misfortune!
What am I to do?!
The horses! They’ll die!
Isabel, please!
Sure!
All right...
Pat, the curse still looms over you!
Ah! Pat!
Blazes! I must tell the mistresses!
I’ll let you go now.
Come on! Run quickly!
Go!
There, there, you'll be all right now.
Pat!
Pat and Janet are inside!
What?!
Pat!
Janet!
Janet...
Pat, quick!
Pat!
Janet!
Pat, Janet!
Miss Roberts!
Teacher! Wait!
My students are in there!
We’ll handle this.
Pat! Janet!
Pat!
Janet!
Thank goodness!
Come on, did you seriously think I’d die?
Pat! Thank goodness!
Sorry!
Sorry...
Thank goodness, Janet!
Injuries?
None!
None at all!
Surprised? Pat’s indestructible!
And Janet too!
No—Pat!
Thanks to your quick action,
the stable only partially burned.
And all the horses are safe,
all thanks to you.
That’s a relief!
But, Pat, too much bravery
can land you in hot water.
If something like this happens again,
don’t take such dangerous action.
O-Okay...
Still, I must commend
your wonderful teamwork.
We’ve decided to award you a special show
at the next school assembly.
Eh?
A show?
And Janet...
Yes?
This arrived for you this morning.
Eh?
Ah...
Jimmy!
Exchanging letters with boys is forbidden.
But this one is probably from a girl.
Headmistress!
Th-Thank you!
"Janet, I’ve been too busy to reply,
but I read your every letter.
This is a token of thanks."
Jimmy...
Far from misfortune...
it’s the greatest happiness!
Perhaps that great misfortune
was that our friendship nearly broke?
So it seems.
Fate can be changed by your own efforts.
Yes! Achieved through effort.
Janet, aren’t you getting tired of fortune-telling?
Fortune-telling? That’s old news.
From now on, it’s all about charms.
My!
Hooray for Jimmy!
Hooray for youth!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Hilary’s father fell ill.
The operation was successful
and his life was saved...
but he had to give up the school he ran.
And...
And what, Pat?
Hilary can no longer pay her tuition fees,
so she must leave St. Clare’s!
Really?
Hilary leaving St. Clare’s—
surely that’s impossible!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Don’t Leave, Hilary!"
Episode 19
Don’t Leave, Hilary!
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End