For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Look! The twins are playing again!
Together, they're our head girls!
The pride of our school...
The O’Sullivan twins!
Go for it, Pat!
I got this, Isabel!
Winning set!
Congratulations, Patricia and Isabel.
You won this one.
Thanks, everyone!
Hey, hear this!
Guess what, Pat! Redroof
has picked you as its top athlete!
Really?
Don't act so surprised.
Pat’s good at every sport—
after all, she’s captain of the hockey team!
Congratulations!
Wait, that's not all.
Isabel’s been chosen for the School’s Honor Roll Award, too!
You did it, Isabel!
She topped every graduation exam but geography.
Huh? And who topped geography?
Pat, of course!
You two are simply perfect!
Such a shame you have to graduate
and leave us so soon...
Thank you, everyone! Thanks a lot!
We won't study in this classroom ever again.
Giving it our best in sports...
Giving it our best in studying...
Still, this school life was unforgettable.
Yeah.
And it was supposed to only get better from here...
It really was.
Why is that?!
Why do we, of all people,
have to transfer to that stupid school?!
St. Clare's...
is a disaster of a school!
How can such folly...
ever be forgiven?
Why should we go to that school
if we don't want to?!
Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
Episode 1
I hate St. Clare's!
Ready? We're going in.
O-Okay.
Father!
We need to talk!
What's wrong, Isabel, Pat?
We'd like you to call off this whole idea
of us transferring to St. Clare's.
Please!
Really, so it's about that?
We're serious, Father!
Everyone says that St. Clare's
is a terrible school!
It's a plain, boorish school.
They let in just about anyone,
even if they're not from a good family.
All the students there
wear torn clothes day after day.
Both Pat and I are outstanding students.
I think we deserve a better school.
Like, for example,
Ringmere School.
It's famous for only letting in rich and bright girls.
They have expensive desks imported from Paris.
You get to wear an evening dress for dinner.
All the girls in our class
will go to Ringmere School.
St. Clare's pales in comparison...
Tell me, you two—
did all that studying up to now
just teach you how to talk so stuck-up?
Mother...
St. Clare's is a wonderful and sensible school.
I know the Head personally,
and I like her a lot.
B-But if we transfer to St. Clare’s, we’ll be newcomers,
who are also at the bottom of the ladder!
We're the local stars at Redroofs!
I'm the head girl and the hockey team captain.
I’d much rather go to Ringmere with everyone else and keep the popularity I’ve got now.
And it’s pretty clear St. Clare’s doesn’t set the bar very high when it comes to studying.
That kind of place doesn't suit us,
exemplary students!
I won't go to St. Clare's!
Crying like babies—
how old do you think you are?!
You two were spoiled and got full of yourselves,
even though you’re really nothing special.
Th-That's not true!
We only say that because we really are...
Listen up, you two.
If you want to become humble and kind daughters I can be proud of,
you will cheer up and start over
from scratch at your new school.
That really is the thing
you two need the most right now.
Now, go back to your room
and reflect on what you just said.
St. Clare's...
is the worst.
Dad and Mum don't understand us at all.
Not in the slightest.
Why must children do what adults say forever?
There are things that children understand way better than adults.
But now it's decided...
I will never forget the feelings I have tonight.
A school like St. Clare's...
I will never agree
to a school such as St. Clare's!
Pat, Isabel, that's the special train to St. Clare's.
Once we get on that,
we'll become students of St. Clare's.
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
This lame uniform is killing me!
And this lacrosse stick…
I wish we were still playing hockey.
It's a disaster...
And yet, we're made to wear...
the same uniform as them.
What are you two still mumbling about?
You need to get on!
Okay...
Wow, she's so elegant!
Nothing like St. Clare's students!
Oh? And you two must be the O'Sullivan twins.
Huh?
You're Patricia, right?
Y-Yes!
And you're Isabel.
Just as the letter said.
Aren't you Miss Roberts of St. Clare's?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Where's your "Hello"?
H-Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Miss Roberts, I know they can be a bit selfish sometimes, but please be patient with them.
Oh no, I believe they both have it in them
to grow into wonderful ladies.
Well, say your goodbyes to your mother now.
The train leaves in two minutes.
Once you settle into St. Clare’s dorm,
I won’t be seeing either of you for a good while.
I'm going to miss you.
Mum!
I’ve been harsh at times too, but only because I care about your spiritual growth.
Don't give up and stay strong.
I'm gonna write you letters.
Me too!
No one here knows us.
I totally wouldn't be able to stand it on my own.
Good thing we have each other.
Okay, sandwiches, everyone!
We also have ginger ale, lemonade, and black tea.
Oh, the lunch is here.
Oh my. Sorry, little one. Newcomer?
Yeah.
Your tie is undone.
I got your lunch as well.
Thanks.
Here you go, little one.
Did she really say that?
She’s from the top class.
Next to you lower-class kids,
she’s practically an adult.
We were in the top class ourselves
at our previous school!
And head girls to boot.
Isabel, I've made up my mind, you hear?
That's right. I'll do the same.
You know what I mean?
Of course! We're twins, after all.
We won't let anyone look down on us!
Seniors or whatever,
they'll all look at us as equals!
No kowtowing to anyone!
No laughing at us!
We'll never become just two of
St. Clare's students!
Yeah.
No way! Don't tell me—are you two twins?
Seems so.
They're so alike it feels surreal!
And who might you be?
I bet we're in the same class.
We've heard about two new girls coming.
I’m so thrilled! I’ve never met twins before.
Pleased to meet you, Surreal Twins.
What's wrong?
Do all St. Clare's students babble like you?
You said it quite right—
we're so alike, it almost feels surreal!
And that means we also share this desire not to talk to you!
We're surreal, aren't we?
That means riding in the same car as you is making us sick!
If you would excuse us...
Wh-What was that?
Ugh! They're the worst!
That's my Isabel.
That line earlier was spot-on.
Let's keep this up.
So awfully rural!
Okay, we're going to take the bus to school now.
Huh?
What an awful country road!
Geez, I can't take this for much longer!
You'll be able to see St. Clare's building soon.
That’s the school where you’ll be spending
the next seven years.
Your friends, teachers, and school building—
everything you will think, worry, and grow with
for the many years to come—is at that school.
No way am I going down without a fight!
Just you watch.
The Twins at St. Clare's
It's not as bad as I thought.
It’s just big and empty—
like some hospital, really!
Pat, Isabel,
Hillary will give you a tour of the school.
She’s the head girl of your new class.
I'm Hilary Wentworth. Nice to meet you.
O'Sullivan twins. Nice to meet you!
This here is our grand hall,
where we also hold the religious services.
So, isn't it breathtaking?
N-Nothing special!
This is our study room.
You do it in all this racket?
We all had a private study at our previous school.
You had all the time in the world
to read on your own.
Here at St. Clare's, only the top form
girls get a private study.
Just as we thought—
we really don't belong in a place like this.
But in return, we get to do some fun things
together in this common study room.
Oh? What kind of things?
I'll show you. This way.
Ah, wait!
Isabel!
The third book from the right
holds a secret message from our class.
News!
A mole on Miss Roberts' nape!
(Is it) a token for "boyfriend wanted"?!
Hey, Isabel, I’ve been meaning to say—
you kind of remind me of Miss Roberts.
Huh?
With your bright eyes,
and your kindness.
You really think so?
Did you forget our vow?
I only smiled a little—just on one cheek, is all!
You must stay on your guard!
What happened, you two?
Nothing.
Hillary, it looks like they've started checking the belongings of new students into the dorms.
Got it!
Let's go see the Matron at once.
She's like a strict but kind mother to all of us.
Patricia and Isabel O'Sullivan, isn't that right?
Yes.
Your mother must be really meticulous.
She’s folded all your sheets
and dresses for outings so neatly.
Yes, our mum's the best.
From now on, though, you’ll be the ones mending any socks or clothes you tear.
Huh?
Ourselves?!
Naturally!
We can't do that!
There were sewing maids
at our other school to do that!
My, that's shocking!
Well, there are no sewing maids here.
So be careful with your things, and remember that they cost your parents money.
Our parents aren’t that tight-fisted! If we rip something, they’ll just buy us a new one right away.
Goodness me! There’s one thing I can’t bear,
and that’s carelessness and waste!
Now that you’re at St. Clare’s,
you’d better get that through your heads.
Ah... How did it go?
She's awful!
She's no "mother."
More like a terrible cantankerous grandma.
I'm telling you—those twins are the worst.
I'll never accept them as my roommates.
And what are you going to do?
I have this to help me.
What?
A mop?
But... What do you mean?
Drop it on them, right?
That sounds like a splendid welcome.
The shower room is at the end of the hall,
the dining room is on the first floor.
And here is Room 7, our room.
Meet our new roomma—
What's up with everyone?
We've got new roommates!
Oh, I can’t believe this—
an eight-person dorm!
You must feel like a litter of puppies all tumbling over each other in your sleep.
Wh-What was that?!
At our old school,
the bedrooms were just doubles,
with maids doing all the cleaning.
Oh my! Look at that, Isabel!
Even the pillows have traces of repairs!
I wonder if they make pillows out of socks.
I bet even their textbooks look like patchwork.
Isn't that right, everyone?
They're asking for it!
It suits you so perfectly!
Our twin princesses!
Pat! Hurry to the bathroom!
Cowards! Anyone can laugh at another
if they set them up like that.
Your hearts are made of rags, and no stitching in the world could mend them.
Wh-What was that?!
Janet!
If you play pranks on newcomers,
you play them on me!
Hilary? Are you really willing to side with them?
They're different from us and a bit headstrong,
but they can be reasoned with if you're patient!
Don’t you remember what Headmistress told us?
You can’t judge someone just by first impressions.
You stay out of it, you honor student!
Janet!
Let's go!
Not so fast, you!
Maybe you lived like princesses back at your old school...
Janet! Let me handle this.
Please understand—
here at St. Clare’s, you take care of yourself
and pull your weight with everyone else—that responsibility is as important as lessons themselves.
I’d bet you two can’t even fasten a single button by yourselves.
I'm not about to waste my precious youth
on buttoning and cleaning!
Ah! So oppressive and tight-handed—
St. Clare's is the worst school ever!
Oh? But aren't you forgetting something important, your highness?
The point is not what you think of St. Clare’s—
but what St. Clare’s thinks of you!
You'd better not make that mistake again.
What?!
You two will never fit in with us at St. Clare's!
What's all the ruckus?
Is there an argument?
N-No...
I've never seen a school this uncouth!
Where's the headmistress's room?
Huh?
I’m going to dump on her everything
that drives me crazy about St. Clare’s!
On the headmistress?
Yes! I'll say everything I want to say!
I wonder if she'll be able to.
Pat...
Come in.
I probably don't need to ask you two
what your names are.
Patricia and Isabel.
The O'Sullivan twins, isn't that right?
Yes.
Headmistress, we need to talk.
What's so funny?
You father and mother really do know you girls through and through.
And they love both of you deeply.
What do you mean?
I was just reading a letter from your parents.
"Patricia and Isabel may rush to the headmistress' room as soon as they arrive.
Pat will do the talking.
When she insists on a complaint,
her eyes sparkle even more than usual.
Meanwhile, Isabel will be a bit timid, thinking,
“Are we really doing the right thing?”,
while batting her eyelashes furiously."
Well then, what are we going to do now?
They ask me to scold you both
mercilessly in this letter.
Just like your parents love you
and want to be proud of you,
I'm also deeply concerned
about every single student at our school.
Many students have come here, just like you two,
and discovered for themselves what’s most wonderful and important while growing up at St. Clare’s.
But if you become rigid and close your heart to change, you won’t ever be able to notice it.
St. Clare's is doing its best for you.
So please do your best to make St. Clare's proud of you in return.
Okay.
Why did you agree with her?
How couldn't I?
It felt like Headmistress had seen right through me,
to the depths of my heart.
That's because you're so shy!
You were actually close
to saying "Okay" yourself, weren't you?
Nope, I made an oath.
Huh?
I won't lose.
I'll give everyone a shock—
even the headmistress!
In sports, studying—everything!
We'll show everyone what we're capable of!
The O'Sullivan twins will be the best at this school.
I'm sure I heard a voice...
Just Kathleen grinding her teeth?
Just you watch,
the real show only starts now.
They'll be in awe when they see our real abilities.
We'll unleash a "twin shock" on St. Clare's!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
JmePenseBon
Next time
I'm Pat.
I'm Isabel.
This girl, Belinda, from the fifth form suddenly summoned us. What might she need?
For you to clean her shoes,
light the stove and boil some water.
And if we refuse, they'll forbid us from going out—you think that's acceptable?!
Consider it a custom of St. Clare's.
We don't care to follow
St. Clare's stupid ways. Right, Isabel?
Yeah!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
Look at my Lacrosse!
Episode 2
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End