Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Hey, they say Miss Lewis
is coming this evening.
Then it won’t be long.
Is Miss Lewis coming in Miss Kennedy’s stead?
So I heard.
What sort of mistress is she?
We know nothing of her.
When we came to St. Clare's,
she was already ill and on sick leave.
The seniors say she is brilliantly original.
In what way?
Kathleen!
Oh dear!
Binks has run away!
Eh?
Your aunt called.
Episode 16
All-Night Debate!
Eh?! He’s run off five times already?
Kathleen, I really didn't wish to trouble you.
Besides, he was soon found
all the previous times.
But this time, Binks simply wouldn't
come back to me no matter how many times I called.
I was wondering if you could perhaps
do something about it?
This is so sudden, how do you expect me...
More importantly,
I have to leave for France shortly.
Pray, do try to help me!
But where on earth might my dear Binks be?
I daresay he’ll head your way.
Surely not!
He always bolts towards St. Clare's
when he runs away.
He’ll be sure to come there.
Please, Kathleen!
Binks! Binks!
Kathleen!
Kathleen! It’s best we wait here.
Quite so! You can't know
from which direction he’ll come.
Still, do you think Binks will really return here?
Even if he runs,
it must take him half a day at least.
Besides, when you took Binks away,
you rode your aunt's motor-car, did you not?
Could a dog really remember the road like that?
There are tales of dogs travelling
thousands of miles to their owners, you know.
But those are just tales, aren’t they?
Some are true, I assure you.
But...
He’ll come back!
Binks will surely return here.
Right... We must get towels ready.
I’ll go fetch them.
The rain stopped.
It’s supper time already.
We must be off.
I’ll remain here.
So will I.
But if too many are absent,
the mistresses will notice and we'll get in a row.
Only the three of us will stay.
You girls go.
Okay, then.
Binks!
A stray, perhaps?
Although he's far too dear for that.
And he doesn’t look frightened in the least.
What’s your name, then?
No answer, of course.
Now, off to home you go.
Listen, there’s nothing for you
if you come with me.
So do go back, will you?
I’m at my wits’ end...
There’s nothing good in following me,
even if you are a stray.
I really can't keep you.
Oi! See? A candy!
There!
I thought I heard a noise.
Yeah.
Oi! You mustn’t go that way!
Oh, so it's just a person.
Binks!
Look, you're wet through!
Welcome home!
You must've been cold.
How splendid!
Now then, off we go!
Yeah.
Oi, you! Wait up!
You can't keep dogs in that school!
Why ever not?
"Wh–Why not?"
I don’t see why you should be telling us that.
Quite right—who are you, anyway?
Could you be a senior?
W-Well, actually, I...
I see! You must be a new girl.
Of course, that explains it!
As for Binks, we’re the ones who keep him,
so kindly mind your own business.
But St. Clare's has a rule
against keeping pets, doesn’t it?
Dash! You sound just like a mistress.
If you’re a pupil,
you ought to stand on our side.
Miss Lewis!
Headmistress!
I've just returned!
Miss Lewis, you’re looking quite recovered.
Yes, indeed!
I ought to have been here sooner,
but I missed the bus and had to walk.
Golly!
S-So, this is Miss Lewis, then?
A real mistress?
Yep, not a new student.
Sorry to disappoint.
By the way, Kathleen, about Binks—
I’ve already heard from the matron.
Headmistress, do let me keep Binks.
Yes! That’s the only way.
Well, well, we’ll speak of that later.
For now, the lot of you must go
and have supper.
Oh yes, supper!
I’m famished.
Come along, quickly, quickly!
Well!
Binks, was it?
No matter how often I sent him off,
he kept following me.
Ah... They say dogs can tell at once
if this or that person likes them.
Isn’t that so, Kathleen?
Yes, quite so.
That’s nonsense.
When I was little, a big dog barked at me,
and I’ve never liked them since.
Still, she looks as if she’d agree
to overlook us keeping him.
What? What’s the matter?
Ah, M-Miss Lewis,
if you’d care for an apple, I have one.
I’ve never cared for apples.
Oh, really? Thanks.
I quite see your position.
But as long as the rule against pupils
keeping pets on the school premises stands firm...
Please, Ma'am!
I’ve been listening for a while,
and I really think you’re being too unreasonable.
If something is forbidden,
it’s forbidden to the end of time.
Miss Lewis!
The rules say so,
and they aren't there for decoration.
But no one but Kathleen can keep Binks!
Yes! He’ll only run away from anyone else.
Now, that sort of sentimental talk won’t do.
The point at issue is the school rule.
But...
It’s late tonight, so we’ll leave it at that.
We’ll decide on the best course
in a couple of days.
Until then, Binks must stay
in the stables as before.
Is that clear, Kathleen?
If only Miss Kennedy were here,
she’d side with us.
Pat!
Very well, tomorrow we’ll hold a debate
on rules and regulations,
and think the matter
through carefully, together!
Miss Lewis!
All right! We’ll floor Miss Lewis!
The Twins at St. Clare's
From today on, I shall give you history lessons.
But today, instead,
we’ll devote the hour to a debate.
Do you mean to drop a lesson?
“Drop” is not the word.
It’s part of our studies too.
But what has history to do
with keeping a dog?
Before you speak, give your name.
Hilary.
Ah, so you’re the Head Girl.
Then let me ask—why do we study history?
To learn from the past and apply it to the present.
Precisely—to apply it to the present!
So that now, and in the future,
we may live better lives.
Then to consider the school rules,
that is to say the rules governing our lives,
is most important when pondering how we shall
comport ourselves now and in the years to come.
This, too, makes for a worthy lesson in history.
Moreover, according to our Byronist creed,
the history of the world
is nothing but the biographies of great men.
Well then, does anyone wish to speak?
Yes!
Are you the one who's Pat?
No, Isabel.
Kathleen has no mother, you know,
nor any siblings, and her father lives abroad.
To Kathleen, Binks is more than a pet.
However, if we move such sentiments aside...
It is not sentiment!
Binks is like a brother to Kathleen.
We must absolutely first understand
how important that is.
So, if he is like a brother, he should be allowed
to live with us here at St. Clare's, is that it?
Well...
Yes! Pat here.
As I said yesterday,
no one but Kathleen can keep Binks.
This is no mere sentiment;
it is a fact which we must accept.
I have a friend who adores dogs—
any dog will take to her.
Shall we entrust him to her?
I'm Sheila.
What is the aim of education?
Whew! Now you’re aiming high.
Of course, it is not to make machines,
but to make men.
A phrase of Jean-Jacques Rousseau, is it not?
See? This is becoming a lesson in history, after all.
To make men is to form character.
Binks is necessary
to Kathleen’s formation of character.
She's gone all in!
There have been times when I, downcast,
have pondered what school
and education truly mean.
Thank you, Sheila.
Quiet now! Do not be too smug.
School rules are made with the forming
of pupils’ characters in mind.
May I?
Hilary?
Socrates said:
"Even a bad law, being law,
must be obeyed."
So even a bad regulation...
Hilary!
Are you arguing for the rule now?
No, not so.
Only that such regulations
are not easily altered,
and unless we recognise that,
we cannot move forward.
I'm Janet.
How, then, may a rule be changed?
By council—by the governors, the committee, and the mistresses in conference.
Yet so far, no rule has ever been altered.
This is getting nowhere.
Are there any who have not yet spoken?
You there—will you?
Alison here.
I think we should ask the dog what he wishes.
Eh?
Whoever Binks would most choose to live with
is surely most important—his own feelings matter!
A quaint notion, but alas,
dogs cannot tell us in words.
Actually... Most importantly,
we have not asked Kathleen her thoughts.
Well, Kathleen?
Speak, do say something.
Yeah! Say what you please.
Don't be shy!
Er...
Hm?
As for Binks...
Binks?
I'd like to take him out to relieve himself.
Relieve himself?
I see. Very well!
If it's decided that I may keep you, you'll be able
to to speak your mind freely thereafter.
What a pity. Has it ended already?
Miss Lewis, we have no more classes today.
So what?
So let’s carry on with the debate.
Great idea! Don’t you think, everyone?
Agreed!
Right then, seeing as it’s come to this,
let’s thrash it out thoroughly
until we reach a conclusion!
A grand debate!
Super-agreed!
To begin with, what are rules?
They are provisions that must be observed
when a person undertakes some action.
Understand?
Those provisions that must be observed
are properly written in the law books.
Then, what matters more to you—
rules or people?
Why, people, of course.
Rules exist for people.
Then please put Kathleen first.
But the rule that says you mustn’t keep pets at school is not a bad one.
For Kathleen as she is now, it is bad!
That’s right!
Of course, rules exist for the sake of people.
But not for a single person—
rather, for everyone.
That, I understand.
Isabel, what're you saying?
Eh?
You mustn’t acknowledge that!
Why? If we don't recognise what is right as right...
It’s true the school rules
don’t contain anything inherently bad.
But that’s the trap!
The trap!
They’re all things convenient for the school.
Not always.
Yes, always! For example,
why shouldn’t we all keep a pet together?
Because the school isn’t a zoo.
So what if it did become a bit like a zoo?
That'd be wrong!
It wouldn’t!
It would!
It’s true, among the school rules, there are those
made solely for the school’s convenience.
But school rules ought to benefit
the pupils as well.
Yes! School rules aren’t for the school’s sake...
They’re for the pupils!
Miss Lewis?
Yes, Kathleen?
Binks looks thirsty,
may I give him some water?
You may, but how do you know he’s thirsty?
I can tell, that much at least.
Right then, let’s continue this in my room!
Yay!
This time it seems they're doing it
in Miss Lewis’s room.
They carried in mountains of biscuits and cakes,
and kept at it without a break.
Why, it’s bedtime already.
Ah, what a pity.
And we’ve not reached a conclusion yet.
Is everyone sleepy?
Not in the least!
Then let’s carry on.
But what if Matron comes on her rounds?
I’ll take responsibility.
We’re relying on you.
Binks, everyone keeps fighting for you.
For people to live together in society,
rules are necessary.
In wider society those are called laws.
And laws must be obeyed.
But laws have special provisions.
In other words, exceptions.
Yes, then this should be
treated as an exception!
Exceptions aren’t so easily handed out.
We must obtain the governors’ approval.
Oh! It’s morning.
Let’s continue outside in the fresh air.
Agreed!
Everyone knows rules are made to be broken.
But this time it doesn’t look
to be so easy for them.
It’s often said there are as many opinions
as there are people,
and truly every opinion has been aired by now.
Even if we never reach a conclusion,
what matters is hearing out everyone's opinion of this contentious point, and giving it due thought.
We saw Isabel and Pat, two sisters,
lock horns in fierce debate,
and Kathleen showed us how deeply
she cares about Binks.
Above all, it warmed my heart
to see everyone’s eyes shining with life.
But this is not the end.
We’ll go on discussing the school rules
whenever there’s a chance.
But we must come to a conclusion soon.
If we don’t, Binks will have no place here.
No, on that matter,
I shall give the conclusion.
Kathleen.
Yes?
You cannot be allowed to keep Binks.
What, really?
Then what was the point
of debating till morning?
However...
nowhere in the school rules does it say
that a teacher may not keep a pet.
Therefore, Binks shall be kept by me.
Do you agree, Headmistress?
There’s no reason to forbid it, is there?
Miss Lewis!
Yeah, coming!
Headmistress, thank you
for the biscuits and refreshments.
Headmistress?
The school exists for the sake of the pupils.
For the pupils!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Isabel, our birthday is coming soon.
Pat, let’s not do anything elaborate,
just sit quietly over tea.
What? But it’s our birthday!
A games tournament, or perhaps
a fancy-dress party might be fun!
Nothing too showy.
It’ll be fine, as long as we keep it under wraps.
Very well then. I’ll hold the sort of party I want!
Let’s keep them separate.
All right. I’ll do just as I please as well.
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Big Birthday Bust-up!"
Episode 17
The Big Birthday Bust-up!
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End