Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Isabel, do hurry or we’ll be late for class.
Wait, I’ll be done in a moment.
Oh, it looks odd somehow.
Does it? I think it’s lovely.
I know it's lovely by default,
but if you tie it like this,
it looks even prettier.
See, it’s a bit crooked, isn’t it?
Ah... I simply can’t go to class
until it looks right.
Alison, honestly...
All she ever thinks about is how she looks.
There, that does it.
Perfect.
You look smashing, Alison.
Episode 24
A Dieting Craze!
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who is the fairest girl of all?
Why, it’s Alison, of course.
Oh, I’m thrilled!
Do you really stand there
and say that every day?
Yes, of course I do.
I knew it.
But you know,
I’m not really the prettiest of them all.
Eh?
There she is, the prettiest girl of St. Clare’s.
I think that’s Madeleine...
from the fifth form.
She’s like a doll.
Like an angel.
Ah... I wish I could be like Madeleine.
Alison, you're one of the few
who have a flair for fashion here at St. Clare’s.
R-Really, Madeleine?
And you’re quite sweet too.
I adore beautiful things—
whether clothes or friends.
We could be friends, you and I.
So, Alison, why don’t you start
by doing as I say from today?
Eh?
First, you must look after your nails.
Nail varnish?
Won’t the teachers scold us?
If they find out,
they might call in my parents.
Not at all, just wear it secretly,
only when you go out.
Right.
Also, dear, that ribbon won’t do,
it doesn’t suit you.
Eh?
Your waist is too thick.
Until you trim five centimetres off your waist,
that ribbon won’t suit you.
Alison, you must lose weight,
if you want to be a beautiful girl like me.
Yes, Madeleine.
Here, biscuits!
Some chocolate as well.
Alison should be here any minute.
"Oh, you girls are horrible,
hiding them from me!
You know full well
how fond I am of sweets!
May I?"
You're a natural at it!
Alison, we brought you some chocolate.
Chocolate?
Eating sweets before bed is shameful.
Eh?
Yes, I’ve decided.
From today, I shall never eat sweets again.
Eh?!
I will lose weight, whatever it takes!
Just watch—Alison’s Grand Diet Plan!
Whoa, meatloaf!
Bon appétit!
That was delicious.
Eh?
Alison, are you finished already?
Yes, I had tomatoes and celery.
Only that?
Yes. Meat is fatty, eggs and margarine are high in calories.
Eat it all and you’ll end up
like a great fat snowman.
Ah? A snowman? Don’t be silly.
It’s no laughing matter.
Don’t you all want to be beautiful?
Well, yes, but...
There! That one mouthful
will make your legs fat.
Swallow that, and Jimmy will hate you.
After all, they say boys loathe fat girls most of all.
If you’re not pretty,
boys won’t even glance at you.
Nonsense! Forget diets and let’s just eat.
Somehow I’ve lost my appetite.
Me too.
Eh?
I’ll go on a diet.
Eh?!
So will I.
And me.
That was tasty!
Hold on!
Girls!
Honestly, they're all hopeless.
I’m eating mine.
Isabel? Not you too...
Eh?
O-Of course not.
Well, maybe a little.
Just a little.
Ham is a hundred and fifty calories...
Cake’s two hundred, isn’t it?
Yes. Eat that and you’re a pig.
But I want it...
No. Resist.
Y-Yes, I’ll resist.
Me too.
Resist, resist.
They’re all late.
Even thought the match
against St. Jullia’s is so soon.
Instead of lacrosse practice,
their heads are full of...
diets, diets.
Ugh! Resist, resist.
Well, we’ve never once lost to St. Jullia’s,
so it'll be fine even without practice...
is what I would've liked to say.
Shall we go fetch them?
Seems so.
Wait just a moment.
Sure.
The first formers leave their meals
half-finished so often lately.
Perhaps the food doesn’t suit them?
I plan my menus with such care,
hoping to please them, for days on end.
Last night’s beef stew—
when I said I wanted to be a cook,
my mother stayed up all night
to teach me to make it.
It was the taste of home for me.
Perhaps the young ones
don’t find it good any more.
Girls, it’s time for practice!
What’s with your faces?
Can’t you see?
We’re doing beauty packs.
It tightens the skin...
and makes you lovelier.
I never!
If you’ve time for that,
you’ve time for lacrosse practice.
What’s the use of being good at lacrosse for a girl?
It doesn’t make you pretty.
Eh? What did you say?
The most important thing for a girl is...
whether she’s beautiful...
or not.
Yep, that’s what matters.
Alison, look, you...
I don’t think your dieting
makes you beautiful at all.
Kathleen, what do you mean?
Think of the cooks, all of you.
Eh?
Every day they picture our happy faces
and put their hearts into every dish.
To waste their food so thoughtlessly...
I can’t put it well, but...
even if you diet and look pretty,
if you can’t be considerate of others,
that’s the most shameful thing of all for a girl.
Yes, you’re quite right.
Kathleen, that was splendid.
Alison, can you answer that?
Kathleen...
is just jealous!
Eh?!
Her nose is flat, and her figure’s so dumpy
you can't even tell where her waist is.
A-Alison...!
She’ll never be pretty, diet or no diet.
She was born plain,
that’s why she says such things.
Stop it, Alison!
Alison, that was cruel.
Even if you’re my cousin,
you’re simply awful!
Oh God, why is it?
Some are born beautiful, others not.
Why must it be so?
Kathleen?
Isabel, Pat, what’s wrong?
Kathleen, we're sorry.
We're ashamed to be Alison’s cousins.
Don’t be.
She’s conceited and frivolous,
but at heart she isn’t a bad girl.
She must be regretting what she said by now.
We can’t ask you to forgive her, but at least...
It’s all right! I’m not upset in the least.
Kathleen...
Thank you for worrying about me.
I mean to do my very best
in the match against St. Jullia’s.
I’m off for a run. Well then.
Kathleen...
But... But...!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Kathleen.
She’s been down ever since.
I must apologise.
But how to begin...
I’m hungry...
Girls, you’ve seemed off these past few weeks.
What’s the matter?
No, nothing...
Tomorrow is the lacrosse match against St. Jullia’s.
Do your best.
Okay!
Oh, it’s no good at all.
You need to lose
at least three centimetres more.
At least three more?
Ah! A cake!
Don't mind if I do...
No, you're not!
It's all right for me.
I never put on weight, whatever I eat.
Delicious.
Oh yes, you’ve got a lacrosse match tomorrow, haven’t you?
Yes.
Lacrosse is dreadful—muddy, bruising.
Positively barbaric.
Feign an illness and stay out of it.
Eh? B-But feigning illness is wrong.
Won’t you do as I say?
All right! The inter-school match is here.
It’s only St. Jullia’s. Easy peasy.
What shall I do?
I can’t pretend to be ill...
But I can’t bear to have Madeleine dislike me.
What’s wrong, Alison?
You look under the weather.
Oh, it’s just...
I feel faint...
Better go to the infirmary.
Will she be all right?
Let her be. That’s Alison for you.
I suppose...
How is it, Alison?
Show me the thermometer.
Here.
Goodness me! Thirty-nine degrees!
No chance of lacrosse for you.
I’ll tell Miss Roberts.
It worked for now.
What, it's Kathleen?
Alison, you’re only pretending.
What? How did you know?
Please, don’t tell anyone.
I won’t, but you ought to own up
to the mistress yourself.
I can’t possibly, not right now.
But Alison, if you become the sort of girl who can lie
without a qualm... that would be dreadful!
It’s none of your business!
It is. I like you.
I can’t bear to think you’d cheat and not care.
Please, muster up your courage.
Kathleen...
I’m sorry, I’ve no right to preach.
Well?
Did the pretence work?
Madeleine, I...
What is it?
Please don’t be angry,
but I think I was wrong to feign illness.
What? Do you mean to tell the mistresses now?
Eh?
Do you, of all people,
have that kind of courage?
Of course not.
Then...
Madeleine, there’s something I must ask.
M-Miss Lewis? Wh-What is it?
I found nail varnish in your room.
I don't remember ever saying
that such items were allowed.
I dislike to do it,
but I must call in your parents.
My parents?
B-But it isn’t mine, it belongs to Alison.
Eh?
She forced her way
into my room, though I said no.
You’ll find more of it in her room.
Madeleine, how could you?
Alison, is it true?
E-Er...
Yes. You know, our Alison
is an inveterate liar, who pretends to be ill to shirk lacrosse.
P-Please, Madeleine!
I beg of you! If my parents
are to scold me, I’d sooner die.
For now, back to your room, Madeleine.
Y-Yes.
Miss Lewis?
Only God and your own heart
know the truth of the matter.
I shan’t press you.
The rest is for you to decide.
Think it over.
Did something happen?
Uh? Yes...
Alison, so you have a fever?
Rest well, Alison.
There, lie down in bed now.
I wonder if something’s wrong with Alison.
Right... But never mind,
it’s time for the match.
Yeah!
What is it, Alison?
I... I must muster up my courage sometimes too!
Please let me watch the match.
Oh, that's hopeless!
I’m too hungry to move.
Joan!
I can’t run another step.
No... No more!
Oh, I'm so done...
Hooray! St. Clare’s are total pushovers!
No courage at all. Easy peasy!
Ah, c'est abominable!
If you lose to St. Jullia’s,
I’ll set you piles of homework!
What’s wrong with everyone?
They are in such a poor shape.
It’s the dieting.
They’ve been eating only one meal a day.
Goodness gracious!
What a terrible strain
for a growing girl!
No wonder they’re faint.
Kathleen, Hilary,
take over from Janet and Doris.
Okay!
Kathleen! Shoot!
That's it! Splendid, Kathleen!
Try to pass the ball to Kathleen more!
Kathleen...
Ugh! I can’t move another step...
Oh, c'est abominable!
We'll replace her with...
I’ll play instead.
Alison? But aren’t you ill?
Alison!
I’m really...
I’m really not.
I was pretending.
Uh?
Alison?
Please, let me play.
Miss Roberts!
We're asking you as well!
Please let Alison play!
Kathleen, Isabel, Pat...
Alison, stay strong!
Don't give up yet!
Alison, pass!
Shoot, Alison!
Twenty-five...
to twenty-four!
We just scraped through.
Nearly disgraced St. Clare’s entirely.
Well, look at that! Alison, that’s hardly the look
of the smartest girl in St. Clare’s.
But I take my hat off to you.
It took courage to admit
you’d been malingering.
Just a tiny bit, though.
I’m ashamed of myself.
K-Kathleen.
Hm?
Now I understand.
Pretty hair, good style, or a slim figure
aren’t nearly enough on their own.
True beauty shines from the whole person—
kindness, honest effort—like you, Kathleen.
Nonsense.
It's decided!
Miss St. Clare’s is Kathleen!
Right, and here’s your reward
for winning the match.
Unless some of you still want to diet!
Ugh! How unkind of you!
I’ve had quite enough of dieting.
Tuck in!
Marvellous! These sweets
are seriously irresistible!
Ah, what bliss!
To eat one’s fill!
Alison!
Hey, that’s mine!
Just as I thought you’d grown up a bit...
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Pat, something awful’s happened!
A boy turned up saying Binks was his,
and he’s taken him away!
What? You can’t be serious!
It’s true! He even knew his name was Binks.
That doesn’t make sense.
After all, it was Kathleen who named him Binks!
That's true.
In any case, we must get him back.
Yeah. For Kathleen’s sake.
Yes, for Kathleen!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"Give Back Binks!"
Episode 25
Give Back Binks!
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End