Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
A midnight feast...
A lacrosse match...
We thought that the days of the first form
at St. Clare's consisted of nothing but fun.
A sudden major incident struck!
We found out that it was Kathleen
who's been stealing money from everyone.
It was a huge shock!
But Kathleen only did it because she wanted so desperately to buy presents and make us happy.
It's in the past now!
Kathleen swore to never do it again.
Episode 7
Stay Strong, Miss Kennedy!
Nothing like a morning jog!
That's true!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Thank you, from the bottom of my heart.
Huh? What for?
You never turned away from me,
but treated me just the same, even after all I’d done.
Are you still worried about that?
Of course...
You slipped up, took a wrong turn—
it could happen to anyone.
But to forgive and forget
is what true friendship all about!
I feel that our friendship only grew stronger instead because of that incident.
Isabel...
I also like Kathleen even more than before now!
Even if we are friends, you still need to earn your place on the team.
Kathleen, Isabel, in the next match,
I'll be on the field!
No, I will!
I will!
I won't lose to you!
Oh?
Oh my...
H-How did that happen?
Miss Kennedy!
I'll bring it back to you!
Ah, thank you!
Good morning!
Thank you. I just wanted
to let some fresh air into the room.
Miss Kennedy, were you studying all night long?
I got carried away and lost track of time.
I know. Why don't I treat you
to some cinnamon tea as a thank you?
Wow!
Incredible! I wonder how many years
it would take to read it all?
Huh?
Look, there's a photo of Miss Kennedy!
"Society in Hellas—an approach through the Greek myth."
Miss Kennedy's paper is in a magazine?
It's a famous magazine!
"Miss Kennedy, who teaches history
at St. Clare's School,
is an excellent researcher with two degrees..."
Wow!
We had no idea you were such
an accomplished academic, Miss Kennedy!
If it were me, I’d be talking about it
on every street corner!
It's not a big deal.
Studying and writing papers
are two things I can never get enough of.
Incredible!
In the classroom, I try to share with the children all I’ve learnt up to now, with all my heart.
I made an oath the other day,
when Janet brought fire-cracks to the classroom.
"I will conduct marvelous lessons, for the girls."
We're really sorry for that time...
Never mind it.
I remember, when I was your age...
I wanted to study history
at Oxford University.
At Oxford University?
That was my dream.
She's kind...
Not a trace of self-importance...
Miss Kennedy truly is the best kind of teacher...
I wish I could say that.
And so... That's why Louis XVI was...
Ah! We covered this last week, didn't we?
Now, where was it...
If only her classes were good too...
No offense, but her voice is like a lullaby to me.
It's an interesting class,
but only if you listen really closely...
Hey, Hilary.
Is it true that the second formers
also bully Miss Kennedy like we used to?
They give her no quarter.
They ask her weird questions,
swap her chalk for fake ones...
And call her "Old Kenny."
Can you believe that?
So crude!
They're all the things you used to do yourself!
I-Is that so?
Hey! This is serious, people!
It's the first such incident
in the history of St. Clare's!
What? What is it?
Our Mam'zelle...
Mam'zelle?
Caught a cold!
They say French class tomorrow is cancelled!
Hooray!
But wait, that's not all.
What?
Instead of French, we’ll be having
a joint class with the second form!
With the second form?
And which teacher do you think will be taking it?
Miss Kennedy will be taking the joint class?
That's right.
We, the second form, will have to attend Old Kenny’s
class tomorrow together with the first form.
Should we put our plan on hold, then?
Of course not!
We'll carry it out as planned.
Take a look. Remember what Old Kenny
hates the most in the world?
A cat?
Yes! Tomorrow will be fun!
Girls, I’m sure we’ll have a splendid lesson today, seeing how the first
and second forms have filled
this classroom so peacefully together.
This is a new experience for me,
but I'm going to do my best to teach you.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing for you pipsqueaks to worry about.
Pipsqueaks?
Now, open your textbooks to page 90...
Miss Kennedy! We're scared!
I... I'll see what it is.
You all calm down now.
M-Miss Kennedy!
S-Somebody! Take it away!
I'm allergic to cats!
Somebody!
Miss Kennedy!
"Take it away!
I'm allergic to cats! No!"
Hey, you think she's gonna tell Headmistress?
Don't worry.
Old Kenny won't get mad
no matter what we do!
H-How awful!
Wh-What's going on?
I've run away again.
Miss Kennedy!
Miss Kennedy...
Ah! Oh no...
Mam'zelle!
Mam'zelle! You have a cold,
what on earth are you doing out here?
See, I’m practising to ride a bicycle.
That’ll certainly blow the cold away.
I wanted to take today’s classes properly,
but Headmistress made me take the day off!
Miss Kennedy!
Y-Yes?
Please support from behind.
O-Okay.
Ah, there she is.
Wh-What's going on?
So? I’m a quick learner, aren’t I?
Y-Yes...
I'll be able to cycle to school
together with my students in no time!
Oh, so that's what you're practising for?
It's a challenge from life!
Everything is a challenge!
You're incredible, Mam'zelle!
There's a bush!
Slow me down!
I don't know how to turn yet!
Are you okay?
Is this really enough to get you so impressed?!
M-Mam'zelle,
i-it's a marvellous feat!
C-Compared to you,
I'm a failure of a teacher.
What happened?
I'm...
a fraud.
A fraud?!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Miss Kennedy, what do you mean
when you say you're a fraud?
I say that because I simply can't
teach my students properly.
I can't ever finish a class,
I'm getting paid for nothing.
I'm but a fraud.
If I don't quit now,
I will only be a burden.
Miss Kennedy...
I...
Oh, I can't believe my ears!
Miss Kennedy!
What are you trying to do,
whining like that?!
You need to be more...
assertive!
But I don’t have the same sort
of strong backbone as you.
Why are you acting like a child in your age?!
Yes, I am a child!
Weakling!
And a weakling too!
Well, if you're a weakling,
how come you're so stubborn?!
Go ahead, quit!
This job, filled with love,
emotion and pride, is not for you!
Oh, really? Then quit I will!
Oh, no!
Miss Kennedy!
Tiens! Were you girls eavesdropping?!
N-No...
How could you!
Miss Kennedy is an amazing teacher!
She's the best!
That much I already know!
No, you don't!
She's kind...
and excellent?
She's considerate...
and humble!
So you do know!
But she has a different path in life.
Different path?
Tant pis! That's a secret.
A secret? What is it?
R-Regardless, w-we're in no position
to discuss this issue!
The important choices in life
are for one to make oneself.
That's one of the rules of being a human!
Rules of being a human?
But if Miss Kennedy really does quit...
I do want to become a good teacher.
But...
Wh-Who is it?
It's Pat.
And Isabel.
Miss Kennedy! Please don't quit!
Please!
We think you're a wonderful person,
more confident than anyone else!
We think you should puff out your chest and hold your head high, as the greatest teacher at St. Clare’s!
We’ll avenge you—by thumping those haughty second formers in a game of lacrosse!
Miss Kennedy!
Pat, Isabel...
Y-Yes?
Are you awake?
It's Mam'zelle!
Shoot!
Isabel, get in here!
Yeah...
Mind if we talk for a minute?
S-Sure.
It's nothing major, though...
Care to take some advice?
Sure...
You know, there was a time
when I didn’t have any confidence either.
Students kept belittling me,
and I ended up sobbing every day.
But just one good opportunity
to show them their place is enough!
Mam'zelle...
First, you need to adopt
a disagreeable personality.
Become forward, like me.
Then your students won't have...
anything to say!
G-Good evening, Mam'zelle...
So you don't really mean...
to make Miss Kennedy quit?
Silence!
Why aren't you at the dorm at this hour?!
Not teaching others how to live their lives—
wasn't that one of the rules?
I... I mean...
The rules...
are there to be broken.
My, who is it this time?
Kathleen!
So many guests here!
What's the matter, Kathleen?
I'm sorry, there's something
I'd like to discuss with you privately.
S-Seriously?
They kicked us out?
Geez, that Kathleen...
How unfriendly!
Um... I don't know if it's my place
to say something like this at all, but...
But I...
I also had no self-confidence once!
I was always on edge,
afraid of falling out of everyone’s favour.
Especially of Pat's and Isabel's.
I thought we wouldn’t be able to be friends
if I showed them my bad side.
But I was wrong.
Even when I messed up big time, those two said
they only grew to love me even more.
And now I've learned to love myself too—
when I'm cheerful and gentle.
And I'm proud to be friends with the twins.
I've decided to keep doing my very best,
to become an excellent girl, like Isabel and Pat!
And then I learned to look forward
to every single day!
Kathleen...
Kathleen,
I admire you.
Hey, Kathleen!
What did you say to Miss Kennedy?
Isn't that a secret?
Huh?
No fair!
Everyone, thank you very much
for coming here tonight.
I've never felt like this before.
But as a teacher,
I want to remain strict with myself.
If I can't give even one good lesson,
I don't deserve to keep this job.
Miss Kennedy...
I'll try once again tomorrow.
Got it? Remember the plan.
If this lesson is a success,
I'll stay at this school.
Is it true that Miss Kennedy might quit?
Depends on the class she's giving right now.
I'm worried.
It seemed like the second formers
were plotting something again today.
Please open page 90 of your textbooks.
Isn't Old Kenny somehow different today?
Same as usual.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Now!
One-two...
What's going on?
Miss Kennedy! Are you okay?
Shoo! Go away!
What... What an awful prank!
What do you want?
We're having class!
It's you, aren't you?
The twins who think themselves popular,
always acting so high and mighty?
The stuck-up twins who're so full of themselves!
Wh-What was that?!
That's not true! They've never...
What?
Why, if it isn't the thief from the other day!
Who told the thief about this?
Tessie!
You take those smearing words back at once!
Be mindful of how others feel.
Respect what others take pride in.
Those who forget this etiquette have no right
to sit and learn at the same desk as the others.
To learn is to love.
It's about learning to love
your friends and teachers.
To look at yourself from the outside—
that takes courage!
That, and so many other things,
were what I wanted to teach you. But…
the most important thing...
being considerate to others—that I never managed to teach you, and that's what I'm ashamed of.
The class is over.
This is bad!
Miss Kennedy went to see Headmistress!
She's quitting St. Clare's!
Headmistress! Where's Miss Kennedy?
Left for London to complete the formalities.
For London?!
Although she wanted to keep it
from the students,
in fact Oxford’s lab
had invited her some time ago.
Oxford?!
However, Miss Kennedy felt
that she couldn't leave this school.
She loved too deeply our school,
and each and every one of you.
Miss Kennedy!
She's gone!
We're too late!
Don't give up!
Miss Kennedy!
P-Please stop!
It was a great lesson!
It was the best!
I will never forget what you said to us!
We have so much more to learn from you!
We have so many of your lessons yet to attend!
Hey, miss!
If you don't get on now,
the train will leave.
The Oxford you dreamed of will be out of reach!
Please go without me!
Right now, I only dream
about being a teacher at St. Clare's!
Miss Kennedy!
Thank you, girls. Thank you!
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Hey, Isabel, don't you feel frustrated?
We can't go to the circus we've been looking forward to!
That's true!
I know that culprit who broke the glass
in the classroom is still at large,
but that's no reason
to cancel our excursion to the circus!
That's right!
Hey, Isabel, let's go see it anyway.
Agreed! After all, we've already made a promise to Jimmy, the flying trapeze artist.
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
"The Four Presents."
Episode 8
The Four Presents
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End