Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
Isabel, it's been a week already
since we came to St. Clare's.
Yes, Pat.
A lot has happened, but it's still not that different
from the school we expected it to be.
I was surprised by how far ahead in the curriculum they are.
Yes.
But with a friend,
even this place can be quite fun.
Kathleen surprised me with her kindness.
Belinda Towers is full of surprises.
No wonder she’s the fifth form team captain.
But thanks to her you're on the lacrosse team.
True. But I still remember our vow.
The O'Sullivan twins
will never fit in at St. Clare's!
Right?
Yes!
I'll keep doing my best.
Episode 3
Mam’zelle Abominable
Why did I end up with a B minus in math?
We're still not even close
to the bottom of the list...
But we were number one at Redroofs!
What's wrong, twins?
Someone who got an "A" wouldn't understand.
Ah, don't sweat it.
It’s only because you two are newcomers,
while we’ve long since gotten used to St. Clare’s ways.
Is that really the case?
Of course! So cheer up, won't you?
Hilary's such a nice girl.
All right, let's cheer up, then!
But we have French class next.
Don't you think that teacher
is way too strict on us?
Mam’zelle, huh?
"C'est abominable!"
"Oh woe is me!"
Yes, exactly!
Hey, let's call that teacher
"Mam’zelle Abominable!"
Yeah!
And maybe we can think
about something even more fun to do!
Such as...
After tea time today...
Yes! I can't wait!
It'll be our first time since coming to St. Clare's...
We're going to the movies!
Hooray!
Did you say "movies"?!
How dare you even consider that
after handing in essays like this?!
C'est abominable!
Oh woe is me!
This isn't French at all.
What on Earth have you been taught before?
At our old school,
we focused on conversations.
Our strong suit is speaking it.
Patricia, Isabel, speaking alone
is not enough to understand French.
You have to study the grammar too.
Regardless, no movies for you two.
You're rewriting this essay and bringing it back today.
But... But we already bought the tickets, and...
I don't care about your tickets!
What matters is for you two
to learn proper French.
That's what my job is!
Here, work through all the mistakes,
and hand it in again after supper.
Next is Hilary.
Oui?
Très bien!
Okay, next is Janet.
Oui!
Okay, there were a few minor hiccups,
but you almost got it. Keep doing your best!
How cruel!
We didn't refuse to rewrite it,
so what's wrong with doing it tomorrow?
Instead, she denies us the movies
that we've been looking forward to.
It's the worst...
You don't wanna be
on Mam'zelle's bad side, Pat!
I just poked a little fun at her once,
and she made me write down verbs after tea time.
For a full week, no less!
I'm going to the movies.
No, Pat! You can't!
It'll make a huge mess!
Let's stay and rewrite the essays...
I'm definitely going!
And I'll rewrite the essay too, though it hurts.
You should go too, Isabel!
But…
Just slap something together
for her during lunch.
All right.
Come on, let's eat now.
Hey, twins.
I'll plan our nature study,
so please stay a little after lunch, okay?
Huh?! I-Is it going to take long?
Relax, we’ll have it wrapped up before art class. I’m counting on you!
Guess we'll have to hurry even more,
after art class.
Both of your sketches are coming along nicely.
Keep that up when you turn them into finished pieces.
All right, let's finish it off
with watercolors today.
Don't worry, there's enough time.
I was hoping to finish early...
It felt real nice when Miss Walker praised our pictures,
but we almost ended up being late for tea time.
Pat, let’s skip tea and use this time
to rewrite our essays.
You can't be serious!
I'm starving already.
Art class always makes me
hungry for some reason.
While drawing that big apple, I almost felt like
I could reach out to it with my hand.
Come on, the tea is waiting.
Pat...
Wait! I'm coming too!
Janet, this plum jam is amazing!
My grandma sent it.
Grandma's jam is the best in the world.
Oh? But I was sure our mum's jam
was the best in the world. Right, Isabel?
Uh? Yeah...
Oh? How about you try it, then?
Don't mind if I do!
Pat, look at the clock.
Yikes!
What happened?
Could they still be going out?
I'm not going to the movies.
Why?
We mustn't go.
Mam’zelle will be totally livid when she finds out.
I said I would go, so I'm going!
Don't go, Pat.
Don't worry, I have an idea.
Look: Mam’zelle told us to resubmit it after supper,
but she never said when.
What do you mean?
When everyone goes to bed,
we'll slip out in our nightgowns.
We'll correct the essay in the study room
and take it to Mam’zelle.
No way we can do that! In our gowns
in the middle of the night? Are you nuts?
It's Mam'zelle's fault.
Besides, we didn't wanna
come to St. Clare's in the first place.
They could expel us and I wouldn't care.
How can you say that, Pat...
Have you thought about
what Dad and Mum would say?
Maybe they'll finally realize
sending us to this school was a mistake!
Pat, what would the girls
back at Redroofs think?
Enough about that. I made up my mind.
If you’re not coming,
go ahead and play the good girl by yourself.
Oh, come on...
Going to the movies, twins?
That must mean you finished your French essays.
Not yet!
You girls must really be fools.
Why make things more difficult
than they need to be for no reason?
Isabel, we need to head back soon,
lest we be late for dinner.
Yeah.
I still feel uneasy somehow,
as if we never went to that movie.
That's true...
All right, lights out!
Oh? But where's Miss Roberts?
She said she needed to go see the headmistress,
so I'm acting as her deputy.
So the teacher's not coming?
You'll regret it, Doris!
Oh, really, Joan?
Why won't you give it a rest?
I'm killing the lights!
Ah! Oh no!
We gotta gather them!
I'm sorry, but time's up.
Miss Roberts will come to check on us
in about an hour.
C'mon, hurry!
Ah! It's so hard to find them now!
It's as if a cat's been chasing
hens in our dormitory!
You're all so sly, even though
I'm the one who would get scolded for this!
Yeah, but we gotta sleep now!
Good night!
Night!
Isabel!
But what if Miss Roberts comes?
We have no time to waste.
If Mam’zelle falls asleep, it's all over.
If we leave it like this, she won't notice.
Come on, hurry now!
Pat!
All quiet here.
The Twins at St. Clare's
I hate those cumbersome
French verb conjugations.
Why must we even learn French
in the first place?
I'll finish it at any cost,
then hand it in with my head held high.
Won't Mam'zelle be angry
if we hand it in at such an hour?
She won't have a leg to stand on!
She said hand it in after supper,
and that's what we'll do.
Okay, done.
So, shall we go?
My knees are shaking at the very thought!
Cheer up, won't you?
Let's do it.
Excuse me.
Huh? She's not here.
Maybe she's in her bedroom?
Maybe she fell asleep already?
I think we should cover up to this point
in the current term.
Is that so?
That's Mam'zelle's voice!
She's in the fourth form classroom.
But there's someone else there, it seems.
Probably Miss Walker, the art mistress.
She's friends with Mam'zelle,
so it doesn't matter. Let's go.
Come in. Who is it?
Mon dieu! Tiens!
Headmistress...
What's wrong? Are you girls unwell?
It's not that.
We've brought you our rewritten essays.
You said hand it in after supper, right?
So here we are.
Mon dieu!
But why are you doing it this late?
Surely, Mam'zelle meant
that you should do it before bedtime.
We didn't have time to rewrite it earlier today...
Ah! Such bad children!
You went to the cinema after all,
instead of doing my essays!
Ah! Abominable!
Headmistress, these twins
make my hair grey! The work they do!
And their French is all over the place!
It is impossible that they went
to a school before they came here!
We did go to a school,
and it was a jolly fine one!
Much better than St. Clare’s!
I think we won’t decide
anything tonight, nor will we talk about this.
It is too late. Go to bed, twins.
And come and see me
at ten o’clock tomorrow morning.
Ask Miss Roberts to excuse you
for fifteen minutes.
Okay.
What bad luck to have run
into Headmistress like that!
What happened?
Hilary? You're awake?
I woke up at the sound of Miss Roberts
coming around to check on us.
Did she realize we were...
Don't worry, she didn't notice anything.
I did, though.
Where on earth have you been at this hour?
Really?!
Honestly, I think you’re mad.
You behave like a couple of babies!
Nobody would ever think
you’d been head-girls at your old school.
Good night, Hilary.
Good night.
Good night, twins.
"Like babies"—can you believe it?
But maybe what Hilary said...
Was actually just right?
Pat, what's going to happen to us now?
To think it'd come to this...
Rebelling against Mam’zelle is all fun and games...
Until it suddenly isn't.
Come and see me
at ten o’clock tomorrow morning.
I wonder if Headmistress
will write to our parents about it.
What are they going to think about us?
Why did I have to do something so stupid?
Okay, open the next page now.
Patricia and Isabel, don't you need to go?
Yes.
What's that?
What happened?
Hey, did you know?
Headmistress summoned them!
Really?
Quiet, please.
What now, Pat?
My legs are still shaking.
I've had a lump in my throat
and my heart has been pounding all morning.
Come in.
Sit down on that sofa and give me a minute.
Do you think Headmistress is angry?
I wish everything that happened yesterday was just a dream...
I have been looking through the reports
that your father sent me from your last school.
They had me properly impressed.
You seem to have been responsible
and conscientious children there.
I can’t imagine you completely changing your character in just a few weeks.
So I am not going to treat you
as naughty, irresponsible girls.
I know there must be a good reason
behind your queer behaviour from last night.
Really, my dears, you gave Mam’zelle and me quite a shock when you walked
into that classroom in your dressing-gowns.
Headmistress, the French teaching methods here
are nothing like at our old school.
You can't well expect one
to speak a foreign language perfectly.
Mam’zelle is simply too nitpicky.
What happened yesterday
wasn't our fault either!
The whole thing started because Mam’zelle blew up
over a trifle and ordered us to do the impossible.
What do you think, Isabel?
I do think Mam'zelle is a bit too harsh at times,
but what happened yesterday...
I wish I could say it was Pat’s fault, but that’d make me sound like I’m playing the goody two-shoes here.
What do you girls
want to be in the future?
We haven't really...
thought about it yet.
If you two were to become English teachers abroad,
could you just sit back
and ignore your students butchering the language?
No, we'd want to teach them proper English.
Looks like Mam’zelle already had her sights
on becoming a teacher when she was about ten.
And she takes great pride
in being a French teacher now.
What matters is for you two
to learn proper French.
That's what my job is!
You have not been well grounded
in the writing of French, it seems.
Mam'zelle has offered to give you half an hour’s extra French a day until you have caught up to the others.
Extra?
All this bother has come from the fact
that you were behind your class in one thing—
and if you are willing to work hard to fix it,
there is no need to say any more about last night.
Thank you, Headmistress!
We'll try!
Well, go to Mam'zelle now and arrange what time
will be best each day for the extra lesson.
And don’t go marching through the corridors
in your dressing-gowns at half-past ten any more.
Yes, Headmistress!
Isn't that great, Pat?
We gotta thank Mam'zelle Abominable too!
We were rather the idiots yesterday.
We're really sorry! We won’t be again!
And thank you for saying you’ll help us
every day with extra lessons!
Well, now we'll see how clever you can be
at catching up to the others.
We shall be good friends, n’est ce pas?
Although we really expected
those extra lessons to be a huge pain...
Attention, Patricia!
This is not avoir.
"Tenir"?
Exactement!
It was a stroke of luck!
Mam’zelle is teaching us very carefully,
so we can understand everything.
That's right.
I feel that I'll grow to like French soon!
Both the language and Mam'zelle, right?
Yeah!
Patricia and Isabel...
Très bien!
We did it!
It's all thanks to Mam'zelle!
Yeah! She is a truly great teacher.
What?
I recalled what Headmistress said, and it made me curious what Mam’zelle must’ve looked like at ten.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Quality check
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
JmePenseBon
Next time
I'm Pat.
I'm Isabel.
Did you hear?
The parcel of “fire-cracks” arrived for Janet!
Fire-cracks?
Yeah! And she's going to put it
under the desk of that timid Miss Kennedy.
Wow, that'd surely make her jump in surprise!
But if it were me,
I'd put them into the stove.
Imagine the explosions!
Next time on The Twins at St. Clare's:
"Janet is up to Tricks."
Episode 4
Janet is up to Tricks
Don't miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End