Blasphemboys' Production
The Twins at St. Clare's
If only there were no tests,
School would've been a fun place for me.
I never cared much for studying.
I just stared out the window all through class,
Always dreaming away.
But if I'd at least taken English seriously,
By now I'd be some cool international girl.
Better to study a little than not at all,
There must be at least one thing you're good at.
Better to study while you still have the time,
Realizing too late won't help you then.
For your health, please keep the room well lit and watch it as far from the TV as possible
At long last, the long-awaited swimming pool
has been completed.
To mark the occasion there will be
a medley relay between the forms.
The anchor for each team
will be that form’s mistress.
Which means our anchor in the first form
will be Miss Roberts?
That's... exactly what it means.
Naturally, swimming lessons
will form part of P.T.,
but before that, the pupils are to give their views
on what sort of swimsuits they would like.
The middle one, of course!
No, the one on the left!
Certainly the one on the right!
Episode 20
Bonjour in Bathing Suits
This takes me back...
I was fond of swimming
when I was a girl, you know.
And you, Mam'zelle?
Well, frankly... only a little.
Blimey! Mam’zelle was never any good
at sports of any kind.
Those two are strong swimmers!
We might even win!
Why?
Because Miss Roberts
is said to be a marvellous swimmer.
Really?
Wow! Look at that!
Eh?
Hey, which of us was faster?
I don't know...
Hmm...
About the same, I think.
I was faster!
No way, I was!
It was Janet!
Janet wins, because she kept her stroke to the very end.
Oh, really?
Bye now.
Oh, crumbs.
How can one believe a word
of what Mam’zelle says at this rate?
No! It was me.
Get real, I'm sure I was faster!
Not at all, it was me!
What's wrong, Alison?
Aren’t you getting up on the starting block?
But I...
I can’t swim!
Eh?
Alison!
But you told us yesterday you could.
I said that because it was
too much bother to explain.
Geez...
But you told us you went
to the seaside all last summer!
I do fancy the sea!
Going out in yachts, walking along the sands,
collecting pretty shells...
But you never went in the water?
Mother says I ought to learn to swim properly like Pat and Isabel, but I simply don’t like it.
Then you must have special coaching.
Special coaching?
Now that we have a splendid pool,
every St. Clare’s pupil must learn to swim.
That is the rule of the school.
But one can still marry,
even if she can’t swim...
What was that?
Oh... Nothing.
Just thinking out loud.
Mam’zelle!
H-H-Help!
Oh dear!
Alison!
No! You mustn’t help her yet!
But she’s going under!
It’s all right.
Just watch what happens!
I can’t just stand and look!
No! I said no and no it must be!
Let go!
Look!
She’s swimming!
Alison!
You did it!
Are you serious?
I thought I was gonna die!
But you swam, didn’t you!
That’s what matters.
Pardon me now.
I hate Mam’zelle!
Alison!
Yes, Miss. Fifty-five B.C.
Caesar crossed the Rhine and invaded Britain...
Stop!
Who told you to read?
Eh?
That’s not it at all.
I heard Mam’zelle pushed you into the pool.
Yes, indeed.
I very nearly drowned.
But at least you can swim now, can’t you?
It’s often said the best way to teach a non-swimmer is to throw her straight into the water.
Nonsense! I can only swim now
because I had the talent in me all along!
By the way, girls, the prize for the victory
in the upcoming commemorative tournament
has been fixed to be
a magnificent cup this big!
Quiet!
You think you’ve already won because of Miss Roberts, but don't be too smug.
What do you mean?
Don't forget the fifth form
have me as their form mistress!
Eh?
You're taking part too, Miss Lewis?
Naturally.
And how good of a swimmer are you?
It’s what I do best.
Especially the crawl.
Besides, the fifth form
can count on their several
formidable all-round athletes, such as Belinda or Pamela.
So we’re up against truly formidable rivals.
Which form will claim the coveted cup
of the very first commemorative tournament?
Each of us must strive for victory!
And we’ll not be beaten!
Yeah!
From now on we’ll practise every afternoon.
Agreed!
It’s the fifth form!
What spirit!
But we won't be beaten!
Oh my, Mam'zelle?
What brings you here?
That shouting distracted me.
I had hoped to find somewhere quiet to read.
Then the woods yonder would suit you.
Quite right.
I shall go there.
Funny—those cheers give me a thrill.
Oh?
Weren’t you going into the woods, Mam'zelle?
Goodness me, this isn’t the wood at all, is it?
How foolish of me to wander here.
Ah, Pat! Relax your shoulders!
Eh?
Like this, move lightly...
Careful!
What are you staring at?
Shh. I'm watching the birds.
Vraiment? I never thought you’d have such a hobby.
It's a rare bird that is seldom seen in these parts.
Let me see too!
Ah! It’s flown!
Don’t lose sight of it—keep after it!
Wh-Where is it now?
The pool!
The pool?
What is it doing?
Swimming.
Swimming? That bird?
The first form team will be as follows:
First, Hilary—crawl.
Then Joan—butterfly.
Next, Kathleen—backstroke.
Then Doris—breaststroke.
After that, Janet—crawl.
Then Isabel—breaststroke.
And lastly, Pat—crawl.
Seven in all.
Right—we’ll do our best!
Fifty metres each, is it?
Yes—save for me, the anchor,
who swims a hundred.
Eh? A hundred meters, right?
Impressive!
I’ve chosen by watching you swim,
but those not picked mustn’t feel downhearted.
Downhearted? I’m relieved!
Figures!
Those not on the team—
cheer us on, won’t you?
Yes!
Miss Roberts, we’ve yet to see you swim!
So you haven’t.
Very well—let’s to the pool.
There’s Miss Lewis!
Keep it up, Miss Roberts!
Keep going!
Wow, they're going toe-to-toe!
Go, go, Roberts!
It's a decent battle, first form.
But the victory is ours!
Like we'll ever lose!
The Twins at St. Clare's
Tomorrow decides it!
The second form are already all fired up,
after vowing the first commemorative tournament cup shall be theirs.
Oh, but the sixth form are fired up too.
Naturally, they want to claim the cup
as a farewell prize before graduating.
Every form is bound to be after it.
But looking at the line-up from first to sixth,
it seems the real battle
will be between us and the fifth form.
But our anchor might just be
what gives us that critical edge.
Quite so! Miss Roberts is faster
than Miss Lewis, after all.
But Miss Lewis declared
she would not be beaten in the real race.
Either way, it’s certain to be a fine contest.
Lucky for us, Mam’zelle isn’t our anchor.
If she were, we’d totally be nailed to last place.
Too true!
Well then, tomorrow
we’ll do our utmost for victory!
Yeah!
Go, go, fifth form!
Go, go, first form!
Is each form gathered in full strength?
Yes!
Time to march in, then.
Miss Thomas?
What about the anchor mistresses?
They shall enter from the other side.
Parade of competitors!
Hold on tight! Don't let us down!
For victory!
And now, the anchors!
Huh?!
Hi!
Eh?
M-Mam'zelle?
What’s going on?
Miss Roberts had to leave for the Ministry of Education on official school business.
Her meeting ran long,
and she could not return in time for the race.
Mam’zelle has kindly agreed to stand in.
No way!
Oh, that’s outrageous!
A plot, surely!
Ah... Now we’re doomed to last place.
What was all our practice for, then?
In that case, we must at least show our spirit.
What spirit is there to show?
We must at least lead until the final lap!
Ah, I see!
We’ll prove the first form is the one
that's truly the strongest.
Exactly, with or without the cup!
Come on, everyone!
Yeah!
On your marks!
Go, go, Hilary!
Hilary’s in the lead!
Ugh! Pamela’s overtaken her!
Relax your shoulders, Hilary! Relax them!
Who's next? Go, Joan!
Shoulders loose!
Go, go, Joan!
Keep going!
Go, go, Kathleen!
Don't give up!
Go, go, Doris!
Yes, that’s it!
Go, go, Janet!
Shoulders relaxed. Perfectly relaxed!
Go!
Geez, is that the only thing she knows?
Ah!
The fifth form are closing in!
Come on, Janet!
Oh, crumbs! She’s overtaken me!
All right, we'll be first, even if only for a moment!
Go, go Isabel!
Splendid, Isabel, keep it up!
We must hold the lead at any cost!
Pat's in the lead!
Great! We're first again!
Great! We're top ranked!
Until Mam'zelle's run...
She’s not surfacing!
Sh-She’s sinking!
Wh-What shall we do?
Teacher! Mam'zelle!
Quick, someone must save her!
Ah!
I-Incredible!
Mam’zelle is swimming beneath the water!
Such speed!
And such grace!
If she finishes like this…
Yay! We’ve done it!
Mam’zelle! How on earth
do you swim so well?
Allow me to tell you.
Mam’zelle was once hailed
as a prodigy of French swimming.
Huh?
Backstroke was her speciality,
and she was even chosen for the Olympic team.
But she turned it down.
You see, Mam’zelle chose the life
of a teacher over that of an athlete.
It must have been a hard and painful choice.
Wh-Why didn’t you ever tell us?!
Mam’zelle, for all her appearance,
is not one to boast of past glories.
"For all her appearance"—
what do you mean by that, Headmistress?
I should like to know that!
Well, we can talk this over some other time.
But one thing I can say for certain: I was happy to swim with you all with all my strength!
Will you swim with us more from now on?
Oui.
Mam'zelle!
Please keep this victory cup in your room.
Eh?
Because it was thanks to you that we won.
Please!
Thank you…
But this belongs to everyone.
To everyone.
Mam’zelle, this is your Olympics—
the Olympics of a teacher.
I'll never forget, looking up at the sky from this hilltop,
The morning sun so beautiful, on spring days, just us two.
All the hardships and the sorrows,
Carry them away gently from this hilltop,
together with the wind.
This vast, blue sky—may it never change,
And may my dearest friends stay just the way they are.
Translation
Editing
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Next time
Pat, that Miss Walker has given us
the most awful assignment!
Making a trinket box out of boards—
and on top of all the other homework!
It takes ages to make even a plain box,
and she’s given us only a week!
But Vera and Doris
have come up with a clever idea.
Eh? What sort of idea?
They asked a furniture shop
to make the trinket box for them.
Eh? But that’s not allowed!
Next time on Twins at St. Clare's:
“Miss Walker’s Gift.”
Episode 21
Miss Walker’s Gift
Don’t miss it!
The Twins at St. Clare's
The End