It's 1955.
After recovering from
the chaos of defeat, Japanese society
is about to enter a period
of rapid economic growth,
alongside an explosive rise in consumer culture.
This is a love story of the young people
who hung out near Shonan Beach around that time.
These teenagers who unleashed their raw energy upon the world
were called the "Children of the Sun."
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
Season of
the Sun
Ishihara Shintaro
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Dangerous Youth
That's it! Keep it up!
Now I get it. She's the one that sent you
the flowers before the match.
Why'd she wear a kimono
to a boxing match?
This isn't a picnic.
Good luck, Tsugawa-san!
I'd met Eiko on Saturday,
five days earlier.
Hey, look at that!
Wow!
It's beautiful!
We went to town for some fun,
We couldn't afford
the professional girls,
so we thought we'd try
to pick up some normal girls.
Excuse me.
I-I'm from the Meisei
University Sports Club...
No, I mean, I'm Tatsuya Tsugawa from the Boxing Club.
Oh, a boxer?
Yes. A featherweight.
We were hoping that you could hang out with us for a bit.
We don't know any girls in this town, so we were in a pickle. Right...
We promise to behave ourselves.
So if you're free, won't you please go out with us?
I promise you won't be disappointed.
Hey!
Great!
Thanks!
Meisei University
Medical Center
Thanks for the flowers, but please don't make such a fuss anymore.
You're distracting me from fighting.
I'm happy to see you too.
Who knew you'd be so tough?
Weren't you wearing a kimono?
Where are the other girls?
They went home.
After that, we met a lot.
You'd be surprised
how many friends Eiko had.
A lot of them were men too.
But I didn't care.
I wasn't planning to commit to this relationship.
There's a girl here to see you.
She's a looker.
Hi.
I happened to be passing by.
"Happened"?
It's almost summer, right?
I was going to Hayama
to prepare our summerhouse.
Want to go sailing?
Are you going back to Tokyo tonight?
I don't know.
It's a long drive, so I'll probably stay in Hayama tonight.
Then you can stay at my place.
Have a bath, dinner, and a good rest.
Sorry, but I need to take a bath first.
Meanwhile, you can wait here.
Eiko-san.
I want to see you punch
that sandbag. Right now!
I love you.
What's happening with
Eiko-san these days?
Nothing much, really.
But I see her a lot.
Is that so?
Then it was you dancing with her
at the Katsupi Club two days ago?
I should've called you.
Two days ago?
My old man frequents this place to entertain clients,
so I often tag along and take advantage of his tab.
Tsugawa, he's here.
The guy who was with Eiko at the Katsupi.
Where?
The show-off,
over with that laughing girl.
Come on, Matsumoto-san!
That's Matsumoto-san!
He's the bandmaster and trumpeter
for the Five Roses band.
These days, they perform at Katsupi,
always playing to a full house.
Tsugawa, don't start anything.
I know. I'll just step on his toes a bit.
Hey, hold it!
MARONIE
Do you know why I hit you?
Because I stepped on your foot?
Asshole! Don't pretend you don't know!
Oh, no!
Tatsuya, you're jealous!
Summer, my favorite season,
had finally arrived.
Tch. Such a nice song at the wrong time.
Too bad there's no room to dance here.
It's sea sparkle!
No, it's a sea devil.
Can't be!
Hey! Come on in!
Hold on!
What's wrong?
Something bright swam past me.
Just a jellyfish.
Let's go back to the boat. I'm scared!
You're such a sissy.
But...
It's nights like this that make me believe in those cheesy stories about the moon.
You asleep, Tatsu?
Nah.
It's only eleven, and there's a party at the hotel tonight.
It's a golden opportunity!
Let's go hunting for virgins.
I'm going to sleep. I'm tired.
You guys have fun.
Okay. See you.
No matter where I went, Eiko always showed up.
We played around in the water naked at night, but that's not our usual life.
But if kindness is too much,
then how many loves can there be?
Have a good trip!
Yeah, thanks.
Jump in, Sally.
Ah, finally!
Love is parched like hot desert sand.
Even if called a crow's affection,
I don't mind being refused.
May our two loves overlap, entwine.
Midsummer youth, cradled in my heart...
Come on, Tatsuya!
Good morning!
Really?
Oh, I can't believe you!
Eiko's with me now.
She's no longer into you.
You don't have to make excuses
just 'cause she slept with you once.
All I've gotta do is crook my finger,
and she'll come running back to me.
Really?
Then let's see you do it tonight.
If you do it and she dumps me,
I'll give you 5,000 yen.
And if she refuses,
you'll fork it out yourself.
In either case, think of it
as severance pay.
Deal.
I lost.
Just one condition.
You can't add conditions now.
Look, Tatsuya, I want you out of here today.
If you stay, it'll make things difficult later on.
Go to the mountains.
I'll pay for the trip.
Fine. If you want her that bad,
I'll sell her to you for 5,000.
Really?
Yeah.
It's a deal!
I made myself scarce.
Then I went to a boxing club training camp in Niigata.
The summer finally came to an end.
I'm going home.
It's boring here.
I wonder where Tatsuya is?
He's not interested in you anymore.
And besides...
Besides?
He's a man of his word.
What word?
You'll have to ask him.
Anyway, let's go for another swim.
Wow! Look at all the girls waiting for us!
In the training camp, the thing I missed most wasn't food or women.
It was this sunset in the city.
What was your promise to Michihisa?
I knew you'd ask me about that.
Tacchan, does that mean you sold me?
I guess.
For 5,000 yen, I promised my brother that I wouldn't lay a finger on you.
Did you think I'd agree to that?
You didn't have to.
It was between me and my brother.
What happened to the money?
I spent it.
I see.
Then I'll make sure
to pay Michihisa back.
But what will you do if we make another such agreement?
Doesn't matter. I'll keep on paying until you guys give up.
That's stupid!
Are you going to do it again?
Yeah.
Why are you trying so hard to hurt me?
If you really hated me, you wouldn't go through all this trouble.
I'm sure of it.
Please, tell me the truth.
Don't you still love me, despite all that?
I guess I do.
Then why can't you just love me,
without all the pretense?
I thought I couldn't do it either.
But after that night, I knew I could only truly love you.
We've both been hurt before,
just like everyone else.
But we can change that!
The same deal, one more time.
Just send it to her and she'll pay you for it as many times as you want.
I feel a little guilty.
She blew you off, right?
If you want to pay her
back in kind, sign here.
I guess.
Just as I expected,
Eiko sent him the money again.
After that, I kept sending the contract
to my reluctant brother to get him to sign,
and Eiko always paid it back the same day.
But I got a strange feeling,
once the total reached 20,000 yen.
Not feeling good?
I'm pregnant.
That's what I wanted to tell you today.
Whose is it?
How can you say that?
I'm three months in.
It's gotta be yours.
What should I do?
What do you mean?
Should I have it?
I want to have the baby.
Then have it.
There's nothing wrong with a kid.
Do you really mean that?
Look! It's the champ.
CHAMPION
He's completely different outside the ring.
When it's like this, he's finished.
It won't be long before he starts his fall from glory.
I've changed my mind.
I don't want a kid.
I expected you to say that sooner or later.
But why?
It cramps my style.
Understand?
Operation in Progress
She's dead?
Don't lie to me!
Operation in Progress
I'm telling the truth.
It was four days after her Caesarean.
Operation in Progress
She developed peritonitis.
The funeral will be
the day after tomorrow.
"Then why can't you just love me,
without all the pretense?"
You idiot!
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness