Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
Student
Days
Takeyama Michio
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Amulets
Excuse me! You dropped this.
Oh, I'm so clumsy. Thank you.
It's bad luck to drop
your exam success charm.
That's true,
but it's not for me.
My auntie asked me to buy it.
Her brother is taking the First Higher School exam.
Then you shouldn't tell them you dropped it.
Yes, good idea.
Thank you again.
Hello!
Kenkichi, you're early. Come in.
Thanks for putting up with me this year, Sis.
This will be your study room.
I'll start right now and study
until your husband gets home.
Yes, sounds good.
Excuse me!
Oh? Who could that be?
Really? He just got here,
and he's already studying?
Yes, but the test is pretty soon,
so he's in crunch mode.
HARMONY
It's hard getting into prep school, isn't it?
You mind if I say hello to him?
HARMONY
I also wanted to give this to him.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt your studying-
Ah! I-It's you!
My! So it's you!
Oh, so that's how it is?
Amulet
You're taking the First entrance exam?
You must be smart.
Amulet
Not really. Anyone can take the test.
But I know that you're going to pass.
I hope so...
but I failed it last year.
This is my second try.
Plenty of people only pass it
on their second try.
Besides, with my support,
you're sure to pass!
Right...
Besides, with my support,
you're sure to pass!
Yes! This time I'm going to pass!
Oh? Are you going out?
Yes. My friend in Tokyo
is also on his "ronin year,"
so we're going to cheer each other up.
Have you made any progress yet?
For me, it's a complete dead end.
I've also barely started tackling algebra.
I lost my confidence
after failing the first time.
I think I'll give up on the First and try for the Fourth this time.
I see... I'd probably be better off lowering my sights too.
But you're under a lot of pressure from your parents' hopes.
You should go for it.
I'm sure you can get into the First Higher School.
In any case, I guess it's time to get serious about it.
Yeah, it's time.
Let's do our best, starting tomorrow.
Yeah. We'll both give it our all.
Matsui didn't seem to care much about his studies yet.
Even though I knew it was pointless to feel reassured by such things,
my heart still felt at ease.
Sign: Guesthouse
Hey. Glad you could make it.
Aren't you going to take the test?
I sure will. For the First again.
Anyway, have a seat.
Are you using this for your prep?
I don't see anything that resembles a textbook here.
I'm taking the test,
but I don't care if I pass.
What?
If I don't take the test for the First,
my family will stop sending me money.
So, Kenkichi, want to hit the town tonight?
I know some great places.
You've never been to Yoshiwara, have you?
Here, drink this.
It'll give you courage!
H-Hold up! I'm going home!
See you later!
It was shocking.
It had been a while since I'd seen Sato,
but he'd become a complete degenerate.
Matsui had given up on the First, settling for a provincial school in Kanazawa.
Would I wind up like them
if I kept wasting my time too?
There wasn't much time
left before the test.
I had to make haste.
And then...
Kenkichi, Sumiko's here.
Come down and have a cup of tea.
Okay! I was just thinking of taking a break.
Hey, Kenkichi-san, would you take me
to the First's school festival this Sunday?
The First's school festival?
I'd feel odd, since I'm not a student yet.
Don't worry about it.
You'll be a First Higher School student next year.
I don't really have time now.
I need to cram hard.
You can't just cram all the time.
Don't you need a break sometimes?
Come on, let's go.
Right, but...
What a stick-in-the-mud.
Okay then, I'll just have to get someone else to take me.
I'll go!
This won't affect your studies, Kenkichi?
Oh, that's wonderful!
Hi!
Good to see you, Kuno-kun.
It's been a while.
Come on, I'll show you around.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'm with a guest already.
You seem pretty relaxed.
I'm sure I'll see you here next year.
Enjoy yourself, miss.
Who was that? These First Higher School students are so handsome!
Don't be fooled. He got in
via a recommendation.
But he'd like you to think it
was his own test scores.
Nighttime Aerobatics
You okay, Sumiko-san?
It's too crowded here.
Please stay close to me.
Don't let go of me.
Sumiko's warmth still lingers on my hand.
That's it!
I'll get into the First Higher School
and then propose to Sumiko!
Oh?
I thought you were studying all day long.
I was, but...
So when will he be coming to Tokyo?
The letter from home said he'd be coming right after graduation.
Oh? Then he should be here soon.
So Kenji-kun plans to take
the First Higher School test too?
I hope both of your brothers can get in this year.
Yes. That would be wonderful!
Thanks for having me today!
A toast to the scholars getting
into the First this year!
Cheers!
Kenji, are you sure you can get
into the First Higher School?
No, not at all.
Oh... But you're going
to take the test anyway?
This time, I hope Kenkichi manages to pass it.
I'm just taking it as a practice run.
So that's why you're so relaxed.
Well, good luck to both of you.
Thank you!
Do you really think you can just read books like that and call it a day?
Yeah. There's nothing for me to worry about.
I can always take it again next year.
Right.
Matsui, are there any empty rooms at the temple?
The room next to mine is open. Why?
I can't concentrate on studying
with my brother around.
I have to pass this test no matter what,
and there are only a few weeks left.
All right, then. I'll ask around.
Really? Thanks.
Hello, Kenkichi-san.
Oh!
Pleased to meet you.
I'm his younger brother, Kenji.
Kenkichi's brother?
Yes. My brother went to live
with a friend at the temple.
Oh, really?
He should come soon.
He always drops by on Mondays.
Huh? Why?
That's the day Sumiko-san comes over.
That's you, right?
My brother wrote me about you.
He said you were beautiful.
Would you agree,
having seen for yourself?
You're too good for Kenkichi.
That's funny!
Here he is.
You're right!
What are you two laughing about?
Oh? Were we laughing?
Yeah. I heard you all the way from outside.
Did something funny happen?
No, nothing.
Nothing at all. Right?
Yeah...
Hey, you studying?
Nope. I can't seem to get into it.
Wanna talk for a while?
Sure.
How are you doing?
Not too good. I can't concentrate.
Did you go to see Sumiko-san?
"Bad, worse, worst."
I should have studied
English grammar more.
Well, study and romance just don't mix.
Can you solve this one?
A geometric proof?
Everyone tried it at the cram school,
but no one got it.
Okay, I'll give it a try.
Well, you shouldn't rush.
This one's impossible
to solve immediately.
Hikari Cram
School
I did it.
Really? Let's see...
Wow! You got it!
Let me see it.
That's amazing!
You're a genius!
It took all day, but I finally got it.
I can't believe it!
Come on.
Hey, Kenkichi!
Sumiko-san. Are you going home already?
Yes. I came over early today,
since I knew I'd be busy this afternoon.
And where are you going, Kenji?
Well, uh...
When I told Kenji I was going home,
he offered to walk me back,
since he needed to shop
for some supplies there too.
I'm out of tally sheets, so I was going to get
some straw paper. I'll be back soon.
I see. Goodbye, then, Sumiko-san.
So long.
I'm sorry you missed Sumiko-san.
That doesn't bother me.
Anyway, are your studies going well?
Yes, more or less.
Can you solve this problem?
Geometry?
A proof problem, right?
I think I've got it. Is this right?
That's it!
It's just the opposite of the sample problem in the workbook, right?
Yeah...
The exams are only a few days off.
Yeah... Good luck to both of us.
I was suddenly overcome by anxiety and unease, and I couldn't stand it.
Had all my studying been for nothing?
Goodness, you're burning up.
Kenkichi, I'm so sorry to have to call you here the day before the test.
Sure, but what's wrong?
What should we do?
Best not to push him too hard.
Besides, he only planned
to use this exam as a practice run.
If only I'd taken better care of him.
What should I tell our father?
It's not your fault.
You can't prevent someone getting sick.
Father will understand.
I just hope his fever
goes down by tomorrow.
ENTRANCE EXAM VENUE
Hello.
Can I help you?
I'm Yatabe, the Dean.
No, sir. My brother's taking the test right now,
and that's what worries me.
Oh... Why?
He caught a fever yesterday.
I told him it'd be better for him
to skip the exam this year,
but he just wouldn't listen to me.
I'm afraid he might collapse up there
and disturb the other students,
so I have a rickshaw here
waiting for him.
Do you know your brother's test number?
Yes.
He's number 16 in division 3.
Wait here, please.
Ah! Dean!
Don't worry.
Number 16, how are you feeling?
I'm fine, sir.
Kenji came to the test?
Good. Then you should just relax and do your best.
Don't worry. He seems to be doing fine and making good progress.
My, is that so?
Thank you for your support, sir.
I must issue a warning to you all.
Do not let your blank forms hang from the edge of your desk.
I don't think I need to explain further.
You! I'm disqualifying you!
Leave the premises at once!
Tch! Don't make me laugh.
I was about to leave anyway.
I wrote all the answers ages ago.
Wrote all the answers?
It's blank!
What did you want to see me about?
I'm in love with Sumiko-san.
I'm serious about this.
I want to marry her in the future.
Oh, my.
If possible, I'd like to get engaged
as soon as possible.
Would you act as my intermediary?
Of course.
But at the least, let's wait until you're accepted at the First Higher School.
They'll post the results soon.
Kenji was sick, so he probably failed.
But I'm sure you passed.
Once the results are official,
I'll talk to Sumiko.
Is that all right?
Really?!
Wonderful!
All right!
54     51     50     45     42     39     38    35    29    27    24    22    19
89    84    79    76    69    63    60    58    54     51     50     45      42
I'm not there!
89    84    79    76    69    63    60    58    54     51     50     45     42     39     38    35    29    27    24    22    19
No... It can't be!
And Kenji?
6          4           3         1
19     16     10        7
How...
How is that possible?!
Kenkichi...
Has Kenji seen the results already?
Yes.
You're a student at the First Higher School now! That's great!
I wish my brother had made it too.
Oh, well. He simply didn't have it in him.
I'm just happy that you made it.
SAKE
Driven solely by the desire to escape despair, I drank myself blind.
And before I knew it,
I had completely degraded myself.
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness