The Inoue Platoon,
deployed to Burma during the final stages of the Pacific War,
met the end of the war there.
After the surrender, the captain ordered
one of their soldiers, Private Mizushima,
to go to Triangle Mountain and negotiate with a Japanese unit
that had holed up there
and kept on fighting.
Mizushima took his beloved harp with him.
During the war, he had mastered the Burmese harp.
His playing could lift the morale
of the entire battalion immediately.
He was loved by everyone.
A few days later, the Inoue Platoon was transferred to a POW camp in Mudon.
But even several months later,
Mizushima hadn't joined them there.
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
The Harp
of Burma
Takeyama Michio
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Part 2
Song of Parting
Isn't that Mizushima?
Impossible. It can't be.
But he looks just like him.
The Burmese monk looked exactly like Mizushima.
But if it was Mizushima,
why didn't he say a word to us?
No, rather, why would he shave his head
and pretend to be a monk?
That was the question on everyone's mind.
I knew it wasn't Mizushima.
Mizushima must've died on Triangle Mountain.
That was the only answer
that made sense.
What brings you here so soon?
I had stuff to trade, but the battalion next door was away.
Hey, look at that parrot!
It's just like the one that monk on the bridge had.
Yeah, that one was green too.
Oh, you met that traveling monk too?
Granny, do you know him?
He looked like a distinguished monk.
This is the younger brother
of the bird that monk has.
My husband caught
three birds in the woods.
That's when the monk approached him,
asking for directions.
My husband gave him one of the parrots for his blessing.
Granny, would you sell that bird to us?
I'd be glad to, but what are you going to do with it?
This is to thank you for everything you've told us so far.
Oh, thanks a bunch!
You can teach him Burmese, or Japanese, or whatever you like!
Take a rest!
Why did the Captain buy that parrot?
As a souvenir, maybe.
He'll teach it to sing to replace you,
since you're so bad!
"Hey, Mizushima,
come home to Japan with us."
"Hey, Mizushima, come home to Japan with us..."
Now you say it.
Hey, Mizushima...
Good boy.
"Come home to Japan with us."
Come home. Come.
It's no use. It's too hard for him.
Captain, why are you teaching the bird these words?
We're already eager enough to go home,
but you're shaking the platoon's morale.
Please don't do this.
I'm sorry.
But for some reason,
I can't get over the feeling
that Mizushima is still coming back to us.
That Burmese monk we saw on the bridge
might have actually been Mizushima in disguise.
Next time we see him,
I plan to put this bird on his shoulder.
If it's Mizushima, the bird will tell him what we want to say,
and he'll probably give us some answer.
But if he still says nothing,
we'll know it's not him.
That's when I'll give up.
Several days later, there was another strange incident.
In spring, a cherry blossom viewing party is held in the high tower
We heard a harp that sounded exactly like Mizushima's.
The moon's shadow shines
on the cups we exchange
Shining through pine tree branches
that have lasted for a thousand years
Where is the glory of the past?
In autumn, the camp-
That's Mizushima's harp!
Yeah, that's him!
It's coming from the forest!
No, it's coming from inside that statue!
What?!
That's odd. Are you sure it came from here?
It's solid stone. There's no way in.
Found it! Here's the entrance!
Mizushima, are you in there?
We know it's you, Mizushima!
If you're in there, answer us!
Say something!
Mizushima! Answer!
Mizushima!
What are you doing?
Stop! Stop doing that!
Go back to work!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Then, at the end of that summer,
an order came in I was not expecting.
Hey, they're sending us back!
We're all going back to Japan, people!
What?
All the POWs in Mudon
are being sent home!
We leave in three days!
We're going home?!
Really?!
The Captain told me! He just talked to the British commander.
Hooray!
Thank God!
Hey, Mizushima,
come home to Japan with us.
Right. We should go along with the Captain's plan
and give that parrot to the monk
one of these days.
If he really is Mizushima...
Yeah, he'll come back to us!
And then we can all go home together.
But there are only three days left.
How are we going to give the parrot to that monk?
We can't just go search
for him on our own.
Oh! I know!
Wh-What?
We'll sing every morning,
as loud as we can.
Mizushima will definitely hear it and come!
The Hakone Mountains are
the steepest place in the world
More so than Kankokukan,
there's no comparison
Sky-high mountains with a bottomless ravine
Two days passed, and we sang until our throats were raw.
Rising in the front, shored up in the rear
That Burmese monk might be
Clouds are on the mountains,
fog circles, and the dales fill up
among the audience gathered outside the camp.
No, we knew for sure that
he'd come once he heard us sing.
Even during the day,
the rows of cedar trees are dark
But it turned out that all our work was for nothing.
The narrow path of moss...
I knew it wouldn't work.
My throat's killing me.
Whose great idea was this?
Congratulations! I'm very happy that you boys get to go home.
Thank you.
You sure helped us out a lot.
Once I get home, I'll tell my mother all about you.
Here's something to remember me by.
Me too.
Yeah, and me.
Yes, thanks, everyone!
I'm sure I ain't ever forgetting you either.
Granny, could you give this to that monk
we've talked about before,
the one who keeps a bird?
Oh, but that's impossible.
He's a traveling monk, so I don't have any way of knowing where he is.
Please! We're leaving tomorrow!
I'm sure you can find him!
Please!
Granny, please!
Very well. I'll see that he gets it, then.
Dontcha worry about a thing.
Then, later that evening...
He's here! He's here! He's here!
What? Who's here?
Mizushima's here!
Mizushima?!
No, I mean that monk.
He's right outside the fence.
That's the bridge monk, all right.
He has both parrots.
Granny must have found him.
Take a good look.
Is he really Mizushima?
Come home to Japan with us.
Maybe it's not him, after all.
Let's sing anyway.
Mid pleasures and palaces though we may roam
Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home
A charm from the skies seems to hallow us there
Which seek thro' the world, is ne'er met elsewhere
Home! Home! Sweet, sweet home!
There's no place like home
There's no place like home!
Mizushima!
Thank God! You're back!
We're going home tomorrow!
Come back with us! Mizushima!
Mizushima!
Mizushima.
Come home!
Please!
Note: Mizushima is playing Tabidachi no Hi ni, also known as the "Japanese Graduation Chorus Song," a symbol of an immediate and inevitable parting.
Mizushima!
Mizushima...
Hey, Mizushima!
Come back!
Mizushima!
Mizushima...
We left the POW camp the next day.
A transport ship picked us up near Mudon
and departed toward our motherland of Japan.
As we left camp, the peddling granny came running up.
She gave us a letter and a parrot.
Naturally, they were from the monk.
I mean, the letter was
from Mizushima for us.
Is everyone here?
I'm going to read the letter now.
I think this letter's supposed to explain
why Mizushima couldn't come back with us.
"Captain, my friends, you don't know how much I've missed you.
You have no idea how much
I'd wanted to come back to you,
to work, talk, and sing with all of you,
and how much I longed to return to Japan.
No words can express that.
But I cannot just go home now."
Back then, when I left all of you,
I set out for Triangle Mountain.
My mission was to persuade the Japanese forces
who continued to resist there.
Unfortunately, I couldn't complete that mission,
and I was badly wounded in the process.
An old Burmese monk found me.
He saved my life.
But all I wanted was to return
to my platoon, no matter what.
It was the only thing I thought about.
In desperation, I walked relentlessly to Mudon.
But along the way,
I saw something terrible.
These are Japanese.
I knew I couldn't hope to bury more
of those bleached bones on my own.
So I hurried on to Mudon
as fast as I could.
I'll finally see you all tomorrow!
Why are you playing so early in the morning?
For practice.
The British soldiers pay me to play for them.
And thanks be to God, who delivers me through our Lord Jesus Christ.
So then, my dear brothers...
They're from the British hospital.
More of the wounded Japanese soldiers died this morning.
Amen.
Tomb of Unknown Japanese Soldiers
I remembered all those bones
of my compatriots, scattered across Burma,
exposed to the elements.
I knew I couldn't just abandon them like that and return to you.
So I turned around and went north again.
And on my way back, on the bridge,
I passed by you all.
You can't imagine how I felt,
seeing you back then.
But I knew that I had to do what was right.
I couldn't rejoin you,
and I couldn't tell you who I was.
The only thing I could do was keep walking north, silently.
No, I can't go back home yet.
Mizushima must have
said that every day.
So even the parrot managed
to remember it.
I climbed the mountains, crossed the rivers,
and returned to the dead.
'Mid pleasures and palaces though we may roam
As I worked to bury
the drenched corpses,
I was tormented by uneasy misgivings.
Why must such misery exist in this world?
Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home
Why must such insanity exist?
The Captain said we'd all return to Japan, without leaving anyone behind,
to work together to rebuild our homeland.
A charm from the skies seems to hallow us there
Even now, his words are
echoing in my heart.
But once I'd seen my dead compatriots
left there to rot,
I knew I couldn't abandon them.
Which, seek thro' the world, is ne'er met elsewhere
I've decided to remain in this land
to create a place of rest
for the souls of hundreds of thousands
of my fallen compatriots.
I don't know how many years it'll take, but when I'm done,
Home, home, sweet, sweet home
I'll finally be able to come home.
No, probably not even then.
I'll probably spend my entire life here.
There's no place like home
I think this is my fate.
The other day,
when I was inside the statue,
I heard you calling out to me.
An exile from home, splendor dazzles in vain
I wanted so much to run out
and greet you all.
Mizushima, are you in there?
If you're in there, answer us!
Mizushima! Answer!
Mizushima!
Oh, give me my lowly thatch'd cottage again!
So today I forgot my oath and came to play my harp for you.
The birds singing gaily that came at my call
No matter how many farewell words I write, they will never be enough.
I am staying in Burma
to wander everywhere,
Give me them with the peace of mind dearer than all
from the snow-covered mountains to the seashores,
shining under the Southern Cross.
And when I can't stand the loneliness anymore, I'll play my harp again.
Home, home, sweet, sweet home
I can't thank you enough
for all your friendship and loyalty.
I sincerely wish you
all the best in your endeavors.
There's no place like home
Mizushima Yasuhiko.
The End
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness