Willow trees overlook the front gates of the Yoshiwara district.
Though it's the Meiji era,
it continues to be
one of the few red-light districts
licensed since the Edo period.
The entrance bustles with busy people,
and the rickshaw traffic is heavy here.
This district is named after the Daionji Temple and should be distinctly Buddhist,
but it is inhabited by carefree people.
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
Growing Up
Higuchi Ichiyo
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Which one should I get?
This one!
Here.
I want this one!
This should pay for everything.
Keep the change.
Oh, thank you as always.
Girls, you should all thank Midori.
Thank you, Midori!
Oh? She's pretty generous for a child
whose kimono sleeves are still tucked in.
Well, that's thanks to her older sister Omaki,
who works at Daikoku, a prosperous brothel.
So it's no surprise she can be generous.
Okay, let's go.
I see. I look forward to seeing what she grows up to be.
I bet she'll be even prettier than Omaki.
We're so lucky.
I really wanted this one!
Wow, really?
Out of the way!
Look out!
No spacing out!
Shin!
Here, let me clean that off.
No need. You'll stain your towel.
What rude people
those rickshaw drivers are!
Thanks, but you really don't have to.
Hey, look at the couple!
You look good together!
What a sight! The temple monk and the Daikoku geisha together!
Makes sense. Better to call dibs on her now, before she's
a full-fledged Daikoku geisha and the talk of the town!
W-Wait, Shin!
You still have mud on you!
When you're the son
of the corrupt head monk,
no wonder you're too shy
to show your face on the street!
It wasn't Shin of Ryuge Temple's fault that he acted so curt.
When he heard something so detestable,
his upright character wouldn't let him act otherwise.
He couldn't bear to hear that
about the father who had brought him up.
Oh, Bunji? Ushimatsu's here too. Come on in.
What?! Kids from the main-street gang were that disrespectful to a Ryuge Temple monk?
Yeah. I bet they knew Shin was with our back-street gang. That's why they did it.
Fine. Maybe them making the first move was a blessing in disguise.
Chokichi! You better not start
any more fights!
I know.
We can give them what for
at the next festival.
If we don't do that, I, who dragged Shin
into my back-street gang by force,
will lose face!
Thanks to swaying the Ryuge monks, even the guys who bowed
to Shota before are flocking to the back-street gang!
This year, we're not backing down!
Look, guys. Even if Shota's got
the best grades or his parents are rich,
the pawnshop they're running is a racket!
All their pawnshop does is suck money out
of honest working people with extortionate loans!
Beating him to death
would be a favor to society.
Chokichi! Don't you plan any fights!
Okay...
At that time, Shotaro was still unaware of the danger that lurked nearby.
He visited Midori at the Daikoku Brothel
to discuss their plans for the upcoming festival and how to make the most of it.
I know! We could make a magic lantern!
That would be wonderful!
Everyone could enjoy it!
I can get some of the stuff
from my place.
Midori can buy everything else at the stationary store.
I can be the photographer,
and Sangoro from the back-street gang can narrate.
Yes, Sangoro would be the perfect narrator.
And his face is sure
to make it even funnier!
Fine! Let's get everyone properly excited for the festival.
Shotaro attended the public school,
while Shin and Midori went
to Ikueisha, a private school.
Shin!
Do you know the name
of this beautiful flower?
No, I don't.
Shin gave a snappy answer because
he was worried the kids would see him
with Midori again and make fun of him.
But Midori knew nothing of this,
so naturally, she rashly decided
that she would never even so much as greet him again.
The Senzoku Festival
was held on August 20.
In it, various towns tried to outdo each other in the showiness of their floats.
The traders from Nihonzutsumi to Kuruwa
and their toys captured the attention of the kids right away,
making the festival even more exciting.
This year, Shotaro didn't join in
the festival chorus,
and he spent the eve of the festival
quietly with his friends.
They're late.
What's keeping Midori?
We can't start until she
and Sangoro get here.
Sorry I'm late.
I was babysitting my little brother.
Sangoro! For being late,
you have to go get Midori now!
M-Me?
Yes. Now stop arguing and get going!
Ya got it! Have no fear!
Mother, everyone's waiting!
Hurry up!
Right, right. I'm trying,
but the festival only comes once a year.
I want you to be as beautiful as possible.
Midori, hurry up!
Fleeting is the hidden love...
But next time I see her...
Oh my, Shota. You're barely thirteen.
The path of love is still ahead for you.
I'll go get Midori!
Come with me, people!
There you are, Shota!
I've been calling you!
Why didn't you come home for dinner?
Now, let's go!
B-But...
Oh, I'm sorry, kids. You can come over
and play with him later.
Come on.
H-Hey...
You're kidding!
You made my Shin the underboss of your back-street gang?
Well, I truly feel sorry for you.
With him around,
the atmosphere dampens at once.
Even today, he talked to me
about not drinking and eating eel,
about the virtues of poverty.
Look, he's lecturing me!
I sent him to a store in Tamachi
just to get rid of him.
You mean he'll be late today?
Yeah. If I'd known you were coming,
I wouldn't have sent him away.
But I guess he'd be gone for the Buddhist lantern festival anyway.
Say, Chokichi,
aren't festivals made for everyone to get rowdy once in a while?
Go out and enjoy yourself
as much as you can.
Show them the spirit
of the back-street gang.
W-Will do, sir.
After all that panting and rushing over,
this is beyond anticlimactic!
To be fair to Shota, his grandmother is the only family he has.
And she came all the way
over here just to get him.
I'm sure he'll be back right after dinner.
Well then, ladies and gentlemen,
what would you say to a lively rehearsal of our Yoshiwara impromptu skit?
If you slowly look around you
at the heyday of your life,
the paper lanterns shine cheerfully,
hanging off the eaves of homes.
They're always so bright and...
Sangoro, you there? Hey, Sangoro!
Get out here! Hurry up!
Okay!
You dirty two-timer!
Blinded by money, you think you can pull all this crap?
You traitor of the back-street gang!
Get him!
Shota, come out and fight!
I, Chokichi, will face you!
Hey, stop hiding!
What's the matter?!
Sh-Shota's not here.
You bastard! If you're covering up for him, I'll kill you!
I-I swear! He's not here!
Fine! I don't care anymore.
Let's get them all!
Right!
Stop it! You can't fight in here! Get out!
Tch! Shut up!
Come on, give us Shota!
Where's he hiding? Tell me!
Talk!
You bastard!
Stop it!
Stay out of it, Midori.
Chokichi, Sangoro never did
anything to you!
If you want to fight Shota,
don't drag everyone else into it.
He didn't run away, and he's not hiding. He's just not here.
Taking it out on Sangoro is just awful!
If you want someone to fight,
if you have a grudge,
then take it out on me, you coward!
What was that?
Shut your mouth, you whore!
Young man! How dare you
say that to Midori?!
Tch! She'll just grow up to be a whore
like her sister, so who cares?
Ow!
Now you've done it, Chokichi!
Serves you right.
If you don't like it,
come fight us anytime.
But watch out, 'cause Shin
of Ryuge Temple is with us!
He is?
Tch! The front-street gang are all chickens!
Crap! It's the police!
Sangoro! If you're quitting the gang,
then watch your back!
This is unusual.
You don't usually skip school.
It's like snow on a summer day.
If you don't want breakfast,
how about we order some sushi later?
I'm going to the shrine.
I could go for you
if you're not feeling well.
I'm the one who's been praying for my sister's prosperity.
I have to go myself.
The day the festival ended,
Midori skipped school.
She could wash the mud
from her forehead easily,
but she could never erase the shame from her heart.
Everyone knew how violent
Chokichi could be,
but without Shin's backing, he wouldn't have dared to go that far, she thought.
Even though Shin was older,
a young master of the Ryuge Temple
with an outstanding academic record,
Midori wouldn't see him, even to give him
a single sheet of paper.
She thought, "My sister Omaki,
a celebrated courtesan at Daikoku,
is well off now, despite coming from a family that had fallen into poverty at one point.
I'm lucky I can live in the Daikoku dorm
and look after it when everyone's gone."
Unwilling to tolerate Chokichi's injustice,
and too vexed by the Ryuge monks now bothering her,
Midori suddenly stopped attending school.
She spent her days in the company
of her close friends, doing nothing.
Meanwhile, Shin was disturbed
by the festival incident,
which surpassed his worst fears.
It happened while he was away,
so there was no use blaming them now
for the things done in his name.
Still, he was overwhelmed by the feeling of guilt
for the pain inflicted
on Midori and Sangoro.
The summer finally ended.
Oh? I thought I just heard someone stepping on the planks outside.
Oh? Really? Okay.
Who's there?
I called him, but he wouldn't come.
He was just passing through.
Was it Shin?
That's a shame.
If he came in,
it'd only be to bully someone,
but he ran away
when he heard we were here.
Ah, it's cold!
Midori, what's wrong?
Nothing.
He'll be pitiful as a priest.
He acts all meek in public,
but behind the scenes,
he's been egging Chokichi
and the others on to do awful things.
I've never met anyone so twisted, spiteful, and mean-spirited!
But I heard that Shin didn't know anything about the festival fight.
Who told you that?
Chokichi apologized to Shin at school.
He was making up excuses,
but he was sorry for starting the fight.
And Shin said,
"What's done is done,
but don't pick on the weak anymore."
He said it was shameful
to bully Sangoro and Midori.
It'll probably rain all day.
Oh?
Mother, lend me some cloth.
Someone tore a sandal outside.
When he realized he was passing by Midori's house,
Shin remembered what happened, became distressed,
and tried to hurry past it,
but unfortunately,
the rain had weakened the thong on his sandal.
The embarrassment was
already unbearable.
Then he heard footsteps
skipping across stepping stones,
and he felt as if a bucket of cold water
had been poured over him.
Midori, what are you doing?
Come back in. You'll catch a cold.
Yes, okay!
Oh? Shin, what happened to you?
I was going to my sister's place
to deliver something,
but my sandal broke, so I'm stuck here.
Okay, take mine. Here.
I'll take yours home and store them.
Come on, hand them over.
But I feel bad about this.
Forget it. I'm used to it.
See you later, then.
Yeah.
Oh, Shota? Not collecting the interest today?
Have you seen Midori?
I've been looking for her all day.
I saw her passing by my house earlier.
She was going over the drawbridge.
So she was going into Yoshiwara?
Oh, it was nothing like usual, Shota!
Her hair was all done up,
a full-blown pompadour!
Maybe she's about to become a geisha?
I'm going to the dorm.
She sure is pretty.
Oh, is that you, Shota?
Where's Midori?
In the back.
Midori?
Oh, that hairdo looks really nice on you.
Are you feeling okay, Midori?
She's been in a bad mood
since this morning.
Why don't you try to cheer her up, Shota?
I have to start steaming the rice now.
Did you have a fight
with your sister?
What's wrong?
Did I say something wrong?
Hey, tell me!
I don't want to grow up.
I want to go back in time a year or two.
Why are you talking about that now?
I want to go back.
You're acting weird.
Leave me alone, Shota!
M-Midori!
I'm begging you to leave, please!
Why are you so angry?
I don't want to see anyone anymore!
Or talk to anyone!
I said go away!
Sorry I was such a bother!
Starting next year, everyone in the back-
street gang will switch to your side.
After all, if Shin goes to some Buddhist monk school,
Chokichi will lose his right-hand man,
and it'll be a piece of cake.
From that day on, Midori had suddenly become much more mature.
She went to the red-light district to take lessons from her sister,
and she stopped going out to play.
The front street now felt deserted,
as if the fire had gone out.
Shin.
It was finally the day for Shin to leave, to go far away,
and learn how to be a full-fledged priest.
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
MUZUSSAWA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
MUZUSSAWA
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness