I left my lodgings as soon as Porcupine told me to go.
But I had nowhere to go, so I continued to wander around the town.
Slowly, the sky turned to twilight.
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Botchan
Natsume Soseki
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Orphan Fansubs presents
Part 2
Exterminate Red Shirt!
Is this the Kajiya district?
Yeah. It's mostly ancestral mansions.
Then they probably won't be renting rooms.
Oh yeah!
Unprepared lives in this area.
Well, that's just terrible!
It is. Do you perhaps know of anyone around here who's looking
for a boarder or could just let me stay for a night?
Hm, well...
Ah, right!
There's an elderly couple named Hagino living behind us.
They told me they'd rent out their vacant tatami room to someone trustworthy.
I see. Much obliged!
Thanks to Unprepared, I became a resident at the Hagino house that night.
After that, I didn't speak to Porcupine at all.
A meeting was held to decide
the punishment for the boarding students
who pulled my leg
the other night while on night duty.
Obviously, this was entirely their fault.
I was certain that everyone would demand strict punishment, but I was wrong.
Red Shirt, Buffoon, and the others
suggested leniency.
I got more and more furious
and decided to voice a protest.
But just as I was about to speak up,
Porcupine stood up first.
He was... the one who incited the students to begin with.
I already know he'd be lenient
like the others.
I couldn't disagree more with what
the vice principal and others have just said.
No matter how you look at it,
this incident was obviously fifty of our students conspiring
to humiliate a rookie teacher.
The vice principal suggests that the fault lies with said teacher's character.
With all due respect,
I think that's inappropriate.
He was put on night duty
after less than 20 days on the job.
The students couldn't possibly have had time to evaluate his scholarly
or personal character
in such a short period.
Without any provocation,
they chose to ridicule and dishonor him.
If we let such a conduct
from students slide,
it will affect the school's reputation.
I'm going to ask for a harsh punishment for all the students.
I was shocked.
He agreed completely with me.
But why would the instigator call for punishment of his own accomplices?
Maybe Red Shirt was the real liar.
In conclusion, I kindly request
that you approach this matter with the utmost seriousness.
There's one detail I forgot to mention.
That night, the teacher on night duty
left the school to go to the springs.
I find that behavior outrageous.
Punishment for students aside,
I believe the principal should also
take disciplinary action against the teacher in question.
I admit it. I did go
to the hot springs that night.
I was wrong, and I'm sorry.
Say, Koga, what did you think
about the vice principal's speech?
When he said teachers occupy
an elevated position in society?
"Spurn all worldly pleasures."
Meaning you can't go
for soba or dumplings.
Instead, you should fish,
read literature, and write poetry.
And that teachers should only seek spiritual pleasures.
Did he really say that?
Weren't you listening?
Yes, but I had something else on my mind.
To me, tasty dumplings and tempura soba are a spiritual pleasure!
The vice principal's got some nerve,
talking like that,
when he's sneaking out to meet
a geisha named Madonna himself.
Are you all right?
Yes...
There's no geisha named Madonna?
Oh, no.
"Madonna" is a foreign word,
meaning "beautiful woman."
Right... Thank you.
Then maybe it's somebody's nickname?
Perhaps it refers to Miss Toyama.
Your friend, Koga, who brought you here, was engaged to her.
All the arrangements had been made.
But sadly, Koga's father
passed away last year.
Since then, a lot more has happened,
and his family has found themselves in reduced circumstances.
He's a fine young man,
but he's often taken advantage of.
For one reason or the other,
the wedding kept getting postponed.
Then the vice principal jumped the gun and proposed to her.
I see. So that's what it was.
Red Shirt is just a treacherous viper!
Miss Toyama also felt obliged to Koga,
so she didn't accept
his proposal right away.
But the vice principal persisted.
He wanted the Toyama's status.
Then, at last,
he succeeded in taming her.
One two-way ticket for the hot springs.
Oh, Koga, are you going to the hot springs?
Yeah.
Well, I think I have to apologize to you.
I didn't know all the circumstances,
so my joke about the geisha...
Madonna really is beautiful.
I'm no good at describing what makes a woman gorgeous,
so I won't try.
Looking at her made me feel like I was cradling a ball of crystal
that had been warmed in perfume in my palm.
Oh, hello!
I thought I'd be late,
so I was in an awful rush,
but I still have several minutes.
You must really like hot springs.
Yes. They're great. They're the only good thing about this place.
Oh, no. I know you can't really mean that.
I'm not from this area either,
but this is a good town.
Once you've lived here a while,
you'll grow to see it too.
Ah, the train's finally here.
I didn't see Red Shirt at the hot springs.
There were many baths,
so I didn't expect to run into him
for a second time in one night.
Shimokawa's Cafe
Hot Spring Specialty Dumplings
Sweet Potato Soup
The moon was beautiful when I left the bath,
so l decided to walk home.
If we just wait a little while,
everything will resolve itself.
How long is "a while"?
Oh, about six months maybe?
That's too long. I hate waiting.
Okay, then three months.
One month.
Even I can't do that!
That's way too soon.
Well, let's head home now.
But...
It's getting late.
I've decided to let you treat me
to shaved ice, after all.
Good!
In fact, I'm afraid
I have to apologize to you.
Apologize?
Yes, for believing your landlord.
I checked up on his story.
He told lies about you
because you wouldn't buy his antiques.
Can you forgive me?
Don't worry about it.
By the way, have you heard?
What?
Koga's been transferred.
Wh-What?!
So Red Shirt has finally managed
to chase him off.
Koga's a good man. Maybe too good.
Let's rough up Red Shirt
at the farewell party.
We can't! We'd just make more trouble for Koga.
If we're going to rough Red Shirt up,
we'll have to catch him
red-handed at one of his schemes.
At Unprepared's farewell party,
the vice principal stood up
after the principal.
He showered Unprepared in feigned praise.
He even said that to lose
such a good man
was a personal tragedy
that left him in deep sorrow.
Previously, Principal and Vice Principal
called Koga's departure a tragedy.
I completely disagree.
I hope that Koga can escape
from here as soon as possible.
The town that he will be moving to
may be less materially convenient than where we are now,
but I hear it's a place
of remarkably simple customs.
I doubt there'd be even a single smooth-talking dandy there,
who'd shower Koga in praise through his teeth,
or a vain beauty who will manipulate our trusting friend.
I'm sure they'll recognize Koga for the gentleman he is
and welcome him with open arms.
I congratulate him
on his future good fortune.
Did you know that Red Shirt has been seeing a geisha?
Oh, of course.
She was at Koga's farewell party.
You're pretty sharp.
When she arrived,
Red Shirt completely ignored her
and walked right past her when he left.
He won't stop at anything in his schemes!
I can't stand him!
Yeah. Damn right.
"Smooth-talking dandy" back then
wasn't strong enough.
Then what should I have said?
You should have called him a loathsome,
slimy, lying, twisted, festering, pathetic little dandy!
I'm not that good with words.
With a vocabulary like that,
why don't you give more speeches?
No... My vocabulary's no good
for speeches, only for arguments.
Speaking of that, this morning,
my students almost had a fight
with students from the normal school.
Middle schools and normal schools are always like cats and dogs.
Right... Well, then, with all the meat gone,
I could use a walk to help settle my meal.
Right, good idea.
Teacher!
Teacher! This is big!
What?
There's a fight with the normal school!
So it finally happened?
Please hurry!
Fine. Where are they fighting?
On the riverbed!
Teacher, hurry!
It figures.
But we can't just stand here and do nothing. Let's go!
We must end this
before the police arrive.
What should we do?
For now, just break them up.
Okay!
Break it up! Enough!
All of you, stop it!
Hey! Stop fighting!
Stop it!
Stop with the violence!
You are disgracing your school! Disperse!
Ouch!
Now their teachers are helping!
They're too big to beat like that. Use rocks!
Behave yourselves! Stop fighting!
It's the police! Run!
This newspaper story
is a total fabrication!
Hotta and I didn't start the fight.
We tried to stop it!
That's just unforgivable!
"A certain impudent new teacher, just transferred from Tokyo..."
They should at least use my name!
Now, don't get worked up.
Your bruises are still fresh.
I'm going to complain to the paper!
Will you come with me?
Please let me take care
of this newspaper affair.
I'll see that they print a retraction.
No, thank you. I'll go alone.
If you get in a row with the editor,
the next story will be even worse,
instead of a retraction.
Just let me handle this, okay?
Come in.
This article is utter nonsense!
Principal, you must believe me.
Of course. By the way,
why don't you two take a day off?
No, thank you, sir!
The article was printed
at Red Shirt's request.
Can he really do that?
You bet he can.
Then we'll probably be dismissed.
Only if we slip up one more time.
Oh, here's my class.
Quiet down!
Hey! I said be quiet!
Dammit! There's no retraction!
Matsuyama
Junior High School
Why don't you want
my resignation too?!
Why did you ask Hotta
to resign, but not me?!
The school has its reasons.
Those reasons are wrong.
Why should Hotta resign, while I...
Yes, you're quite right.
Hotta's dismissal was unavoidable.
We did not see any need
to sack you as well, however.
Masuya
It's me.
How are things at school?
Same as always.
Does anyone suspect I stayed behind
on the second floor of Masuya?
They all think you've long
gone home to Aizu.
This is all Red Shirt's fault.
Just looking at his face makes me want to vomit, yet I can't tell him!
I can't wait to go back to Tokyo.
Once we punish him,
we can both go home.
I can give them my resignation any day, now.
Will Red Shirt really visit that inn?
Don't worry. He'll come!
How many days have we been waiting?
Seven days.
Sorry I'm late.
You've been staying out
especially late recently.
Sorry.
She's here.
They're finally here.
Kosuzu and another geisha
arrived around 7:30.
Was Red Shirt with them?!
No.
Then this is pointless.
Two geisha is actually good news for us.
Wh-Why?
Red Shirt's a tricky bastard.
He'll try to sneak in later.
Yes. You might be right,
but isn't it already after nine?
It's 9:12.
Hey, extinguish the lamp.
If that fox sees our silhouettes up here, then the plan's blown.
I'm giving up if they don't come tonight.
I'll stay until my money runs out.
It looks like they won't show up tonight, either.
There they are!
It's been a while, so I'm excited!
They're out of our way now,
and everything's settled down again.
They had plenty of energy,
but no plan.
I must say, the kid's such a Tokyo fool!
Well, for a Tokyo fool, he still has the gallantry of a botchan,
so there's certain charm to it.
You should have seen him when he tried to resign.
I could hardly hold back from laughing.
KADOYA
That's true! Very true!
Those bastards!
They've finally shown their true colors.
Hey, let's rush into Kadoya now
and catch them at the scene!
No! We can't.
If we force our way in,
the innkeeper will have us
arrested for assault.
And if we knock,
they'll escape out the back door.
I guess we'll just have to wait
for them to come out.
KADOYA
Stop!
Hotta!
Just what was our vice principal doing all night at the Kadoya Inn?!
Am I forbidden from staying
at an inn because of my position?
It is forbidden for you to see a geisha!
Can you prove that I brought a geisha with me?
Shut up! You called me
a foolish Tokyo botchan!
I-I wasn't talking about you!
Oh, a liar!
The two of us just stayed
there for the night.
Some geisha came at 7:30,
but we never met them.
Shut up!
Enough talk!
Th-This is assault.
It's against the law to hit someone because of your suspicions!
I don't care about the law!
A beating is the only answer I've got for scum like you!
You...
Take this!
How about this?
Y-You're out of your mind!
S-Save me! Please!
You two are nothing but crooks!
Consider this your divine punishment.
Learn from this and reflect!
Say what you want,
but justice will prevail in the end.
I'm not going to run or hide.
I'll be down at the harbor until 5 PM.
Come find me.
Bring the police or whatever!
I'll be there too!
I checked out of my lodgings
and went down to the harbor.
We waited until 6 PM, but nobody showed up, not even the police.
At sunset, Porcupine and I sailed away from this town.
Kiyo!
B-Botchan!
Kiyo, how are you?
Well, you sure came back rather early.
I'll never go to the country again.
I'll stay in Tokyo with you.
Botchan...
A friend was able to get me
a job as a streetcar conductor.
The salary was 25 yen a month.
Our rent was only 6 yen.
Our house wasn't very large,
but Kiyo was happy with it.
Sadly, Kiyo caught pneumonia and passed away this past February.
The day before she died,
she called out to me:
"Botchan,
after I die, bury me in your temple."
"I'll wait for you there
until we can be reunited."
So I buried Kiyo
at the Ryogen temple in Kohinata.
I write a letter to my loved one
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
Timing
NINJACLOUD
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I feel like I'm sinking
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness
Encoding
ANONYMOUS