One evening,
as I returned to my room
in Monbijoustrasse,
while passing by Klosterstrasse,
I noticed a young girl sobbing
near the closed door of the church.
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
The Dancing
Girl
Mori Ohgai
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Orphan Fansubs presents
In 1884,
a certain government office
sent me to study in Germany.
My destination was Berlin.
I was assigned to the office there.
But this time, my trip to Europe was more than sightseeing.
I was to live there for several years,
working with senior officials.
I was burning with ambition.
My life began in the good old
capital city of Berlin,
where Wilhelm I still reigned.
Fortunately, at my parents' urging,
I had studied German and French as a child.
I found work quickly after graduation.
There were plenty of opportunities for a skilled interpreter.
Thanks!
That winter,
something happened
that changed my life forever.
That was the year I met Elise.
Can I help you, Fraulein?
You look so forlorn. I felt I had to ask.
Perhaps you can tell me your problems.
Don't worry. You don't need
to be afraid of me.
I live on Monbijoustrasse.
My name is Ota Toyotaro.
I'd be happy to help you if I can.
Don't cry. People are staring.
Where do you live? I'll walk you home.
Please help me. My mother threw me out of the house.
She kept beating me.
My father's dead.
We have to hold his funeral tomorrow,
but we have no money!
I understand.
Come on, I'll take you home.
Who is it?
It's me, Elise.
Where have you been?
You've been gone
for more than an hour! Come in!
We haven't even buried your father yet,
and you're wandering off somewhere!
Mother...
Excuse me, Mein Herr.
I didn't mean to be rude.
Our place may be a rather decrepit,
but please come in.
The mother told me that her husband
had worked as a tailor, a good one.
He had just passed away,
after a prolonged struggle.
As a result, the family's finances
had deteriorated to the point where they didn't know if they'd eat tomorrow.
Mother wanted me to go
to the moneylender living nearby.
Moneylender?
He's a nasty character. We've already borrowed money from him before.
But this time he wanted me as collateral!
He was really persistent too.
I'd rather die than go live
with a man like him!
I know it's an outrageous request,
but could you lend us some money?
I'll pay you back every month
from my salary.
And we won't bother you ever again!
You have a job?
Do you know the Victoria Theater?
Yes, they often stage ballets there.
I'm one of their dancers.
I only have two or three marks
in cash at present.
It would obviously not be enough,
so I'd like you to have this.
Tell the pawnbroker's man if he calls on Ota at 3 Monbijoustrasse,
I'll redeem it.
I'll never forget your kindness.
And so, from that day onward,
my relationship with Elise deepened day by day.
Thanks for waiting.
Let's go. I'm hungry.
Okay.
Your dancing was beautiful.
You're making me blush.
Why?
I was just one in the crowd of dancers.
I bet you couldn't even find me.
No, on the contrary.
You were the only one I saw.
Oh...
Unfortunately, our happiness wasn't meant to last.
I had a sudden stroke of bad luck.
Some of the staff at the embassy
had never liked me.
They reported my behavior to the main office in Japan.
They claimed that my relationship with Elise was affecting my work.
That was a slanderous
distortion of the facts,
but it was enough to incur
the director's wrath.
If he returns to Japan immediately,
we'll cover his return trip, at least.
Otherwise, we'll cut off
all salary and support.
That's too cruel to be true!
I can't stand it!
I couldn't live without you!
Please, Toyotaro! Don't go back!
Don't leave me!
Don't worry.
I'm not the kind of man
to give in to their blackmail.
I won't leave you.
I love you, Toyotaro.
I couldn't live without you.
I love you too, Elise.
I could never leave you.
Tomorrow, I'll look for another job.
I'll take any job, whatever it may be.
And I'll have to find a new place to live.
You could stay at my house!
Your house?
Unless it's too small for you, please do.
At least to save you rent money.
What about your mother?
That's all right.
I've already talked to her.
I told her we might be married soon.
Elise...
But it would be better for now
not to tell her you've lost your job.
She gets very unpredictable
when it comes to money.
And so my new life began.
Though, of course, I felt
an indescribable emptiness
at the thought of never seeing my homeland again.
I'd be lying if I said that I felt no regrets.
But for the time being, I was more preoccupied with how to make a living.
Ota.
Aizawa!
My boy, I've been looking for you.
I didn't know you'd moved out
of your rented room.
I'm sorry.
Let's go someplace we can talk in peace.
But I...
I may have work for you.
That man was Aizawa Kenkichi, a foreign ministry secretary,
who'd been dispatched to Berlin around the same time as I.
He'd been a friend since college.
A correspondent for the Tokyo Daily News?
Yes. They're a daily newspaper,
but the articles don't have to be highly specialized.
Politics, art, lifestyle... anything goes.
You'd write about the everyday happenings
of your life in a column called "The Berlin Diaries."
It's more than I'd ever hoped for!
After learning of my dismissal,
Aizawa talked
to his acquaintance,
the editor of the Tokyo Daily News.
It was the first time I'd felt this immense gratitude for having such good friends.
And that winter...
Just a cold from overwork.
It's not serious. However...
Your wife also seems to be pregnant.
It would be better if she refrained from performing on stage for the time being.
Pregnant?
Although I should have been elated,
in my heart of hearts,
I couldn't bring myself to feel any joy.
Did I really want to spend
the rest of my life in this foreign land?
But I was going to be a father now.
I loved Elise,
and that was the result of it.
It was from Aizawa.
Minister Amakata, for whom he worked as a secretary, was on his way to Berlin,
and Aizawa absolutely wanted me to meet him.
Aizawa thought it might be my only chance to redeem myself.
Remember to be polite.
If you impress him, they might make you an incredibly good offer.
What do you mean?
They might offer you a job.
You're such a talented interpreter!
Just as Elise predicted, the minister
hired me as his personal interpreter
for the duration of his stay.
But when Aizawa invited me
to dinner one night,
he delivered a fatal verdict to me.
What? You want me to leave Elise?
Yes. I know it's cruel,
but your entire future hangs on this.
You still have a chance to put it right.
But that means...
Listen, Ota.
You have the perfect opportunity here.
Minister Amakata is very impressed with you.
He's prepared to offer you a major post
if you'll return to Japan now.
You can't pass this up!
What you need to do now is to take the initiative
and live up to the minister's expectations.
You have no shortage of education or talent, so why must you
remain forever entangled in your affection for this foreign woman?
I can't stand to see you wasting your life like this!
Sorry, I'm not trying to say something bad about her.
But even if you really love her,
I know it was just the loneliness of living abroad that drove you to that.
You'll have to make up your mind once and for all!
No, sorry, you don't have to decide immediately.
Next week, the minister will be traveling to St. Petersburg in Russia.
Naturally, he'll want you along to interpret for him.
You'll have to make the call
when you two return to Berlin.
All right?
I understood Aizawa's
concerns all too well.
And I was glad to have him.
But does he really think
I'd be able to leave my life
with Elise behind so easily?
No, how could I ever leave it behind?
She was carrying my child.
But I couldn't get Aizawa's words about this being
the watershed moment
of my life out of my head.
He may be right. This probably is my last chance to make up my mind.
Darling, I hope you're well.
It's only been ten days since you left Berlin,
but it already feels like many months have passed.
Maybe it's because of the loneliness,
but I've gotten a little sicker these days.
The doctor says it's anemia.
I'm trying not to push myself,
for the baby's sake,
and to look after myself.
I've been praying that everything goes well for you with the current job, but...
When I think that after this, they might want you to go back to Japan anyway...
I can feel my heart sink.
But you're my husband.
You promised that you'd stay here in Berlin with me forever.
And I'll always trust you.
Goodbye, my beloved Toyotaro.
They say some things in this world are able to foreshadow our future.
Elise's letter must've been one of them.
I'd promised to Aizawa to make
a decision by the end of the trip.
But I couldn't bring myself to do it.
What should I do?
I was at my wits' end.
Darling!
Elise.
Welcome home, darling!
Welcome back. We missed you.
How did it go?
It was fine.
You look a little emaciated.
Are you feeling all right?
No, I'm fine. Just a little tired.
And how are you, Elise?
I feel much better,
now that you're home again.
Look!
Do you know what these are?
No.
They're diapers.
Diapers?
Yes. It took me a while,
but I sewed them all.
Aren't you proud of me?
I hope our child has dark eyes like yours. He'll be lovely!
Let's give him a Japanese name too!
Ernsttaro. Or maybe Ernstjiro?
They both sound so lovely!
And finally, the fateful day arrived.
We can't wait any longer.
The minister's leaving next week.
He said that you could return to Japan with him.
But you have to make up your mind!
Ota, as your friend,
I'll say it one last time.
If you pass this up,
you'll never return to Japan again!
Is that what you want? Well?
Tell the minister...
I'd like to accept...
his offer.
My mind was in a blur as I walked away from the hotel.
I didn't know what I was thinking,
or where I was going.
But I did feel a stabbing pain in my heart,
and an accusing voice ringing in my ears: "Traitor! Traitor!"
Idiot!
Forgive me, Elise! Forgive me!
He's late.
I hope nothing's happened.
Darling! What's wrong?
Hold on, darling! Toyotaro!
I finally woke up five days later.
I've been feverish and unconscious this whole time.
But in those five days,
a catastrophe had struck.
Go to sleep in your mother's arms...
Poor girl. I'm afraid it's my fault that she ended up this way.
Forgive me, Ota.
When I heard you were sick,
I came right over.
I had to tell them everything that happened the night before.
You're lying! It just can't be true!
Toyotaro would never betray us!
He'd never abandon us!
It's gotta be a lie!
If it's true,
then I'll kill him!
And then I'll kill myself!
It's a lie, isn't it, darling?
Hey, tell me it's a lie!
Please!
It's a lie!
And then she lost her senses.
The doctor said she'd suffered an extreme mental shock.
I think it was at least a saving grace
that it happened while you were asleep.
Go to sleep, go to sleep...
Sleep in your mother's arms...
Elise...
Do you need your medicine?
I'll bring it for you.
Go to sleep... Go to sleep...
Sleep in your mother's arms...
Forgive me, Elise! This is all my fault!
Go to sleep...
A few days later, I left Berlin and was on my way back to Japan.
Aizawa gave Elise's mother enough money
to support herself, Elise,
and my unborn child in my stead.
But...
That did nothing to lessen my crimes.
I'd have to live with this burden
for the rest of my life.
In this harsh world, a friend like Aizawa Kenkichi is very rare indeed.
Yet a trace of hatred for him
still lingers in my mind to this day.
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness