'Mid pleasures and palaces though we may roam
The war left us all with tragic memories.
Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home
This is the true story of one battalion in the Japanese army.
July, 1945
The Burma Front
A charm from the skies seems to hallow us there
July, 1945
The Burma Front
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
The Harp
of Burma
Takeyama Michio
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Part 1
No Place Like Home
Which, seek thro' the world, is ne'er met elsewhere
The situation on the battlefield turned against us.
Home, home, sweet, sweet home
Everywhere, the British and Indian armies pushed us back.
We moved camp every day,
from mountain to mountain.
We had to cross the border
into Thailand, still nominally
an independent nation, when required.
There's no place like home
Make sure the ammunition is tied down!
It's the enemy!
Scatter! Get down!
Retreat, everyone!
Take cover behind the rocks!
Everyone okay?
Let's go, men!
Watch out.
Hurry up!
We should sing.
Times like this are what a choir is for, to cheer us up!
Mizushima, would you play your harp?
Okay.
On a drowsy autumn night
Under the sky of travel
I am alone with a lonely thought
I miss my hometown
And my remembered father and mother
In my dreams, I am following
We sang pretty well, really.
The way home to my hometown
I was a music student before the war,
so I taught the troops how to sing.
My dream was shattered by the window storm
The enemy could find us at any moment, and we'd be killed the next minute.
But until then, we at least tried to fill our hearts with song.
That's what I'd hoped for
when I started the choir.
My heart is lost far away
Private Mizushima was an expert
on the Burmese harp.
He hadn't played anything before coming to Thailand,
but whether or not it was innate talent,
he improved remarkably fast
and soon began devising and playing splendid accompaniments himself.
The main problem for us was food.
The enemy was always lying in ambush, one village ahead of us.
We couldn't let our guard down.
Then, one day, we spotted a village below a cliff.
Commander!
The village is safe. Let's go.
It was a fantastic welcome.
They held a feast
and even brought out wine.
The Burmese are devoted Buddhists and are strictly forbidden to drink.
But the villagers somehow managed to get this wine just for us.
We're deeply touched by this unexpected welcome,
so we'll sing a song in gratitude.
In spring, a cherry blossom viewing party is held in the high tower
The moon’s shadow shines
on the cups we exchange
Shining through pine tree branches
that have lasted for a thousand years
Where is the glory of the past?
That prompted the Burmese to start singing as well.
The feast turned into a lively party,
almost like one in the city.
We had such a good time
that it took us a while to notice.
To Xuzhou, Xuzhou, both man and horse advance
Before we knew it,
all the Burmese had vanished.
Is Xuzhou a good place to stay,
a good place to live?
Turning back at the humorous lyrics...
Hey! Stop singing!
We suddenly became nervous.
It wasn't uncommon for villagers
to welcome us warmly and warn the enemy at the same time.
The situation was reversed.
We had to prepare for a battle immediately.
Don't move. Keep singing.
The enemy in the jungle may have
surrounded this assembly hall.
But we can't let them know
that we've figured it out now.
Keep singing while we prepare.
They're receiving flowers in their beautiful cups
Reflecting the shadow of the moon
in their delicious sake
And indulging in dreams of security
While looking down on such a prosperous society
The youth of the five dormitories
rising in Mukogaoka are in high spirits
The enemy appears to be
a substantial force.
You never know when they'll open fire all at once.
It'll be dark soon.
We need to buy time until then.
Keep clapping your hands, laughing, and singing.
Captain, our ammunition
is still out in the open.
If it's hit by enemy fire, it's all over.
We have to find a way to get that inside.
Once more!
You bet!
'Mid pleasures and palaces though we may roam
Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home
A charm from the skies seems to hallow us there
Which, seek thro' the world, is ne'er met elsewhere
Home, home, sweet, sweet home...
Night came quickly.
In the tropics, the boundary between day and night is distinct,
and once the sun sets,
it turns pitch black in an instant.
...though we may roam
Be it ever so humble, there's no place like home
A charm from the skies seems to hallow us there
Which, seek thro' the world, is ne'er met elsewhere
If a body meet a body,
comin' thro the rye
If a body kiss a body,
need a body cry?
Ev'ry lassie has her laddie,
nane, they say, ha'e I
Yet a' the lads they smile on me,
when comin' thro' the rye
The evening sky clears and the autumn wind blows
Moonlight fills the sky,
a bell cricket chirps
I think of the sky of my hometown, so far away
Oh, I wonder how my parents live
The evening sky clears and the autumn wind blows
If a body meet a body, comin' thro the rye
Moonlight fills the sky, a bell cricket chirps
If a body kiss a body, need a body cry?
That night, they told us the war had been over for three days.
I think of the sky of my hometown, so far away
Ev'ry lassie has her laddie, nane, they say, ha'e I
Oh, I wonder how my old parents live
Yet a' the lads they smile on me, comin' thro' the rye
That night, we threw down our weapons.
We've surrendered. Japan has surrendered.
I don't know how to feel about this yet.
And as for our future...
I don't yet know where they'll take us,
or what they'll make us do,
or even whether we'll live or die.
But we've been through life and death together all this time.
And we'll face the fate coming to us together as well.
We may end up buried here in Burma,
but even then, we'll go as a single unit.
If we're lucky and we get
to go home one day,
we won't leave a single man behind.
We'll go home together
to rebuild our homeland.
That's all I have to say for now.
I think they're planning to move us
to the POW camp in Mudon soon.
Finally.
When they lock us all up in the camp,
they might just execute us then.
They wouldn't!
Where's Mudon, anyway?
I don't know.
Mizushima! Where's Mizushima?
Here!
I've just received a report.
A Japanese unit is holed up
in the mountains over there
and won't surrender, no matter what.
Three days ago,
the British launched an attack,
but they still couldn't smoke them out.
If this continues, the unit will be completely destroyed.
I asked the British commander
to take one of us to the mountain,
so he can explain things and prevent unnecessary casualties.
What do you say, Mizushima?
Will you go?
If you won't, I will.
I'll go.
Good to know.
I'm not sure how I can explain it to them,
but if I speak to them directly,
I'm sure they'll understand.
They're transferring our unit south soon, to Mudon.
After you've done your part,
be sure to come there too.
I talked this over with a British officer,
so he promised to send you there personally.
I understand.
Once I'm done,
I'll be joining you in Mudon.
Good luck!
Take care!
Mizushima!
Soon, the British moved our unit
out of the mountains.
We crossed the Sittang River and headed down to Mudon.
Mudon
For a long time, many years on end,
we had hardly ever spent such quiet days.
The days spent consumed by battle,
constantly hounded by tension and anxiety,
now felt like a distant fairy tale.
In any case, as we waited
for the day we'd return home,
many peaceful, quiet days passed.
But gradually, an uneasy feeling
began to stir among us.
Although many days had passed,
Mizushima still hadn't returned.
We began to wonder
what had happened to him.
I wonder where Mizushima is.
We've been here a month,
and we haven't heard a thing.
It ain't right!
Maybe he's dead already.
Don't talk nonsense!
Misushima's too smart
to get himself killed!
But I hear fighting continues in that village on Triangle Mountain,
so even if he didn't die, he might be injured and lying in some hospital.
That'd be good, but I wonder if there's any way we could know for sure?
I should have gone myself.
Back then, I figured Mizushima would be more convincing,
so I asked him to go talk to them.
But now I realize that
it was my responsibility.
Don't worry, Captain.
Mizushima will be back, sooner or later.
He probably put on a loincloth
and went native.
I'll bet he's receiving a warm welcome in every nearby village.
He'll just stroll in later, saying, "Sorry I'm late!"
Cheerful, like nothing happened.
Another month thus passed,
but there was no still sign of Mizushima.
Hi, Granny! Good to see you!
We've been waiting!
That bonehead Indian soldier!
He asked if I had a permit with me.
There's always a new one
who doesn't know me yet.
Hey, Granny, would you give me
a banana for my shirt?
Sure.
Hey, how about some chambakka for this broom?
I made it from Yashi leaves.
Oh, good workmanship.
Okay, it's a deal.
This old lady has been doing business with Japanese soldiers
from when the Japanese army was still in power and stationed in this town.
A huge Japanophile,
she’d picked up the language
from the occupying Kansai unit,
and now spoke with a thick Kansai accent herself.
Granny, did you look into
what I asked before?
What did you want again?
Have you forgotten?
Oh, the soldier that was sent to Triangle Mountain!
Yes. Is it true that the wounded soldiers
being treated at the hospital in this town
were really captured at Triangle Mountain?
And if so, is there a Japanese soldier
from a different battalion
who was sent to negotiate with them?
And what happened to him?
That's what I need to know.
I'll make sure to ask around
in that hospital
if I happen to pass by
in the next few days.
If you do, we'll repay you
in any way we can.
Don't forget this time!
Remember!
Make sure you don't forget again!
I got it, don't worry.
Thanks for your things.
Bye now. Goodbye!
A few days later, she told us what she'd learned.
It was news that plunged us
into even deeper despair.
The soldiers at that hospital
were definitely stationed somewhere called Triangle Mountain,
or something like that.
And they remembered the man from another battalion
you were asking about.
Thanks to him, they stopped fighting before it was too late,
and their lives were spared.
But they don't know
what happened to him.
They said he was running across
the battlefield through a hail of bullets,
so he probably got killed.
He died in battle?
But several days later, at sunset, we saw something strange.
We were on our way back from repairing a bridge outside the village...
What's that?
He's so incredibly like him!
He looks just like Mizushima!
Let's call him by name!
No, you fool!
After working all day,
everyone fell asleep instantly.
But I couldn't sleep that night.
That Burmese monk reminded me
of Mizushima too much.
But why would Mizushima come to see us dressed up like that?
And if that Burmese monk was Mizushima,
why did he just rush by without speaking?
It must have been someone else.
"We know... that Mizushima is dead."
That's what I kept telling myself.
To be continued
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
QC
NEMESIS
PAUL GEROMINI
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness