Dan-no-Ura
Eight hundred years ago,
the Heike and Genji clans fought the final battle
of their long-standing feud at Dan-no-Ura,
in the waters of the Kanmon Straits.
Although the Genji had more ships,
they were initially
at a disadvantage against the Heike,
who were more skilled in sea battles.
Still, with the power of their determination,
they pushed the Heike westward against the shore.
Then the samurai of Shikoku and Kyushu defected to the Genji side.
The Heike were trapped,
with nowhere to escape.
The Heike clan, once so proud
of its military glory,
was completely wiped out
and met a bitter end at Dan-no-Ura.
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
A Ghost Story
Koizumi Yakumo
(Shincho Bunko edition)
The Story of Hoichi
The bell of the Gion temple
Tells of the vanity of worldly things
Hoichi-san!
Here! I'm over here.
Right, the monks at the temple
said you'd gone to the beach.
I was looking for you.
I'm sorry, but it's very nice here.
My lord asked me to find you.
If you're not busy,
he'd like you to play for him.
I'm not busy right now.
Wonderful! My lord is entertaining
a guest from Akashi.
He heard about your skill
with the biwa,
so now he's dying to hear it.
All right.
Then... let's go to your master.
Give me your hand.
Yes, sorry.
Careful!
What's wrong?
You almost stepped on a crab.
A Heike crab?
They say the crabs were once possessed
by the spirits of Heike
who died here at Dan-no-Ura.
Even now, the crab's shell holds the image of a human face.
My word, that stuff is creepy.
What would you like to hear?
I'd like to hear The Battle of Dan-no-Ura, of course.
All right.
Hoichi's rendition of that song
is magnificent.
Then please let us hear it, Hoichi-san.
The soldiers of the Genji boarded the Heike boats
There they took up swords
And cut the Heike down
Hoichi.
Chief Priest, are you going out?
Yeah.
I'm going to Sugino village.
Yasuke-san, hasn't the chief priest returned yet?
He won't be back until tomorrow morning.
Hoichi!
Hoichi.
Yes! I'm sorry, but I can't see.
Who are you?
I beg your pardon.
I am staying near this temple.
I have need of you.
Y-Yes?
My lady is a noble ruler
who leads a great retinue of vassals.
They are staying in this area.
We've come to see
the battlefield of Dan-no-Ura,
and we heard that you excel
at recounting the details of the battle.
Will you bring your biwa and sing the story for us?
Yes.
Come with me now.
I will take you to my lady.
Open the gates!
Please, take my hand.
There's a staircase.
I had no idea there was a mansion so close to the temple.
Yes, but please, try to be as quiet as possible while you're here.
O-Of course.
We have arrived.
Minstrel Hoichi, we ask that you perform The Tale of the Heike on your biwa.
Certainly.
The entire tale is too long to tell.
Which chapter do you want first?
Play for us "The Battle of Dan-no-Ura."
That is a particularly tragic tale.
Elsewhere
The Genpei war continued to rage
Throughout the realm
The winds of spring
You truly are a master of the biwa.
My lady was greatly pleased.
We have returned.
Thank you very much.
Remember, tell no one of this visit
and what happened tonight.
My lady's presence here
must remain a secret.
I understand.
I will return tomorrow at the same time.
He's still asleep?
Hoichi-san. Hoichi-san!
Yes?
Are you feeling unwell?
No, I just overslept.
Really, is that all?
The sun's already in the west.
It's that late?
Hoichi, will you come with me once more?
Such fine biwa playing!
We are deeply pleased with your skill
these past two nights.
We will grant you a reward
that matches your skills.
Hoichi-san!
Hoichi-san, the chief priest wants you.
I'm not mad, just worried.
You're blind. You can't go wandering around alone at night.
I'm sorry, Chief Priest,
but there's something I must do,
and I can only do it in the late evening.
If Hoichi leaves the temple again tonight,
I want you to find out where he's going.
Yes, sir.
I have a sense of foreboding
that I can't do anything about.
Tch. It's getting pretty dark.
I'll get a lantern.
Do it.
Hoichi, are you prepared?
Yes, I am.
There he goes!
What's taking Chinnen so long?
Hurry up. Hoichi-san just left.
You worry too much.
He can't have gone far so soon.
He went out the back gate.
That's odd.
This is the only road to town.
He's faster than I thought.
We just have to find him.
Yeah.
Now, that's definitely not right.
We should have caught up already.
Maybe he went to the beach?
But that road winds
through the graveyard.
It's too difficult for him.
Just a moth.
It scared me.
Let's check the beach.
Through the graveyard?
That's the only way.
And the Genji pressed them toward the beach
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
It sounds like a biwa.
You're right.
It's coming from the graveyard!
All the arrowheads lay in wait
Hey, look!
That's the Heike graveyard.
He's under a spell!
Hoichi-san! Hoichi-san!
Come back to the temple!
Striking down the rowers
It's no use. He can't hear me.
Directionless, the Heike ships sank to the bottom
Or they floated adrift
Don't let them fool you, Hoichi-san!
Let's go back.
You mustn't be so impolite.
We're in front of nobility!
Come on, let's go back now.
The chief priest is worried about you.
You must be quiet.
W-We have to get out of here!
Poor soul. You're treading
on extremely thin ice now.
Your skill with the biwa has led you to the brink of doom.
I never guessed that
I was playing for ghosts.
Their spirits are disturbed now.
Sadly, you, a mortal, have already answered their call once.
What's worse, you promised to play
for them seven nights in a row.
They'll come for you again tonight.
What should I do, Chief Priest?
If you go again,
they'll tear you limb from limb.
But don't worry, we can still save you.
This evening, you'll go with them as usual, but before that,
I'll paint sutras over your entire body.
That should protect you.
I'm done.
Wait on the porch tonight.
Your guide will come for you again.
But no matter what happens,
you must not answer him.
Okay.
Don't even move.
If you move even slightly
or make the smallest sound,
they'll find you.
You won't even be able to call for help.
Yes, I understand.
But if you do exactly as I've told you,
the danger will pass.
You'll have nothing to fear henceforth.
Yes. Thank you, sir.
I'll be in the kitchen all night,
so if you need me, just call-
Ah, sorry, you can't.
Hoichi.
Hoichi!
Where is he?
That's his biwa.
Only two ears!
The biwa player has lost his mouth and cannot answer me.
Only his ears remain.
I'll have to take these ears
back to my mistress
as proof that I searched
as hard as I could.
It's all my fault. The poor soul.
I forgot to write sutras on his ears.
It was unforgivable.
Don't blame yourself.
At least I'm free of the danger now.
That's true, so cheer up.
They'll never come for you again.
The bell of the Gion temple
Hoichi received good care,
and his wounds soon healed.
Tales of this strange incident reached far and wide.
Hoichi the Earless became famous,
and his story is remembered to this day.
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
KOKUJIN-KUN
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
KOKUJIN-KUN
I write a letter to my loved one
Timing
NINJACLOUD
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
QC
Nemesis
Paul Geromini
QC
Nemesis
Paul Geromini
Encoding
ANONYMOUS
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness