Hatsue!
Jump over the fire to me.
And... And we...
Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
Orphan Fansubs presents
The Sound
of Waves
Mishima Yukio
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Part 2
The Storm of Summer
W-We can't, after all!
Why not?
I... I just decided.
I want to marry you.
So... So we can't until then.
Hatsue!
I found this at the beach this morning.
Keep it as a token of our promise.
I'll treasure it forever.
Shinji—
Really?
Uh-huh.
Wait!
That's got to be Hatsue.
Chiyoko!
Yasuo is here!
Hi!
I was in the vicinity,
so I thought I'd stop by and chat about good old Tokyo with you.
I saw her.
That girl Hatsue...
She's gotten awfully close to Shinji.
Wh-What?
Because the island's water supply is sparse,
one of the women's tasks is fetching water.
Who's there?!
Why, it's you, Yasuo?
I thought I'd sneak up on you
to surprise you.
What are you doing here?
I wanted to see you about something.
What are you doing?
Now, let's sit down
and talk without rushing.
You'd better do what I say,
or you'll regret it.
What are you doing?!
T-Take your hands off me!
If you don't want me to tell everyone about you and Shinji,
you'd better do what I say.
M-Me and Shinji?
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't play dumb.
I know you jumped the gun on me
and got it on with Shinji!
Don't be an idiot.
We haven't done anything.
I know the whole story.
What you and Shinji were doing
on the mountain on the third.
See, you're blushing.
So you can do the same thing with me!
Come on, Hatsue. Hatsue!
Stop struggling, Hatsue!
Hatsue!
Ow-ow!
Hey!
N-No, stop!
Wait! What are you doing?
I could get hurt!
Calm down. I won't do it again. Okay?
Hatsue, you're not going to tell your dad, are you? Are you?!
Oh, please! I'll do anything!
Don't tell him.
Well, if you draw water and carry it
to my house for me, I won't.
Really?
Yes.
Uncle Teru's one scary bastard...
All right, I'll do it!
I'll draw water or whatever you want!
The following day,
Shinji's brother Hiroshi was due back from his school trip.
You! Get back here!
Taste my blade!
Really? Shinji did what?
You sure?
Yep, I'm sure.
He sneaked around our backs
and got a little taste of Hatsue.
Really?
That sly dog!
Gotta keep a close eye
on our Shinji, don't you?
Oh, how nice of you to buy
your mom a souvenir.
Thank you!
Uh, Mom...
They're saying Shinji went and got a taste of Hatsue.
Wh-What?
Hiroshi, who told you that?
Everybody's saying it.
But what does "get a taste of" mean?
Cretin!
UTAJIMA PUBLIC BATH
Old man Miyata Teru must be goin' senile.
Yeah.
He don't even know his daughter's lost her cherry.
Shinji got it on with Hatsue, the sly dog.
Stupid old man Teru don't even know Shinji's made off with the goods!
Whaddya think you're doin'?!
Shinji.
Have you heard the nasty rumors
about you and that girl?
Did you sleep with her?
I didn't. I swear!
Well, that's good.
But be careful.
Rumors spread very quickly.
Because it was a small island,
the rumor spread quickly
all over the town.
You mean she and Shinji did it already?
That Hatsue...
I wonder what she's thinking.
Seriously...
Is Miyata-san home?
Ah, Auntie?
I want to talk to your father.
Would you call him?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry... Father says he can't see you now.
What? Can't see me?
He doesn't want to see me
because I'm a poor widow, is that it?
My Shinji hasn't done anything
like what those gossips are saying!
I came down here to tell him so!
The rumor that Hatsue has been
locked up in her home
because of an affair with Shinji
has also reached Chiyoko.
Chiyoko, shocked by the consequences of the tales she spread,
is suffering deeply from her own act of jealousy.
Shinji!
Ah, the lighthouse keeper's daughter?
You're up early.
I'm going back to Tokyo today.
I came to say goodbye.
Shinji, am I ugly?
I am ugly, aren't I?
Not at all.
You're beautiful!
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Shinji, we're leaving.
You are! You're beautiful!
You really are!
Shinji said I was beautiful.
Me, the ugly girl
who told tales out of jealousy.
Shinji.
This morning, when I went by Uncle Teru's house...
.Miyata
Terukichi
I thought I was getting
a love letter... at my age.
It thrilled me, for sure.
But then I looked at it,
and it was for you.
So here you go.
Thanks!
I'm hurrying to write this
while it's still dark out.
Since my father heard the rumor,
he's keeping me in the house
from the time you come
home from fishing
until you leave again in the morning.
But I'm going to make him understand
and let us be together someday.
Shinji...
Days passed before the two
could see each other.
Suddenly, a new development occurred.
The captain of Terukichi's ship,
the Utajima-maru, came to the island.
UTAJIMA FISHERIES COOPERATIVE
It was said he came to pick
two new members for his crew from the island's young men.
UTAJIMA FISHERIES COOPERATIVE
Wow! Just like a head
of the youth committee oughta!
Yeah, you got picked to be
a crewman on the Utajima-maru!
Well, it wasn't really my idea
to go on the ship,
but since Uncle Miyata Teru wants me to, I guess I'd better!
So who's the other guy?
Idiot, you think I know that?
Shinji, I heard from the captain.
I'm real happy for you.
Don't worry about the fishing.
We can handle it ourselves.
Go on and take the offer.
It'll be good for your future.
Then, I'd be happy to work for you, sir!
So it's decided, then!
Yeah, now I see why Teru told me
you'd make a good sailor.
What?
When I mentioned your name,
he agreed without a moment's thought
that it should be you.
Yatsushiro Shrine
Auntie!
Um...
Would you please give this to Shinji?
Well, I won't be gone long,
but please take care
of the youth committee for me.
Shinji!
Take this.
AMULET
Shinji, hurry up!
The Utajima-maru has docked at a port in Okinawa
in order to load scraps.
The typhoon front, brewing near Ishigaki Island,
is growing stronger and is expected
to cross the Okinawa mainland soon,
so all ships in the area are advised
to steer out of the way.
Oh, no! It's heading straight for the Utajima-maru!
What? We lost the mooring line?
Yes! What'll we do, Captain?!
They said the typhoon
peaked at one o'clock.
If we can tie a mooring line now,
we'll make it.
Do I have any volunteers
to go tie the mooring line?!
No one at all?!
You cowards.
I...
I'll do it!
All right, go for it!
Do your best, Shinji.
AMULET
YATSUSHIRO SHRINE
He'll be fine, I'm sure.
He's just like his late father.
He once swam around this island five times. He swims like a fish.
He did it! We're saved! Tie the rope!
Shinji's feat was reported by radio.
Even before he returned,
it became the new hot topic in town.
Shinji...
Hatsue!
Shinji!
Oh, look at the lovebirds!
I'm the one who's gonna marry her.
After receiving Chiyoko's letter from Tokyo,
the keeper's wife understood the real story
and decided to speak to Miyata Terukichi
on behalf of Shinji and Hatsue.
I've already decided
who Hatsue will marry.
Yes, we heard.
But Hatsue loves Shinji, not Yasuo.
That's what I'm saying!
Shinji's going to be my son-in-law.
I asked the captain to find out
which man was best.
And you know the result.
A man's gotta be strong!
Yeah.
Shinji's the kind of man
who's got that strength.
When I'm twenty, I'll get a seaman's competency certificate.
I want to be a sailor
just like my old man was.
Then we can get married, all right?
Do you remember this?
I do!
AMULET
I write a letter to my loved one
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
Timing
NINJACLOUD
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
QC
PAUL GEROMINI
NEMESIS
Encoding
ANONYMOUS