Masterpieces of Japanese Literature
The Izu Dancer
Kawabata Yasunari
(Shincho Bunko edition)
Orphan Fansubs presents
I'd been traveling through Izu for four days.
I was filled with wonder and anticipation as I ran.
Would I catch up with the minstrels,
just ahead of me on this Amagi mountain pass?
Personally, I hoped so.
Mountain Pass Tea House
Here.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
Please have a seat.
Thanks.
This was my third meeting with the dancing girl.
I passed her on the way to Yugashima.
She had a drum.
Two days later,
they came to perform at the inn
where I was staying,
and I saw her dancing
on the wooden floor at the entrance.
Sansui
Goodness, you're soaking wet!
There's a fire inside. Why don't you come in and dry off?
No, I'm fine.
Come along.
Here, this should warm you up.
Thanks.
Does that troupe pass
through here very often?
The minstrels.
It sounded like you knew them.
I see them every year.
I don't think those kinds of geisha
make much money these days.
But some people still like them.
The whole family works together.
The whole family?
The older woman there is the mother,
followed by her eldest son,
his wife, and younger sister.
The girl's name is Kaoru.
She seems like a nice girl.
Kaoru?
We're lucky it cleared up.
Y-Yeah.
You walk pretty fast.
No, not really.
He's a high school student.
I know that.
Students often come to our island.
Island? Which one?
Oshima.
Port Habu.
A lot of students come for the swimming.
In the summer, right?
In the winter too.
They swim there in the winter?
She's such a silly child!
INN
This is where we part ways, then.
Mother, he said he'd like to travel with us.
Why, that sounds wonderful!
Journeys are quicker
when you travel with friends.
It will certainly make the trip
more interesting.
Now, come join us.
H-Here.
Thank you.
I'm sorry!
Goodness, take this!
What a little flirt!
I've found a room for you.
Come, I'll show you.
I was hoping there'd be room at your inn.
Certainly not. It's no place for a gentleman like you.
I'll show you a much nicer place.
Oh, I don't mind at all.
Nice view, isn't it?
It's excellent. Thank you.
It's no trouble. Besides,
we'll be performing here tonight.
We'll also be coming
to check out the baths.
You're all one family, aren't you?
Yes. My wife and I,
my sister, and my mother.
We enjoy working together.
I see.
I chose the wrong path in life,
so I'll always be poor.
I hope that at least my younger sister
won't have to do it for the rest of her life.
Well, good night.
Can't you stay a little longer?
No, we have yet to start
working tonight. Bye.
Hey, your move.
That's a strange move.
Your mind isn't on the game.
W-Well...
Your mind is on other games.
You're thinking about that minstrel girl, aren't you?
N-No, I...
Your move now.
Kaoru, enough washing. Get into the bath. You'll catch a cold!
Okay.
What are you doing? Get in here!
You always act like such a child!
But...
I had a full view of the dancing girl's pure white skin.
Last night's worries vanished like a dream,
and I couldn't stop smiling.
Good evening.
Are you going to try and find more work tonight?
Yes.
Would you like to rest for a while?
How about it? Should we call it
quits tonight and go visit?
I doubt we'll find any more work.
Hurray!
We wouldn't be an imposition?
Not at all!
Thanks for the invitation.
Be my guest.
Oh! How pretty!
You have a Go board!
You're a Go player?
Yes.
Want to play?
Sure!
Pardon me.
The innkeeper said we could use their baths. Shall we?
Let's go!
Won't you join us?
I'll wash your back.
Uh, thanks, but I just took a bath.
We'll be back soon, then.
I'll play you when I get back.
Sure.
I'm done!
R-Really?
So... can we play now?
Sure. Let's play.
I'll be white. You can be black.
Here.
Oh, so you want to play
"Five in a Row"?
Yes.
Fine.
No way. I lost.
I'm so happy!
You're good at this.
One more game!
I-I'm sorry.
I-It's nothing.
I'll go see how they're doing.
The next morning,
refreshed after the bath,
the troupe headed toward Shimoda.
Naturally, I went with them.
It is indeed more reassuring
to travel together,
so Kaoru's mother asked me
to accompany them.
That's Oshima, isn't it?
It looks so huge from here!
You'll visit us there, won't you?
You're not even tired.
I'm used to it.
I haven't felt this good in a long time!
Want some grapes?
They grow all over the place here!
Give me a second.
I'd only met her two days before,
but Kaoru, the dancing girl,
had already stolen my heart.
Some people may say
she's still but a child,
but I can't help but feel
an indescribable admiration
for Kaoru, the young girl
who is trying her best to grow up.
Here!
What's on your face?
This is yours, isn't it?
Oh!
You're wearing such a plain comb?
My mother bought it for me.
I wanted a red one, but...
I'll get a new one for you
when we get to Shimoda.
Really?
Sure.
I'm so happy.
But... that's not necessary.
Why not?
It wouldn't be right.
There's nothing wrong with it.
I want to buy it for you.
Koshu Inn
You must be tired.
No.
Actually, I have to leave tomorrow.
I have school, and there are things I need to do first.
I kept trying to think of a way
to postpone it for a day, but...
Really? That's too bad.
I'm sorry.
Why, you have nothing to apologize for.
Thanks to you,
our journey was very nice.
It was nothing.
I completely forgot you'd be leaving once we reached Shimoda.
Thank you.
Would you mind
if I took Kaoru out tonight?
I thought I might take her to the cinema.
Thank you.
Go on, Kaoru. I don't think
we'll have any work tonight.
Can we go to the cinema?
Hold on a minute!
He's here! I'm going to the cinema!
Can I borrow some money?
No.
Why not?
We have to work.
But brother said...
Too bad, but we've been hired to perform.
No way!
It's true.
Hurry up and get ready.
We've been suddenly hired.
Oh, let her go this once.
Why can't she go to the pictures?
She was looking forward to it.
That's exactly why she can't go.
A Tokyo student could never
love a minstrel girl.
But she's just a child.
She might look that way to you, but she's no longer a child.
What if that student
does come to Oshima,
and Kaoru falls in love with him, what are you going to do then?
But Mizuhara's a nice boy.
I know that.
But in this life, some things just can't be helped,
even if you're a nice person.
Hey.
What's wrong?
We have work. I can't go tonight.
I see.
Please forgive me.
Well, I guess I'll have to go alone.
I'm leaving on the first boat
for Tokyo tomorrow.
It's at dawn, so I may not be able to see you again.
Please say goodbye
to your family from me.
I'll come visit you in Oshima someday.
Well, goodbye.
Good night.
I know you worked late last night.
Thanks for coming.
The picture wasn't all that interesting.
Here, I promised this to you.
Well, take care.
I'll come to Oshima this summer.
Goodbye!
I write a letter to my loved one
Translation
CENTRAL PARK MEDIA
Translation Check
PEREVODILDO
I write and tear it, tear it, and write again
I throw the rolled up paper at the window
Timing
COLLECTR
It's raining outside, just like the tears on my cheeks
Life is a sea, youth is a boat
My love, please come and save me
S.O.S.
I feel like I'm sinking
Not a single star in sight, in the sea of ​​sadness
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
Editing &
Typesetting
COLLECTR
QC
Paul Geromini
Nemesis
QC
Paul Geromini
Nemesis
Encoding
ANONYMOUS