Orphan Fansubs presents
Koiko's Days
KABUKICHO
Yesterday, someone
Was crying there
Would you like a refill?
Yeah, thanks.
Today, someone
Here, sir.
My, what a guy!
There, by the window.
Is still crying there
Huh? You know that guy's
a yakuza, right?
No way. I don't believe it.
Welcome, sir.
Sorry you had to wait.
Don't mention it.
I just wanted to be happy
That's it. Your turn to act, Sabu.
I understand.
Show 'em what our young
yakuza boys are made of.
Is still crying there
I'll do just that.
Welcome, sir.
Lemon Squash.
Understood.
At night, in Shinjuku
That's a nice rear bumper.
Well, since we can't
shoot him dead just yet,
A man and a woman are together, just for a night
leaving him half dead would do.
...just wanted to be happy
...don't want it to end
What's wrong, Sabu?
She even waved to me.
Who's that?
Huh? Sabu, who is she?
My wife, sir.
Y-Your...
Where'd you get a woman like that?
I just wanted...
I'll just break an arm or two
and make him sign the check for us.
What's her name?
Sir?
Your wife's name.
Boss, why are you asking me that?
It's only natural that I at least know
the name of my right-hand man's wife.
So? What's her name?
Koiko.
Koiko?
Is the "koi" spelled with
the character for "carp"?
No, it's "koi" as in "love."
Sabu-chan!
Welcome back!
She seems like the straight type.
Well, isn't it all the same?
I don't mind the straight type either.
You're a lucky bastard, Sabu.
You damned punk!
Did you hire him as your bodyguard?
No, that man's just a relative of mine.
It was a coincidence.
Whatever you say.
Either way, we need to sit here
and resume talking where we left off.
Hang on there for a little longer.
Once Kameda-san signs that check,
I'll get you a doctor.
Okay...
How'd it go, Sabu?
Well, we know you're a seasoned pro,
but the boss still asked me
to check on you.
Matsu.
Yes?
I need you to deliver
this check to the office.
Sure.
Welcome back. We have a visitor.
Boss?
Pardon the intrusion.
I'm honored.
Right. I decided to see
where my employee lives.
Though I was sure
you'd already be back by now.
So how'd it go?
On my way here, I met Matsu.
He's delivering the check to the office.
I see. Good.
Koiko-san, Sabu-chan is among
my most resourceful men.
Is that so?
Hey, Sabu-chan, let's invite
Hoshinaga-san to have dinner with us.
Y-You're right.
No, I can't accept that.
Please don't be shy.
No, it's not shyness.
Boss has business elsewhere, Koiko.
It's not that I'm busy either.
Then stay!
Mukoda-san probably won't let it slide
if you don't pay him a visit today.
True, but it won't matter
if I wait till tomorrow.
Koiko, serve us some beer
as an appetizer.
And something to snack on too.
Sure.
Here, boss.
Huh? Yeah...
Listen, Sabu. You should be grateful
to have such a fine wife.
No...
What's that "No" I'm hearing?
She really is a very special kind of wife.
Sabu needs to learn
to appreciate you more, ma'am!
You think so?
You weasel. How dare you hide her
from us all this time?
No, I didn't mean to...
Whenever one of our boys
gets himself a wife,
it's our custom to introduce her
to the boss, you know?
Y-Yes. I-I was planning to,
one of these days.
It may not be exactly to your taste.
No, that shouldn't be a bother at all.
And I know I'm not
very good at it.
Don't worry. Say, ma'am, why don't you sit here and have a drink with us?
No, I'm not really-
Okay, here you go.
Then, if it's only one drink.
Splendid, splendid!
Something tells me Koiko-san
is blood type B.
Wow! You're right.
Type B women are the best.
Best in what sense?
They're compatible with men
with blood type A.
Is that so?
As a matter of fact, I'm type A.
Wow! Sabu-chan, what's your blood type?
The pot's boiling over.
Ah! Oh my, oh my.
Ouch!
Sabu, are you sure?
About what?
The thing about yakuza is
that they're always hungry for more.
Are you sure you'll have the guts,
when the time comes?
Yes.
You'll have to throw away
your family and happiness.
Yakuza that are too bound by it
don't get promoted.
No, I'll be fine.
Are you also prepared to go
behind bars in my stead?
Yes.
You'll have to leave your wife behind
for maybe five or six years.
Y-Yes.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Here, good morning.
Oopsie-daisy.
You didn't have to drink any beer, you know.
You mean yesterday?
How come? You accepted
a glass from the boss freely!
But how could I turn down
a traditional formal greeting?
Wouldn't it be rude for me
not to accept a sake cup from him?
Idiot!
I get it. You're jealous.
You've become jealous of me.
I'm jealous?! You wench!
Not so fast!
Ow, that stung!
Oh, I'm sorry.
How dare you hit a yakuza so casually!
Right, my bad, my bad.
No, we can't do this.
Matsu-chan will come to fetch you soon.
Screw Matsu. K-Koiko?
Come on, put your pants on now.
Good morning, Matsu-chan.
Good morning.
We haven't had breakfast yet.
Come eat with us.
Sorry for the trouble.
Hoshinaga took me
to a cabaret last night.
Good if true.
But even that ain't the best part.
He kept chanting, "Koiko-san's a fine woman, Koiko-san's a fine woman,"
all night long!
Wow, really?
Hoshinaga-san may have a tough face,
but he's actually very interesting.
Listen, Sabu.
You'd better watch out.
Hoshinaga is merciless
when it comes to women.
Yeah, say what you will,
but he's prayed five times for it!
When he spots a good woman,
he digs in his claws... Ouch!
You idiot, watch your mouth.
Sorry.
Thanks a bunch for the meal!
Sabu-chan.
Didn't you forget something?
Ah, right. Wallet. My wallet.
I'll be waiting downstairs.
They need to consult with me?
They really want you to show up at the office today, apparently.
Hey, Matsu. Tell me something about boss Hoshinaga.
Isn't he taking too many risks lately,
and now the cops are onto him?
Maybe.
Did he mention anything
at the cabaret?
Nothing much, sir.
Koiko-san was the only thing on his mind.
He was so upset!
"Sabu's got a wife,
but he never said a word about it!
She's a fine woman.
She's too good for Sabu.
Too good, I'm tellin' ya!"
Me, I think you two are
a perfect fit, without a doubt.
Thanks.
By the way, Matsu,
is Kayo-chan doing well?
Yes. Sorta.
You'd better treasure her.
Being a yakuza means you'll end up
making her cry someday.
Come in.
Yes, who's there?
I'm from MHK.
MHK?
I'm collecting the TV license fee.
License? But we don't watch MHK in this house.
However, if you own a TV...
My husband hates MHK.
You see, this is a national policy,
so everyone has to pay them.
I see. How much?
2080 yen for 2 months.
This is our TV.
Quite small, isn't it?
It's a 12 inch, I think.
Can I get a 50% discount?
The cost is the same for 26 inch as for 12 inch.
Don't you think it's strange?
Yes, quite strange.
Ah, no, either way,
the fee is the same for everyone,
regardless of the size.
It feels like we're being
discriminated against, somehow.
Um...
Hello? Yes, it's Nagareyama.
Oh, it's you, Kayo-chan?
Yes, I think so.
Okay. 1:30, right?
Good. I'll be there.
Then, see you later.
Excuse me, if I could
have a minute of your time...
Oh? You're still here, gramps?
W-Well, you still haven't paid the fee.
Ah, I'm so sorry!
Menso
Group
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
RIGHTEOUSNESS
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
I want to become a man
I want to die as a man
I want to be a man
Good morning.
Morning. Where's the boss?
In the back.
Good morning.
You seem to be in a bad mood, Sabu.
Did you quarrel with your wife or something?
She's a nice wife, if I've ever seen one.
Have you two been together long?
Only half a year.
So you're in prime time for it.
What are you thinking, really?
About your wife...
With all due respect to how handsome you are,
I really don't see why she'd want
to become a yakuza's wife.
I wonder if she had an ulterior motive.
She didn't have anything like that.
Boss, you wanted to confer with me?
That's the thing.
Actually, I wanted to talk
about your wife.
About Koiko?
Listen, Sabu.
You should think about Koiko-chan.
This is a good time,
'cause you've only been together for half a year.
You see, she doesn't deserve to live
in a wooden apartment forever.
Excuse me, what did you want to confer about?
That's the thing, Sabu.
I wanted to talk about
a snack bar I'm managing.
Things aren't doing great.
So I was wondering if we could get
Koiko-chan to work there.
But, sir...
Naturally, we'd take her on as "mama."
She'd get to keep a quarter of the sales.
Isn't that generous?
Boss, Koiko isn't cut out
for the entertainment business.
No, no, we welcome amateurs as well.
That's what we're all about.
Hey, just try asking her.
Do we have a deal, Sabu?
Well, I could try talking to her once.
Wouldn't it be better for Koiko-chan
to learn a little about the real world?
Without that, she won't be much use to her gangster husband.
Sorry I had to call you out like this.
It's all right.
I had nothing to do anyway.
Right, you don't have to go to work.
I mean, it's not a life of luxury,
but we're living comfortably enough for now.
Sabu-chan is so reliable, isn't he?
So is Matsu-chan!
No, not him.
Matsu-chan wasn't cut out
to be a yakuza.
About that, Koiko-san,
I have a small favor to ask.
What is it?
What's on your mind,
gazing into the distance?
Nothing.
Are you bored?
Impossible!
I have my Sabu-chan with me.
What about the times when I'm out?
What do you mean?
Aren't you bored then?
That's what I'm asking.
I'm not.
Don't you ever feel
like going to work too? Huh?
Not at all.
I mean, I would go to work
if we had nothing to eat.
But other than that, I hate working.
I'll be earning plenty from now on.
That's why I'm happy as we are.
Right. We shouldn't be
forcing you to work, Koiko.
Hey, why are you bringing that up?
I'm at a bit of a loss as to why.
I was just wondering
what would happen if someone
offered you a job
with really good conditions.
Do you know of a job like that?
No, not at the moment.
That's what I thought.
Working is difficult, they say.
But in our family, thanks to your hard work in the yakuza business,
I have the luxury of a relaxed life.
I appreciate that.
The yakuza business, huh?
Good morning!
Isn't the weather nice today?
For sure!
Who's there?
The cop from the police box over there.
A flatfoot?
One day, I brought in a lost child,
and we became acquainted.
Look, Koiko, you should be
more mindful of my occupation.
Don't get too friendly with the cops.
You're right. I forgot.
What are you thinking, really?
Nothing.
Hey, hold it, bro!
Huh?
You got a problem with me or somethin'?
I-I didn't say anything.
Don't give me that bullshift!
I saw that look on ya face.
Y-You're mistaken!
You got a death wish or what?!
What was that?
You're getting on my nerves!
Stop it, Matsu.
H-Huh? Okay.
We're not here to harass
ordinary people.
Right.
Tokuichi Snacks
Damn you!
You're bothering other customers in the store.
Damn it. You got any idea who I am?
No, I don't think so.
You scum, you're talking to Hirota
of the Tengenji Group!
Yeah, whatever.
Behave and go home now.
You jerk!
You asshole! I'll remember this!
Chef, he won't come again.
Sorry to bother you, Sabu-chan.
Three beers are enough, right?
Yeah.
I'm off.
What is it?
The wind!
The wind lifted my skirt all the way up.
Hey, you moron!
Whatcha looking at?
Why did you do that, Sabu-chan?
It's your fault for shrieking
like a banshee!
I wouldn't say I did that.
Anyway, since I'm going shopping,
what would you like
in your bento tomorrow'?
What?
I want to make a bento
for my beloved spouse.
Don't talk nonsense!
You ever heard of a yakuza
with a bento?
Oh, is that what you think?
What's this?
Life insurance?
It's for my life.
"Basic life insurance package
includes an insurance payout
of 3.8 million yen at end of term.
In case of death,
the payout is 15.28 million yen."
Why did she insure my life
without telling me?
15.28 million yen.
If I die, Koiko will have to live off this.
The death rate among yakuza is high.
Why, it's you, Sabu?
Life insurance?
Hypothetically speaking, boss.
If I get stabbed in a fight
and don't make it,
will they have to pay in that case too?
Hey, Sabu, what in the...
Let's see. If you die
in a casual street fight...
I'm not sure either.
When I see the boss tonight,
I'll ask his lawyer.
By the way, about Koiko-chan...
Hey, Sabu! Are you listening?
Later.
I'm home!
Did it quicker than usual.
That's because I was running.
Did you fall asleep?
Yes, for a moment.
But you'll have some beer
with me, right?
Now, here you go.
Something on my face?
Tell me, what's on your mind?
Not a thing!
I'm a yakuza, after all.
Why'd you get life insurance
for a yakuza?
What's more, you hid it from me!
What kind of game are you playing?
If I die, she gets 15.28 million yen, huh?
Hey-hey-hey-hey,
Sabu-chan, Sabu-chan, Sabu-chan!
Say it already!
I heard you the first time!
A man named Yokoyan had
his finger cut off. Scary stuff, isn't it?
Who is that guy?
Matsu-chan told me about him.
I wonder if he had insurance
to his name.
What?
The more severe your injury is,
the larger your insurance payment is.
I wonder how much it is for your
dominant arm, or your right leg,
how much for above the knee,
how much for below?
You'd better not get
your finger cut off, Sabu-chan.
Your pinky costs the least.
It's not even worth the pain.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's not supposed to mean anything.
BATH
Sabu-chan, did I make you wait?
That was a really long bath.
Sorry.
Hey, walk more slowly.
Just as I finally washed my sweat away,
you're making me sweat again.
Sabu-chan.
Sabu-chan!
I heard you the first time!
I'm going commando, you know!
Look at you!
Ow!
Koiko, let's hurry home.
Why are you in such a hurry?
No reason.
I’ll work up a sweat!
You actually didn't put any on!
Oh, cut it out, Sabu-chan!
Koiko, it's pretty late,
so come to bed now.
Okay.
Dishes can wait until the morning!
Okay!
Hey, Koiko! How long
you gonna be doing this?
Okay!
Koiko!
Sure, give me just a minute more.
Good grief. Now I'm finally done.
Oomph, oomph.
Where are you going?
Tomorrow is a kitchen waste day,
so I'm taking it all out.
Hey, I'm telling the truth!
It was love at first sight for me and Mi.
Is he really that much of an alpha cat?
He's the boss of all the other cats in the neighborhood.
So I have to keep calling him:
It's "Mi-Mi-Mi-Mi" all day long and running around after him.
How long are you two gonna stand there and chitchat, you blockheads?
Koiko.
Sabu-chan.
A Colt, huh?
I need you to keep it for some time.
Having it here is too dangerous.
What if the cops come
and raid the place?
Understood, sir.
I'm putting a lot of trust in you.
I know that you won't let me down
and won't tell the cops you got it
from me, even if they find it.
Right.
And while we're at it...
Hey, Sabu, did you give it a shot?
What, sir?
Did you actually tell Koiko-chan about my proposal?
I did.
She'd be getting a fourth of all sales.
Anyone would jump at this opportunity.
But Koiko is just not...
I was planning to hand the business over to Koiko-chan for cheap, eventually.
Boss, if I may ask,
why are you so concerned about Koiko?
More than Koiko-chan, I'm concerned about you two as a couple.
You're like family to me.
We raised cups together.
That's true.
It's natural, then, for me to be concerned
about my family, isn't it?
S-Sabu!
Hey.
We're sorry for all the trouble
Kayo is giving you.
Trouble?
Come on, Kayo!
You bow your head too.
I'm truly sorry.
What's going on? Come on,
what are you talking about?
It's about the insurance, Sabu.
Matsu-chan said I should
get myself a respectable job.
Right.
If she keeps working at a massage parlor,
her health is gonna suffer.
You concern is quite justified.
And my aunt trades
in insurance contracts.
I wanted to try my hand at it,
but I couldn't get anyone
to sign a contract.
So this idiot couldn't think of anything better than going to Koiko-san.
It's fine, it's fine.
I see. So that's what this all is about?
Kayo-chan, you've got
nothing to worry about.
Still, I'm sorry.
Say... why don't you guys make up
while watching a movie together?
Sabu...
We're sorry!
Where was I going again?
Koiko.
Hm? What is it?
If I die...
I know you won't die.
But I'm a yakuza and all.
I could die any day.
Wouldn't it be better for me
to get life insurance?
I suppose.
Then, if I die, money will rain down on you.
In that case, I'll be sure
to give you a grand funeral.
Everyone will think you were a badass yakuza boss.
And after that, I'll die too.
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious? I won't be able to live without you.
Sabu-chan, you absolutely mustn't die.
Koiko...
Sabu-chan is such a nice person.
Isn't that what I've always told ya?
It would be even better
if he wasn't a yakuza.
I'm a yakuza too.
I'd rather you weren't a yakuza either.
This thing is heavy.
I wonder what's inside.
Awesome! A pistol!
Koiko, what are you doing?
Hands in the air!
H-Hey, cut it out!
That thing is real!
Hey, Koiko, give it to me!
Bang! Bang!
Now you've done it.
Where was it?!
What was that noise?
It sounded like something exploded.
What was that?
What made that sound just now?
You idiot, firing a gun
at home of all places!
So it was real?
In my trade, owning an iron
or two is nothing unusual!
Yakuza, right?
Your ignorance is mind-boggling.
You do realize they can arrest you, don't you?!
What should we do, Sabu-chan?
Hey, it was from this direction!
This is bad. They're looking this way.
Isn't that the cop
from the local police box?
Exactly! And he sure as hell
knows I'm a yakuza.
That's why he'll suspect me first.
That was pretty loud, wasn't it?
I wonder if it was a gas explosion.
No.
Or maybe a car tire got punctured?
We're currently investigating the cause.
Please, don't be concerned
and go to bed.
Thanks for your hard work!
They're gone, gone!
You have some nerve, don't you?
It's okay now.
The cops won't be that naive.
Keeping it here is dangerous.
Maybe I should let Matsu
have it for the time being.
Look, I'm sorry.
Remember not to overdo it, ever.
I know.
Good morning.
I knew Kayo was with you
from your footsteps.
Aren't you two close?
No, I'm just taking after you, boss.
I came to apologize to Koiko-san again
about the life insurance thing.
Let's not mention it to Koiko.
I'll also pretend I don't know anything.
What's going on, Sabu-chan?
You've put your shoes on?
If you're going out somewhere,
then give me a proper goodbye.
A gangster kissing his wife
goodbye is funny?
Something's wrong with you,
you freak!
Sorry!
Matsu.
Yeah?
I'm giving you this iron for safekeeping.
Of course. I got this.
I won't take my eyes off it.
Sorry for the trouble.
But why did boss Hoshinaga
ask you to hold onto it for him?
Well, that's because I earned his trust.
Right. That's what I thought too.
When the time comes, you won't spill
that the boss asked you
to keep this thing for him.
Saw right through it.
He's set this up real conveniently.
Matsu!
I mean, if you go behind bars,
he'll be obliged to look after
your bereft wife.
Enough of that talk!
But please, remember this:
If something happens to you, I'll...
I'm prepared to serve time in your stead!
You absolutely mustn't ever leave Koiko-san alone.
I'm treating you to a drink tonight.
A baby?
I see. So you two are having a baby?
Yes.
What did Matsu-chan say?
To keep it.
Isn't that great?
You're so dense sometimes, Koiko-san.
Sorry, force of habit.
I've been working in a massage parlor for quite a while.
Perhaps Matsu-chan doubts
whether the baby in my belly is his.
If he told you to keep it,
he doesn't have any doubts!
I just want us to be happy.
I haven't been truly happy
since I was a child.
You'll be all right.
Matsu-chan is a kind and reliable guy.
Matsu-chan is still a yakuza, so he won't be able to make a woman happy.
"She's either a sex friend or a hostess."
They don't see women
as anything more than objects.
A hostess?
That's what often happens
to their wives.
When times are desperate,
they'll make their women sell
their bodies without a qualm.
Some probably are like that,
but I'm sure not all of them.
Yakuza will be yakuza.
It's the same for Sabu-chan.
I'm sorry. I said something inconsiderate.
Don't worry.
Perhaps I'm easily upset
because I'm carrying a baby.
Then it must be a boy!
Sabu-chan is different
from Matsu-chan.
He's got courage and
is much more manly.
You don't need courage to become a yakuza.
But you need plenty of it to quit.
Sabu-chan would certainly
be able to do it.
See you.
Till later.
Mama!
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
How about some wine once in a while?
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Bargains
30% Off
German Wines
1500Y
Drinking wine isn't like you, Matsu-chan.
Then what is like me?
Something like shochu
with yakitori, I suppose.
I'll show you that wine
suits me just as well!
Boss Sabu sure is sharp.
Remember? Yesterday, I forgot to mention that we finally made you heavy,
but Sabu softened his tone
as soon as he saw my face.
When you think about a respectable job,
your face always lightens up.
Kayo, I...
Hey, there!
It's me. Surely you haven't forgotten?
You sucked my lieutenant
the other day.
She's the girl from
the local massage parlor.
Hey!
Huh? What are you, her pimp?
You jerk!
I see now. You do have the face of pimp.
Enough, you two.
Kayo!
Asshole! You'll regret this!
There!
Look, look!
Matsu-chan!
You'd better find a more reliable pimp.
Shit, I'll kill him.
Come back! Where do you think you're going, carrying that thing?!
Shut up!
Matsu-chan!
Matsu-chan, I'm carrying your child!
Isn't that Matsu-chan?
Hold it!
Assholes, I'll kill you right here!
Who's that, the useless pimp again?
Take this, shithead!
Shit! There! Take that! Die!
Stop it, Matsu-chan!
Where are you going, Matsu-chan?!
What? Matsu shot someone?
Not just someone. Those guys
were from the Tengenji Group.
That's serious. Where's Matsu?
No idea. He ran off somewhere.
We're in deep shit. Good grief.
Do you know what happened to Matsu-chan?
How do you know about that?
Did Matsu call you or something?
No, no.
I was there, at the scene.
What?
I was shopping when I saw
Matsu-chan with a pistol.
He shot it and blood flew in all directions.
The dead man fell with a heavy "thump."
What were you thinking?
He attacked those two.
Only one was injured, in the hip, and the bullet passed through.
Oh, really? I guess I was too excited.
Apparently, the guy with the hip wound
also got away on his own.
They were yakuza too. If the police got involved, it would've been dangerous.
Dangerous for me as well.
I entrusted Matsu with that gun.
Even though Matsu-chan
is having a child soon...
What? A child?
You didn't know?
I thought you'd found out before I did.
I see. A child, then?
I wonder where he is now.
Even Kayo-chan won't
answer their phone.
Sooner or later,
he'll come see me here.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
Want me to make you some udon?
Is it really that hard?
What?
Is it that hard to quit the yakuza?
Yeah. Joining the yakuza is easy,
quitting is the difficult part.
Quitting, then?
Sabu-chan. Sabu-chan!
Koiko, I need your lips
for a morning greeting.
No, we can't do that now, Sabu-chan.
What's this, a rebellion?
There, see?
Boss!
The gun Matsu fired is the very one
I entrusted you with, isn't it?
Yes. If worse comes to worst,
I'm prepared to face the consequences.
That's very commendable.
You'll probably have to spend
only a few years behind bars.
But don't you worry.
While Sabu is away,
I'll be sure to look after you, Koiko-chan.
We appreciate that.
Really, I'll take care of everything.
If we don't handle this situation
with the Tengenji guys delicately,
things could escalate into a war.
Well, that's not impossible either.
Luckily, I often exchange drinks
with the underboss
of the Tengenji Group,
so we're sworn brothers.
Last night, I met with him,
and he agreed to settle things peacefully.
Oh, that's a relief!
In that case, Matsu-chan
can come out of hiding, right?
Right, right. We'll be in trouble
if he doesn't show up.
After all, I have no choice
but to present Matsu to Tengenji Group.
Present him?
Without that, the Tengenji Group's boys won't be placated.
Even if their boss wants
a peaceful settlement...
That's just how our world works.
Right, Sabu-chan?
Matsuda is a small-fry gangster.
He should be able to answer
for his actions himself.
What will happen to Matsu-chan?
They said, it's to placate the boys.
That could only mean...
No way! It can't be!
This isn't peaceful in any way at all!
Aren't you a naive girl?
Hear me out. This is far
preferable to a gang war.
Sabu, it'll be fine. Find Matsu and bring him back ASAP.
I will.
That bastard Matsu got
his girl heavy, right?
Yes.
But you two still got nothing.
What seems to be the problem?
Well, I'd like to know that myself.
Koiko-chan wants to have a baby, doesn't she?
Yes.
Then you gotta cheer Sabu-chan on
so that he keeps trying.
He's already trying hard enough.
But you know what they say:
Children are a gift from heaven.
Good thinking!
Aren't you a bright girl?
And I absolutely love bright girls!
I hope you don't mind me
stopping by every now and then?
Sure, feel free!
Sabu, that fine by you?
Yeah, sure.
You wench!
Look, I'm just trying to get you promoted
by being amiable to your superior.
There are yakuza superiors
and yakuza wannabes.
Oh, is that you, Matsu?
Where are you now?
You moron, what a stupid blunder!
Tengenji Group
I'm Nagareyama Saburo
of the Menso Family.
Matsu-chan's parents
allowed him to return
and take over as the manager
of their bicycle shop, to start anew.
Then they've accepted your marriage, right?
So what will you do now, Matsu-chan?
Well, I... Before that,
I have to see the Tengenji Group
and settle the score with them.
I'm not sure they'll let me
go home alive.
After all, yakuza don't ordinarily kill one of their own.
Anyway, I think you should consult
Sabu-chan when he returns.
Sabu-chan!
What happened, Sabu-chan?!
Sabu! What happened to you?!
I paid a visit to Tengenji
on your behalf.
Sabu-chan...
Boss Sabu!
They were even happier
that I showed up instead,
because I'm usually
a pain in the ass to them.
Sabu, I'd made up my mind to go,
even knowing I might die there!
No way. You would've died there for sure.
Against them, you'd need a body
as strong as mine.
Sabu!
Besides, you've hardly ever fought
anyone in your life.
Go and get yourself
a worthwhile job.
Sabu, you're telling me to quit, but...
You were prepared to get your finger cut off for Kayo's sake, right?
Listen, Matsu.
Do that and offer it to the boss,
along with 500,000 yen
for your girl's redemption.
That's the established custom.
I'll ask my father to scrounge up 500,000 yen for us somehow.
You want me to cut my finger off?
Matsu-chan...
I understand, Kayo.
If it's for you and our future child,
I'll quit.
Okay, do it here and now,
before you lose your resolve.
Kayo, watch him closely.
Matsu is severing his finger for you.
Matsu-chan...
Come on, do it.
Boss!
What's that? You boys playing finger-cutting?
He can spare himself the trouble, Sabu-chan. Times have changed.
Whenever the cops see a guy
with a missing finger,
they cuff him and start
a grievous assault case.
Here, Matsu.
Expulsion notice... Boss!
Even has the chief's
stamp of approval on it.
Thank you so much!
"Notice of expulsion.
First, I'd like to express my gratitude
for all the patronage you've shown me
during your time in office.
On this occasion, I'd also like to inform you that the Tokyo Shinjuku branch
had recently expelled our young member Totsuka Matsugoro.
He will have nothing to do
with our Menso Family in the future,
so he thanks you for your understanding and cooperation.
Chairman of the Menso Group,
Menso Tokuemon,
henchmen leader,
Hoshinaga Sayuri."
Hoshinaga-san's full name
is Hoshinaga Sayuri?
Is it strange?
No, it's so very cute!
Boss...
Sabu, I didn't do it to win
more points with Koiko-chan.
Nobody ever said you did.
Well then, do your best now.
Kayo-chan, I hope you have
a healthy baby.
Sabu!
Matsu, no regrets.
Bro...
Sabu-chan!
Thank you so much
for everything you've done for us!
Koiko, let's go.
Okay.
Wait!
Yesterday, someone
Was crying there
Today, someone
Is still crying there
I just wanted to be happy
Why are you lying to me?
At night, in Shinjuku
A man and a woman are together, just physically
However sad, it seems it's all over
But the two of them don't want it to end
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Perevodildo, Collectr
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair
Topper3000
WOWmd