Orphan Fansubs presents
Koiko's Days
The Story of a Young Couple
♥
Whoa! Oops, oops.
Whew...
Koiko. Is that you, Koiko?
Oh, Kawabata-san?
What a surprise.
So you've returned to Japan?
Come on in now.
Make yourself comfortable.
I have to go back to the office, though.
It won't take long.
I suppose.
I heard rumors that you got married.
We decided not to have a ceremony.
I see.
Oh, have a seat.
How about a cup of coffee?
No need. I just had some.
Instead, tell me, what kind of man is your husband?
What kind of man...
You wanna see a photo?
Yes.
This has to be the best one.
Here.
My, how handsome he is!
You think so?
There's something primal about him,
something intimidating.
What's your husband's profession?
A yakuza.
Don't joke like that.
It's the truth.
Oh my, I hafta go. It's so late!
Koiko, you'll have to excuse me.
Okay.
Hey, what's your deal?!
Want your ass kicked, huh?
Hey, Reiji.
Why are you raising hell here?
No, I didn't mean to...
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll grab a couple more drinks tonight.
Okay.
You take the car
and drive it to my garage.
Thank you, sir.
Have a nice evening.
Make sure not to scratch her.
Of course.
Well, boss, I'll take my leave too.
What are you saying, Sabu-chan?
Are you really that impatient
to return to your sweet Koiko-chan?
I wouldn't say that.
If so, I want you to accompany me
throughout the evening.
Of course. I won't leave you.
I see. So you're also type B?
I can't quite explain why,
but I happen to have great success
with type B women!
Oh, really? Isn't that great?
Sabu's wife is type B too.
It's almost mysterious
how well we get along!
Hoshinaga-san, are you sure
you should be saying that now?
But what can I do if it's true?
Right, Sabu?
Yeah.
There, see?
Hey, Natsuko,
you seem down in the dumps.
You think so?
Cheer up, girl.
You asked me to bring
Sabu along, so I did.
Nat-chan becomes speechless
whenever she's near Sabu-chan.
What a regrettable condition.
Sabu, you've gotta be more active.
Come on now, at least say hello.
Fancy a drink?
S-Sure...
Poor thing. She's shaking like a leaf.
Natsuko, are you really
that into our Sabu?
But you shouldn't give up.
Sabu's still a half-time husband.
No, I wouldn't say that.
Hey, what are you thinking?
Welcome back.
Sign: Menso Group
I see.
Sir?
Water.
Water!
Okay. Hey! Boss wants
his medicine served to him.
Got it!
Hoshinaga, I also have to commend
your remarkable mentorship.
Sir, I'm honored.
I owe it all to the magnitude
of your reputation.
Here, sir.
Oh, Sabu?
Yes, sir.
You're a yakuza, my boy.
So you'll likely have to sacrifice
your life one day.
I understand.
Really? Well, that's good to know.
I heard that you married recently,
so I was a little worried about her.
Sir, I appreciate your concern.
Thank you, sir!
Thank you, sir.
Oh, come on now, sardines again?
They're delicious and nutritious.
But eating them every day?
You can't be serious.
No complaints,
as long as we have no money.
I gave you 400,000 this month!
I used it up already.
But it's been less than two weeks.
Look, I had to buy you new shoes.
Then it's probably my clothes.
And then, also...
I bought a sack of rice.
Newspaper costs...
After that, I didn't spend a yen more.
Don't be stupid!
When has any housewife spent 400,000 yen in two weeks?
That's a fair point.
I wonder how I managed to spend that much.
Then keep a household account book!
What's so funny?
Well, a yakuza who's telling me
to keep a household account book...
It's raw!
I'm sorry.
Do you need help, mister?
My condition has deteriorated...
I see. That's serious!
I-I have the medicine with me,
but water...
Water... Got it!
Wait here just a moment.
Y-You're going to give me
a drink mouth-to-mouth?
I'm sorry. On second thought,
mouth-to-mouth is a bad idea.
Really, I didn't mean that, mister.
Can you walk, even a little?
My home is a short way from here.
That was refreshing,
so I'm feeling better already.
But you'd feel even better
if you took your medicine, right?
I suppose.
Then let me walk you to my home.
Go ahead and lean on my shoulder.
I'm sorry, girl.
It's nothing special for a housewife.
Oh, so someone has got himself
such a cute wife?
Here.
Come inside, mister.
Please feel at home.
Your husband is still resting?
It's all right. He doesn't
wake up at the first sound.
If so, pardon the intrusion.
It's best that you down the medicine
with lukewarm water, right?
Yeah...
I'm sleeping here!
Sorry, Sabu-chan.
I met an old man who's feeling bad,
so I brought him home.
You should've left him there.
The old farts aren't as fragile as they used to be.
Oh, come on.
Hoshinaga says so too.
Oldsters are living way too long.
He was talking about your gang leader, wasn't he?
Hoshinaga's ticked
that he can't take over
because the leader
refuses to kick the bucket.
But the leader's probably gonna keep kicking for quite a while.
They say it's because he likes
young women a lot.
But maybe it's because
he's taking a ton of medicine.
Wow!
Isn't it impressive?
Please rest a bit more.
No, no...
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
I'd still like to express
my thanks once again.
There's no need for that.
Hey, Koiko.
That guy just now...
Was it someone I know?
No idea. Certainly not someone I know.
I feel like I've heard his voice
before somewhere.
Like, uh, maybe it was the old guy
from the district administration?
No, no!
Sabu-chan, I'm sorry for waking you up.
It's still early. Get some more sleep.
Only if you put your body into this futon.
No way. I'm still drenched in sweat.
I don't mind.
No way.
Who do you think you're saying "no" to?
Ah! We can't!
Hey, Sabu.
Boss?
Did the leader summon you?
Yeah, I just saw him.
What was it about?
I couldn't figure it out.
But he was in a totally shitty mood.
Very angry with me.
"There's no way I'll let someone
like you inherit my group."
I wonder what got into him.
Oh, and also,
"Don't you hope that
I'll die any time soon."
He said a whole lot
of weird rubbish to me.
Sabu.
Yeah?
You're not trying to discredit me
with the leader by any chance, are you?
Boss!
Okay, that told me enough.
I know you're not that kind of guy, Sabu-chan.
Come on, let's go grab
a drink somewhere.
Gone already.
Hey, Sabu-chan, what time
will you be home today?
Don't ask me that before I've even left.
Fine.
Hey, Sabu-chan.
Jeez, you're noisy. Can't I have even a minute of silence to myself?
Oh, come on.
And tell me, why'd you bring me
this cheap newspaper?
There's nothing for me to read!
The old guy advertising it
looked very classy.
I want my sports newspaper back!
Fine.
What? Are you throwing that out?
It's kitchen waste day today.
That's not what I was asking, goddamnit!
Didn't I tell you to be more frugal with food?
You mean that?
Do you think we're getting our food for free?
What are you doing?
Will you eat it?
Idiot! It’s filthy now!
See?
Why do you buy a whole daikon
if you know we'll throw half of it out?
Whether it's daikon or cabbage,
I'm sure they'll sell you a half.
I don't feel right unless
I buy the whole thing.
But you feel right throwing it out?!
And by the way, stop sending
every little thing to cleaning.
If you can wash it yourself, then do it!
Like socks, the other day.
All right, I get it. I'm sorry.
What's that half-assed apology?!
Are you making fun of me again?!
You rascal!
Sabu-chan, it doesn't befit a man
to be fixated on such petty things.
What? And who's gonna give a damn instead? You?
It's more manly to keep quiet, even if you notice!
You bitch!
Officer.
What's the matter?
A yakuza is chasing me.
A yakuza?!
There's no one there.
Traffic
Safety
I guess it was a mirage, then.
Traffic
Safety
Sorry for bothering you.
TAPES FOR RENT
What is that idiot thinking?
LATAZO
So you're planning to do away with your leader?
What if I am?
Whoa there, brother.
Isn't that more than you can chew?
Don't you wanna become the leader yourself?
From what I can tell, your gang leader's lived a pretty long and eventful life.
My brother Hoshinaga,
you're in your prime years as a man.
Now's the time for you to take over.
My brother Tachibana,
our leader has been taking
care of me since I was 19.
Welcome.
Hey, Natsuko.
Let me help you.
How's it going?
Has Sabu visited you lately?
Not at all.
What a pity.
Brother, you're still naive.
Being the leader means
everything in our world.
It's more or less like being the president.
As your brother, I'll always be there
whenever you need advice.
Mister!
Are you going shopping, child?
Yeah!
I couldn't forget how you helped me
a few days ago.
I wanted to thank you once more,
so I waited for you in the morning
on that exact same spot.
I change my running course all the time.
Oh, is that so? Well, why don't you
come visit my place this time?
Sure.
Right...
I'll draw you a map, so please stop by
whenever you're in the vicinity.
Hurry up and flee, mister!
Ouch!
Face me directly!
You're strong, mister!
No, it's all thanks to your commendable courage.
When I saw the knife, I grabbed his arm without even thinking.
Well, you have amazing reflexes.
You think so?
Once again, you looked after me.
Fire Extinguisher
Mister, is someone after you?
Why don't you ask my Sabu-chan to be your bodyguard?
No, no, they must've mistaken
me for someone else.
I can't think of any reason
someone would want me dead.
You probably noticed it yourself,
but my Sabu-chan is a yakuza.
Fire Extinguisher
So he could be your bodyguard.
Really, I'll be all right.
And let me say it again.
You've got guts, girl.
My Sabu-chan tells me all the time
that I'm too impulsive.
Your husband is a happy man.
You idiot.
This one is spoiled too.
How long has this milk been here?
And what's all this?
It's moldy!
Ugh, what is she even thinking?
Crap.
What's in here?
This fermented bamboo is moldy too.
Of course she'd tuck
all sorts of stuff in the back!
Oh no.
So he's seriously determined to clean out the fridge now.
What should I do?
What'll he say to me if I go in now?
Lucky me!
Welcome!
Such a warm welcome for me?
We're happy to have you here
anytime, Hoshinaga-san.
I'm flattered.
Go ahead.
Hey, Koiko, get over here! Uh...
Hey.
B-Boss?
We ran into each other on the stairs.
I'll go make some coffee now.
Oh? Sabu, have you been
cleaning out the fridge?
You wouldn't believe
how economical Sabu-chan is.
Sabu,
the thing is... It's about the leader.
Our leader? Who do you think is targeting him? What group?
Nothing's clear yet,
but I have my suspicions.
Is that so?
Sabu-chan, can you believe it?
I saved that old mister today.
Well, the one I helped before.
Are you going out?
Yes.
What about your coffee?
I'm sorry, Koiko-chan.
I'll be sure to stay for longer next time.
Where are you going?
To help another old guy,
except this one is our boss.
The singer Yagami Aki got in trouble
while trying to cut ties with her producer.
Yagami Aki's manager asked me for help,
so I went there to do the talking.
I made sure they learned their lesson.
However, the production staff made
a tearful appeal to the Tengenji Group.
That was probably why
they targeted our leader.
Hoshinaga!
It appears that once again
I've unintentionally caused you trouble.
I can only offer my sincerest apology.
Please allow me to rectify
my mistake, sir.
It's all right. When you've lived for this long, you gotta pay for it, somehow.
Sabu, is Koiko doing well?
B-Boss, how...
How could I not know the name
of a young soldier's wife?
Isn't that a basic qualification
for a leader?
Yes, sir.
Well, you take good care of her, you hear?
Yes. Thank you, sir.
You two come inside and have a drink with me.
Right, sir.
I'll ask my missus to tend to you.
RAMEN
So the underboss of Tengenji said that?
What the hell is that bastard thinking?
RAMEN
He's after our turf, no doubt about it.
Sabu, do you think I'd betray our boss?
No, I know you're not that kind of guy.
I'm glad you understand.
Boss, are you going
to get rid of him for good?
Does walking under the umbrella
really make you that happy? Huh?
That's because we're walking together.
Come home early today, okay?
If all yakuza go home early,
who'd keep the business going?
But it's my birthday today.
Oh, I see.
Then let's meet up and go somewhere.
It's fine. No need to force yourself.
Just try to come home early instead.
Okay.
Peace Cafe
You have what it takes
to look intimidating, kid.
Brother Hoshinaga, you've done a good job
nurturing your gang's youngsters.
Yeah.
By the way, brother,
aren't you glad that your leader is safe?
Yes, thanks to you.
Well, I'm not sure if everyone
in the organization shares this view.
You'd like it more
if I was the new leader by now?
I'm sure you actually feel
a little bitter about this.
I don't suppose you did it because you were trying to be courteous to me,
Tachibana.
But why'd I want to do away
with your group's leader?
It wouldn't gain me anything.
I'm not so sure about that.
After all, our leader is famous for his wisdom.
Your gang could take advantage of me as leader much more easily, if they wanted to.
We let you take over,
and then we start a war.
We gobble up your turf
before you get a grip on things.
You've got some nerve
to say it out loud.
C'mon, it's thanks to us being bros
that I can crack a joke like that.
Hey, kid. Promise to stay for longer and let me treat you next time.
I like you. I mean it.
I appreciate the offer, but I don't normally drink without a cause.
Oh? You just keep growing on me.
I don't like this.
Well, I thought it'd be better
if you knew him personally.
Tachibana of the Tengenji Group.
Like hell I'd forget him.
Sabu, keep a close eye
on him at all times.
Of course.
But he certainly is poised to start a war.
Matsu-chan? It's been ages!
Now, come on in.
Is Sabu still at work?
That's right.
But he promised to be home early today, so you can wait for him.
Very well. Ah... This is for you.
Oh my, that wasn't necessary.
Kayo insisted that I give it to you.
Is Kayo-chan doing okay?
It's almost time for the baby to be born.
Yes.
Matsu-chan, you look good too.
Is your business going well?
It's 50-50.
I'm in Yoyogi today on business.
Really?
I'm sure Sabu-chan
will be happy to hear that.
Sure enough.
Boss is doing okay too?
I can't wait to see him again.
Motherfucker!
We're bothering the other customers here.
Let's go outside!
The fuck was that?!
Hey, Reiji, that's gotta be enough.
That's what you get for messing
with me, you shithead!
Reiji, people come to this district
to drink away their fatigue.
Not to cause trouble for others.
If you understand,
you'll pay your bill now and go home.
I've got you covered.
Please handle it with all due seriousness.
I'll send Sabu over.
Yes, I understand.
Sabu, sorry to ask again after you just got back, but I need another favor.
All right.
"Maidens Garden" called.
They've got a troublesome customer.
Reiji, let's go.
See you.
Problems just keep piling up tonight.
That's strange, goddamnit.
The service here is awful!
Sir, please stop attacking our girls.
Piss off, you jerk!
Sabu-chan!
You're bothering our other customers.
Why don't we settle our altercation outside?
What? You wanna do it?
No, I just want to talk outside.
Who the fuck are you?
Nagareyama of the Menso family.
I see. You're that bastard
they call Sabu.
Shithead, you're from Tengenji?
I knew it!
Get back here, you fucker!
K-Koiko's birthday party...
Boss! Boss!
Hey, call an ambulance!
Y-You idiot, we can't call no ambulance.
Oh? I understand.
Get one of the firm's cars!
O-Okay.
Boss, hang in there!
Koiko-san, I need to get going.
But I'm sure he'll be back
any minute now.
Maybe I should try calling the office?
I'll tell him, "Matsu-chan is here.
Come home at once!"
That sounds like a bad idea.
Boss hates it when you do
that kinda thing.
That must be Sabu-chan now.
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Sabu-chan was stabbed.
What?!
Hello? So how bad is the wound?
Kusunoki Hospital?
Matsu-chan, they said
it's a deep wound.
Don't die. You can't die, Sabu-chan!
Sign: Kusunoki Hospital
Hoshinaga-san!
Koiko-chan.
Did you run all the way from home?
I couldn't catch a taxi.
Is Sabu-chan okay?
He'll make it.
Sabu wouldn't let them
get him so easily.
Huh? If it isn't Matsu?
Yeah.
He came to see us at home.
Boss, long time no see.
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
Reiji.
Boss.
Where's Sabu-chan?
They're operating on him now.
So what about his injury?
It's deep, but it seems
the vital organs are intact.
See, it's just like I said.
Don't worry. He's a pro at making it
out of the worst situations.
Matsu-chan, why are you here?
Hey, Reiji. I was at Sabu's place, visiting.
But aren't you an honest man now?
I am.
At times like this,
it's best that you stay calm.
Right...
So... how does it feel to be
a full-fledged yakuza wife?
It feels very dramatic.
That's the spirit.
It's okay now. I've calmed down.
Reiji, we need to talk.
Sure.
So you're certain of it?
It was Shimizu Bunji of Tengenji Group.
It's like he knew Sabu would come
and was waiting for him.
So Tachibana decided to fire
the first shot of the war.
Boss, please lend me a gun.
I'll avenge Sabu.
If you do that, you'll walk right
into the trap they've set.
Forget about this nonsense, Reiji.
Roger.
I bet that wimp Tachibana
was terrified of Sabu.
Sabu-chan. Sabu-chan!
Sabu-chan.
Koiko... Did I make you worry?
Could we get a word with you,
while we're still here?
Boss...
I'm glad, Sabu. The injury wasn't serious.
I'm sorry, boss.
I screwed up big time.
Forget it. That guy was waiting
there for you all along.
You think so?
Boss, I was there, but I couldn't help...
You've done a lot for me,
when I needed it the most.
Thank you.
Hey, Matsu, what are you doing here?
Boss.
Did you want to ask me something?
That can wait now.
Sabu, I guess we'll take our leave now.
Boss...
Meanwhile, you make sure
to get all the rest you need.
See you, Koiko-chan.
Yeah, Matsu. You go home too.
Sure. Sabu, I'll come again.
There's no need, Matsu.
Sabu-chan.
So we couldn't throw
a birthday party for you.
Matsu-chan and I were waiting together, if that counts.
I wonder if Matsu's doing okay in his new business.
Yes?
This is Hoshinaga.
I'm sorry. Give me a moment.
I'm still changing.
Please take your time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No-no-no.
I was going to the hospital.
Come in. I'll get you some tea.
No need. I'm really busy today.
I just came to deliver this.
This?
Compensation from me.
Please give it to Sabu.
Thanks.
The family will cover
his medical expenses.
Don't worry about anything.
Thanks a lot.
If I can, I'll come check on Sabu today,
though it'll probably be at night.
Tell him that.
Okay.
Bye bye!
Oh?
You've got a scary look, bro.
I'm glad that you found time
to check on me, Matsu.
But aren't you an honest man now?
Yes.
Then don't show up
near here ever again.
Oh, Matsu-chan is here?
Pardon the intrusion.
Sabu-chan, Hoshinaga-san
gave me compensation for you.
Hoshinaga-san is actually a caring person,
even if he's very good at hiding it.
He's also incredibly attentive to me.
He's a man with a gentle soul.
Sometimes I even feel like he's my father!
Your father, huh?
Ow, it hurts.
Sabu-chan, are you okay?
Shit. Ugh, it hurts so much...
It's still too soon for you to be laughing.
SHINJUKU KUSONOKI HOSPITAL
If he's sleeping,
I'd rather not wake him up.
I also decided to let him sleep
to his heart's content tonight.
After all, he hasn't slept much
in the last three days.
I see. Then, let me take you home,
at least halfway.
When do you think Sabu will be discharged, Koiko-chan?
What now? Asleep already?
Well, it's not surprising.
She had to stay awake for three days.
Hoshinaga?
Unforgivable. That's full on unforgivable!
She's thoroughly exhausted.
Sleeping like a corpse.
Want something to eat, Papa?
No, I'm good.
I still have some legwork to do.
Actually, let her sleep until morning,
then call a taxi to take her home.
Okay.
I think I told you not to bring Kiyomi here.
She just follows me on her own.
That's no good, Kiyomi-chan.
You've gotta listen to what Mama says.
But...
Reception
Please come again!
Go to sleep, kid.
Reception
Die!
Wait. Who are you?
Damn you!
Hey, Matsu, is that you?
Yeah. You guessed it.
What's your problem?
Good question!
Ask yourself, asshole!
Wait a minute.
I actually have no idea.
You're not yakuza, so why...
While Sabu's fighting for his life
in the hospital, you're taking Koiko here.
Damn you!
Ah, that?
I know you've been eyeing Koiko-san
ever since you first met her!
Matsu, there's been a misunderstanding.
Shut up! You're not fooling anyone!
You scum!
Calm the fuck down, dumbass!
Didn't you become an honest man?
Y-Yeah.
Then that was really dumb of you.
You got yourself roughed up too.
As if there weren't enough casualties in our ranks already.
Well, I guess you guys
are more naive than most.
What a dope.
Guess he won't succeed
in becoming an honest man.
I feel sorry for Kayo-chan.
Meanwhile, their child is due soon, huh?
Sabu's about to be discharged
from the hospital.
Sign: Tengenji Group
Hoshinaga will need to maintain face,
so he'll probably demand that you turn yourself in.
Understood.
By the time you return from prison,
the Menso family will be wiped from the face of the earth.
Since I'm gonna be serving time anyhow,
I should've messed Sabu up more.
Oh, about that, I just might know
of an interesting way to do that.
Um, excuse me.
May I ask you for a favor?
Yes, what is it?
My grandma's rheumatism got worse,
now she just sits there
and refuses to go anywhere.
Could you please help me
walk her to the taxi?
Sure, no problem.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
Well, I gotta return to the office now.
See you again.
Yeah.
Whoa! Ugh! Ouch!
Tachibana-san, you're kinda devilish, even for a yakuza.
It's just a shot of sedative, nothing more.
Of course you're not feeling anything.
Bunji's gonna serve time, not you.
I have a reputation to uphold.
Anyway, I'd rather you not use
my place for that kind of thing.
Bunji here.
I brought her, as arranged. Yes.
That Sabu sucker has got himself one helluva wife! Tsk...
Do it while she's still unconscious.
It starts to work after 10 seconds.
After that, you'll pass the baton to me.
Did she see your face?
Yes, from close-up.
That means you'll be alone on this job.
Yeah, I know that.
Better just tell me...
After I'm done,
it's up to you what you do with her.
I should've practiced at least once.
Damn it.
No, wait! Don't move!
What's that idiot doing?
She's not home yet?
Boss!
Reiji, what happened?
Try not to laugh, boss.
Do you recognize these?
What's the matter with you?
Just take a look, please.
Reiji, are those...
Do you recognize them?
Those are Koiko's shoes, ain't it?
Just as I thought.
Where did you find them?!
Hey. Is she asleep?
No. I bent the needle.
Do you have a spare?
Can't you do anything at all?!
I'm sorry.
Sh-Shit...
Did she jump from here?
What is it, Bunji?!
She's gone, boss!
There's no way she could jump from up here!
She could've been feeling desperate.
Have you checked the toilet?
Not here!
Did she really jump down, then?
All right, I'll look for her outside.
And you check the room once again.
Okay.
So you were right here under our noses?
No! No! Stop it!
Sabu-chan!
Coming!
Did someone call for me?
Sabu-chan!
Sabu-chan...
Fooling around with a guy like that.
You need to find a good hobby, desperately.
But you were away,
and I was so lonely.
Now, Koiko, step back a little.
Bring it on, you schmuck.
Bro!
Anyone got a light?
Quit trying to play it cool.
Fine. I'll light you up.
Die, you smug prick!
I'm not so clumsy as to get stabbed twice.
Tachibana-san, are you gonna leave Bunji to his fate?
This should cover the room rent
and collateral damage.
I don't need that!
Yakuza still live by nature's laws.
You scratch my back, I scratch yours.
Could you bring my shoes?
Asshole!
Take this!
Koiko!
Should we finish him off, bro?
Doing it here would land us in trouble.
Y-Yeah, he's right.
We know what group he belongs to.
There's no need to be hasty.
You're a lucky bastard!
Are you sure you don't need
to return to the hospital?
Nah, let's have a belated
birthday party at home.
Matsu-chan's here.
What's that idiot doing here?
Wait for me.
Bro, I've been to the hospital.
I have no business with you.
Matsu.
Bro, I'm serious.
Please readmit me to the family.
Look, you...
Kayo also said I should
return to being a yakuza.
Kayo did?
Please!
I'm a yakuza through and through.
There's no such thing
as a yakuza through and through.
Start moving, driver.
What did Matsu-chan say?
He wants to rejoin the yakuza.
After all he's been through to quit!
That moron.
Where are we going now, sir?
For now, just drive straight.
Meanwhile, I'll think of where I wanna go.
Yesterday, someone
Was crying there
Today, someone
Is still crying there
I just wanted to be happy
But now, I'm crying
At night, in Shinjuku
A man and a woman are together, just physically
What a pity, I guess I just can't be happy
Translation & Timing
Editing & Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair
Topper3000
anonymous