This video is based on experiences
our readers shared with us.
Human life is ever so fleeting.
When lingering regrets won't let some depart this world,
they're forced to wander
the Earth for years to come.
This is...
"I witnessed a wandering spirit."
A first-hand account of horror.
Orphan Fansubs presents
School Ghosts 4
Death Doll
This doll has sad origins.
You can't even say that the school
where this doll lives belongs
to any particular prefecture.
That's because the mere mention
of this doll puts you in grave danger.
Wow, it's burning!
You're right!
Amazing!
I wonder if black things are quicker to burn than anything else.
It works! It's already smoking!
Hey, Ooki!
Fire's not a plaything to be toyed with!
Do you want that doll to catch on fire?
All right.
BOYS
Komikoro
I should probably go to sleep.
It burns! It burns!
We don't really need
a new Book Club room.
Geez. All we do in the Book Club
is carry books around.
I'm sorry.
Well, time to go.
Oh, there's Keiko-chan.
Let's go home together!
Motoko-chan!
My arm was broken
in the same place as the doll's.
Then, after consulting a teacher,
I decided to consecrate that doll at a temple.
Spirits often get attached to dolls.
It may get especially vicious if it's a child's spirit,
because children are so careless.
This is...
The spirit of an eight-year-old girl,
who was caught in the war.
Mom! My doll!
Mom!
She lost her mother in an air raid.
Mom...
Even after her mother died,
the girl continued to search for the doll.
And eventually, she also died
in one of the subsequent air raids.
However, while the doll was supposed to be consecrated,
it suddenly disappeared
from the temple.
And before we knew it,
it was back at our school.
Ugh, it's been raining
for a week straight.
Man, I feel you.
It's such a bummer!
I wanna be able to practice batting outside again!
H-Hey, watch it!
It'll be fine.
Be careful, okay?
Stop pestering me.
I need to do it like that, with a swish.
Oh great, didn't I tell you?
I-It's their fault for placing a doll in a place like this!
Hey, Yasuo!
But... it was mine.
An unbelievably horrible accident
happened to Yasuo-kun soon after.
The doll is currently kept in the principal's office.
And it seems, even without anyone touching it,
it looks in different directions every now and then.
It's said that after nightfall,
the girl comes to play with her doll again.
Behind Me
Ah, I'm so tired!
I can understand it
when the teacher works us hard,
but that meeting afterward was too long!
Hey, it's already dark outside.
What are we gonna do
if some ghosts appear?
Our school is also where
they're most likely to appear.
Apparently, many people have seen them already.
Over there...
What?
...is my towel.
Oh geez, will you ever stop doing that?
But hey...
Tell me, don't you wanna see a ghost
at least once in your life?
Let's look at them, then.
There's one story. Whenever you tell it
at school, a ghost appears.
Wanna hear it?
Yes. What about you, Ryoko?
I wish you two all the best and goodbye!
Will it really appear?
Yes. A few years ago, we had a transfer student named Ishimura-san.
She was a lively girl
when she was in Tohoku.
But she had to come here
because of her father's work.
She tried to become friends with everyone,
but she was teased because of her accent.
As a result, she spoke less and less.
Eventually, her classmates would bully her
whenever they got a chance.
They were merciless.
Ishimura-san felt overwhelmed and went to complain to her homeroom teacher.
But he wouldn't listen to what she said.
He kept saying that the one being bullied is as much at fault as the bully.
No one understood her feelings.
Finally, she...
And then?
After her memorial service on the seventh day,
her spirit appeared in the classroom
and embarked on the path of revenge.
Revenge?
Yes. The three students that bullied her the most soon all died...
violent deaths.
And then...
And then?
Her homeroom teacher became paranoid.
On the 49th day after Ishimura-san's death, he killed himself.
There was a lot of talk about it in school.
As seniors passed it down to their juniors,
this story gradually became a funny anecdote more than anything else.
But to her, it was the same as if they were bullying her like before.
Her hatred was now directed
at the junior students who gossiped about her for the fun of it.
Her grievance continues to this day.
Even now, whenever someone gossips about her at school,
her spirit appears.
She haunts anyone who hears her story.
And then kills them.
Kills them?
Kills anyone who hears about it?
That's ridiculous!
Wait, that means me too?
But what about you?
Me too.
It can't be, since you're still alive and well!
Alive?
Ishimura-san killed me as well.
She killed me for being too curious.
Just like you.
I want to rest in peace like everyone else.
To do that, I need to recount her story to the next person.
That's you.
Will you carry Ishimura-san's blessing for me?
Several Years Later
Hey, if you tell a certain story at school, a ghost will appear.
Huh?
Do you know it?
I don't.
I wish someone would tell me.
Want me to tell you that story?
The Animal Spirit
That Saved My Life
Okay, okay, Vongole, I'll get up now.
I'm getting up, you hear?
Vongole, are you coming along?
If so, hurry up.
Come, boy!
What's wrong? Don't wanna walk?
For me and my dog ​​Vongole,
walking every morning was a daily routine.
But strangely enough, on that day,
Vongole rebelled against going
on his favorite morning walk.
Oh, so you even understand traffic lights now?
Really, what's with you today?
If we keep dawdling,
we won't have time for breakfast!
This isn't how our walk
is supposed to go!
Here you go, your favorite rolled omelet.
No! Vongole, stop it!
Mom! I need some help here!
He's acting up!
What are you doing?
What's going on, Vongole?
Vongole is a very bad boy!
See you later!
Vongole acted weird this morning.
Bye. See you tomorrow.
Yeah, see you.
Bye-bye!
What's wrong, Vongole?
Bad dog! Be quiet!
Vongole! Cut it out now!
Yes. Hello. You're through to Sato's.
Huh? What did you say?!
Yes! So is she...
Surgery Underway
Will Hiromi be okay?
The surgeon's currently doing his utmost.
Surgery Underway
Please wait here.
Forceps.
Clamp there.
Roger.
At that moment, I wondered why I had decided to sleep in a place like that.
It was a truly beautiful place.
I could move freely wherever I wished,
even without walking.
What a beautiful river!
Who's that?
Grandpa! Grandma!
Grandpa, Grandma, what's wrong?
Why do you look so sad?
I can walk!
Vongole, let go! It hurts!
Let go! Stop! I just want to go to my grandma!
Vongole!
Surgery Underway
Hiromi-chan has been a very strong girl.
She'll be fine now.
Thank you!
Truly... Thank you ever so much!
She'll live. She'll live!
You can't bring a dog to the hospital.
How did you get here, boy?
Did you bring him along?
No.
Vongole, so you were worried too?
Thank you!
If Vongole hadn't pulled me by the leg back then, I'd definitely have died.
What a truly fascinating occurrence.
Later that year, Vongole drew his last breath on my lap.
Thank you, Vongole.
Wandering Feet
This is a service issue.
What will I do with you?
You're still here?
So that was you, Mr. Security Guard?
Sorry I had to stay until late.
The nights sure are hot
this time of year.
Yeah, that's true.
Ah, wait just a second.
Heave ho.
Huh? I can't close it.
Excuse me, Sensei,
could you please hold this for me?
Thank you.
Huh?
Wait a minute!
Is something wrong?
No, I just saw a girl wearing geta.
Stop!
Huh?
Where did she go?
She's gone.
I'm sure she went this way.
I checked before,
and every room was closed.
The emergency exit is open.
That's odd. I'm sure I locked it up earlier.
Is anyone there?
I wanna see her.
Who are you?
Where are you?
I wanna see her.
What are you doing over there?
Why are you at school at this hour?
What could that be?
Let's come back tomorrow, Sensei.
I know a good spiritualist.
I'd like him to attend too.
I suppose you're right.
Please.
It's a geta.
It looks pretty decayed,
so it's probably quite old.
Yeah.
You know, Sensei, I heard crying last night. Do you think...
Let's talk to the owner of this geta.
I-It...
Right.
I see.
I understand, yes.
"I want to see my mom, my mom."
That's why she cried.
So she misses her mother?
Their house was washed away in a severe flood in 1881.
Her legs got caught in a large tree,
and she couldn't move.
Her mother tried her best to save her.
That was when a raging mudslide
washed them both away.
Her legs were torn off.
The stream engulfed her and her mother's bodies.
Sorry to hear that.
Somewhere, there's a grave where her mother lies.
That must be where we'll find the rest of the girl's body.
She wants to be reunited with it.
I see.
Got it.
We shall find your grave and
reunite you with your mother.
The bird showed me the direction.
It's around here.
There's a temple here.
We're looking for tombstones from 1881, right?
Yes.
Found something. Murakawa family grave.
1881. Kiku, 28 years old. Hana, 7 years old.
So it's Hana-chan?
Your legs kept wandering this earth,
searching for your own and your mother's bodies for the last 120 years.
Poor thing.
Hello, Hana-chan? Did you find
the body you've been looking for?
Did you find your mother?
You can rest in peace now.
Good for you, Hana-chan.
Boy at the Crossroads
When you're in peril?
The word is "dangerous."
D-A-N-G-E-R-O-U-S.
There, nailed it.
Dangerous, huh?
Somehow, it feels like a bad omen for today.
What's he doing?
Maybe he needs help?
Hey, hey!
Hey, are you okay?
The boy... The boy jumped...
jumped right in front of me.
It's him. It's that boy's fault
for jumping out!
Where did that boy go?
Hey, you!
No way!
This guy doesn't look good.
Akiko, you pass by that intersection every day and yet you don't know?
Every day or not, I only moved here
about three months ago.
Did something happen there?
Listen, then.
About 15 years ago, at that intersection...
Rumor has it, that boy keeps appearing at the intersection from time to time.
What you saw was probably him.
This is wrong. Maybe we should talk to him and ask what he wants.
You might have a chance.
He's there several times a year.
But it could be pretty difficult.
How come that intersection is my only way to school?
Listen, Akiko.
You must never make eye contact with that boy.
You'll be overwhelmed
by hatred and loneliness.
He drags down with him
anyone who meets his eyes.
All right.
So I just need to avoid eye contact.
I don't like where this is going!
I guess I'd better not look around.
No!
Jogging Old Man
No, I... can't go any further.
Maybe I should call it quits for today?
I've been jogging for a week already.
Now Mom can't say
that I don't stick to something for long.
That's better!
Good morning.
Doing your best, huh?
I've only been doing it for a week.
Ah, that's commendable.
Good things come to those who endure, you know.
I suppose.
Let's go for another one.
Good morning!
The weather is nice today as well.
Good morning.
It's one hell of a nice morning!
Yeah.
After that, the old man and I ran together every morning, even when it was raining.
Okay, good job today.
See you tomorrow morning.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Then, another week later, as summer vacation was about to end, this happened.
Hello, this is Mizuno.
Yes, it's me, Yuuko.
Good morning. I'm the jogging old man.
Good morning. What's the matter?
Not bad, finding my number like that!
Thing is, Yuuko-chan,
I won't be able to run with you from today on. Forgive me.
Why?
But if I may say so, running with you
was a whole lot of fun.
I had fun too.
But why? I'm going to miss you.
I just called to say thank you.
Well, goodbye now.
Mister, I hope you'll be well.
Thank you.
Can't be helped.
I'll have to run alone today.
I approached the intersection
where I'd meet the old man every morning.
And indeed, he wasn't there.
Guess he really is gone.
Watch out!
At the last moment,
the old man called out to me
and saved me from getting hit by a car.
Mister!
I'll go thank him on my way home.
Maybe he got hurt or something.
I wonder if someone in their family passed away.
Shockingly, the photo on the altar
was that old man's.
May we help you?
You know...
I got a call from that old man this morning.
What?
Then, later, when I almost got hit by a car,
he called out to me and saved me.
Father's health suddenly deteriorated yesterday morning.
What?
So he died right after jogging yesterday?
Not at all! He collapsed about a year ago
and had been bedridden ever since.
Bedridden?!
No way! I've been jogging with him every morning through my summer vacation!
He loved jogging, but that's impossible.
Even since he became bedridden,
he'd often say to us, "I want to run like in the old days once more."
Mister...
Come to think of it,
for the past few weeks,
he's been looking very satisfied
and happy every morning.
Perhaps my father's strong feelings
materialized to run
with you every morning?
When I looked at that old man's photo,
he still had that kind smile
he always had while we jogged together.
Every morning of summer vacation,
I had jogged with that old man's spirit.
Then, his spirit called me by phone
and protected me when I was in danger.
He was a really kind old man.
Ever since then, I've always felt like someone was watching over me.
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Perevodildo,
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Topper3000
"Cappucino"