This video is based on experiences
our readers shared with us.
Human life is ever so fleeting.
When lingering regrets won't let some depart this world,
they're forced to wander
the Earth for years to come.
This is...
"I witnessed a wandering spirit."
A first-hand account of horror.
Orphan Fansubs presents
School       Ghosts
Transfer Student
That girl was a bizarre transfer student right off the bat.
But at the time, no one said anything.
Even the teacher didn't notice.
Class 5-3
Shingo, it looks like we're getting a transfer student.
Really?
Yeah. I was in the staff room earlier,
and Kitagawa-sensei was talking
to a girl I haven't seen before.
The seat next to you is vacant,
so she'll probably sit there.
Is she pretty?
Well, you could say she's a little prettier
than the other girls in our class.
Oh, here she is!
Stand up!
Bow!
Sit down.
Good morning, everyone.
Let's start this morning by introducing
our new transfer student.
She will now be a student in Class 5-3.
Yoshikawa Megumi-san.
Let's say hello, everyone.
Hello!
Hey, I'd say she's rather pretty!
Y-Yeah.
Everyone's nervous when they see their new class for the first time.
Well, it's fine if you take it slow.
Okay, everyone, please be nice to Yoshikawa.
Okay!
Now, where should we seat you?
Ah, Shingo, the seat next to you is vacant. Let's seat her there.
Shingo, Yoshikawa doesn't have a textbook yet, so please share yours with her.
Okay.
Enough already!
I'm Nakai Shingo. Nice to meet you.
When we step out of the warm Inuit tent ​​
and look up at the night sky,
we raise our voices unknowingly.
But even then, our voices seem to freeze immediately and disappear somewhere.
A curtain of light seems to permeate the pitch-black sky.
It's the aurora, the mystery of nature.
Shining in different colors, the curtain of light above me sways in the wind.
Nakai, read the next fragment.
Nakai.
Shingo!
R-Right!
N-Now...
Th-Thank you.
Crossing the harsh blizzard,
riding a dog sled in temperatures of minus 40 degrees, we arrive at... extra...
Extremely cold place.
E-Extremely cold... Ah, so it's extreme.
We arrive at an extremely cold place,
where my dream comes true.
Nakai Shingo
Here, use this.
It has my name engraved on it.
Nakai Shingo
Ouch...
Your hands... are kind of cold.
But thank you.
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
Now then, what should I do to calculate the area here?
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
To find the area of ​​triangle C
in the diagram on the left
Area of ​​rectangle ABCD
Huh? Hey, Nakai, what happened to Yoshikawa?
Uh? Well, she was in the hallway during the last break.
But she hasn't returned from it.
That's strange. I guess she was unwell and went to the infirmary.
Sorry to interrupt your class, Kitagawa-sensei.
You've got a call,
and they say it's urgent.
Staff Room
Yes, hello. Kitagawa here.
Yes, that's correct.
Huh? Wh-What?
Yoshikawa Megumi's family
d-died in a traffic accident?!
But that means...
Huh? Yoshikawa Megumi too?
This can't be right!
Th-That's just...
That's ridiculous!
Hey, Mama. I can't wait to make lots of new friends at my new school.
Yes, I hope you do, Megumi-chan.
Nakai Shingo
It can't be! Yoshikawa Megumi passed away moments ago?!
So... was that her spirit?
It seems the accident took place
the day before, a hundred kilometers away from here.
Doctors were fighting desperately to save her life,
but eventually, she passed away
without regaining consciousness.
Apparently, immediately after Megumi-chan's spirit
stuck her band-aid on my knee,
the real one drew her last breath.
As it turned out, what Kitagawa-sensei, I,
and everyone in the class saw was her astral projection.
It looked like we could really become good friends with her, so everyone was sad.
Ghost on
the Railroad Tracks
I'm off!
Good morning.
I have another test today.
Aren't you lucky not to have any?
Another accident!
So creepy.
And it's right next to us.
Why can't people follow
the railroad crossing rules?
Poor guy.
Okay, put down your pencils.
Now, pass your work forward.
Why did we even need a test for that?
Well, we have another math test tomorrow, and that should be it for midterms.
I haven't studied for the math test at all.
What should I do?
Ah, I'll be burning
the midnight oil tonight.
Me too. But we gotta do our best,
no matter what.
Yeah.
See you then. Bye-bye!
See you!
Ah, studying?
What a bummer.
Really, you're such a lucky guy.
It's this late already?
No, I have to keep going.
What's going on?
No!
Don't call me...
Don't call me!
My arm...
A ghost?!
No... I don't wanna go!
No!
Help me...
Help me!
Ever since then, I've been bedridden
with a fever of unknown nature.
Following the advice of my father's acquaintance,
I moved out of this house immediately.
After that, my fever subsided miraculously,
and I haven't had any more
terrifying visions since then.
I heard that the house remains vacant to this day.
House For Sale
Contact Info
False Psychic Abilities
Hey, wanna draw another one?
Sure. Who's choosing?
Let's decide now.
Rock-paper-scissors! Rematch! Now!
I lost!
I'd just transferred to a new school.
I didn't have any close friends yet.
That's when it happened to me.
Oh?
Rie-chan, you're going home alone?
Keiko-san, Yoko-san.
Hey, you've only transferred here recently,
so you don't know it yet,
but a ghost appears under the fourth willow tree from that corner.
My sister's boyfriend saw it.
It appears in a white kimono
and beckons you with its hand.
That's just a made-up rumor.
It's all okay.
No! Don't make eye contact with it!
What now?
What happened?
You dashed off like a spooked cat.
That's because Rie-chan said that
we shouldn't make eye contact with it.
Who shouldn't we make eye contact with?
Did you see it? The ghost.
Yes.
Yes, I did.
Don't tell me... You have psychic powers?
Since you saw it.
So... what kind of ghost was it?
It was a man without legs,
wearing a white kimono.
And my sister's boyfriend saw
an old woman in a kimono.
Oh?
He must've mistaken that man
for a grandma because of the long hair.
Amazing! That’s amazing!
Y-You think so?
It is amazing!
I'm not so sure.
Rie-chan!
Hey, you're Rie-chan, the psychic, right?
Uh? No, that wasn't...
Hey, I think we took a ghost photo.
Will you take a look?
What is the meaning of this light ray?
Well, I think it's a re...
A restless ghost?!
So I hurt my right eye because of this ghost?
Isn't that right?
S-Seems so.
What should I do? Is there a chance my right eye will get worse?
Hey, what should I do to deter it from doing
any more weird things to me?
Well...
Well, I guess I should exorcise you.
Give me the photos and the negatives.
Really? Thank you so much!
Let's be friends now, Rie.
With me too!
Sure.
I'm glad I managed to make some friends.
But I'll feel bad
if I have to keep doing this.
Rie, look! As soon as you exorcised me,
my eye healed wonderfully.
You've got amazing power.
I see. Good for you.
That's just a coincidence.
Don't be stupid.
But it worked!
Hey, there are ghosts
in our school too, right?
The warehouse to the right
of the gymnasium is off-limits.
Rumor says the ghost of a boy from the baseball team appears there.
Can you feel it?
That's right.
Then let's go on a psychic tour after school today!
What do you mean?
We'll go to the forbidden warehouse,
along with Rie, and summon that ghost.
Then I'll be willing to believe
in Rie-chan's psychic powers.
For now, I think psychic powers are just a myth.
Looks empty in here.
Hey, do you see anything, Rie?
What do you think?
If you don't say something,
we're through!
I have to do something.
There's a spirit in that corner!
What? What's so special
about this corner?
You see something here?
Open the door!
Rie, do something!
That's right, anything at all!
Rie, do something about him!
Yeah, do something!
Rie!
Please, Rie! Please!
We're sorry. Please forgive us.
We won't disturb your rest ever again.
Please let us out of here.
What?
You're in pain?
I'll remove that rope for you, okay?
So please forgive us.
It's off.
It was painful, wasn't it?
Don't stay here forever.
Try to find peace.
It's open...
I didn't really have any psychic powers.
However, as a transfer student,
I couldn't afford to lose my friends,
so I had to keep bluffing.
Of course, I wanted to save everyone back then.
But I still don't understand
how I was able to come so close
and remove that rope without fear.
All I can say is that somehow, the pain of that guy
from the baseball club came through to me clearly.
I can only assume that as a human being,
at that moment,
I could hear it with my heart,
with abilities or without them.
Rie, thank you!
Cat's Grudge
That alarm clock is no good.
I have to buy a new one.
What?
It's dead?
I-It's the cat's fault.
Jumping in front of cars like that...
Class 4-3
So, friends, I have
the voting results here,
and it says our class
has chosen Yuuta-kun.
Stand up!
Bow!
Sit down.
Good morning.
What were you voting on?
You see, on his way to school,
Yuuta-kun found an injured female cat.
D-Did you say "cat"?
We voted on whether to keep it
in our class until it gets better.
Aren't you sorry for her?
Teacher,
there's been a traffic accident.
That driver must be a monster.
Y-Yeah...
So, what are you going
to do with this cat?
We've voted on the matter
and decided to keep it.
N-No!
You absolutely can't!
But why?
We're at school,
and school is where you study.
No way. You can't keep it in class.
How about I ask other teachers
if someone else can take care of the cat instead?
But the majority vote was to keep it ourselves.
Why not?
No means no!
You should hurry up and leave. Alone!
Ah... Finally halfway done.
Just because I left it there, they wouldn't burn a cat, would they?
I left the lid open, so it must've gone somewhere right after.
Wh-Who's there?
H-Help me!
Help me!
S-Someone... help.
Stop!
Well then, please say your final farewell now.
Help me!
Open it!
Don't do this! No! Somebody!
Open the lid! Help me!
Open it!
No!
Print Fantasy
I've never believed in the sixth sense,
so that was a particularly strange experience for me.
In my second year of high school, near the end of first semester,
I went alone to buy a birthday present for my younger brother.
Even girls like that can get a boyfriend.
I want a boyfriend too.
Why are you such an indecisive person, huh?
Are you going in?
If not, we're going first.
Right?
Why are they acting so high and mighty?
Sticking their faces in
and jumping the queue!
There's no fun in choosing a present for someone like your little brother.
Ma-kun, look!
Look, isn't it cool?
Not bad, I suppose.
Hey, how about I buy it for you?
Why did they put it in a place like this?
Maybe it's broken?
Print...
Land!
No way!
It's working!
Taking pictures alone is a bummer, though.
They're here!
We have a full house today!
Purin purin.
Now, let's see if I look good on these!
What?
What are you doing?
Let's hurry up and go.
Huh? What?
What are you saying?
You asked me to introduce you to a boy I know. Let's go!
What's going on?
Who is this girl?
Thank you for waiting, Daiki.
Yuriko? You're late again!
You know you'll be fined if you're late three times.
Well, whatever. This here
is Morikawa Kotaro.
Nice to meet you.
Huh? Marina, did you know Kotaro?
Ah? N-No...
But I had that...
You had that what?
Are you daydreaming?
Dammit!
Let's have fun elsewhere, then.
Okay...
Let's go.
Yeah.
What on Earth is happening here?
Who are all these people?
Hey, do you know them, Marina?
How is it possible?
Maybe we've met before?
Ah, I can't remember!
I don't know how,
but it seems they know me really well.
Those three are on very good terms.
Well, I guess that's what being friends is all about.
And this guy Kotaro seems
like a very nice person too.
Hey, Daiki, isn't this nice?
Yeah, that's one hell of a thing.
Hey, Marina-chan.
Would you like to listen to this?
Sure.
I'm...
sorry.
Kotaro, we need to leave now.
Get along, will you? Bye!
Hey, Daiki!
They just left!
Hey, should I walk you home?
Well, it's pretty late already.
I'm an idiot.
What's wrong?
Not so fast.
C'mon, catch up!
Let's hurry!
It's here!
This shop...
Oh, what a pity.
I think it's amazing
they can do it together.
Those two are so close.
It's here.
That's...
What?
Hey,
let's take a picture together in that.
Sure.
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Huh? It's not working.
Maybe it's broken?
B-But I used it earlier today!
It's broken so they threw it away.
Print...
Oh, it works!
...Land!
You're right.
Okay, let's take a photo.
Here.
Thank you!
Now then, which frame should we choose?
Ready? I'm taking it.
Okay.
You look good with those.
Without them too.
It's to commemorate the day we met.
Okay, say cheese.
Here.
Thank you.
I guess it is broken, after all.
But I feel like it worked just a moment ago. Come on...
Today is such a lousy day.
Who is this? A prank call?
Huh?!
Ah, sorry. I wasn't watching where I was going.
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Perevodildo,
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Topper3000
"Latte Macchiato"