This video is based on experiences
our readers shared with us.
Human life is ever so fleeting.
When lingering regrets won't let some depart this world,
they're forced to wander
the Earth for years to come.
This is...
"I witnessed a wandering spirit."
A first-hand account of horror.
School Ghosts 6
Final Chapter
Picking Up on a Rainy Day
Conference Room
Thank you very much.
If you'll excuse us now...
See you, Sensei.
What's wrong, Mama?
I just need to do well on the next test, right? I won't let you down!
I'll hold you to that.
The rain is getting stronger.
I can't stand thunder!
Mama, hurry up!
Coming.
Hitomi, we can go home
under the same umbrella.
You can lend your umbrella to that girl.
That girl?
The one standing there... Oh?
Who was there?
No way! Mama, what did you see?
Don't tell me it was...
"Don't tell me it was..." what?
A girl with a red skirt
and a pink hair clip?
You saw her too?
No! We can't help her!
That was a ghost.
She died eight years ago!
I'm waiting, Mom.
Mom...
Mom... Mom said she would come to pick me up!
I guess I have to wait
for Mom, after all.
If Mom is coming to pick me up,
I'd feel bad leaving without her.
Mom...
Why didn't you come? Mom!
Sometimes,
students with a strong sense for
the supernatural see her standing there.
She doesn't try to hurt anyone,
but they say she looks awfully sad.
So... do you know that girl's name?
I think someone once said it was Haruko-chan.
Why?
That Haruko-chan is still waiting
for her mother to come for her.
We need to let her mom know.
I know that girl's family.
GROCERIES
They run a produce store in Kitamachi.
Hello, welcome.
What can I get you?
Excuse me, are you Haruko-san's mother?
Haruko?
Y-Yes, that's me.
May I talk to you in private?
Kinoshita-san, what is this weird nonsense?
Indeed, I may have wronged my child that day,
but I arranged a proper and respectful funeral for her.
Don't turn the memory
of my child into a ghost!
You're the only one
who can help Haruko-chan.
It's impossible. She is my child.
Haruko could never turn into a ghost.
You're talking nonsense!
No, that's how much Haruko-chan
wanted you to come pick her up.
But turning into a ghost...
Not a ghost. It's Haruko-chan's soul.
Haruko-chan's soul is
still waiting for you.
Haruko-chan has been waiting
all these years
for her mother to come
pick her up in the rain.
That day, Haruko called home and
made me promise that I'd pick her up.
But then, I suddenly had a lot to do at the store,
and I couldn't go pick her up.
Try walking that way.
And don't be scared.
Why would I be scared?
Even if she's turned into a ghost,
she's still my daughter.
She's not here?
She couldn't be here.
Haruko becoming a ghost...
That was a weird idea from the start.
Mom...
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You've been waiting
for me all this time?
You were waiting for your mother
to come for you?
I'm so sorry I couldn't come...
I'm sorry!
Would you come home with me now?
I'm so glad, Mama!
You're right. It's great.
School Trip Stone
Give it back.
Who's there?
Where did you hide it?!
Give it back!
Give it back.
Give it back...
No! Stop!
Help!
What's wrong, Miyako?
Miyako! Miyako!
I started having nightmares every night.
It happened after I brought home a fancy stone from a school trip one day.
Look! A cow!
Wow, you're right! It's huge!
What is?
I wish I could keep one.
Hey, Kanae. Would you like to swap for some of these?
Sure. Pick what you like.
Then, don't mind if I do...
I can't spear it.
There, speared it.
Now you choose.
Kanae, look. I found a sharp one.
And this one looks like a face.
Ah, this one has a pretty pattern.
Show me.
Wow, it's beautiful!
Didn't I tell you?
Yeah.
Hey, there. What are you up to?
We're looking for pretty stones.
Found any interesting ones?
Sort of. This one.
I'll take it home and place it in my room.
I think you'd better not.
Why do you say that?
This area has always been subject
to floods, and battles were fought here.
A lot of people died here.
And what has that to do with my stone?
Villagers used roadsides and riverbanks
to dig holes and buried the fallen in them.
Because they couldn't give everyone a headstone,
they made one from whatever stones they could find.
Why are you saying this?
To show off your smarts?
You must be jealous that
you didn't find this fancy stone.
You're saying that so I'll return the stone to where I found it,
and you'll take it for yourself later, right?
Don't be a fool!
I'm saying that because...
Enough is enough.
Miyako, let's go over there.
Yeah, let's go.
Miyako, Sensei asked everyone to assemble.
Give me a minute.
Remember, if you don't hurry,
you'll be left behind.
Yeah.
That's a pretty stone.
I wonder if I can make it shine even more by polishing it?
Miyako, dinner is ready.
Okay!
Give it back!
Give it back.
Give it back...
Ouch!
Huh?
Give it back!
No!
I'm sorry.
Give it back.
Give it back!
Give it back...
Give it back.
No!
Ever since then, whether day or night,
I've had nightmares when I go to sleep.
I was very scared,
so I decided to return this stone
to the riverbank where I found it.
After that, I stopped having nightmares.
If only I had listened to Satomi's advice back then,
I wouldn't have undergone this awful experience.
Abandoned Temple
Tetsuo, wanna go get some water?
I'm quite thirsty myself.
So good!
The place looks really empty.
That's only natural.
It's summer vacation.
I wonder if there's something interesting to do.
Tetsuo, have you ever been
to that mountain in the back?
I haven't.
I haven't been there either.
So what? You think there's something interesting on it?
Yeah. Someone told me about it.
There's a temple on the verge of collapsing.
Let's check it out!
Fine by me.
Guess we'll have to walk from here.
Yes, sir! Whatever the expedition leader commands me to do!
Are we there yet, leader?
I heard it's further up this way.
See? There it is.
You're right.
Wow, so there was a temple right here.
That's interesting.
Even the monks would run away
from such a dilapidated temple.
Anyone home?
Oh, it's really chilly in here!
Feels good to cool down.
Tetsuo, be careful.
The floor looks like it's about to fall in.
Okay.
Geez, that sure was scary.
Leader, should I lay this on the floor?
I suppose. Good idea!
Let's build a secret base here.
And... now!
What's wrong, Tetsuo?
Oh, it's nothing.
Is there any good stuff here, I wonder?
How could the monks bring themselves to do this all day long?
I'd sure be fun to bring this thing to our music class!
That'd make for a barrel of laughs!
Hey, stop it!
Why?
Don't make that sutra-reading voice.
It creeps me out.
But I didn't do it!
Was it just my imagination?
Look at how scared you are!
It even made you mistake the sound of wind for a sutra, leader!
Wh-Why should I possibly be scared?!
No way. Did you light it, Tetsuo?
I-I can also hear the sutra now, leader.
Didn't I tell you?!
Wh-What's going on?!
H-Help! Help me!
Help us, someone!
Please help!
School Lunch Lady
Good morning, ma'am!
Good morning!
You two are looking lively today!
Why wouldn't we?
Good, that cheers me up as well!
So I'll be sure to make
a delicious lunch for you.
But ma'am, I'm starving already!
Oh no, did you even have breakfast before coming to school?
Give me a minute.
Here.
Awesome!
Bye, then. I'm looking forward to lunch.
Right, right. Make sure to study hard!
Takashi, who sat on the tree, was enveloped in the sweet flagrance of spring.
Japanese Language 5th Grade
Through the branches, he could see
houses lined up neatly on the slope.
Thanks for the meal!
It's great!
Yeah, great!
Auntie Katayama's hamburger steak
is the best part of lunch.
Yeah, it's good.
Thanks for the meal!
Coming!
So, did you like your lunch today?
The hamburger steak
you made was perfect!
It was really delicious.
Thank you.
The buffet lady would sometimes
let us try the food before serving it.
Here you are.
Thank you!
Auntie Katayama!
Sign: Minamikawa Elementary School
Then, after about three weeks had passed...
Ma'am!
She's not here today either.
Yeah.
For some reason, I feel really tired.
If Auntie Katayama doesn't
come back soon,
I won't even have the energy to get to lunch.
Ah, I wanna eat Auntie Katayama's
hamburger steaks again!
Is it Auntie Katayama's...
...hamburger steak?
Awesome!
Yum!
It tastes like Auntie Katayama's
hamburger steak!
Auntie Katayama's back
from the hospital!
Yeah!
Auntie Katayama?
Are you well again?
Ma'am?
Ma'am!
Your hamburger today was even better than before!
Thanks for the dessert!
What's wrong?
Kazu-kun, Nita-kun!
The hospital just called.
Katayama-san passed away a few minutes ago.
What?
It can't be! We just saw her!
After she was admitted to the hospital,
Katayama-san never regained consciousness.
She was in a coma after that.
Poor woman...
No way!
Ma'am!
Ma'am?
Auntie Katayama absolutely made that hamburger steak.
Yeah, definitely!
She let us eat it one last time.
Yeah.
The bananas that she gave us...
Road to School
CROSSING
This happened when I was in elementary school.
I'm off!
Uh... Hey, are you going to be late today?
I see.
All right, deal.
It's okay. I have the key.
I'm off!
Hey!
Good morning.
Here, this is for you.
Are you feeling well?
You know, I'm on class duty today.
I have to go to the staff room
to get the attendance book,
so I have to leave now.
Well, I'm going.
John was a big friend of children.
But even then, I was probably closer
to John than anyone else.
I lived with my mother in an apartment.
Even when I felt lonely and deserted,
even when I was crying endlessly
because I'd quarreled with a friend,
John was always there
to cheer me up and comfort me.
John was a very old dog,
almost 90 years old in human terms.
He really enjoyed playing with me.
I'm off!
Good morning, John!
John?
John!
What happened?
Oh, good morning, Misaki-chan.
Good morning, ma'am.
Um...
Are you looking for John?
He became a bit sick on Saturday night.
When I took him to the vet,
they said they need to observe him
at the clinic for a while.
But when I went to see him yesterday,
he was already better and eating well.
I'm sure he'll get better soon.
I'll be on summer vacation starting tomorrow.
I'm going to my grandma's place in the countryside.
So I won't be able to see John
until vacation is over.
Then, I'll tell John to wait for you to return from your grandma
and play with him again.
Good!
I'm off, Grandma!
Did you take your summer homework?
I'm off for real now.
I wonder if John is feeling better.
Dogs are so lucky.
They don't have any homework.
Ma'am!
Good morning, ma'am!
John!
John...
Thank you. You saved my life.
Dr. Takemoto, Dr. Takemoto,
please come to the internal medicine ward.
I'm glad, Misaki-chan.
You got away with just a scratch.
I've called your mom too.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
I think you made my heart stop there.
What about John?
John?
Then, on the road, John suddenly appeared and pushed me away from the truck.
I can't wait to see him.
There was no dog near you
at the time of the accident,
let alone John.
But John even licked my face.
Misaki-chan, I hate to say it,
but John died three weeks ago.
John died?!
But it was John who saved me!
It was definitely John!
PET CEMETERY
John, you saved your friend Misaki-chan,
even after you'd died yourself.
Good dog.
Thank you, John.
I owe you my life.
May the Earth rest lightly on you.
The Horror at 4:44
Hey, what time is it now?
May I inform you that it's 4:35:30.
Hey, what should we do?
Wanna come to my house?
I don't mind.
What about you, Asako?
What's wrong?
What is it?
Hey, you ever tried to see what the 4:44
art room horror is all about?
Isn't it when you meet Yoshiko-san in the art room?
Nah...
Let's go.
Hurry up, Jun. Let's go!
Wait for me.
Hurry. When I open the door at 4:44,
we all need to go inside.
An eerie sign...
Don't say that!
Apparently, Yoshiko-san...
was the most talented student
in her senior high school art club.
She sent her newest work
to an exhibition.
That was when...
Enough already, geez!
Her incredible stubbornness makes
her keep drawing pictures to this day.
Right, you make it fancier
with every word.
Art.
Room
It can't be. Are you serious?
Then, stay here and wait for us.
No way! That's even scarier.
Initiating countdown.
Five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
zero!
Is anyone there?
No one here.
Because there can't be anyone, right?
Hey, don't you think that's enough?
Don't worry.
We entered this classroom at 4:44,
as rumor demanded,
but there's nothing here.
No, Yoshiko-san.
We've proved it's just
a made-up story, right?
Yeah.
That means we don't have to be afraid, do we?
But hey...
Look!
So? You like it?
D-Don't be stupid, Miho!
Hiratsuka will call you to the staff room
and give you an earful again!
It's okay. It's only held
in place by the clay.
Whew, Jun, you sure are a nervous Nellie.
What's that sound?
What was it?
She's here!
Yoshiko-san from the art room?
Slowly... Let's get out.
It's blood!
Be quiet.
Help!
Help...
Somebody, help!
Help us!
Please help!
Open the door!
Where do you think you're going?
Won't you model for me first?
You're not going anywhere now.
Why don't you quietly help me draw?
So?
You'll model for me, won't you?
We're not models!
That's right. We know nothing about art!
Please let us out of here.
Not happening.
You three will never part again.
My painting is almost done too.
There, take a look.
We're sorry!
We didn't mean to disturb you!
Please forgive us!
Help us, somebody!
Why won't you be quiet?
Please let us out of here.
Will you be quiet?
Will you be quiet or not?!
Why do you keep disturbing me?
Everyone keeps disturbing me.
I've had enough!
Help!
You're not getting out of here.
Don't startle me like that.
What?
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
Perevodildo
Perevodildo,
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Topper3000
"Wiener Melange"
Orphan Fansubs