This video is based on experiences
our readers shared with us.
True School Ghosts
Orphan Fansubs presents
Yeah.
Yeah, that's him.
The guy that came the other day.
Yeah, he's so much fun to be around!
That's because I'm a people person.
I know, I know.
Hey, maybe it's all right?
I think I'll invite everyone.
Yeah.
Oh, don't you worry!
Let's go together.
Dead Person's Cell Phone
Let's go together...
It's true!
All right, I get it.
See you, Yoko.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Yoko, 14 (pseudonym)
It's a cell phone.
It works!
Huh? You're using a phone you found?
I've always wanted to see what it's like.
Still, using someone else's phone?
I know.
But everyone else has one.
I'm the only one without a phone.
And my mom won't buy me
a cell phone either.
So I guess your wish was fulfilled?
Yeah!
Don't be so thoughtless!
You should return it to the owner!
I know.
I'll take it to the police box, all right?
Yeah. Yes. Understood.
See you, then.
Come with me.
You should come with me.
What's going on?
I definitely left it at the police box.
Mom!
You're still awake, Yoko?
Mom, the cell phone is...
Yoko, didn't I tell you that cell phones are a no-no?
That's not it!
The cell phone... just rang!
There isn't any phone to ring.
Are you okay, Yoko?
Didn't you just have a scary dream?
Let's not worry about it
and have a good night's sleep.
Middle School
So you couldn't sleep
a wink because of that?
Yeah...
But your mom didn't
hear the ringing, right?
Yeah...
Then I know what happened!
You've been cursed for using someone else's phone.
J-Just kidding, okay? I'm kidding.
Don't worry about it.
Yoko, you hear?
A curse, then?
Even a good person attains birth in the Pure Land,
so it goes without saying that an evil person will.
Though it is so, people commonly say,
"Even an evil person attains birth,
so it goes without saying that a good person will."
This statement may seem well founded at first...
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
C-Cell phone's ringing...
Cell phone?
I don't hear a phone ringing.
Maybe you haven't properly
woken up yet?
I-It can't be...
I can hear it. I hear it!
I can hear it!
Why... Why am I the only one
who can hear it?
I used a phone I found.
Did that really cause me to be cursed?
But those things aren't
supposed to exist.
Ah, Yoko. Welcome home.
Hold it. Yoko!
It a lie. It has to be!
No!
What's going on?
Why? Why me?
What do you want me to do?
Yoko.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom! Mom...
Yoko.
I have a present for you.
Mom...
Yes.
Look.
It's the cell phone you've always wanted.
No. I don't need it.
I don't want it!
You can't refuse.
It too late, now that we've already become friends.
No!
Come.
We'll have loads of fun.
So? Won't you come with me?
It'll be fun, I promise.
Okay?
There, come with me.
Yes. I'll come with you.
You wouldn't believe
how delicious it was.
Be sure to check it out!
Hey, where did you say it was?
Listen.
It's the bakery on the corner.
Right. What's more, they're now serving Mont Blancs. Huh?
A cell phone!
Someone must've dropped it.
Hey, wanna use it?
No way. The owner must be looking for it.
I'll take it to the police box.
It won't break if we use it
for a little while.
No. Why don't you give it a rest?
Hey, why don't you come with me?
I beg you to stay strong on your path.
Girl of the Night
Really, you've been with me this whole time?
Even if you're feeling a bit lonely right now...
Girl of the Night
Don't come near me!
I guess I just can't live in this world!
Girl of the Night
I'll be with you, from now on and forever.
I guess I just can't live in this world!
Girl of the Night
Goodbye.
Cursed Script
Well then, Kumi-chan.
You've got a tough role, but it's very important, so do your best, okay?
Yes, Shizuko-senpai.
I'll put my soul into it.
See you tomorrow, then.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Did it!
"I beg you to stay strong on your path.
Even if you're feeling
a little lonely right now...
I'll be with you,
from now on and forever.
So please...
Please..."
Hey, this scene is just between
Shizuko-senpai and me, right?
Don't you think
it's the highlight of the play?
Right, right?
Sure, sure, we understand.
You don't have to be so excited.
But this is my first role with lines
since I joined the Drama Club.
And it's an important role too.
I have to rehearse a lot
for the school festival now.
You landed this role, so good for you.
Who cares about us anyway, right?
Girl of the Night
Fukawa Girls' Middle School Drama
"Girl of the Night," huh?
Hey, why did Shizuko-senpai suddenly decide to stage
a play like this at the school festival?
Well, it seems it accidentally caught Shizuko-senpai's eye.
It interested her, so she decided to stage it.
It was probably when she was cleaning the clubroom the other day.
Have you ever heard about that "Girl of the Night?"
Well, I feel like I've heard a story related to this script somewhere.
But where was it?
Girl of the Night
Fukawa Girls' Middle School Drama
I beg you to stay strong on your path.
Even if you're feeling
a little lonely right now...
I'll be with you,
from now on and forever.
Will you really be there
for me forever?
Yes. I'll never leave you alone.
So please...
Nicely done, Kumi-chan.
You've been practicing a lot.
Thank you, Shizuko-senpai.
Okay, I'll try to rehearse my part
one more time. Why don't you watch it?
Sure.
Will you... Will you really be there for me forever?
Shizuko-senpai is doing it
with great dedication.
She becomes a different person.
Of course she does.
She's playing the protagonist.
Don't come near me!
I guess I just can't live in this world!
In the end,
everything was just an illusion.
Goodbye.
Kumi.
Kumi!
What's wrong, Kumi?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
What was it now...
Kumi?
Ah, Hiroko?
You know, Kumi, I figured out what's the deal with the "Girl of the Night."
So?
That play is dangerous.
I thought to myself, didn't my sister also graduate from this school?
So I asked her.
Girl of the Night
It was about ten years ago.
The director of the Drama Club
Girl of the Night
wrote the script for this "Girl of the Night" play.
And she inserted herself as the main character.
Girl of the Night
This time... the main character is Shizuko-senpai, right?
Yes.
Girl of the Night
So she stayed up late every night,
rehearsing her role furiously for the school festival.
She died?
Yes. She became ill.
Apparently, she was physically weak to begin with,
but then she pushed herself to the limit.
She collapsed during rehearsal, was hospitalized,
and died the day before
the school festival.
It seems she was very invested in this play,
and just before drawing her last breath,
she promised to appear in the play
and play the leading role.
That's where things went south.
The performance was to be held
on the day of the festival.
But the girl playing the leading role
was seriously injured
in a sudden accident
in the middle of the performance.
Since then, people have been gossiping that the curse of the dead girl was to blame.
They say this script is filled with that girl's hatred.
So that's why they sealed it?
Yes.
If it's just a rumor,
then all the better.
But if there's any truth to it,
it might be dangerous, Kumi.
For Shizuko-senpai.
After all, she's playing the leading role.
That just...
That can't be!
I hope it's just my imagination,
but I feel like Shizuko-senpai is acting weird lately.
Enough!
We're finally doing it
tomorrow, Kumi-chan.
Yes. I'll do my best.
Everyone's been practicing hard.
We'll definitely make it work.
You're right. Let's all do our best.
With you on board, it'll be a success.
Thank you!
It just can't be true.
It has to be my imagination.
Just my imagination...
Shizuko-senpai's enthusiasm is abnormal.
You must've noticed it too, Kumi.
It's like something is possessing her-
Enough!
It can't be true.
I'm just overthinking it.
There isn't any curse.
Tomorrow's performance
will be a success.
Without incidents.
It can't be...
That's right.
Back then...
Yes, I saw her.
So the curse was real, after all.
The day of the performance came,
but I couldn't bring myself to tell anyone.
Not Chisato, nor Hiroko,
nor Shizuko-senpai.
I beg you to stay strong on your path.
Even if you're feeling
a little lonely right now...
I'll be with you,
from now on and forever.
Will you really be there for me forever?
Yes. I'll never leave you alone.
Fukawa Girls Middle School Cultural Festival
So please... Please...
Things are going well so far.
Yeah. We're almost at the climax.
Will you really stay with me forever?
Yes.
It can't be...
Don't come near me!
I guess I just can't live in this world!
Goodbye.
Stop it!
Not Senpai...
Don't take her with you!
Please!
Kumi-chan?
Kumi-chan!
S-Senpai...
Are you okay, Kumi-chan?
Fukawa Girls Middle School Cultural Festival
Senpai, I'm so glad!
Really, I'm very glad.
Girl of the Night
Needless to say, after that incident,
Girl of the Night was
sealed away forever.
Girl of the Night
Summer Camp Terror
Nitoge Mountain Lodge
Man, oh man. We're finally here.
Hello!
We're from Higashi High School in Kanagawa!
Are we really staying
in this mountain lodge?
Of course we are.
I made a reservation here, after all.
But man, this place is kind of creepy.
Welcome.
This is the old lodge building.
We've prepared rooms for you
in the new building.
I'll show you the way. Please follow me.
This is quite an old mountain lodge.
The old building is,
but we only use it as an entrance.
Oh... Look at that!
Impressive trophies!
Is that the real thing?
Yes, certainly.
Our master shot them in the mountains
and then stuffed them himself.
Oh? So you even have bears around here?
Please take your time.
Thank you.
Ah, just a word of advice.
You mustn't enter the old building at night
unless absolutely necessary.
Well then.
I sure hope this fog
clears up by tomorrow.
What's wrong, Nakajima?
S-Someone just passed
by our window outside!
Don't be stupid! We're on second floor!
No one could pass by the window here.
Don't you need some rest?
I suppose...
Mountain man, listen carefully...
Hello. The hot springs sure feel mysterious with all this fog.
Huh?
Now that was weird.
Tell me, Inoue.
Don't you feel like someone's been watching us ever since we came here?
Yes, kind of.
I wonder if something's
not right about this lodge.
Eek!
What is it?
So many of them.
They all look like they're still alive.
Poor creatures. They were killed just to be beheaded.
Eek!
Huh?
What is it?
Run!
Somebody, help!
Where's the exit?!
This is supposed to be the exit!
Wh-What do we do now?!
This way!
Wait! Wait for me!
Inoue... Inoue, where are you?
Where did you go?
Where did you go, Inoue?!
Inoue, is that you?
Help me...
Please help me...
Good lord...
Help me...
Please help me...
I beg you, good lord, help me...
Please help, good lord...
Give back my body...
Make it stop!
Next morning, we found Inoue and Moriguchi half-dead.
It was a while later before
either of them could speak again.
Spirits' Road
Okay, it should be about time.
Then let's begin, Chiharu.
Go ahead.
Let's see...
Resurrection, resurrection...
Found it!
First, create a Western-style magic circle.
When doing so, please pay attention to the four directions.
Which way is north?
Hm, north should be...
I don't really know
directions all that well.
For now, let's just draw some lines
and try to form a circle.
Hey, I don't think we should do this, after all-
Coward! We're doing it for Chiharu, remember?
I do remember that...
but I'm still too scared.
Geez, you're a nuisance.
Now then, next mark the symbol of each zodiac sign.
North represents earth,
east represents wind,
south represents sun,
and west represents water.
Hey, Megumi.
What now? You're scared too, Chiharu?
Yes. Are you sure... Are you absolutely sure we'll get to see her?
Leave it to me! It'll be fine.
Is it even real? Can we actually resurrect the dead with it?
Will you be quiet?
I'm trying to concentrate.
Now, next is...
"You can resurrect the dead."
I was the first one to propose it.
Grandma...
It can't be, Grandma!
You promised me!
When my summer vacation comes in August,
you promised to celebrate my birthday with me!
You said we'd go to the amusement park together!
Hey! Wake up, Grandma!
Wake up, Grandma!
Why won't you wake up?!
Grandma!
Wake up, Grandma...
Wake up, Grandma!
Even a week later, I couldn't believe it.
I felt like if I went home now,
Grandma would come out to meet me as usual.
I'm home!
I'm home, Grandma!
But Grandma was nowhere to be found.
The Obon festival is approaching.
They say that during Obon,
the dead return to this world
and then depart for the afterlife again.
I wondered... if it meant that my grandma
would return along with everyone else.
I wanted to see my grandma at least one more time.
That was when our occult maven Megumi said this to me.
Hey, Chiharu, you wanna see your grandma again, right?
Yeah, but that's not possible.
It is! We'll perform a ritual.
A ritual to bring back the dead!
Done!
All right!
Now that the magic circle is complete,
the next step is to say
the resurrection spell
while everyone holds hands.
Come on, let's hold hands!
Now chant this with me:
Elohim Essaim, Elohim Essaim.
Come on, Chiharu, hurry up!
Elohim Essaim...
Hey, what are you waiting for, Ayako?
It's for Chiharu, remember?
Elohim... Essaim...
Elohim Essaim, Elohim Essaim,
Elohim Essaim! Elohim Essaim!
Okay, now the next one.
Bring back Grandma!
Bring back Grandma.
Nothing happened.
Huh? That's strange.
She's supposed to be back by now.
Wait, give me a minute.
If the spell doesn't work,
check your magic circle again.
Did you draw the directions correctly?
Did you cast the spell properly and clearly?
Hm, I guess I got the directions
wrong, after all.
Liar.
You're a liar, Megumi!
I said give me a minute!
It's Obon today,
and the time seems okay.
As long as the conditions are met...
What's this?!
See, it worked!
It's not real, right?
There!
A shining!
What's this?
Grandma?
Wh-What's this?
Don't tell me they're all ghosts!
I see! They're the spirits that return to this world for Obon!
The spirits' road goes right through our school!
That can't be right!
They're coming this way!
They'll take us with them to the afterlife!
Let's run away!
Run!
Chiharu?
Chiharu, what's the matter?!
Grandma... Grandma might be in there!
Grandma!
This isn't the time to worry about that!
Grandma! Grandma!
Grandma!
Grandma?
Grandma?!
Grandma!
Grandma...
How could you, Grandma?
You promised to take me to the amusement park, didn't you?
But now I have to wake up by myself every morning!
I even eat the green peas now.
I hate them, but I eat them all for you!
Hey, Grandma, wake up!
Wake up, Grandma!
Come on, Grandma!
When second semester comes,
I'll definitely score over 80 points on the test!
Hey, Grandma, wake up!
Hey, pinky promise me this time!
Promise you'll never do it again!
Never leave me alone!
Stay with me forever!
Hey, Grandma, don't go!
Grandma!
Wait!
Wait, Grandma!
You can't go!
Grandma!
Grandma...
Wait! Grandma!
Wake up, Chiharu!
Stop!
Let go! I'll go with her!
Idiot! You wanna become one of the ghosts?!
I don't care! I'll be with Grandma forever!
Chiharu...
Grandma!
They're going away.
Grandma will disappear!
She's really leaving!
Grandma!
They're gone. All of them...
There! So, isn't my magic amazing?!
No, it wasn't your magic.
It was the Obon festival.
I can't take it anymore!
Huh?
Just admit it.
My magic had a hand in it too!
You had nothing to do with it!
But they appeared all at once,
like with a spell!
They'd have done it anyway.
Goodbye, Grandma.
The second semester came.
I didn't notice the exact moment,
but eventually,
I came to terms with the fact
that Grandma was dead.
You look happier already.
Yeah.
Wanna do it again?
The resurrection ritual.
No, that's enough.
Grandma no longer
belongs to this world.
Yes, Grandma is dead, after all.
I see.
Then...
Hey, why don't we try this next time?
It's a ritual to summon the devil.
Don't do it!
I absolutely won't take part in that.
How can you say that-
I don't care!
Isn't it all the same?
But sometimes,
my grandma's smell, the way I remember it
from the old days, comes to my mind again.
At times like that, I become convinced
that Grandma will come back again someday.
She'll come again
during the Obon festival
to see that I've grown up a little more.
Yes, she'll walk the spirits' road again.
Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Presented by
Perevodildo
Perevodildo,
ninjacloud
Collectr
Nemesis
Topper3000
"Amaretto Latte"
Orphan Fansubs