This animation is based on experiences
our readers shared with us.
Human life is ever so fleeting.
When lingering regrets won't
let people depart this world,
they're forced to wander
the Earth for years to come.
This is...
Orphan Fansubs presents
School Ghosts
"I witnessed a wandering spirit."
Orphan Fansubs presents
School Ghosts
A first-hand account of horror.
Kagoshima Prefecture "S" Middle School
Music Room
You're still here?
It's already dark outside.
You should hurry home.
Okay.
It's this late already?
I'm sorry. I got carried away.
You're always studying until late, huh?
Yes. I have a test coming up.
I was on sick leave for quite a while.
You'll worry your mother,
staying out this late.
C'mon, hurry home.
I'm turning off the lights.
Not yet!
Forgotten Notebook
I forgot my notebook.
Mourning
Please accept my sincerest condolences.
I was the one
who told her to hurry home.
And she forgot this notebook.
What a truly hard working,
fair young lady she was.
I-It's her!
What's wrong with the custodian?
A Few Months Later
What's that sound?
I-Is someone still here?
Th-There's no way.
It's 2 A.M. already.
It's just the pump?
What are you doing here this late?
I-It's you!
I-Impossible!
Mister...
Help me! She's returned! Help me!
God! Buddha! Save me! Help!
S-Someone help me!
Where's my notebook?
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Crap!
God, Buddha... G-God, Buddha...
God save us all, God save us all...
God... Buddha... God... Buddha...
I made it through?
Give me back my notebook.
N-No!
Batting Ghost
This strange phenomenon
started about a month ago.
The first time it happened was when students who were going home late
took a shortcut across the campus,
after preparing for the school festival.
Wanna get something to eat?
Sounds good.
What's wrong?
What's that?
Since then,
the school has been rife with rumors,
either of someone standing still,
or of someone swinging a bat on campus.
What they saw was
the ghost of Nagao-sensei.
Next one's to the left!
After Nagao-sensei became
the baseball team's new coach,
they had a streak of victories
and even dared to dream
about playing at Koshien.
Starting with the team itself,
everyone from fellow students
to the PTA had high hopes.
But then, the third batter,
Matsumoto-kun, fell into a slump
and failed to hit 30 times in a row.
But Nagao-sensei refused to change
the batting order or team members,
expecting that Matsumoto-kun would start hitting soon.
Rumors said that it happened two weeks
before an important game.
Excuse me, Nagao-sensei.
Can we talk?
What is it, Matsumoto?
I don't want to drag the rest
of the team down any longer!
I'd like to stop hitting third.
What?
I can't hit anymore.
I want to quit baseball!
Don't quit over some small
hurdle, you dimwit!
Nagao-sensei encouraged Matsumoto-kun and took him to the batter's box.
Go on, swing the bat.
Swing! I said, swing!
Okay.
Lower your head. Tuck your chin in.
What now? Why'd you stop?
Swing!
Sensei, I...
Matsumoto, toss for me and look closely to understand what you're doing wrong.
See? You can hit it. You have what it takes to be a batter!
All you need to do is swing more confidently.
Okay, keep tossing.
After about five more
minutes of doing it,
Matsumoto-kun fumbled the ball.
Matsumoto! Are you okay?
Apparently, Nagao-sensei's bat hit Matsumoto in the back of his head.
They got an ambulance
for him at once.
However, Matsumoto-kun was paralyzed from the waist down.
The faculty treated this
as an incident of teacher bullying.
The media and the PTA
unleashed a storm of criticism
on Nagao-sensei's teaching methods.
Because he had a stronger than usual sense of responsibility,
a few days later,
he hung himself on a branch of the sakura tree
in the far corner of the campus.
Sensei's death was a shock to everyone.
But even more shocking
was that his ghost then started silently prowling the campus every night.
As the manager of the baseball team,
I visited Matsumoto-senpai many times,
trying to persuade him that we needed
to pacify Sensei's spirit.
Matsumoto Liquor Store
Leave me alone already!
I don't hold a grudge against Nagao-sensei or something.
All I want is to forget the whole thing.
But I really need to pacify Sensei!
Like I said before, his spirit comes to campus every night,
puts his hands together,
and hangs himself!
I don't need another reminder of what happened!
My feelings won't change,
no matter how many times you ask!
I'm sure Nagao-sensei appears every night
because he wants to apologize to you!
But... I don't believe in that kind of stuff!
It's nonsense. It can't be!
Then come and see for yourself whether it's real or not!
The ghost hasn't appeared.
Can we go already?
Just a bit longer.
Is that...
S-Sensei...
Sensei! Nagao-sensei!
Enough already!
Sensei, that's enough!
It wasn't your fault!
I keep my spirits up,
even in a wheelchair.
You don't have to feel guilty!
Stop this already!
Nagao-sensei! It's me, Matsumoto!
Enough is enough! In all this time,
I've never regretted
playing baseball with you!
So please... Stop condemning yourself!
Nagao-sensei!
S-Sensei...
After that,
the sightings of Nagao-sensei's ceased.
But every year,
when the sakura tree blossoms,
the baseball team gathers under that tree to offer their prayers.
Cursed Summer Camp
Kanagawa Prefecture "S" Girls' High School
1989, Summer
Here! Go ahead, pass it to me!
Kanagawa Prefecture "S" Girls' High School
1989, Summer
Nice!
Here!
Pass it to me!
Shoot!
Nice!
That's all for today's practice.
Captain, it's getting late, so finish cooling down and clean up now.
All right. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Can you turn on the light?
Sure.
What time is it?
Um, I think it's around half past nine.
I hope Mom recorded the video.
I'm beat.
Don't you think everyone is a little too excited for the first day of training camp?
That's true. I thought so too.
Phew, that was spooky.
Who turned off the lights?
I bet it was just our senpai's prank.
Let's head back to the dorms now.
Okay.
It's pitch dark.
I have a bad feeling.
C-Cut it out.
Don't use that tone.
You're totally creeping me out.
Seriously, you're a scaredy-cat.
Wh-What was that?
A-A cat?
I knew we shouldn't come
to school at night.
If you weren't so slow,
we wouldn't be here!
Did you know?
The captain and Imai-senpai saw it last year.
What? Saw what?
A ghost, obviously.
Stop! I'm not listening to any of that!
What's wrong?
Did you just make that noise?
No, I didn't! Are you trying to scare me again?
I'm not! I really heard something.
Let's hurry back to everyone.
Ah, wait!
Captain, is it true you saw a ghost last year?
It's not true, is it?
I did see it.
B-But how?
A long time ago,
this school was... a hospital.
A hospital?
S-So it was covered in blood, or missing a hand?
The ghost I saw was a nurse.
Ugh... I really need to go
to the bathroom.
Hey, Chiko.
I haven't eaten it yet.
Hey, don't fall asleep!
What is it? Don't wake me up, Kana.
I was just about to try a scrumptious cake.
Look, let's go to the bathroom.
I don't need to.
Please! Come with me.
I'm too scared to go alone.
Oh geez, you're hopeless.
Wait for me. Are you still out there?
You're there, aren't you?
Don't you leave without me, Chiko!
Sure, sure, I'm waiting.
Sorry for taking so long.
You may pass now, you may pass,
here on this narrow road
Hey, cut it out! Don't sing something so gloomy.
What kind of song
would you like, then?
Geez, Chiko you big jerk!
I-I couldn't help it.
Did you hear that?
I-I think so.
Wh-What was that?
It sounds like it's coming from down the corridor.
Wh-What is that?
A wheelchair.
And that's a... n-n-
n-
A nurse?!
She's here!
She's heading this way! Let's run!
N-No way. I can't move.
My legs won't move!
Seriously?
We've gotta run now, Kana!
I-I can't.
Oh geez!
Wh-What's going on here?
Listen! Something's wrong!
She stopped.
It's here!
Help us!
It hurts...
Hurts bad...
Someone help us!
It's here! Here! Here!
W-Water...
Water...
Please give me water...
Senpai! Captain! Help us!
Help us!
What's going on?!
They're here! Here!
What happened to you?!
Hang in there!
Painful...
Water...
Kill me...
Please, water...
Night on a School Trip
A school trip is the most exciting event
in a high school student's life.
We were all very excited.
Yukari spent the trip clutching onto
the karaoke mic and posing as a star.
We happily followed our scheduled events
for the first, second, and third day,
and made it safely to our final stop.
After you've found your rooms,
ask Nakai-san to show you around.
Next, Suzuki and the other girls from
the third group will stay in the Blue Room.
Lacquer-ware
Okay!
Now then.
S-Sensei, actually...
I see. There's no other way, then?
Third group's room has been changed from the Blue to the Pure Room.
It's a nice detached room.
Huh? Did you say the Pure Room?
Lacquer-ware
Yes, that's right.
I-I see.
Follow me, then.
The Pure Room...
What a nice garden!
We're lucky to get a detached room just for ourselves.
We're the VIP guests here!
True, true!
We can make all the noise we want!
Logo: Inn
Pure Room
Wow, this is a nice room!
Is there a problem?
N-No.
Look, you can see the ocean from here!
Wow! You're right.
What a room! You can tell it's detached.
But guys...
Doesn't it smell a bit musty in here?
And that stain over there
looks like a face.
What do you mean?
Doesn't look like one to me.
Really? But I totally see a face there.
Hey, why don't we open the windows?
Good idea!
It won't budge.
Let me try.
Huh?
It won't open because
it's nailed shut down here!
Why aren't we allowed
to open the windows?
I wonder.
I've prepared tea. Dinner will be served
in the hall of the main building at 7.
Okay...
Nakai-san, sorry to ask, but could you take a picture for us?
Huh? Here?
I'm not good with a camera. S-Sorry.
B-But...
What was that made-up excuse?
For real.
Well, whatever. We'll use
the timer. Gather round!
C'mon, hurry up! Right here!
After dinner, Yukari said she was unwell and went to sleep.
Pure Room
Okay, Yukari, we're going to the baths.
It's a shame. I knew you wanted to try the open-air bath.
And don't go calling Sanada-kun
while we're not around, you hear?
Of course not.
I thought I'd just get some sleep.
All right, then.
I'll get the lights.
So hot...
It's hot, so hot in here.
Why is it so hot?
Join us...
Wh-What's this?
No!
Join us...
No! No! No!
No!
Everyone is... calling for me.
Join us...
I gotta go. Everyone is calling for me.
No! I can't open it! I mustn't!
Join us...
What are you doing, Yukari?! Stop!
I was so scared!
We told the teacher what had happened
and asked for another room.
After that, morning arrived
without incident,
and we left the ominous inn behind.
Still, it was really difficult for us
to believe Yukari's story.
But when we looked at that photo,
a chill went down everyone's spine.
No!
Much later, I found out
that the cliffs below the detached building we stayed in
were famous among locals as the place where those who died at sea
often washed up.
Kagome, kagome, the bird in the cage
When, oh when will it come out?
In the evening of the dawn
The crane and the turtle slipped
Who is behind you now?
Hanako-san
I heard there was someone
at my school named Hanako-san.
Hanako-san
Quiet! You can only practice calligraphy
when it's quiet, both inside and outside.
Okay.
Flower
Finished! It came out nicely this time.
Would be even prettier with this!
Hanako
It's Hanako, right!
Hey! Cut it out!
You'll regret it!
Hey!
I'll make you all clean
the bathroom as punishment!
No fair!
Hanako
You know, they say Hanako-san
lives in this bathroom.
The girls from Class 1
saw Hanako-san here!
No way.
It's true. I heard it directly
from one of them.
Sounds interesting.
Let's go meet Hanako-san.
B-But...
M-Meet Hanako-san?
Sounds like fun.
I-I'd rather not.
It'll be fine. Hanako-san must be feeling very blue,
spending her days all alone
in this bathroom.
R-Right.
But they say you shouldn't
make fun of Hanako-san.
Look at how scared you are!
But even so, we can't do the cleaning
unless we go in there.
Hanako
Wh-Which door?
The furthest one.
I-Is anyone in here?!
Doesn't seem to be.
We've gotta make sure.
Wh-Who's going to do it?
Please, Mina. Won't you go knock on the farthest door?
B-But...
If you don't, you're out
of our friend group.
For five or six years,
or maybe even forever!
C-C'mon, knock on it!
Hurry up! Just a couple of taps!
Ah! Wait!
Did anyone answer?
Let's stop this now.
No way! Not until we knock more confidently.
This time, call her by her name
while you knock.
Then why don't you
do it this time, Aigo?
Too scared, aintcha?
Fine, whatever.
I'll do the knocking myself.
You three better not run away.
O-Okay.
H-Hanako-san?
Hanako-san? Hanako-san!
Hey, let's stop this.
Ha-na-ko-san!
Ah! It's here!
What are you doing?!
It won't open!
Pull harder!
No way! It's stuck!
Why... Why is this happening?
We must have angered Hanako-san.
That's right! It's Aigo's fault!
We shouldn't've made fun of Hanako-san!
That's right! Aigo did it!
What are you saying? All I did was...
What's going to happen now?!
H-Hanako-san is here!
Mina, what's wrong?
Was it you three who summoned me?
Mi-Mina?
Hanako-san has possessed Minako!
Don't treat me as a plaything.
You three called me here for no reason.
So why don't I avail myself by playing with you, as per your wish?
Please... No!
Shut up!
N-No, it hurts. Help!
You're the one who called me here, you selfish girl.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Why don't I teach you a fun game to play, you mortal thing?
How does that sound?
I promise we won't call you anymore! Please let Aigo go!
We're sorry! We're sorry!
We won't do it again! Don't kill Aigo!
Will you leave me alone, in peace?
Y-Yes.
Do you promise?
Y-Yeah. I promise... I promise you!
You promised me.
Ai!
Are you okay?
Okay?
Please!
I...
Mina.
Mina, are you all right?
Why shouldn't I be?
What happened?
Do not forget your promise.
Kagome, kagome, the bird in the cage...
Red Eyes
I-It hurts!
Takeda-sensei, Morita-kun is hurt!
What is it?
Morita-kun broke a beaker.
What?
The red eyes... The red eyes...
Get him to the infirmary quickly.
Staff Room
Sensei.
Attendance Record
What's with all those wondering looks?
Don't worry about Morita. He'll be fine.
But sir...
Morita-kun's injury... Just like in that chemistry room legend.
Attendance Record
The rumor about the spirits of the fallen
haunting the chemistry room?
Do you guys seriously
believe that stuff?
Come on! Everyone in class says,
if you make eye contact with them,
they'll punish you. Right?
Morita-kun said he saw red eyes too.
That's nonsense.
We live in the scientific age, you know.
What are ghosts if not an invention
of someone's fancy?
Well then, I gotta report for duty.
But Sensei!
Geez...
Hey, where are all the boys?
They're always so late.
For real.
Even when it's the boys that slack off,
we get the shaft.
You know, we should play a trick on them when they come!
Sounds like fun.
But this room is...
It'll be fine. Don't you wanna see the boys scared out of their wits?
Okay!
Now we're cooking!
See? The atmosphere's just right.
Can't argue with that.
Preparation Room
An amazing find, isn't it?
You good?
Geez! Don't scare us like that, Kaoru!
My bad. So where should we put it?
Right in front of the entrance
should be good.
It's sure to spook the boys.
Do your worst, smiling partner.
I bet he was a handsome guy before he became a skeleton.
I don't know about that.
Enough fooling around. Let's hide!
Okay.
Ready? I'm getting the lights.
Hey, Aki, you there?
Y-Yeah. It sure is scary in here.
I hope the boys show up soon.
They're here!
Wh-What...
What is this?
C-Could it be?
Th-They're here!
Spirits of the fallen!
Make sure not to look them in the eyes!
Help!
Takeda-sensei!
Sensei!
Th-They really came
to the chemistry room!
Who did?
The spirits of the fallen!
We hid to scare the boys when they arrived, then suddenly...
Injured samurai with bright red eyes showed up!
So... you didn't look them
in the eyes, did you?
No way I'd ever look them in the eyes!
We were so scared we kept
our eyes shut all along! Right?
I see. That's good to know.
You didn't look them
in the eyes, did you?
in the eyes, did you...
Just my imagination?
Just my imagination.
Original Subtitles
Translation Check &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Flapsubs
Perevodildo
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair
Nemesis
"Coffee"