This animation work was based on experiences shared with us by the readers.
Human life is ever so fleeting.
When lingering regrets won't let some depart this world,
they're forced to wander
the Earth for years to come.
This is...
"I witnessed a wandering spirit."
School Ghosts
A first-hand account of horror.
Kagoshima Prefecture "S" Junior High School
Music room
You're still here?
It's already dark outside, you should go hurry home.
Okay...
Ah! It's that late already?
Excuse me, I got carried away.
I see you're always studying until late?
Yes. I have a test coming up.
I was at a sick leave for quite a while.
Stay out this late may worry your mother. C'mon, hurry home.
I'm cutting the lights.
Ah! Not yet!
Forgotten Notebook
Ah! I forgot my notebook.
Mourning
Please accept my sincerest condolences.
It was me who told her to hurry home.
And she forgot this notebook...
What a truly hard working,
fair young lady she was...
I-It's her!
What's the matter with the custodian?
A few months later
What's that sound?
I-Is someone still here?
T-There's no way.
It's 2 A.M. already,..
It's just the pump?
What are you doing here this late?
I-It's you!
I-Impossible!
Mister...
Help me! She's returned! Help me!
God! Buddha! Save me! Help!
S-S-Someone help me!
Where's the notebook?
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Crap!
God, Buddha... G-God, Buddha...
God save us all, God save us all...
God... Buddha... God... Buddha...
I made it through?
Give back my notebook.
N-No...
Batting Ghost
This strange phenomenon started about a month ago.
The first time it happened was when students who were going home late
from preparing for the school festival tried to take a shortcut across the campus.
Wanna get something to eat?
Sounds good.
What's wrong?
What's that?
Since then,
the school was rife with rumors,
either of someone standing still, or someone knocking a ball on the campus.
What they saw was the ghost of Nagao-sensei.
Next one's to the left!
After Nagao-sensei became the baseball team's new coach,
they had a streak of victories
and now even dared to dream about playing at Koshien.
Starting with the team itself,
everyone from fellow student to the PTA were setting their hopes high.
But then, the third batter Matsumoto-kun fell into a slump
and was scored with 30 no-hitters in a row.
But Nagao-sensei refused to change the batting order or team members,
expecting that Matsumoto-kun was going to start hitting soon.
Rumor has it, it happened two weeks before an important game.
Excuse me, Nagao-sensei,
can we talk?
What is it, Matsumoto?
I don't want to drag the rest of the team down any longer!
I'd like to retire from being the third batter.
What?
I can't hit anymore, I want to quit baseball!
Don't quit over the smallest hurdle, you dimwit!
Nagao-sensei encouraged Matsumoto-kun and took him to the batter box.
Go on, swing the bat. Swing! I said swing!
Okay.
Lower your head, tuck the chin in.
What now? Why'd you stop? Swing!
Sensei, I...
Matsumoto, toss for me and look closely to understand what you're doing wrong.
See? You can hit it, you have what it takes to be a batter.
All you need to do is swing more confidently.
Okay, keep tossing.
After about five more minutes of doing it,
Matsumoto-kun fumbled the ball.
Matsumoto! Are you okay?
It seems, the bat that Nagao-sensei swung hit Matsumoto in the back of his head.
They got an ambulance for him at once.
However, Matsumoto-kun was paralyzed from the waist down.
The faculty treated this as an incident of bullying by teacher.
The media and PTAs
unleashed a storm of criticism on Nagao-sensei's teaching methods.
And because he had a stronger than usual sense of responsibility,
a few days later,
he committed suicide by hanging himself on a branch of the sakura tree
in the far corner of the campus.
Sensei's death was a shock to everyone.
But even more shocking
was that his ghost then started silently prowling the campus every night.
As the manager of the baseball team,
I visited Matsumoto-senpai many times,
trying to persuade him that we need to pacify sensei's spirit.
Matsumoto Alcohol Store
Leave me alone already!
I don't hold a grudge against Nagao-sensei or something.
All I want is to sooner forget the whole thing.
But I really need to pacify sensei!
Like I said before, teacher's spirit comes to campus every night,
puts his hands together and hangs himself!
I don't need another reminder of what happened!
My feelings won't change, no matter how many times you ask!
I'm sure Nagao-sensei appears every night because he wants to apologize to you!
But... I don't believe in that kind of stuff!
It's nonsense. It can't be!
Then come and see for yourself whether it's real or not!
No ghost ever appeared.
Can we go already?
Just a bit longer.
Is that..?
S-Sensei...
Sensei! Nagao-sensei! Enough already!
Sensei, that's enough! It wasn't your fault!
I keep my spirits up, even in a wheelchair.
You don't have to feel guilty!
Stop this already!
Nagao-sensei! It's me, Matsumoto!
Enough is enough! In all this time, I never regretted
playing baseball with you!
So please... Stop condemning yourself!
Nagao-sensei!
S-Sensei...
Since then,
the sightings of Nagao-sensei's ceased.
But every year, when the Sakura tree blossoms,
the baseball team gathers under that tree to offer their prayers.
Cursed Summer Camp
Kanagawa Prefecture "S" Girls' High School
Summer of 1989
Here! Go ahead, pass it to me!
Nice!
Here!
Pass it to me!
Nice!
That's all for today's practice.
Captain, it's getting late, so wrap up the cooling down exercises and clean up now.
All right. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Can you turn on the light?
Sure.
What time is it?
Hm. I think it's around half past nine.
I hope mom recorded the video.
I'm beat.
Don't you think everyone is a little too excited for the first day of training camp?
That's true. I thought so too.
Phew, that was spooky.
Who turned off the light?
I bet it was just our senpai's prank. Let's head back to the dorms now.
Yeah...
It's pitch dark.
I have a baaad feeling.
C-Cut it out.
Don't talk in that tone,
you're totally creeping me out.
Geez you're a scaredy-cat.
W-What was that?
A-A cat?
I knew school was no place to come at night.
If you weren't so sluggish, we wouldn't be here!
Did you know?
The Captain and Imai-senpai saw it last year.
What? Saw what?
A ghost, obviously.
Stop! I'm not listening to any that!
What's wrong?
Did you just make that noise?
No I didn't! Are you trying to scare me again?
I'm not! I really heard something.
Let's hurry back to everyone.
Ah... Wait!
Captain, is it true you saw a ghost last year?
It's not true, is it?
I did see it.
B-But how?
A long time ago, this school was...
A hospital.
A hospital?
So, it was covered in blood, or missing a hand?
The ghost I saw was a nurse.
Ugh... I really need to go to the bathroom. Hey, Chiko...
I haven't eaten it yet...
Hey, don't fall asleep!
What is it? Don't wake me up, Kana.
I was just about to try a scrumptious cake.
Look, let's go to the bathroom.
I don't need to.
Please! Come with me. I'm too scared to go alone.
Oh geez, you're hopeless...
Wait for me. Are you still out there? You're there, aren't you?
Don't you leave without me, Chiko!
Sure, sure, waiting...
Sorry for the wait.
You may pass now, you may pass,
here on this narrow road...
Hey, cut it out! Stop singing something so gloomy.
What kind of song would you like, then?
Geez, Chiko you big jerk!
I-I couldn't help it...
D-Did you hear that?
I-I think so.
W-What was that?
It sounds like it's coming from down the corridor.
W-What is that?
A-A wheelchair.
And that's a... N-N-N-N-
N-
A nurse?!
She came!
S-She's heading this way! Let's run!
N-No way, I can't move. My legs won't move!
Seriously?
We've gotta run now, Kana!
I-I can't...
Oh geez!
W-What is going on here?
Listen! Something's wrong!
She stopped...
Get out of here!
Help us!
It hurts...
Someone help us!
It's here! Here! Here!
W-Water...
Water...
Please give me water...
Senpai! Captain! Help us!
What's going on?!
They're here! Here!
What happened to you?!
Hang in there!
Painful...
Water...
Kill me...
Please, water...
Night on a School Trip
A school trip is the event of highest magnitude in a high school student's life.
We were all very excited.
Yukari spent the trip clutching onto the karaoke mic and posing as a star.
We happily followed our scheduled events for the first, second, and third day,
and made it safely to our final stop.
Once you've found your rooms, ask Nakai-san to show you around.
Next, Suzuki and the other girls from the third group will stay in the Blue Room.
Okay!
Now then.
S-Sensei, actually...
I see. There's no other way, then?
Third group's room has been changed from Blue to the Pure Room.
It's a nice detached room.
Huh? Did you say Pure Room?
Yes, that's right.
I-I see...
Follow me, then.
Pure Room...
What a nice garden!
We're so lucky to get a detached room just for ourselves.
We're the VIP guests here!
True, true!
We can make all the noise we want!
Pure Room
Wow, that's a nice room!
Is there a problem?
N-No.
Look, you can see the ocean from here!
Wow! You're right.
What a room! You can tell it's detached.
But guys...
Doesn't it smell a bit musty in here? And that stain over there looks like a face.
What do you mean? Doesn't look like one to me.
Really? But I totally see a face there.
Hey, why don't we open the windows?
Good idea!
It won't budge.
Let me try.
Huh?
It won't open because it's nailed down here!
Why aren't we allowed to open the windows?
I wonder...
I've prepared tea, dinner will be served in the hall of the main building at 7.
Nakai-san, sorry to ask, but could you take a picture for us?
Huh? Here?
I'm not good with a camera, s-sorry.
B-But...
What was that made-up excuse?
For real.
Well, whatever. We'll use the timer. Gather up!
C'mon, hurry up! Right here!
After dinner, Yukari said she was unwell and went to sleep.
Okay, Yukari, we're going to the baths.
It's a shame, I knew you wanted to try the open-air bath.
And don't go calling Sanada-kun while we're not around, you hear?
Of course not.
I thought I'd just get some sleep.
All righty then.
I'll get the lights.
So hot...
It's hot, so hot in here...
Why is it so hot?
W-What's this?
Join us...
No!
No! No! No!
Everyone is... calling for me...
Join us...
I gotta go. Everyone is calling for me...
No! I can't open it! I mustn't!
Join us...
What are you doing, Yukari?! Stop!
I was so scared!
We explained to teacher what happened
and asked for another room.
After that, morning came without incident
and we left the ominous inn behind.
Still, it was really difficult for us to believe Yukari's story.
But when we looked at that photo, a chill went down everyone's spine.
No!
It was much later when I found out
that the cliffs below the detached building we stayed in
were famous among locals as the place where those who died at sea
would often wash up.
In the cage, in the cage,
a bird is being held
When, oh when will it come out?
In the evening of the dawn
The crane and turtle slipped,
Who is behind you now?
Hanako-san
I heard there was someone at my school named Hanako-san.
Quiet! You only practice calligraphy when it's quiet, both inside and outside.
Okay...
Flower
Finished! It came out nicely this time.
Would be even prettier with this!
Hanako
It's Hanako, right!
Hey! Cut it out!
You'll regret it!
Hey!
I'll have you all clean the bathrooms as a punishment!
Eh? No fair.
Hanako
You know, they say Hanako-san lives in this bathroom.
The girls from Class 1 saw Hanako-san here!
No way.
It's true, I heard it directly from one of them.
Sounds interesting, let's go meet Hanako-san.
B-But...
M-Meet Hanako-san? Sounds fun...
I'd rather not...
It'll be fine. Hanako-san must be feeling very blue,
spending her days all alone in this bathroom.
R-Right.
But they say you shouldn't make fun of Hanako-san.
Look at how scared you are!
But even so, we can't do the cleaning unless we go in there.
Hanako
W-Which of the doors?
The furthermost.
I-Is anyone in here?!
Doesn't seem so.
We've gotta make sure.
W-Who's going to do it?
Please, Mina. Won't you go knock on the furthermost door?
B-But...
If you don't, you're out of our friends' group.
For 5 or 6 years. Or maybe even forever!
C-C'mon, knock on it!
Hurry up! Just a couple of taps!
Ah! Wait!
Did anyone answer?
Let's stop this now.
No way! Not until we knock more confidently.
This time, call her by her name while you knock.
Why don't you do it this time, Aigo?
Huh?
Too scared, aincha?
Fine, whatever. I'll do the knocking myself.
You three, better not run away.
O-Okay...
H-Hanako-san?
Hanako-san? Hanako-san!
Hey, let's stop this...
Hanako-san!
Ah! It's here!
It won't open!
Pull harder!
No way! It's stuck!
Why... Why is this happening?
We must have angered Hanako-san...
That's right! It's Aigo's fault! We shouldn't have made fun of Hanako-san!
That's right, Aigo did it!
What are you saying? All I did was...
What's going to happen now?
H-Hanako-san is here!
Mina, what's wrong?
Was it you three who summoned me?
Mi-Mina?
Minako is possessed by Hanako-san!
Don't you treat me as a plaything.
You three called me here for no reason.
So why don't I avail myself to playing with you, as per your wish?
Please... No...
Shut up!
N-No, it hurts... Help...
You're the one who called me, you selfish girl.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry!
Why don't I teach you a fun game to play, you mortal thing?
How does that sound?
I promise we won't call you anymore, please let Aigo go!
We're sorry! We're sorry! We won't do it again! Don't kill Aigo!
Will you leave me alone, to my peace?
Y-Yes...
Do you promise?
Y-Yes... I promise... I promise you!
You promised me.
Ai!
Are you okay?
Okay?
I...
Mina.
Mina, are you feeling fine?
Why shouldn't I? What happened?
Do not forget your promise.
In the cage, in the cage,
a bird is being held...
Red Eyes
It hurts!
Takeda-sensei, Morita-kun is hurt!
What is it?
Morita-kun broke a beaker.
What?
The red eyes... The red eyes...
Hurry him to the infirmary.
Staff Room
Sensei.
What's with all those wondering looks?
Don't worry about Morita, he'll be fine.
But sir...
Morita-kun's injury... Just like in that chemistry room legend...
That rumor of the spirits of the fallen haunting the chemistry room?
Do you guys seriously believe that stuff?
Come on! Everyone in class says,
if you make eye contact with them, they'll punish you. Right?
Morita-kun said he saw red eyes too.
That's nonsense.
We live in the scientific age, you know.
What are ghosts if not an invention of someone's fancy?
Well then, I gotta report for duty.
But Sensei!
Gee...
Hey, where are all the boys? They are always so late.
For real.
Even when it's the boys who slack off, we're getting the shaft.
You know, we should hide and pull a prank on them when they come!
Sounds fun.
But this room is...
It'll be fine. Don't you wanna see the boys scared out of their wits?
Fine.
Now we're cooking!
See? The atmosphere's just right.
Can't argue here.
Preparation Room
An amazing find, isn't it?
You good?
Gee! Don't scare us like that, Kaoru!
My bad. So, where should we put it?
Right before the entrance should be good.
It'll be sure to spook the boys.
Do your worst, our smiling partner.
I bet he was a handsome guy before becoming a skeleton.
I don't know about that...
Enough fooling around. Let's hide!
Okay.
Ready? I'm getting the lights.
Hey, Aki, you there?
Y-Yeah. It sure is scary in here.
I hope the boys show up soon.
They're here!
W-What the?
What is this?
C-Could it be...?
T-They're here!
Spirits of the fallen!
Make sure not to look them in the eyes!
Help!
Takeda-sensei!
Sensei!
T-They really came to the chemistry room!
They came?
The spirits of the fallen did come!
We hid to prank the boys when they come, when suddenly...
Injured samurai with bright red eyes came!
So, you didn't look them in the eyes, did you?
No way I'd ever look them in the eyes!
We were so scared we kept our eyes shut all along! Right?
I see. That's good to know.
You didn't look them in the eyes, did you?
You didn't look them in the eyes, did you...
Just my imagination?
Just my imagination.