Our blooming apprentice bride
had to face a fully armoured warrior who attacked her out of the blue,
as she doesn't know how to tame anyone but dogs.
She's all alone, without any supporter left,
and even a luxurious and
beautiful room can't comfort her.
But now
she's in dire straits, since she doesn't know western manners at all!
What you gonna do?
Huh?
What you gonna do, High Collar Lady?
I won't weep 'til I win!
Young Lady!
Lunch is ready!
Ah, right, I forgot about it.
Oh, silly me, I need to remind myself
that she's not in this house anymore.
Making food even if Benio is at Ijuuins'...
How heedless of her.
Oh, Benio, my beloved...
Nanny, isn't there one too many plate?
Ah, yes, how silly of me.
It hurts to see, so please put it away.
No, it's a kagezen for Lady Benio.
A kagezen, huh.
"Kagezen" is a term used to define a meal made for an absent person.
Maybe I'm drinking a bit too much.
Ah, that's right.
I have to make her favourite grilled chicken.
Ma'am, Young Lady is now at Ijuuins'
and I'm certain that
she'll be eating lots and lots of delicious food.
Lord, please look after her.
What should I do?
I don't know what to do...
I don't know western manners!
Don't worry, go ahead, Lady Benio.
Easier said than done...
This evening I truly did my best!
Go ahead, eat as much as you desire to.
Well, I'm hungry, so...
But even if I wanted to...
How am I supposed to use
this small katana and this rake?
Well, as long as it's just soup, I should be alright,
this ladle should do.
Shinobu.
Hey, Shinobu.
What is it, Grandmother?
Since your fiancee is finally here,
we should choose the day in which we'll announce your engagement.
Yeah,
t-that's right.
Bingo!
Everyone is focused on chattering, so they won't look at me.
Go! This is the one!
Delicious!
Nice!
Very good!
Huh-oh...
That didn't go well...
It's not that special of a dish,
understood, Benio?
What's the issue, Ma'am?
Oh no, my ladle-
Oh, I'm so careless!
Excuse me.
Wait!
Crap...
My only means of eating!
That waiter'd better remember this...
Disrespecting food is terrifying!
Oh, did anything happen?
Is the food not good?
N-No, it's not like that!
As expected of a vassal's daughter,
all of those barbarians don't know western manners!
Come on, it's not nice to make fun of her!
Shinobu.
Benio.
Just look at how I do.
Yes!
The small katana goes on the right hand and the rake on the left one.
I got it!
This looks tasty...
What sort of hellish sound is this?
Right.
Excuse me.
Oh, darn!
So this is how you do it...
Then, let's make a toast the western way!
What went wrong?
This is such a hilarious show!
A woman that doesn't know western manners at all
should not be allowed to step into this house!
She'd better go home right away!
Well said.
Kisaragi!
Ha-ha! I won!
I'm already leading by one point!
I'm so angry!
I can't stand that old geezer!
What's that? Am I bad just because I don't know
western manners?
That idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
In the end, I didn't manage to eat anything,
so my stomach is still empty!
I'm such a fool...
How did it come to this?
If I were home right now...
Here you go, help yourself.
Bon appetit!
Grilled chicken...
Benio's favourite...
I still have to realise that Young Lady's not here anymore...
So this is Boss's favourite dish.
Yum! This rocks!
Benio... What are you doing now?
Right... Worry after worry, I'm going to lose weight.
Huh, for real?
Me too!
I'm so worried for her...
Hey, Nanny, what kind of things do they teach at marriage apprenticeship?
Let's see, in such a renowned noble family...
Cleaning, sewing,
cooking and all sorts of female duties.
They'll educate her in all aspects.
Will Boss manage to learn all of that?
Not at all.
I know, right?
I can't bear it,
thinking about Benio getting scolded is painful.
Ushi!
You're just eating in such a serious situation!
You dummy!
N-Nanny, in which direction is Ijuuin's mansion at?
It should be there.
Boss! I, the goldfish-tattooed Ushigorou, will come to rescue you
tomorrow morning!
M-Me too, hang in there, Benio!
I'm starving...
I'm sick, I'll be going home.
Who'd ever like to stay in such a place?
Who's there?
It's me!
Good evening, Benio.
Shinobu...
I brought some food. You must be hungry, right?
Here you are.
I'll place it here.
Uhm, Shinobu...
I'll be heading home!
What did you say?
U-Uhm,
I'll be heading home.
I can't keep on going like this,
I had planned to make a mess of your house
and get kicked out...
I guess that you hate me now.
Huh, so what?
It's not looking like I can do it!
S-So...
So you're turning tail and retreating?
It's not like you.
But I don't think I'll ever get used to
this atmosphere, also I don't know manners...
Shinobu...
Benio, you see...
What is it?
I think that
you could bring some fresh air in this family.
Fresh air?
Right.
Some fresh air in this old house.
Remember what I told you.
Neither my grandmother nor my father could marry of their own free will.
So I think that someone should break these customs.
And it could be you, Benio.
But, Shinobu...
In any case, giving in for so little
is not very high collar-like.
Also,
since it'll probably take you a while to sleep...
You can take this book. Read it if you'd like to.
Well, it's already late, so I'll be leaving.
Shinobu, I...
Good night.
At any rate, it's time to eat!
Delicious!
It looks like I got won over again.
As Shinobu says, giving up this easily would be frustrating.
What kind of books could he like to read?
Kant?
Hegel? Schopenhauer? Dialectics?
I don't understand a thing!
"We think, therefore we exist".
What the hell is this?
Ah, I'm getting sleepy.
Wanting your own house to be messed up...
What a weird guy.
Wake up! Wake up!
What-what-what?
W-W-W-W-Wha!?
Is there a fire?
It's time to wake up.
To wake up?
But it's only four.
Indeed.
It's the habit in our residence.
I have to wake up this early...
Only postmen and market workers do this.
From today on, you'll be learning wife duties.
If you want to become a good wife,
you'll need to learn all the humblest duties
for your future husband!
Hurry up, get ready!
Let's start by cleaning the main hall.
These two girl will be helping me, right?
That's right.
Oh,
so you're kind sometimes.
I don't know much,
so excuse me in advance.
Go! Don't hold back!
Yes, ma'am!
What are you doing?
Your assistance ends here!
Yes.
Ah...
Darn, I should've expected something like this.
I'll see if this yakuza wannabe will still wants to act up after I teach her.
Be it cooking or sewing, I, Fujieda Ranmaru, can do all the domestic duties,
and I'll help Benio with all of them!
Come on, let's go!
Get outta my way! Go-go-go-go-go!
Hey, Ushi, why did you stop?
Ask it to these dudes!
Now start cleaning!
I'm afraid I'm not cut out for these things.
Benio!
Ugh, I lost my lead.
And now, cooking!
Do I have to peel all of these?
Of course.
Ugh,
she really hates me.
Ushi, don't you understand what we came here for?
I-If you want to complain, do it to these dogs!
Phew.
I'm done!
Let me see.
Should these be potatoes!?
Sure, any complaint?
Be patient, be patient...
Shall I wash these dishes next?
I can't let her make any more disasters!
Stop!
Uh?
Already?
Enough with the kitchen, go sewing now!
I'm even worse at that!
First of all, sew a yukata.
If it's just a yukata, it's all a-ok!
Here, I'm done.
Should this be a yukata?
Keep calm, keep calm...
Oh, this is bad,
I forgot the iron on!
Oh no!
I completely ruined the cloth.
Whose is this?
M-I-N-E!
Oh,
I'm so sorry!
It's my fault I lost three points!
Now you saw why I failed all of my domestic classes.
Oh, I should head to school now.
Kisaragi, my breakfast.
Come here.
In the kitchen?
Women and children eat in the kitchen by Satsuma traditions.
Ack!
I can't stand this chauvinism!
One-point lead!
I'm late!
Have a nice day.
Two-point lead.
If I arrive late again, they'll kick me out in the hallway!
Ushigorou! Ushigorou!
Boss!
Benio!
Why are you so slow?
I don't know what to do with those dogs!
Oh, you two,
did you want to protect me?
Ah, Benio, school is more important than that!
Oh, right.
Get out of my way! Let's go-go-go-go-go!
It's no good, the bell has just rung.
Hey, stop, stop!
I'll be late if I enter normally.
Alright, understood.
Then, I'll see you later, Ushigorou!
Take care, Boss!
Come on, hurry up!
I got it!
Hop!
Aaah!
I saw that...
Our High Collar Lady
is on her path to become a good wife,
but she's still tomboyish
and her way to go is truly, truly long.
Our apprentice Benio is getting scolded over and over
and Benio is struggling,
and now her heart has started beating for Shinobu...
next time on Here Comes Smart-san:
The first palpitation
don't miss it!