A new era begins,
our High Collar Lady is determined to fight for freedom,
and while she was on a mission to destroy that old mansion,
the enemy line's defence was firm,
the commander didn't withdraw
and training after training,
Benio naturally got fed up of it.
While Shinobu's kindness made her heart race,
after her bitter enemy insulted her,
she lost control once and far all, and now she's about to fight him
and show him her tomboyish combat style!
Episode 10
Gulp down the medicine of love
Oh,
he doesn't look in a good spot.
How did this little girl do it?
She eluded my attack.
However, my spear is way better than her bamboo sword, I can't lose!
I need to go all in,
and not treat her as a woman.
If he strikes a blow... I might die.
Benio...
They're done.
What was that?
Lord!
Hang in there!
Just 10 more centimeters
and my life would have been no more!
It hurts!
You monster!
Can't you be a little gentler, huh?
It's because you move too much, I can't apply the patches.
Just stay still for a second.
I'm good!
No, you're not.
It's nice to take care of you once in a while!
Oh, for God's sake...
Getting defeated by that young girl like that...
It kind of reminds me of something...
What is it?
That...
goes back a long, long time ago.
Shinobu's father, Soichirou, was still a child.
Well done! You're strong, Soichirou!
And thirty years after that,
he abandoned Shinobu and went abroad.
Only to never come back...
That Benio's look...
it's the same as Soichirou's.
Oh...
That girl's really something!
Dear!
Ah, shut up! Get out!
Jeez,
I want to be left alone!
Heh,
you got shy.
Outta my way, go-go-go-go-go!
I'm in a hurry!
Hey, Ranmaru!
Come here, Ranmaru!
What happened?
Ushi!
That guy's really a weirdo.
I know, right? He always goes crazy if the neighbouring girl is involved.
Yo, Nanny, big news, big news, big news!
Oh, Ushi,
you look enthusiastic,
did you find a 200 yen coin?
Even better! I'd be richer than the God of commerce!
Let's see...
One, two, three!
Ushi!
Did anything happen to Benio?
Oh, Ranmaru,
What happened to Lady Benio?
Nanny, you need to prepare a grand meal!
Eek!
Hey, Ushi, tell me the good news!
After many things happened,
Boss will soon come back home!
Really!? I didn't expect it!
I know, right!
She hit that stubborn geezer with her sword
and he floored him! You should've seen that!
That's amazing!
Hooray, Benio!
Calm down, you two!
Then Lady Benio will be surely expelled.
Of course, to cap it all!
Did someone call me?
We need to give her a warm welcome.
I'm so happy, aren't you too?
Me too! Nanny, we need to have a grand dinner.
How foolish of her to break such a great engagement,
what a waste!
I'm so frustrated!
Oh, it's you, Benio.
Uhm, I need to tell you something.
I see... What is it?
So... How is Count doing now?
Ohh, so it was about this.
Yes!
I am really sorry for acting recklessly!
It's not that big of a deal.
He's always been in good health,
so please, don't worry about it.
But...
Rather than that, Benio, what is that?
After all, I did such a thing to Count...
My, Benio,
don't be so worried.
If anything, he was pleasantly surprised by you.
He was surprised?
Yes, that's right!
You're kidding me...
He likes strong-arm tactics,
to him, that's way better than a simple medicine.
That is true.
However, because of his stubbornness,
he'll never openly admit it.
Benio, you're part of our family,
don't forget it, okay?
Then,
let's go back to your room.
What is wrong with my heartbeat?
Maybe it's something about my health.
Is it, though?
It's you again, hoyden.
What an eyesore.
My heartbeat is completely different now!
I'll be going, Benio.
Boss Benio Greeting Party
Sorry for the hinderance, Lady Benio.
Will I have to fight her too?
Is this for the next schedule?
It's not that, there's a guest.
To see me?
Yes.
I wonder who that guest could be.
Come on, come on.
Hey, hey, it's me!
Humph, you two will never change.
But you don't have to worry anymore,
I won't return to this house ever again, after all!
Oh,
so it was you, Ushigorou.
Aye.
Hey, don't just stand there, come in!
These two damn dogs won't let me in!
I-I understood, I talked too much.
Tenmaru, Chimaru, this is my dear henchman,
got it?
Jeez, how did you learn to do it, Boss?
I didn't do anything, they just grew fond of me.
Then let's hurry home before all the family members
can grow fond of you.
I came here just to take you home!
Oh...
Come on, hop in.
You must know that Nanny made grilled chicken
and even Ranmaru put his heart
into making roasted potatoes!
I'm not coming home, though.
How can it be, you hit that old man on the head!
It seems like that made him like me more.
I can't believe it...
But they still won't kick me out.
Then, even that stubborn geezer
got won over by Boss.
At this rate, they'll all become her henchmen.
I can't let it happen! I can't be replaced!
Then, let's go home, Boss!
I'm sorry, but my mission isn't complete yet.
What mission?
I have to make a mess of this mansion!
That's one hell of an idea! I'll join too!
I'll always be...
by your side...
Sorry, sorry.
Alright, scratch that.
So, are you sure won't come home?
Grilled chicken and many delicious things are waiting for you!
I am weak to food, I know...
I want to eat them!
Now you're talking!
You can eat all of them.
Gah!
But I'll definitely eat them when I'll come home.
So you're saying that I'll have to meet these dudes again?
Shinobu, oh you,
are you satisfied with just this woman?
What a shame.
Real men can pull many women.
This is an insult!
I can't believe that he came to like me!
Grandfather...
You see, men from the Meiji era were admirable.
Very, very admirable.
With their strength, they could afford to have multiple lovers.
Should I add some milk?
This is outrageous! You monster!
My bad!
I apologise on behalf of Japanese women!
What did you say?
You...
Grandfather, times have changed.
Benio, you can leave.
How long have I been living here?
I thought I'd go away in a snap,
but it's taking so long.
Father, are you okay?
Nanny...
She always gets nervous when it rains for long.
take care, okay?
Ranmaru, what are you doing?
Benio!
You can't get married yet! Come back!
I, too, want to come back home.
What is this sound?
What happened? It's pretty noisy.
Lady Benio, sorry for the loud noise.
Ah, don't mind me, did anything happen?
Yes...
Because of this rain, his neuralgia is worsening
and it doesn't look like it's going to get better.
Didn't you call the doctor?
Of course I tried to call him,
but unfortunately, he is away.
Neuralgia, huh.
Nanny went through it too, it's a though illness.
Then, excuse me.
Ah, wait.
What is it?
Do you have any geraniums?
Huh?
The Chinese medicine ones?
Yes, after that...
swertias, chameleon plants,
plantagos, aractylodes, ginseng,
red spider lilies,
et cetera.
Then, could you find them and bring them to me?
Understood.
Way to go!
Time to make my medicine!
Here it is!
Hanamura's special medicine!
The smell is so strong that it makes those dogs run away.
Whatever, it's not like I'll drink it myself.
Ugh!
Count.
What do you want?
I told that nobody must enter here.
This is a medicine for your neuralgia.
I don't need it!
Shinobu
Just seeing your face is painful enough.
Go away, go away.
But my nanny recovered thanks to this,
try drinking it.
What is that?
It's a Chinese herbal medicine.
I don't need such an unscientific thing!
My wife only buys reliable medicines from Germany!
This works better on Japanese people.
Drink it and see.
What is this stench?
It makes me dizzy, I don't need it.
Not brave enough?
Brave, you say?
If you're a real man as you say,
this medicine is nothing special, right?
G-Give it to me!
What was this?
As expected!
Shut up,
what is this lizard-like thing?
It's a charred newt.
It's very effective!
A-A newt...
A newt!?
Oh, Count, you're already asleep.
Oh, you're visiting him.
Yes.
Then I'll look after him for a while,
you can go rest, Lady Benio.
Don't worry, I'll do it by myself, you can go to sleep.
Leave this to me.
No, don't mind!
Are you awake, Count?
You were here all along.
How are you feeling now?
It looks like it got better.
As I thought! Amazing!
Count...
How shameful!
I got healed by the daughter of a vassal!
You see, Count,
that might true, but that goes way before the Meiji Restoration.
I know that much myself,
but I still despise vassals as a whole!
Moreover, my wife...
She did what?
Before marrying me, she was in love with a vassal.
Who should be my grandfather, right?
Correct.
And even after she married me,
she still won't forget him no matter what.
Count...
I was aware that I wasn't as handsome,
so I tried to keep calm,
but she never stopped thinking about her first love
and could never forget him.
Dear!
She heard it!
That is not true!
You!
You heard that.
How shameful,
did you always think I was like that?
N-No, it's not...
And to think that I even had a son with you...
how shameful, how shameful.
That story is just a beautiful memory of the past,
but it's not like I've been dwelling in the past.
Ever since I married you, you've always been my priority.
Then, you...
But you just kept on working and treating me as a bother,
even though I...
love you so much...
Dear, what do you think about me?
S-Shut up!
I'll go to sleep!
Dear...
He has always loved her,
that's why he hates vassals so much.
I had a bad impression,
but in reality, he's a good person.
If only I could find someone who loved me that way...
it'd be lovely, lovely!
Uh, Shinobu?
What an absurd guy...
He'd even marry without loving,
as he said, right?
So give him to me!
Whaddya want?
I won't give you anything!
Give him to me!
Wait!
A lady's heart changes like wind in a storm,
and there's nothing wrong with a High Collar Lady desiring love in the Taishou Era.
But where is her bluebird?
To officialise the engagement,
an outdoor celebration is being held.
But hold on,
our High Collar Lady doesn't know high-class manners
and many troubles await!
On top of it, all of a sudden,
a seductive maiden appeared.
next time on Here Comes Smart-san:
Welcome to the party of grief,
don't miss it!