Everybody makes some mistakes,
but if you break a precious plate of all things, you just have to die!
The Count got madly furious
to the point Benio couldn't help but take all remaining plates and tear them apart!
this just added fuel to the fire and the stubborn Count stated that Benio had to die as well!
Benio can only rely on Shinobu, who is, however, staying still and dumbfounded.
Benio can't back out anymore and she blames Shinobu for that.
Farewell, failed bride
Come on, en garde!
Ma'am!
Benio!
Ah, stop!
What is it?
Count, please wait a minute.
Is she trying to sneak off?
No need to worry, Tenmaru, Chimaru.
Benio must have a plan on her mind.
What!?
B-Benio!
Sorry for the wait, Count.
Then, you can continue.
Get ready.
Then, begone!
B-Benio is going to die!
Accept your fate!
Forgive me for what awaits you.
M-Ma'am, we need to stop them right now!
No.
Huh!? Are you letting Benio die?
Do you think he'd really do it?
He is waiting for someone to stop him.
I-I'll kill you!
No point in stopping me, so nobody dare stop me!
Alright, it's getting too awkward now,
let's go help.
Go, Tenmaru, Chimaru!
Ugh, now these dogs, to make it worse!
I'll split you open too!
In reality, he is relieved by this intrusion!
Grandfather, it's enough.
Shinobu? This is not your time to be here.
You don't need to be so stubborn.
Well, it looks like this is settled.
Huh!?
This ends with...
your loss.
My precious plates of a lifetime...
Benio, you've already done a lot.
Hey, you! Don't just shut up and watch! Why couldn't you do something earlier?
I was so frightened, you know!?
But despite that, you didn't lift a finger!
Well, since nobody cares about me, I'll just go home!
Really?
Benio...
I don't belong to this house anymore.
If I go away, you'll be able to marry with the one you really like, right?
Benio!
That's not right, please listen to me.
Don't stop her, Shinobu!
Goodbye, Shinobu!
Wait, Benio!
Benio...
Here, here they come!
Then, let's get going, Ushigorou!
Good job!
There, go ahead.
Benio, wait just a minute!
Don't stop me, it'd be pointless!
Sure, I won't.
You forgot this, Benio.
Oh, my mourning dress.
That's right.
From now on, you'll be part of the Ijuuin family.
In case something happens to him, you'll have to wear this.
- Benio...
- Benio!
Boss?
Benio?
Grandmother- no, Countess Ijuuin,
I'm resentful towards you.
After all, you,
Countess Ijuuin, once were in love with my grandfather
and since you hoped that it would flourish someday,
I, a totally naive girl, have to go through this.
On top of it,
I even had to think about possible tragedies
and my Father made me bring this mourning dress.
So I... I...
had to go through painful times.
please don't make this happen ever again.
Have you ever thought about
how much this could hurt a naive girl like me?
Countess Ijuuin.
Benio, please stop calling me Countess Ijuuin,
please call me
Don't say anything.
Goodbye, Countess!
Benio!
Thanks for waiting, then, let's go.
Anytime!
Tenmaru, Chimaru,
you're the only ones who are sad about me leaving this house.
In this house animals are better than people, eh?
That's right.
Tenmaru, Chimaru, goodbye.
No, don't follow me.
Don't come. This is an order, got it?
There we go! Go-go-go-go-go!
Goodbye, Tenmaru, Chimaru!
Shinobu, aren't you going to stop me?
Please understand, Tenmaru, Chimaru.
I'm sure that time will solve everything.
Hyono! Hyono!
Hyono District
Boss, today's such a lovely day!
We gotta have a toast!
Oh, Shinobu...
Hey, you, don't make Benio drink any alcohol!
You know what'd happen!
Come on, it's such a nice day!
Then let's have some anmitsu.
Anmitsu!?
Ranmaru, how girly can you be?
Ah, you don't understand.
While my body is a boy's, my mind is a traditional woman's.
You're weird...
I have a body and a mind too, you know?
Here she is again!
Famous bean soup
Renowned onigiri
Famous Renowned
No matter how much I eat this, I'm not a fan...
Boss, something wrong with your stomach?
No, not really.
I got it! As I thought, we gotta drink!
Let's spice it up, shall we, Boss?
It hurts!
Ushi, don't make her think strange things!
After all, it's true that in these tough times
I'm not in the mood for anmitsu.
I know, right?
Cut it out!
Miss, they make delicious anmitsu here!
Miss, hurry up!
Oh...
Oh no, this is bad!
Ah, Ushi...
Oh, this is of good omen.
Alright.
Oh dear Lord, please listen to me.
Ma'am, what good things are going to happen today?
Congratulations, Miss Kichiji.
Why congratulations?
It's finally your time to shine. Shinobu will surely be yours.
Then, excuse me.
H-Hey!
Ushi, I leave the bill to you!
Benio!
What in the world is happening?
What's wrong? The betrothal just backfired.
What did you say...!?
I'll put the bill here.
Thank you very much!
Excuse me, I'll borrow your phone.
Sure.
Excuse me.
In 1904, the number of telephone subscribers exceeded 180,000
and the number of telephones continued to increase.
Hello, am I speaking to the Ijuuin home?
In 1925, after the Great Kanto Earthquake, sales exceeded 870,000 units.
Hello, I am Ijuuin...
Oh, it's you.
Shinobu, did you really break your engagement with Benio?
How do you know that?
I happened to stumble across Benio,
are you okay with letting go of her?
Benio misunderstood something about you.
Then, all the more so!
Benio burst crying
and she said that you could be mine.
A noble and a worthless geisha like me togeher,
I'm fully aware that it could never happen.
No matter the situation,
it's not fair to make such a good girl cry.
I can't explain now,
however, you'll definitely understand.
Hold on!
You did what?!
Yes, I broke the engagement, rejoice!
I thought that there'd be good omen...
Hey, bring me some tea!
Tea!
Hey! I told you to bring me some tea!
What's wrong with you and those long faces?
You are free to complain!
Isn't it obvious to kick out a girl like that?
After all, she's never met my father!
And she destroyed all of my precious plates!
You three! If you have anything to say, tell me!
Kisaragi, you surely feel me, right?.
That unreasonable girl drove you mad all the time, didn't she?
Yes, you are correct.
I know, right? You are free to say everything you think about her.
Yes, I've been working in this mansion for many years,
but I had never met anyone like her.
Well said!
So, what did she do?
She's the only one who didn't give in to your obstinacy!
I went through some difficulties myself,
but we'll never meet anyone quite like her.
Yes, that's true.
Ever since Benio came here, I thought that things would change...
I've always taken care of Young Master
and I wondered whether he'd have a son with Benio,
so that I could continue my job,
raise the child and sing him lullabies...
I thought about this so happily.
Benio's son would be our great-grandchild!
Great-grandchild, eh?
But now you'll never be able to meet him!
Yes, this is also Count's fault!
Silence! It's not like I killed her or anything!
Shinobu!
Yes?
What the hell are you waiting for?
Isn't Benio your fiancée?
Then go get her!
L-Lord!
Then...
I knew you'd say this,
but since you usually don't get influenced by others' opinions,
I didn't interfere.
I've been waiting for you to say those words.
I dispatch.
Go!
Even you changed, Dear, didn't you?
Benio made you reflect.
The Meiji Era was a long time ago.
Refill!
Cut it out, it's already the fifth one!
Why bother, Nanny?
You know, I couldn't eat this delicious grilled chicken there!
This is not the time to put on airs, for God's sake!
What is your father going to say about this?
Getting kicked out before marrying...
I feel so bad for your mother...
Oh well, I can't say that I didn't expect this.
What's wrong? After all that effort to go back home,
at least show some nostalgia.
There must be something you want to talk me about.
Ah...
Shinobu...
We won't meet anymore...
You see, I happen to be in love with Young Master.
Enough, I don't care about that womaniser anymore!
Could it be Shinobu!?
I am home.
What a bummer, it's just dad.
What? Benio has?
Yes, that's true.
Benio.
Oh! Welcome home, father!
Oh, it's not long since I last saw you, but you got fatter!
Oh, really?
I slimmed down!
Father...
Benio, follow me.
Is it true that you got kicked out?
That's not true, it's a misunderstanding, father.
What, so it wasn't because you got kicked out?
I see. Glad, so glad to hear.
Yes, you can relax, I wasn't kicked out, I left on my own.
I see, I see.
What?!
This is just the same thing, you dumbass!
B-But, you don't know the whole story!
It was a haunted house, after all!
What are you saying? A Count lives there, it can't be so bad!
Don't say such silly things!
No, Mr. Hanamura, there was a crazy geezer there.
A-Are you that famous girly guy?
Ah,
it's just me!
Oh, you're Ranmaru?
Yes, it's been a while, Mr. Hanamura.
What's that disgraceful effete look on a boy?
You mean that I'm beautiful?
Hey hey hey, back off, you're annoying!
I'll have nightmares tonight.
After all, I had to do it to be close to Benio.
Close?
Yes, we even slept in the same room.
I was so glad...
What now?
Benio!!! What is this indecent behaviour!?
Y-You misunderstood, Father!
What did I misunderstand?
Misunderstandings, misunderstandings...
Here we go, I stacked these!
Whaddja say!?
Father, you don't understand...
I've understood enough.
Benio.
Do you understand why I have this dagger here?
After finally parting ways with the stubborn count,
Benio still can't breathe a sigh of relief.
There seems to be one more stubborn man in her own house!
While Benio left the Ijuuin mansion to go back home,
her stubborn father can't accept it.
With no choice left, she runs away to wander about unknown places,
however, even alcohol can't relieve her from her stress,
our youthful and naive High Collar Lady.
Next time in Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Petals of a wandering flower
Don't miss it!