Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
Here, here, here
Here, here, here she is, the High Collar lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Benio came back to her small, yet lively house,
after a lot of effort,
only to confront her old-fashioned father
and be kicked out once again.
Thus, she had to leave right away.
Shinobu went to look for Benio
but she couldn't find her for a small time difference,
as she's already wandering far away.
Benio kept drink and drinking and before long
her violent drunken side surfaced,
but she chose a dangerous opponent:
none other than Shinobu's direct superior!
Episode 18
Incurring grudge is dangerous
Here's a fight! A fight!
A woman's riotous!
A woman is riotous? Could it be Benio!?
Excuse me, please let me see.
Aren't you the one who bumped me first!?
Shut up!
You dare to lay your hands on me?!
You saw it, right?
Mr. Officer, be my witness!
He's the one who laid his hands first!
You whore! Don't you dare oppose me!
Oh, really?
Make way! Make way!
What's going on? Huh?
Those two are picking a fight!
This officer saw it all, he can testify.
Damn you...
Then you four will come to the police station.
I can't.
I'm in a hurry, you know.
Please don't be so cold, I need you as a witness!
Benio...
Where are you now?
What are you doing?
Now you've got me real mad...
What's with you? You're the one who bumped me first, am I wrong!?
I'm sorry, she got into a bit of a drunken frenzy.
Shut up!
I ain't got no drunken frenzy!
I ain't drunk at all-
I...
You lowlife, you think you can fool me?
Shinagawa Police Station
Can't you understand? I've already told you enough.
At any rate, you see, I'm in a hurry.
You'll have to excuse me now.
Listen up though, why would someone in a hurry get off their horse?
Did you have any reason to watch the fight!? Tell me!
You see, I, uhm...
I still want to ask you something
so stay here for another while, understood?
You're talking with the 1st Division in the Imperial Army,
have some respect!
Come on, don't be so agitated.
Here. Wipe your face with this.
Lieutenant, that is a dust cloth!
What?
Apologise for making a fool of me!
Shouldn't you apologise instead?
I don't know if it's the 1st Division or whatever,
but you still troubled other people.
Can't you drink silently!?
I am silent, though.
You should apologise for being so domineering!
You lowly brat, you're speaking to an imperial soldier!
Here they go again with this soldier thing.
Even my dad...
Even Shinobu!
Even Shinobu. Shinobu is a soldier, too.
Shinobu, you idiot! Idiot!
Benio, are you a maudlin drinker?
What a vulgar woman!
Right.
She may be a woman, but she affronted the Imperial Army,
so I guess she's ready for a fight!
Obviously! I'm ready and steady!
Benio! Shh! Shh!
I don't care at all,
even if it's one versus five!
They multiplied in the blink of an eye...
How cowardly! You're too many!
Oh no!
No matter how strong Boss is...
she's drunk and she's against five people!
Moreover, there's no way she could beat a professional soldier!
I gotta get in touch with Shinobu!
Where are you going, Ushi? No-no.
You mustn't go away!
Look, Ranmaru, if you're a real man and you're in love with Boss,
defend her with all you've got!
Gain some time!
Even if you say that- hey, wait!
I'm just a pretty boy,
I have no money nor power.
Hey-hey, Ushi! C'mon, Ushi!
My...
Sounds fun. Sounds fun!
Don't steal it!
I can't go through this if I'm sober!
I know, right?
Gimme, Ranmaru.
Hey, refill!
Refill!
Whoops-
Ouch!
Get rid of her!
Alrighty then, bring it on!
C'mon!
Bitch, you think you can get away with this just 'cause you're a woman!?
Let's go!
My, I didn't mean to.
I've got a drunken frenzy too!
Way to go, Ranmaru!
So I don't have to worry about it.
Take this!
Now it's your turn!
Don't hurt me!
Benio...
Stay behind me, Ranmaru.
Huh, you've got guts despite being a woman.
You can't escape now!
Sorry for troubling you for so long.
Goodbye.
Go!
Benio!
Where...
Where is she?
A fight here! A fight!
Hey! A fight here! Come witness it!
Wanna fight?
Alright! Bring it on!
You bastard!
Still somebody else.
Why do I always think of Benio when I hear about fights?
It's a bad habit of mine. I need to fix it.
We're surreounded! What can we do, Benio?
Hey! It's just a girl!
Come on, attack her!
Benio!!
Take this!
Yay! I'm seeing stars! So happy!
Uh, what's wrong?
Take this! And this! And this! And this!
Well done, mate!
Why did it go like this?
Who's going to pay for this?
50.000 yen for the room divider!
Even more for that barrel and those bottles.
Hey, it's just me, it's Ushigorou!
Hey, don't ya understand?
Boss is in big trouble!
Why can't ya understand?
Please let me go!
I beg you!
Ya'll never understand, won't ya...
That call... has Lady Benio perhaps come back?
We have to welcome her warmly!
Let's check out!
Oh, I hope so!
My dear, you're very fast!
Shut up, I have to open the door!
Hey, how rude! How dare you get ahead of me?
Opening the door is my job, after all!
Benio.
Benio!
Benio, is that you?
Benio, where are you?
Benio!
Hey, hey! Why are ya so worked up?
I'm at Boss's service!
It's Boss, don't you understand?
B-O-S-S!
I've got an idea!
I'll make you remember her smell.
So...
This one.
Oh, pardon, this is Ranmaru's loincloth, isn't it!
Sorry for my mistake.
Here it is, it's this one, this one!
So? Got it?
The Boss is my priority!
I gotta let Shinobu know 'bout this!
It's serious!
Alright? Then let me go!
Understood?
If I don't do anything, I'll feel restless.
I shouldn't say this,
but this mansion is so tidy without her.
It's bad, it's bad, it's bad!
That noise...
I'm so fed up with this!
Hey, where's Benio?
Yeah, yeah,
She's surrounded by five soldiers, where's Shinobu? Please contact him!
Shinobu is currently looking for Benio.
Darn it!
It's time, it's time!
It's a fight!
I might be old, but I'm still a Satsuma samurai!
I have to do this to protect our family betrothal!
Bring me my spear and my horse!
Alright! I'm ready to go!
Dear!
At this rate, your back will strain again!
It's a fight. Don't stop me!
I must go!
My dear!
Get off me! I gotta go!
No, don't go!
Aaah!
Then, let's go!
Let's do this!
I got a little carried away...
This old man doesn't seem very reliable, huh...
Ladies and gentlemen, we're in for a ride.
Then I'm counting on you, Ushigorou!
I have to win this fight!
Good gracious, what's with fighting all of a sudden?
He must be nostalgic for the old times.
We have to hurry up, Ushigorou!
Benio, hang in there,
I'll come and save you!
Ushigorou, go!
Hip, hip, hooray!
My dear!
Lord, are you feeling well!?
You idiot! Hey, wait!
I'll chase you!
You! Wait!
Wait, Ushigorou!
When did he get off the rickshaw?
Slam!
Customers, please stop!
Take this!
Why the hell are you so slow?
How can it be that five soldiers cannot win against a single girl?
You cowards!
Such a selfish thing to say.
He's only been watching.
I'm worn out...
Naturally, facing five people at once is unfair.
They've only used one fifth of my energy.
Go on the right, I'll go on the left.
This is the one.
Do it! Do it now!
Take this!
Here I go!
I got you.
What are you doing? You monster!
Isn't it obvious? We'll destroy you!
Benio, it's dangerous!
What are you doing to Benio!?
Get off me!
Ranmaru...
What is it?
Boss!
Benio! Are you safe?
Count!
Relax,
Now that this old man is here, I can't let him lay a finger on my precious niece-in-law.
Have you got it yet?
Count, what's wrong?
Some back strain.
What's wrong with this worn-out old man?
What...
I might be old, but I still have a lot of experience!
Get ready to die!
Are you alright?
This old man is out of his mind.
I'll go!
I'll go too!
Me too!
I'm done!
I've aged a bit,
but I'm the head of the Ijuuin family!
I'll teach you a lesson!
What? Ijuuin?
Benio, where are you?
Ranmaru and Ushigorou are with her, probably.
A fight here! A fight!
Another one?
Hold on,
did you say 'Ijuuin' right now?
Yes, so what? Are you scared?
That's Ushigorou's rickshaw!
Hold up, hold up,
If you're an Ijuuin, I cannot forgive you.
If you're scared, you'd better give up right now.
Count, don't hold back!
Grandfather, Benio!
Shinobu!
Shinobu?
What the hell are you doing, Grandfather?
Here, of all places..
Moreover, dressed like that...
Ranmaru, are you hurt?
Ranmaru...
I might be a coward, but I was desperate.
If you really want to marry Bennio,
you need to always look after her.
If you can't do that,
I will never leave Benio to you!
Ranmaru, now's not the time for that...
Did I hear somebody call Ranmaru?
I might be wrong.
Hey, hey, hey, Ranmaru, come here.
I need to look after your wounds.
Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
Yes!
What's wrong with you?
Shinobu, how can you bow to that awful man?
That's right! It doesn't matter that he's an officer!
There's no need to pay respects to this guy!
Grandfather, Benio, the person you've been fighting
happens to be my superior.
He's the Lieutenant Innen from the Headquarters.
Oh, I see,
even a  dude like this can become Lieutenant.
I don't think that he's worthy of his role.
Sublieutenant Ijuuin, are these peasants acquaintances of yours?
Ah, this woman is
my fiancee.
In other words, Commander Hanamura's daughter.
Yes.
Getting married with this vulgar and unfeminine woman...
You'd better think it through, got it!?
You're the one who brought five guys to deal with a girl,
you're a disgrace for all men!
By the way, Lieutenant and everyone else, what in the world were you doing?
You have many bruises.
It's nothing!
I bet, how could an imperial soldier of all people
could be beaten up by a woman alone...
It's natural. Rather than that,
if you're an imperial soldier too,
you'd better educate your fiancee properly!
Huh?
How outrageous! L-Let's leave.
Ho-ho, leaving already?
I don't want to see this guy anymore.
Despite being a soldier, he's weak and he has long hair,
I never had a good feeling about him.
I'll teach you a lesson.
Lieutenant Innen is truly furious!
Things can get terrible when he has that expression.
So scary!
Hooray,
the enemy has retreated,
we won!
It's a victory, but too soon to celebrate,
as Lieutenant Innen wants a revenge at all costs.
Remember this emblem, I'll teach you a lesson!
Our high collar lady made an enemy of the Imperial Army.
Incurring grudge
is dangerous!
Right after winning against the soldiers,
our high collar lady gets to rest on Shinobu's back,
she'll have sweet, sweet dreams!
Thanks to this, the familiar situation has got back to normal.
However, behind the scenes the Lieutenant Innen is plotting something...
Next time in Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
"Fleeting Happiness"
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra