Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Anywhere our High Collar Lady goes, she gets herself in a tangle.
Even after hearing Shinobu's tearful story,
the fact he showed what seems
to be grandmother complex
only made her decision firmer.
Moreover, in order to support
Tamaki's one-sided love,
Benio decided to make a farce out of her marriage apprenticeship to break her betrothal.
Who would the goddess of fortune smile to?
Episode 6:
A Fleeting Wedding March.
Howdy there!
Are you Shinobu's nanny?
That's Benio for you.
How rude!
Oh-oh? Your face's pale blue.
What's wrong? Hey, what's wrong?
Young Lady, that look...
What is the big fuss?
I dolled myself up to celebrate
an unreasonably demanding occasion of this kind.
We, as nobles, are taught
to keep composure at all times...
Oh?
Really?
Benio, we need to talk.
Please follow me.
Sure!
What could it be?
Mrs. Kisaragi, we humbly beg you to forgive us!
It must have been tough to raise her.
Yes.
Whatcha squeaking about?
Here we go! Go-go-go-go-go!
Get outta my way!
Hey you, whaddya think ya are,
stopping in the middle of the entryway!
Oh well, oh well, if it's a bother,
feel free to make a detour.
Say what?
It looks like ya don't know
who the hell ya talkin' to!
Listen out!
I am Boss Benio's top henchman,
the one and only Ushigorou!
As my duty is to drive Lady Benio and Young Master to places.
Lady Benio... and Young Master... that means...!
Sublieutenant Ijuuin?
It can't be!
It can indeed be.
Boss is in danger of overthrow!!
Benio.
Oh come on, Father,
you don't need to be this formal!
This...
is the only promise that I had made
to your mother before she passed away.
Mother?
A white mourning dress...
It symbolizes the vow that a woman makes
not to marry a second time ever.
But why are you showing me this
all of a sudden, Father?
Your mother didn't need to wear this dress,
but you're going to marry a soldier,
so, if something tragic happens,
you'll have to do it.
I won't get married again...
But why?
Isn't it obvious?
Can't you guess by yourself?
But...
Hey you!!
Don't tell me if Shinobu died
you would start a new life with another man!
Father, I haven't even got married yet
and you're already talking about
widowhood and such!
You see,
very soon you'll become a member
of the Ijuuin family, so you will seldom visit here.
Father, you see...
About Shinobu...
W-Wait!
Benio, take care of yourself.
Father?
Ugh!
This is damning!
You're still clinging to the pathway like a tick!
Take this! Just scram!
W-What are you doing?
This is a luxurious foreign car! Salt?!
What am I doing? Isn't it obvious? You're trying to kidnap my Boss!
Me? Kidnap? How dare you!
What are you blabbering about?!
Uh, you've got the guts, you shrimp. Wanna fight?
If you have any complaint,
I, Ushigorou, am ready to retaliate!
Salty...
As expected.
What do you think you can accomplish
against my Boss?
Taste that snow!
It didn't take you long to give up.
Exhaust gas, I didn't predict this!
I'll just end up married if I don't do anything,
but I don't want to...
Everyone begs me to do it...
Benio...
Oh,
Ranmaru, what are you doing there?
Benio, so, after all...
After all, you're getting married, right?
Ranmaru...
It's unfair! It's so unfair!!
Come on, dummy!
I won't let myself get married that easily!
I'll be back home in no time!
Really, Benio?
I can guarantee you they'll kick me out right away.
Thank God, Benio!
I-I...
Boss! Boss!
Huh?
Ushigorou?
What happened all of a sudden?
Boss...
Oh, come on, Ushi!
Boss, what's that look for...
Starting a call girl biz?
Call girl biz?!
Excuse me!?
Watch your mouth.
Benio...
Ranmaru, you don't need to worry that much.
It's just apprenticeship.
After being evicted, I'll go home very soon.
Really?
Thank God!
Hey, Benio,
if everything goes well, after being back home,
you could be my wife.
What, Ranmaru?
Ah... ouch, ow-ow-ow...
Until then, I can cook your favourite grilled chicken,
all kind of dishes, I'll be a top-notch chef!
Man, this conversation's going all over the place.
So,
would you become my wife?
I... don't know how to answer.
Young Lady!
What is it, Nanny?
It's about time to head out.
Are you ready to go?
Yes, Nanny.
I have to go. See you, Ranmaru.
Wait!
Benio!
It somehow looks like she'll be gone forever...
Aaah!
It's so depressing!
Tsk!
Man, you sure are annoying.
At this rate, if Benio doesn't come back...
No, no, no!
What should I do?
Ushi, I have to do something!
Hey, don't touch me!
It feels awful!
Anchin missed Princess Kiyo...
she went crazy.
Yaoya Oshichi was lovesick too...
Onatsu Kyouran too...
I feel all of you.
There he goes again,
not telling reality and fiction apart!
Take good care, Benio.
Father...
Please, don't be so sad...
I'll be kicked out in no time, after all!
Benio...
Nanny, look after Father, okay?
Young Lady, take care of yourself!
Boss, see you!
Benio!
Good morning, madam.
Oh, it's you, Tamaki, welcome.
Today is a beautiful day, aren't you going outside?
Yes,
I was walking past here, so I thought of stopping by.
Such wonderful flowers!
They smell so nicely...
Is there any special occasion, madam?
Indeed,
Shinobu's fiancée is coming over.
So, it's for Benio...?!
Uh, I mean, is it for Lady Hanamura Benio...
Yes.
Ah, that's right,
she's your classmate, isn't she?
Yes.
Then, I can imagine you know her rather well.
Certainly,
we're close friends, after all.
Then, could you tell me how the young lady is like?
Well, let's see...
I don't know what it is going to take,
but I'll act as rude as humanly possible!
She's very kind, also...
Boss Benio's car
Boss!
Hey, Boss,
wait for me, Boss!
Hey, hey, here we go!
Let's go!
...and her acquaintances are wonderful people too...
Who's pulling that rickshaw over there?
That's my henchman.
Henchman??
Any complaints?
What's with this girl?
Why is she, of all people, the chosen one to marry the poor Young Master...
Judging from this shocked expression...
I'm already leading, it's 1-0!
Hehehehe...
No,
I won't give in.
Until marriage, I'll do what it takes for her to be taught properly.
Benio, do your best.
I'll be cheering for you
in your engagement-breaking mission!
We're still far from the Ijuuins' residence, aren't we?
No, we're already inside the mansion.
But isn't this just a forest?
No,
this is part of the estate, too.
Look, the mansion is over there.
A castle!?
No way, I had no idea they were this rich...
Benio,
Please do your best, for my sake, too.
Hey, make way!
Go-go-go-go! Boss!!
Huh?
He's Benio's faithful henchman,
he could be a decisive hand on this game.
Oh, excuse me!
Boss!
Ah!
Ah, stop-stop-stop!
No, I can't stand mutts at all!
Ugh...
Calm down, please,
Look at my face, I don't mean threat!
Ushigorou!
If you didn't look threatening,
others wouldn't feel threatened, am I right?
Ugh!
Hey, Tamaki! Enough laughing,
I may be in danger!
Is that so?...
These dogs are the Ijuuins' most faithful guard dogs,
they don't take strangers lightly.
Oh, then,
I'm Boss Benio's most faithful guard, aren't I!
So,
let's negotiate, shall we?
What I'm trying to say is,
we're like the same pack of dogs, right?
Please do something about it, Tamaki!!
Oh?
It's the first time
that I've seen Ushigorou so frightened.
It's kind of cute, isn't it?
Well, shall I escort you to the mansion?
Lady Benio?
Young Lady, you may come in.
Whaddya think of the young lad...
I needa young lad!
Keep cool, we are on the same side!
Tamaki, please do something, I...
Tenmaru, Chimaru,
this man might look threatening,
but in reality it's not like that.
It's just a wrong impression!
Are you complimenting me or making fun of me?
Ushigorou, these dogs are actually very smart.
They'd be eager to see you introduce yourself.
Uh, introducing myself?
Oh!
Sure, just leave it to me!
Hear me out, hear me out.
I'll make it short.
Just like the great Musashi, I was born in Hanakawado, on the district of Asakusa.
I took an oath of serving Boss Benio,
I am the one and only Ushigorou,
don't misjudge me, don't...
Take it easy, take it easy...
H-e-l-p me!!
Mr. Shinobu is still busy and hasn't come back yet,
so please wait here for a while.
Whoa, how splendid!
Clean as a new pin!
This is incredible!
Maybe I went a little overboard with this style.
Well, who cares.
My goal is to act unsavory,
and get properly kicked out,
no need to hold back.
Oh, a cigar!
I'd love a box like this.
What are you doing??
Oh, you must be my stand-in.
I work here as a chef assistant!
But it's soon the time for my wedding,
so I'll have to resign.
Hey, you...
If you're my stand-in, why are you here?
The kitchen is right in this direction!
So you're saying...
...that you think that I look like a chef assistant, don't you?
Yeah, so what?
Yahoo!
I made it!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Hey, what the hell are you doing!?
You sicken me!
What a strange act...
Hey you, get a grip!
Yeah, I sure will!
Thanks to this misunderstanding,
I now feel fully confident!
It's so flat...
I lost my confidence already!
Well, there sure is nobody dwelling there.
I guess this is what kept company to Shinobu as a kid.
That girl is Young Master's future wife?
She doesn't have the look of the position!
I feel bad for Young Master!
This is such an old mansion...
What's this strange sound?
It's... getting closer!
Even if this is an old place,
it can't be... a ghost!
It must be a joke!
What?
It's just an armor.
Anyways, it's good craftsmanship,
en garde!
Ouch!
Oh?
"Made in Japan" armors can speak too?
It's amazing!
Oh, it moves its eyes too!
Alright,
let's see if it's ticklish.
Oh!
Shinobu has another playfellow!
Is he still on service?
Stop, enough games!
Halt now!
There's someone in there!
I need to teach you a lesson, get ready!
Our High Collar Lady is about to get acquainted
with a rusty lance...
What kind of foe wields it?
An armored warrior appeared before Benio,
but the man under the helmet
is none other than Count Ijuuin.
In other words, an intrepid Samurai of Satsuma!
He took a dislike to Benio from the get-go.
As a problem can hide another,
the High Collar-style
engagement-breaking mission takes on water!
Next time on Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Count, Forgive me! Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Ziusudra
Perevodildo