This is no Shakespeare line,
but our High Collar Lady can't decide between staying and leaving.
The egoistical Ranmaru and Ushigorou
got fired up and started their offensive,
which managed to drive
the hard-working Kisaragi crazy.
Shinobu seems to have unmasked Ranmaru,
but for some reason he keeps playing dumb.
Our High Collar Lady can't understand Shinobu's deepest feelings
and this is just confusing and hurting her.
No way! It's my turn this morning!
Never! I'll be doing it!
It's my duty to take care of Young Master!
So leave it to me!
No!
Cut it down!
If you both want to clean so bad, how about doing it together?
You're right.
Yeah, it could definitely work.
Good morning.
Hello!
Hey, look at this! Mine is tidier!
Lies! Mine is sparkling!
That's not true at all!
Benio, shouldn't you be the one taking care of Shinobu?
Hey Benio, are you listening?
Oh,
If I have to look after him
I'd rather treat him this way!
I understand how you feel!
That's a good attitude!
That sublieutenant doesn't care about me at all...
I hate him!
Episode 14
Two blooming admirers
Lady Benio!
Please don't worry!
I'll reassemble it right now!
Let's see...
This is a foot, I think...
Lady Benio! You should rather take care of Young Master at least a bit!
Who cares about him...
Lady Benio!
It's fine, it's fine.
Then I'll do it myself.
Young Master, here you are.
Oh, so pretty.
Today you don't have your pads on your back anymore, good job, good job!
Your mercy is worthy of a samurai!
Oh...
Oh, where are my gloves?
Oh, such disregard!
Someone, please bring the gloves here!
Yes, ma'am!
Ah, wait, though.
Lady Benio!
I sure did it fast!
What's wrong?
It's your job!
Bring Young Master's gloves here once and for all!
Understood.
Couldn't you do it yourself?
This one?
Here they are.
Oh, that's right!
I wonder how he'd react
if I gave him two right hand ones!
Yes, let's go for it!
She is rather late. Why is it taking so long?
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Here.
Yeah, thanks.
Later.
Please return soon, Young Master!
How boring...
He went away without putting them on.
What is it about?
I felt like making fun of Shinobu,
so I gave him two right hand gloves!
Look, the left ones.
Brilliant as usual!
Boss, that could turn out even better!
Why?
If I recall correctly, Shinobu should be a standard-bearer.
Now that I think about it, my father once mentioned this.
Hey, what's a standard-bearer?
Attention!
Salute his Majesty the Emperor.
At ease.
He holds the national flag!
Soldiers!
Yessir!
Salute the flag!
In the regiment, only the most qualified officers
can become standard-bearers.
And to do that, it is necessary to wear white gloves.
Then if someone forgets his gloves...
Exactly what you're thinking!
You fool!
He'll get a good scolding by the commander
And since your father is Shinobu's direct superior,
he'll face the consequences too.
This much trouble?
Then it's all settled!
Yahoo!
This way Benio will 100% be kicked out!
That's it!
Banzai!
Hip hip, hooray! Hip hip, hooray!
What am I gonna do?
Shinobu, I didn't think it'd go this way!
Sorry, Shinobu!
I'm sorry!
Get outta my way! Go-go-go-go!
Boss, what's wrong? You've been quite gloomy!
It's nothing.
The glove matter should have had an effect by now.
This way you'll be able to say goodbye to that mansion, right, Boss?
Why did you stop all of a sudden?
Hehe...
Who are those guys?
Hey hey hey!
This is a public road, so get outta my way!
Don't tell me what to do!
You're the lady who got engaged with the sublieutenant Ijuuin, right?
We are...
the most influent gang
in the whole Kanto district!
Say our name out loud,
Violet squad!
Violet squad...
Oh well...
Stop, stop! Ushigorou, stop!
Ushigorou, stop!
Oh, so then you guys must love
singing the violet song!
Yes, we surely do!
Let's go!
A violet flower...
A violet flower
started blooming
the time I met you-
Shut up! This is not the time to sing!
Sorry.
How funny!
Stop laughing!
I don't hold any grudge against you, but I gotta do what I gotta do,
so I'll have to hurt you a bit.
Huh!? What do you mean by that!?
No arguing, get off!
Hey...
Wanna pick a fight, then?
I see you've got it.
Ushigorou...
I accept your challenge,
but know that I won't take any responsibility.
Heh, don't overvalue yourself,
and bring it on!
Boss, it's looking bad,
these guys rule the streets.
So what of it?
This is a great chance to boost my mood today!
Alright! I'll be facing you!
You-!
Ushigorou!
Keep in mind that you started all of this!
Huh? Don't mess with me!
Way to go!
One down! Now you, attack me from wherever!
This whore! I went easy on her 'cause she's a woman!
Time to get serious!
Bitch!
Get ready!
Boss!
I'll be fine, Ushigoro.
I don't really know why, but it's been a while and I'm excited!
Rot in...
hell!
Bastard!
Hyaah!
Get spanked!
You sure are cheeky!
Take this!
Aaah!
En garde!
Boss!
Ta-dan!
Finally.
Straight to hell.
Time to die!
Wanna kill me like yakuzas?
Then try to do it!
Shaddup!
Die!
Please stop!
Lady Kichiji...
What is wrong with you?
Going three against one!
But we were concerned about you...
Such things are unasked for!
I don't remember ever promising to pay you for anything.
But...
Not a word more!
Go home!
She's pretty. And also so strong-willed!
Boss, are you okay?
I apologise, Young Lady,
for what these guys have put you through.
It's okay.
I am a geisha from Yanagibashi,
my name is Hananoya Kichiji.
So you are Ms. Kichiji?
And this lady is Hanamura Benio?
Yes...
I see.
As I thought.
How do you know me, though?
You see, I happen to be in...
To be in?
In love with Young Master.
Of course it's one-sided
and now I'm completely sure that I can't do anything
if you are his fiancée.
Oh, it's not like that. A-Actually we...
aren't officially married yet,
also Shinobu doesn't really...
What are you talking about?
It is plain to see.
Also, I could never be chosen.
A noble with a geisha like me
would be together only in my wildest dreams.
However, I even started
to think to break your engagement
in every way possible.
After meeting you today,
I understood that I can't compare.
Young Lady.
Take good care of Young Master!
Ms. Kichiji!
Ugh, that shameless womaniser!
Fooling that geisha and doing such things behind my back!
He's just the worst! I'll never forgive him!
Boss!
That hypocrite!
I don't even have a cold though...
Lord Ijuuin!
Did anything happen to Young Lady for you to be here?
Well, I don't want to upset you, so I won't say anything.
Oh, good grief,
to think that it was such a great engagement!
I won't forgive him!
I won't ever forgive him!
Welcome home.
Benio, what's wrong?
Ranmaru, today's the day to pack my things and leave.
I've already done that in foresight.
Uh? Are you a clairvoyant?
If it's about you, I can make my telepathy work!
Just joking. Anyways, I'll bring your things here.
Hold on!
What is that?
This?
Can't you tell? It's today's share of love letters
directed to Shinobu.
Whoa...
It's like this everyday!
I've never seen such a playboy before!
Even the author!? Really?
Shinobu-san
I'm head over heels for you
♥Waki
I've had enough of this!
He's late, isn't he?
I'm here, shall we go now?
One second.
I want to tell Shinobu just one thing before we leave.
What? Do you still have feelings for him?
It's not like that, it's just one quick thing.
Alright then.
Hey, I'm back.
Shinobu!
You got into trouble because of the gloves, right?
What is she doing!?
Leutenant, that was very inconsiderate of me.
I put many people in trouble, didn't I?
I just found it funny!
Thankfully, this world is full of scatterbrains and today
another officer coincidentally brought two left-handed gloves.
So I exchanged my right glove with his left one
and we made it through alright.
I'm glad!
Benio!
Shinobu!
Moreover,
can you guess who this officer
actually was?
None other than your father!
It is probably because
of a careless mistake by Nanny.
Nanny...
Ever since you left her, she must've been feeling lonely
without a moment of relief.
Hence she made this mistake.
Nanny...
So I,
on the way back,
decided to console her a bit.
Such self-aggrandisement,
I can't stand him!
He doesn't know modesty,
this shamless womaniser!
Ah, by the way,
Nanny gave something for you two.
Here, this is for you.
Ranmaru- err, Ranko.
These sure are
a lot of love letters.
I'm not really happy about it,
I get all these letters despite not having any feelings for them.
This is just dull.
I feel you,
it's like this everyday for me.
I don't even know who's sending them,
it's all one-sided.
What?
One-sided?
He's so pretentious!
And these are for Benio, one from Nanny.
Oh, Sabu and Hiroshi.
Who are they?
Two kids in my neighbourhood.
I see.
I didn't expect them to write me a letter.
Dear Benio, let's climb trees and play again sometime!
Crimbing trees?
What about Hiroshi?
Benio, when are you coming back?
I wanna climb a tree!
I'll never forget when we climbed one back then!
- Hiroshi.
What is this? It's all about treeclimbing!
I guess I'm not popular after all!
No love letters at all!
To Benio-san
- Hiroshi
I don't care about these!
Laugh as you please!
Oh, my bad.
Are you gonna keep on laughing forever?
I already know your secrets!
Like your beloved Ms. Kichiji, huh?
You met her?
Your expression changed!
You're...
wrong on her matter, Benio.
Please, don't misunderstand.
I don't need lame excuses.
I hate people like you who play with women's feelings,
I hate you all!
Get out!
Both of you!
Benio!
Out, out!
After all,
no matter what,
I'm just a nominal fiancée.
Just fated to a loveless forced marriage.
This is too much to bear!
It's such a sad fate for a woman
to stay with an unfaithful man
with no chance of divorcing
and being completely overwhelmed by housework.
Why do we have so many children?
It should never happen.
I'm sick of this!
I'll just leave!
Oh?
To Young Lady
A letter from Nanny?
Young Lady, how are you?
As for me, I am living peacefully all alone with your father.
He has never been worried about you,
so, whatever happens,
please never consider returning home.
Moreover, I have never had the wish to see your face again,
so I beg you not to ever come back home.
Never, never come back home, please.
Never,
never come back home, please.
Nanny...
After all,
people always have two sides,
If there's anything you can do to untie the thread in your tormented heart, try it out
and a flower will bloom.
Which will it be?
During the airing of old family possessions,
something slips from Ranmaru's hand and breaks
and oh goodness, it was a precious plate!
The count obviously snaps out and unsheathes his katana,
and, to give all plates the same fate,
Benio decides to break all of them! Big trouble!
Next time on "Here Comes the Smart Alec":
So long, old-fashioned mansion. Don't miss it!