Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
After a messy night at a bar, our High Collar Lady
had sweet, sweet dreams on Shinobu's back.
A romantic breeze blows between the two betrothed
and even the opposing count approves their relationship.
However, there's a problem.
Perhaps, a quirk of fate.
An unexpected villain received the previous night's bill.
What kind of evil revenge is he plotting now?
Sublieutenant ❤ Benio
This is no good, huh.
For real. I'd like to write my name here.
Good grief... Though in every aspect,
we're more charming that her, right?
That's right!
We might have a chance some time!
What's this? I've known her since I was born,
it can't be this way.
Done.
Ranmaru ❤ Benio
Now it's right!
What are you so worried about?
Oh willow by the river...
Oh?
Well, it's not like I don't get Ranmaru's feelings,
but it'll be bad if someone else in here sees this.
Let's change it, just in case.
Ushigorou ❤ Benio
But it could put Boss in trouble...
Well, if it gotta be harmless, I'll do it like this.
Ushigorou ❤ Kisaragi
I wanna say that it's hard to be together!
Oh my!
Oh, what is this...
But I'd feel bad, destroying his dreams.
Let's keep it there.
Episode 20
Who Are the Two Under the Love Umbrella?
How shameful, having all of these love letters...
Oh? More love letters fo Shinobu.
That's right. They keep on coming every day.
Have you ever seen a playboy like him?
Benio, you'd better keep an eye on Shinobu, okay?
So does he read them thoroughly and answer everyday?
He doesn't read them and he tosses them straight away.
Then what's the difference between them not coming at all?
Right?
Why is Benio so kind?
Or perhaps she's defending Shinobu?
I gotta watch out!
I beg your pardon?
Yo, Ranmaru- err, Ranko.
Your letters.
Here.
Throw them away for me.
As you wish.
Ah, hold on a second.
It's fine now, throw the rest.
Do you need anything?
Not really.
Yes, fine by me.
Then, tomorrow at three, at our usual place.
"Tomorrow at three, at our usual place..."
This is bad!
Not too shabby, considering it's mine.
B-B-Benio! It's awful, it's awful!
Oh no, they fell!
It was my masterpiece!
I can arrange all the flowers that you want later,
there's something more important right now!
I saw Ijuuin appointing a date
with a sender of one of the love letters, via phone!
Oh? But didn't you say
he doesn't read any of his love letters?
It was an exception,
understand me!
And who was the sender?
I didn't manage to see that,
I don't do detective work.
Then, it might just be a harmless letter,
and the sender might have been a man.
No!
That was definitely a woman, I can't be mistaken.
A woman's instinct never fails.
I'm sure I'm right. Must be so!
A woman's instinct, huh?
One way or another, tomorrow at three,
Ijuuin is seeing this sender
"at their usual place," he said, too.
But if you think through everything that much,
there'll be no end!
You're right, but I decided that I'd protect you no matter what,
so just leave this to me!
Ranmaru...
Jeez, I can't get if that guy's a boy or a girl.
Now, then. Let's try once again from scratch.
Tomorrow at three, at our usual place...
Shoui... The sender is a man, isn't he?
That's right. It's got to be man.
Even though all his letters are from women...
Ms. Benio, you've got a call.
Oh? For me? Who is it?
You'll learn it yourself, once you answer it.
Ah, really?
Who could it be? Maybe Nanny. Or it might as well be Tamaki.
Hello? It's Hanamura Benio.
Hello, I'm the women's duty teacher from the Girls' School Atonashi.
What now? It's you, teach?
Be respectful!
No, I didn't mean it-
Hanamura, you haven't been at school in a long while,
are you feeling unwell, by chance?
No, it's just that I've been through a lot...
Then I think it's better for you to come back at school,
frankly speaking, your grades are terrible,
you have too many absences and this is a serious issue for your school year.
What do you mean by serious?
That you'll fail!
Understood! I'll be back from tomorrow onwards!
Dear me...
I got behind on so much homework...
Benio? Still not coming to bed?
You know you have to be ready by three.
I'm not worried about the Shinobu matter.
I can't leave this homework undone.
Should I help you out?
English, maths, history, religion, science and writing, which one do you pick?
Have a good night!
Pathetic.
Mhm...
Good.
What's this?
Finished!
I've done all of my homework in one night!
I feel so good!
Will it be
Still worried about that?
It's fine, it's fine!
Oh, I'm going to be late.
Good morning.
Kisaragi,
Don't worry about my breakfast, I have to go to school!
But I've done all of the homework! Look!
You do know it's Sunday, don't you?
If Shinobu has to be there by three o'clock, then he'll go out at two.
Likely.
Then Ushi, you'll be following Shinobu.
Don'tcha think it'd be better if I took his neck
and I asked who the hell he's boutta meet,
until he just blurts it out?
You have no delicacy, don't you?
Hm? Cacy?
Never heard 'bout that.
Don't worry, it's for Benio's sake.
Or are you saying that you don't care
about Benio?
Hell no! Say it again, I dare you!
If there's somebody that won't make her sad,
then that guy is me, Ushigorou!
I'm Boss's best partner!
You're gonna kill me! Let me go!
Ah, my bad...
So, we have to discover Shinobu's true persona,
it's for Benio's sake, got it?
Really? Alright, gotcha.
So, you stay here until it's two,
then you follow Shinobu wherever he goes, got it?
If it's for Boss, I'ma do everything!
Don'tcha doubt me!
Right.
Been a long time since I went shopping!
At times like this, going out to relax is the best.
I might go to Minatoya in Gofukubashi.
Year 1913, the artist Takehisa Yumeji opens Minatoya, his print shop,
which was wildly power among girls.
I might see Takehisa Yumeji's new work.
Look at me, I'll catch that Sublieutenant in no time.
Ah, Boss.
Could I benefit from your service?
Roger.
Err, wait, I can't!
No service today.
So let's go, Ushigorou.
You know, actually, I, uhm...
What are you so hesitant for?
No, you know, it's that...
Benio, you see, I can't today.
If something's wrong, just say it.
It's nothin' serious, really!
Then just hurry up and start moving!
Sure, sure.
Here we go...
Ushigorou, can't you speed up a bit?
Yeah-yeah, yeah-yeah.
What's this, you've turned into a Edoite?
Yeah-yeah.
I'll never be one!
So he's going out, after all.
Ushi!
Where is he now?
Hey.
Looking for someone here?
Did you see Ushi?
If you're talking about Ushigorou,
he went out with Benio a while ago.
That dumbass.
Well then, I'll be going.
I'll go with you too!
Ranko. Ranko!
Oh, come on...
Thank you, Ushigorou.
I'll come back on my own, so don't worry about it.
Yeah.
By the way, what time is it?{時に今何時ですかねー ]
Oh, it should be about three.
What a weird dude.
Shinobu and Kichiji...
At three, somewhere, with someone...
No way, no way.
He's betraying me!
I trusted him...
I trusted him!
But why do I have to hide here and act oblivious?
That's right,
I just have to say something and interrupt them.
But what should I say exactly?
Uhm, "Hello"?
Or else, "the weather is so clear today".
No, it sounds like a set phrase.
No, won't work.
Otherwise, otherwise, going straight to the point...
Oh!
Never mind
Never mind, never mind
Never mind, never mind, never mind
Panicking
Ah, I can't stop anymore!
Ah, stop, stop! I can't stop!
Never mind
I can't stop, I can't stop!
Panicking
Whoa!
Stop, stop!
Whoa, stop, stop, stop! Stop!!!
Young Master...
Yeah?
Did something happen between you and Lieutenant Innen?
With Lieutenant?
When he invited me to the tatami room the other day...
Does the Sublieutenant Ijuuin
come here often?
Yes, we are quite close, in fact.
Don't you know that he has a fiancee?
Well, I...
Moreover, with Hanamura's daughter.
He said that...
I see.
Then something happened, right?
Well, yeah, somewhat.
Please be careful.
The Lieutenant is prone to holding grudges
and he's very influential in the Army,
so something irreparable might happen...
No way, it's all good.
He might be harsh, but I doubt that he'll be
so mad for a thing like that.
Thanks for worrying about it, though.
Young Master!
What could they be talking about?
I can't hear them.
If something happened to you, Young Master, I...
I apologise
I shouldn't have said that.
Kichiji...
Thank you.
So those two... after all, they are...
Young Master!
Kichiji, please let's break all of this.
That's what men tell to geishas, right?
I'd prefer if you told me to die right now.
Kichiji, please forgive me.
I am betrothed to a fiancee.
She's pug-nosed and too ugly too look at,
but I have to endure this for my grandmother.
Young Master...
Kichiji...
Stop!
Get lost, get lost, get lost!
Stop, don't touch!
Stop-
What, was it just a dream?
I'm so concerned about those two that they even appear in my dreams.
But why am I so worried about it?
Okay, if it has to happen, let's turn these dreams in my favour.
Let's have sweet dreams!
Good, good, Ranmaru, set the mood!
Please, forgive me.
I am betrothed to a fiancee.
She's pug-nosed...
Cut! Cut, cut!
I don't really like that line,
change it, got it?
Start!
Please, forgive me.
I have a beautiful fiancee that I deeply love.
She's cute, smart,
has a unique personality,
I feel like I don't even deserve her.
Young Master...
I don't want to see you ever again.
Let's part and pretend none of this ever happened.
If she's such a wonderful girl,
then I don't stand a chance against her.
I'll gracefully step aside.
So you understood it?
Yes. However...
However?
Please, let me see how splendid that girl is
with my very eyes.
Alright.
Benio!
Here I am!
Did someone call me?
Was it you, Shinobu?
Enough!
Why am I always making a fool of myself?
At any rate, those two make for a fantastic couple.
She's always been a way better match than me.
In the end, who is going to be the one under the Love Umbrella
side by side with Shinobu?
Who will be laughing in the end?
Don't give up, High Collar Lady!
Things have yet to be decided!
Fast asleep or awake, Benio can't help but think about Shinobu and Kichiji,
to the point her appetite is long gone.
Is she a fool for being trustful?
Or is the deceiving side in the wrong?
Trouble after trouble,
Benio has finally made up her mind
Next time in Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Life is Short, Yet Riddled with Worries. Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Ziusudra
Perevodildo