Bang!
While Benio, completely drunk, got into a fight,
Shinobu was looking for her through all the town.
Meanwhile, Ushigorou hurried to the count to receive reinforcements,
only to cause even more trouble!
Are you alright, Lieutenant?
This old man is out of his mind!
After Shinobu finally arrived, there was no time to cheer,
as his opponent happened to be his superior, who has now lost it!
This is just the beginning of an endless tragedy!
Episode 19
Fleeting Happiness
Please wait a second.
Uhm... Uhm, you haven't paid for tonight yet.
Hey, pay her.
Sure, but...
Just shut up and pay!
Roger...
Proprietress, how much is it?
It's 50.000 yen.
There!
Much obliged!
Ho-ho, haven't you forgot anything?
What?
Here, don't forget your things!
How dare you, those are a soldier's soul!
A soldier's soul? Gimme those, Ranko.
A stupid sword is supposed to be your soul?
Take a look!
My precious saber!
If a soldier's soul depends on that tin trash, the Japanese Army won't have a bright future.
Idiot!
You're a grown-up, and yet you're so childish...
Asking for more?
Ah! You forgot something else.
Another piece of your soul.
There it goes!
Hurts, damn it!
How dare you...
What's wrong, Mr. Lieutenant?
Benio!
Making fool of officials... I'll remember this.
Serves you right!
Tsk! Hey, we're off.
We won!
Alright, let's go home too.
This is a triumphant return!
Hip hip, hooray!
Count, you're awesome!
Then, let's return home as well.
Yes.
Ah, whoops, oh, eh?
What happened to me?
Aw-aw-aw-aw-aw, my head hurts.
What is it?
Now that the fight's over, my head is spinning.
I embarrassed myself.
Okay, okay, everyone.
Whoa!
I'm spinning round!
Bam!
Should we go home like this?
What a shock!
N-No!
This is so embarassing!
What's so embarrassing? It's just a husband carrying his wife on his back.
Wife?! Wife... He said wife...
Wife?! Wife! Wife? Never! Never!
Yup!
Shut up! Let go of me! Hey!
We've got it, that's what a husband does,
but please look at what you've done for a moment!
Five chairs, three desks, decanters, glasses and plates, for a total of... let's see...
Never! Never! Let go of me!
I apologise, I'll pay for everything.
Just let go of me!
Who cares about paying her back!
I don't wanna give someone like you money!
You'll fall if you keep struggling like that!
Shut up! Let go of me!
Ah! Shut up, you! Shut it, you all!
Are you alright, Benio?
And one pillar too.
Puff
A messenger came from the mountain village...
He came from the mountain village riding a horse...
To tell everyone that the cherries had blossomed...
The double cherry blossoms on the Kurama Mountain...
The count's rather joyful, what is he chanting though?
The Kurama Tengu noh song.
Hey, why are you so gloomy, Ranmaru?
Take a guess...
It feels like this exact same thing happened a long time ago...
Being carried on someone's broad back...
It was... my father?
No...
No, it can't be.
It wasn't my father.
Was it... Was it someone I don't know?
I was fated to be carried on that strong man's back...
It was decided from the very beginning.
But who...
Who was it?
Oh, I slept so well!
Whoa!
So dazzling!
Good morning.
Oh, good m-
Are you already awake, Benio?
What's happening?
How in the world did I return to here?
I look forward to living with you again from now onward.
Ah! Hurts!
What's this? A bruise on my head?
Oh darn! How could this happen all of a sudden?
Can't you remember?
Oh, Shi-
Shinobu!
Morning. Feeling better already?
What happened yesterday is so like you!
By the way, when did this bruise appear?
You really can't recall?
I came back home, I quarreled with my father
and then I drank a bit of alcohol with Ushigorou and Ranmaru.
Just "a bit of alcohol"?
I remember that much, but after that...
I can't remember at all!
What's so funny? I'm worried, you know!
Sorry, this is too like you!
Is it here?
It hurts! Be gentler!
Didn't I tell you would have back pain again if you strained yourself at this age?
What's so funny?
If only you saw yesterday night's heroic feat!
I knocked out every soldier, one after another
and in the end they ran away out of fear!
Hey! What's wrong with you? Are you deaf?
It's okay, just come here and watch what's happening.
Let's see what you stopped massaging me for.
Look, it's such a nice spectacle, isn't it, my Dear?
Tenmaru and Chimaru are really healthy, heh!
This is not about dogs!
But...
Benio has finally returned here.
All of this is only thanks to yesterday night's heroic feat!
Is bragging the only thing you can do?
Those two are making thriving flowers bloom in this old mansion.
If they have children at some point,
they will be our grandsons.
I'm aware!
I may seem like a rustic person, but in reality
I am just bad at expressing my emotions!
Of course I also wish nothing but happiness to those two.
But... if I was so messed up,
how the hell did I come back here?
Could it be on Ushigorou's rickshaw?
Might be. Who knows?
That's not it.
I'm dead sure someone carried me on his back.
But on whose back?
Uhm...
Uh...
I remember now!
Who carried you on his back?
Everything was just a dream,
in reality I got home on my own.
My impossible love
can finally flourish after all this time
thanks to my grandson Shinobu.
Shinobu...
Benio...
You'll be a happy couple.
Please overcome any difficulty you might face in life.
You know, that got me really worked up!
Alright. This is the perfect day to tell her my feelings.
Here, I think it suits you.
Benio.
What's the matter?
There's...
something I've always wanted to tell you.
You see, I...
Hey, Shinobu!
Look, look!
This is so unusual!
Those cockroaches are flying in group!
Whoa! They're in single file now!
A hook shape now!
Hey, don't you think it's unusual?
Oh, by the way, what did you want to tell me?
Oh no, what's wrong?
Are you feeling ill?
Hey, listen to me.
No, I'm fine.
I'll talk about it another day.
But...
It's not the right mood for this topic.
I'll be leaving soon.
Well, see you later, Benio.
Shinobu!
So strange...
He could've just said it.
That guy's truly weird.
Ranmaru!
What are you doing in a place like this?
Can't you tell by looking? I'm working out.
But won't this damage your delicate fingers?
Don't worry, Benio.
Don't trust that Sublieutenant,
I'll be the one protecting you!
I just don't get it,
something must've happened last night.
Good morning, Lady Benio!
Oh, morning!
Oh, what's this voice?
It sounds like Ranko.
Oh shoot!
What could she be doing?
Let's see!
Hold on!
E-Erm, don't go!
How come?
Well, if you go there... Well, you...
After all, Ranko is one of us, isn't she?
Right?
Sounds about right. Right?
Beg your pardon!
This is not looking good...
What's wrong, girls?
Weren't you making strange sounds all along?
I was exercising.
Exercising?
Yes, calisthenics.
Oh, so it was calisthenics.
Wonderful!
I also want to become as pretty as Ranko!
Please give us lessons from now on!
Please!
We're begging you!
Teach us, please!
Really?
Okay, then.
Perfect!
Well, shall we go now?
Thank God! They didn't unmask him!
Then, I'll be going, Benio.
Come home safe!
Come home safe, Young Master.
See you.
Uh, Boss, we gotta go in a couple minutes, y'know.
Where to?
You're way too carefree!
Are you planning to skip school?
Now, hurry up to board.
Boss Benio's car
You're still a student, Boss.
You're right...
So much happened that I had completely forgotten about school!
So this means that you haven't done any homework...
Naturally!
Well then, let's just call it a day off for today.
All settled!
This is the first smart thing you've ever said since I met you!
I'm learning from my Boss!
In that case, I'll just go to town for some business.
Here we are!
Well then, let me know if you need anything, Boss!
Take care, Ushigorou!
Ijuuin... Is it here?
What a beautiful building.
Good for me, they'll pay me in no time!
What's that?!
What do- what do you want from me?!
Somebody help me!
Rickshawman, help me!
Aren't you last night's proprietress?
Yes I am, I'm here to give this bill to the sublieutenant.
Then why don't you go?
Hop, hop...
Please do something about these dogs.
I'm begging you!
I can't do that, these dogs are my nemesis.
Proprietress, I don't wanna be rude, but you better turn around and take another path.
Is this a threat?
Well, you only got one life, so be careful!
Wait, you!
I'm not joking! My life depends on this, you know!
Alright, then I'll just go the other way.
Excuse me...
You cannot come near here.
I need to ask you a favour...
Hey, what happened?
What does she want?
Uhm, actually, I'd like to give this to Sublieutenant Ijuuin.
It's open, come in.
There's a request for you, Sublieutenant.
At ease. What is it?
A woman has just visited to give you this...
Oh, she really went all the way here.
Okay, I got it, so please tell her
that I'll pay for everything.
Yessir, understood!
Alright.
Here I am, what do you need?
I need a favour.
Could you please forward the documents on the desk to Lieutenant Innen?
Yessir, understood!
I will do it right away.
I'm leaving.
Yes, thanks.
Main Administrative Office
I'm so furious.
That hoyden is Hanamura's daughter...
Just thinking about her irritates me!
What is it? Do you need anything, Lieutenant?
No, it's nothing.
I see.
Hey, Commander Hanamura.
Lieutenant Innen,
Sublieutenant Ijuuin sent me here.
What? From Sublieutenant Ijuuin?
Yessir, he told me to give you this.
Understood, thank you.
Ijuuin, huh...
He ignores our military rule of no long hair
and he's not even a pure Japanese.
I can't stand him being in the Sacred Imperial Army!
There's no choice but to give him tit for tat.
What?!
A refund for five chairs, three desks, decanters, glasses and plates?
What's this about?
Is it about yesterday night?
That Ijuuin again...
He sent me this bill to make me pay for it, didn't he?
Oh, he's gone too far!
This is just unacceptable!
He's out of his mind!
Lieutenant Innen's red flag was clear as day.
Oh, a war front in Russia.
We might need to dispatch our soldiers alongside Americans in Siberia.
We'll show them our power.
It is 1918 and Japan is on the verge of dispatching troops to Siberia.
Dispatching troops to Russia...
This could work...
There. Pretty, aren't they?
My Shinobu...
The gentle breeze of love has turned into a violent typhoon all of a sudden.
Will it completely blow away our High Collar Lady's happiness?
Is happiness just a fleeting dream?
You're in danger!
You're in danger, High Collar Lady!
Our High Collar Lady now trusts Shinobu, not caring about his mountain of love letters,
and she decides to go shopping in Gofukubashi.
However, unfortunately, she stumbles across Shinobu's date, and his partner
is none other than the beautiful geisha Hananoya Kichiji.
So what are you gonna do?
What are you gonna do, High Collar Lady?
Next time in Here Comes Miss Modern:
Two lovers, don't miss it!