Here Comes Smart-san
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era dame
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
Whose winning heart lavishes kindness
After getting into a fight, Benio used her tomboyish sword technique
and blew the masterfully experienced count away.
Thus, these two started to celebrate Benio's imminent return.
But hold on,
the count saw his long-gone son's look in Benio's eyes and liked it,
In addition, he was even cured by Benio's special Chinese herbal medicine.
All of a sudden, the counts' mutual love came to light,
while Benio is being forced to accept her arranged marriage,
but she won't ever give in!
Episode 11
Welcome to the party of grief
Thank you so much for today's training.
You're welcome. Be sure to perfect that technique for the next rehearsal.
Sure.
Then, I'm off.
Thank you so much.
Oh,
it's Fujieda Ranmaru, the young kabuki dancer!
He's fabulous!
And a young teacher too!
Wait!
Ranmaru!
Please, wait!
Don't run away!
- Wait!
Young teacher!
Wait, wait!
You're beautiful!
Oh, poor me.
I can't even go out of classes in peace anymore.
Oh, gosh...
Why are all girls the same?
If they are anyone but Benio...
I don't want them.
A man!
A delicious man!
I'm done!
Oh?
It's Ushi!
Ushi!
Ranmaru!?
I've missed you!
Hey, don't touch me, it's embarrassing!
First of all, how did you miss me if we meet everyday?
I've still missed you!
Don't touch me! I'm not interested in those things.
W-What does that mean, Ushi?
Nah, nothin' special.
Hey, Ushi, how's Benio?
Well, you see...
Boss has completely changed,
she's worn out and lost her will.
Moving to a noble mansion out of the blue...
was too hard for her, after all.
I need to do something about it...
Ushi, please go see her at the mansion,
I have a bad feeling about this.
I would've done it,
but it's Sunday,
so I don't have to get her to school.
So you're saying that you won't do it?
Alright, if that's the case, I have another plan!
W-What plan?
You're too close!
Go away!
You're way too close!
Don't touch me!
I get it, I'll go, now calm down!
And this is why Ushi is the best!
Humph...
What are they getting ready for?
A celebration.
A celebration, really?
Don't worry about it,
I only invited my circle of friends.
But...
They all said that they wanted to see you,
they're all excited.
I-I don't wanna!
Even if I am your fiancee, uhm...
Hold on!
I've still not agreed to this marriage.
Don't be so stiff about it, Benio.
Hey, don't just ignore my point of view!
Why is he always so selfish!?
Ugh...
I'm so mad!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ouch!
It looks like Boss is mad about something.
Ranmaru's feminine intuition was right.
Whoops!
He's a male, but whatever, I need to inform him.
You're Ushigorou, right?
I'm in a rush, so I'll see ya later.
No, I won't wait anymore.
Hey, aren't you being too harsh?
Of course, I'm just doing my job!
Whatcha sayin'!? Whaddya mean by this?
Ushigorou, please stop carrying Lady Benio to school on your rickshaw!
Huh!? Why would I listen to ya?
She is a very important lady for this family,
therefore, it's plain obvious that I have to escort her with the Ijuuins' car!
You bastard! Are you stealing my job!?
Sure, if you agree quickly.
What's the difference between agreeing quickly and slowly, you idiot!?
Then you've agreed!
Shut up! You're just trying to spread discord between me and Boss,
it's no good!
Well, I'm a rush, so we'll set things straight later!
See ya!
That damn punk...
They should be here soon.
Here they are.
Whassup!
Yo!
Hey, Shinobu, where's your fiancee?
She's called Benio, right? C'mon, introduce her to us!
Where is your beautiful Mädchen?
Is she the one?
Beautiful?
I didn't know you were into these things.
Lolita complex, right?
Lolita complex, heh!
I see, I see.
Lolita complex,
and borderline boys' love on top of it.
Boys?
Whadja say!?
Sorry!
I only wanted to praise you.
Benio, this is Takayashiki, a buddy of mine.
He's sharp-tongued, but he's a nice guy.
He was really mean!
Nice to meet you!
And here, it's the same Known-not Fellow!
An outdoor celebration?
That's right.
Then, there are many people, there, right?
Probably. I hope Boss won't feel too awkward there.
She's not so good with social skills.
If it's a celebration, there'll also be alcohol, right?
Could be.
Oh no!
Boss had that unknown inclination!
It's terrible! I gotta do something!
Ranmaru, think of something!
Ugh...
Leave it to me! I've got a wonderful idea!
It'll work for sure!
I don't know his plans, but it should be alright.
Cheers!
This is Takayashiki Kaname and he wants to be a poet.
Nice to meet you!
His nickname is Lion.
Lion?
I can kind of understand
Good morning, everybody.
Thank you for inviting me, Shinobu.
Oh, it's the beautiful Tamaki!
Our angel!
Goddess!
Hello, everybody.
Benio, come with me for a second.
Tamaki!
What's with that request?
Benio, what happened to your breaking mission?
There's a fight going on and enemy won't give up.
It's a tough one.
Oh...
Really?
But I'll try my best.
I'm counting on you.
Oh-oh,
This conversation is sure getting lively.
Yeah, Benio is telling me a lot of gossip about the count.
Hey, hey, you two,
don't be shy and join us!
Shall we play a game?
Tamaki, I wrote a poem for you.
Really?
Then I'll read it later.
Later, huh.
You got rejected twice, huh?
Unrequited love is real love,
I'll write a good poem.
Thank you for coming.
Enjoy your time here.
Yes.
Shinobu.
Shinobu, wait!
Shinobu!
Tamaki?
So...
there's something I want to tell you.
How long are you going to detain Benio?
I know everything.
You'll marry Benio just because of your grandmother.
Even if you're engaged...
Benio won't fall for you.
Shinobu.
There must be someone who's better suited for you.
Don't you feel bad for Benio?
Struggling in this mansion all of a sudden...
Someone's talking about me.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Right.
And you're noble too.
Yes, so...
Tamaki, you see...
Just because we were born in this place,
we have the privilege of being nobles.
And we live with it.
I've always wanted to run away from this strange world.
But ever since I met Benio,
I started to think that I could cross this boundary someday.
I began to think like that.
She's a girl that could turn her dreams into reality.
Unlike her, I only dream and do nothing.
Of course, at first I only wanted to do it for my grandmother.
But things have changed.
Benio has such a mysterious charm,
I've never met a girl like her.
Shinobu, deep down you've always wanted someone like Benio.
Shinobu!
I'll never persuade him.
I understand you now.
Tamaki.
You're a fantastic girl, so you'll definitely find a fantastic-
Please, stop.
I... have given up.
However,
Benio is my best friend.
Tamaki...
If you ever make her sad, I...
I won't forgive you!
Oh, lord, where did those two go?
Oh, Shinobu! He's never done something like that to me!
Is she better than me?
What could those two be talking about?
Tamaki is so beautiful...
Tamaki's better suited for Shinobu than me.
What was it?
Let's go see.
Whaddya want? What did I do?
What's wrong?
Stop it!
Shinobu!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, cut it down!
Sit down!
What's going on?
I don't know. These dogs should know Takayashiki pretty well.
Hey, Shinobu, do something!
I've been in this house many times,
but I've never been barked at like this!
Really?
Benio...
Benio, don't you believe my friends?
But I trust these two's pure insinct too.
They must be sensing something strange about Takayashiki just today.
But I don't know what it is.
I believe these dogs. Tenmaru, Chimaru...
bark!
You two! Hush!
Bark!
Hush!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, bark!
Hush, hush, hush, I'm telling you to hush!
Help me!
Benio, please!
Tenmaru, Chimaru, hush!
What's this? They listen to Benio more than me.
That was close.{
Hey, Takayashiki, there's something on your back.
W-What is it?
A wasp!
Everyone, run away!
Oh lord!
I haven't taken a bath in ten days,
I'll be doomed if I get stung!
Good grief!
That sure was a close call!
You're such good dogs! So you weren't barking at Takayashiki, but at the wasp.
Man, they're so smart!
Better than military ones!
Yeah, amazing!
No,
I'm shocked for another reason.
I raised Tenmaru and Chimaru since they were puppies,
so I was astonished that they listen to Benio more than me.
Man, I thought it would end badly.
You said you haven't taken a bath in ten days?
That's so dirty, at least have a shower.
If you say so, Tamaki...
Yahoo!
She's pretty good, isn't she?
She just tamed those two dogs,
but I won't be tamed!
Well, of course!
Here I go!
Man, really, Benio always surprises me.
I'm sorry, everyone,
I spoiled the party because of my carelessness.
You're brand new!
For real.
Then, shall we drink?
Alright, let's do it!
Cheers once again!
Hell yeah!
I... am deeply sorry, but I'll be leaving now.
Oh, Tamaki, why?
I'm not feeling too well.
I see. It's a pity.
Then, I'll escort you with my car.
Yes, thank you.
T-Then I'll see you off.
Hey, Tamaki, is it okay?
If you don't mind, why not!
Riding with the beautiful Tamaki...
Let's go!
I entrust you my car.
Yessir!
Alright then, get in.
Oh,
Ushigorou!
A rickshaw is such a fancy vehicle.
I know right? That looks fun!
Hold on!
Ushigorou,
Hop in, hop in.
I'm always happy to help Boss's friends!
Jump in!
Excuse me.
Ushigorou!
In this male-dominated world isn't this treating her as a property?
Benio...
Understood, Boss.
Sorry, I can't escort you home anymore.
Please get in that car.
Aw, but I wanted to ride it once.
I'm counting on you, okay?
Y-Yes,
thank you so much!
Thank you, Lady Benio!
After the dogs, she won the chauffeur over!
Looks like it.
Be honest, you've grown fond of her.
T-The hell are you saying?
Lady Benio.
Isn't Sunday my day off on my schedule?
It's about a different thing.
Right now?
Yes, right now.
What is it?
Alright, you see...
The new maid said that she wanted to
A new maid?
Yes.
Come in!
Come here.
From today onwards, you'll be serving Lady Benio.
Greet her.
My name is Ranko, I'm glad to meet you, Master.
Wh-Wh-Wha-Wha-?
Ranmaru!?
An unexpected guy in a unexpected place,
the tormented Ranmaru,
desperately wants to help,
with her feminine dedication-
or should I say masculine dedication?
How will things go with Ranko, our newcomer?
The tormented Ranmaru, who's now a maid in disguise,
wants to help Benio, with his inconvenient support,
but he must not reveal his true sex.
As usual, the count's keen look
will question Ranmaru's true identity.
What's next? Big trouble.
Next time on Here Comes Smart-san,
Dance, tormented beauty,
don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra