Here Comes Smart-san
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Have you heard the gossip already?
And have you made sure yourself with those eyes?
Two shockingly beautiful glazzies
A shockingly overflowing romance
The hottest topic now
It's all about this
A charming lady from the Taishou Era
Here she is, High Collar Lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
The ways of God are strange and chose this fiancé for Benio,
leaving her utterly baffled.
One day, all of a sudden,
some bad guys try to beat her up,
but a mysterious woman saves her:
she's a geisha in love with Shinobu.
Shocked, Benio thinks Shinobu is a playboy.
This is the final straw that makes Benio decide to go home once and for all,
but a sudden letter by Nanny hinders again,
our poor High Collar Lady can't decide what to do!
Please treat the objects with care.
We'll carry them to the second floor's balcony in a sunlit spot.
Where should I place this?
Ah, you can place it there.
Are you airing objects, ma'am?
This mansion is rather old, so there's a lot to do.
It must be tough! Then, I'll try to help too!
A-Ah!
Don't!
Benio, you can leave it there,
no need to strain yourself.
well
ha
I feel like you don't trust me...
Episode 15
So long, old-fashioned mansion
Oh, it's you, Benio!
What's with that long face?
I'm feeling left out in this airing.
Oh, aren't you happy that you can slack off?
That's true,
but I'd like some company.
Then how about airing some of your belongings?
But I don't think I have anything antiquated enough...
Oh, there's one!
It symbolises the vow that a woman makes not to marry a second time ever.
In case something happens to him
you'll have to wear this.
You're so old fashioned, Father...
Shouldn't remaining faitfhul to your husband
be determined by the couple's love?
Oh,
it's a dagger.
If anything happens to Shinobu,
I should die by using this...
Shinobu, how do you feel about me?
Our moments together should give you the answer.
Our moments together...
Leaves are falling, but it's not Autumn yet...
I told you to go away! I t-
Come on,
let's flee, quick!
What is this?
My heartbeat...
You see, I happen to be in...
love with Young Master.
It wasn't Shinobu?
Benio, did you meet her?
You'll have to respect him.
My love has finally come true!
I beg you not to ever come back home.
Benio, did you meet her?
Don't ever come back...
You'll have to respect him.
My love...
Stop it! Stop!
How could I ever die for someone
that can't express his feelings!?
I hate this! I hate this so much!
Oh?
Lady Benio, what's wrong?
Stop it! Stop it, I said!
Help me!
It's not what it looks like!
Wait! Wait, I said!
Wait! There's been a misunderstanding!
Wait!
Calm down, for God's sake!
I'll only be calm when I'm safe!
Help me!
Just wait, Mrs. Kisaragi!
Mrs. Kisaragi!
Mrs. Kisaragi, hang in there!
Please, hang in there, Mrs. Kisaragi!
Oh, how silly of me!
Oh-oh-oh! Boss!
You got rid of this hag in the blink of an eye! Congratulations!
What is this nonsense you're saying?
Ushigorou, hurry up and lend me a hand!
Let's see...
Here we are.
You even know resuscitation!
Boss, you truly are something else!
Ah-ah, I have a full mastership, after all!
Wait, Mrs. Kisaragi!
This sword is surely very refined, as expected!
During the battle of Toba-Fushimi
I was so young...
En garde! Get ready to die!
Please, it's enough...
Mrs. Kisaragi, hang in there, please!
Oh, what should I do?
Count, let's call a doctor,
we can't handle this by ourselves.
Well, you can call.
Ushigorou, call Dr. Yamada.
Sure!
Hey, wait!
Don't call Yamada!
Why so?
He lives up and right from here.
In other words, the North-East.
And North-East is an unpropitious direction.
Calling a doctor from an unfavourable direction
would bring no good!
What is this fiction?
It's not fiction, it's faith!
No, it's just a superstition!
Enough!
I'm talking by experience!
It was the 3rd of January at the beginning of the Meiji era,
during the battle of Toba-Fushimi.
I guided the Satsuma battalion,
and near Fushimi, I saw something.
I could distinctly recognise the enemies from a distance.
I realised that that direction would've been unfavourable for us,
so I started to plan.
We turned around,
we waded across the river
and we walked into the enemy's territory!
Attack!
Everyone! Shoot!
We managed to sweep through that battle with no casualties.
All of this was because we avoided an unfavourable direction!
That was just a coincidence!
How long are you planning to say those antiquated things?
You old timer!
What's an old timer!?
It means that your mentality is old!
Grr...
Shaddup, you tomboy!
You blockhead!
What?
You obstinate hoyden!
Good grief, they're wasting my time.
Where the hell did Kisaragi go?
Ah, Dear.
Hey, where's Kisaragi?
We're so busy and she's nowhere to be seen!
Where could she have gone? It's not like her.
Well, take care then.
Thank you very much.
Are you awake?
It's just a bit of overwork, so if you rest for 23 days you'll be okay.
But wasn't Dr. Yamada from North-East?
Yes, I firmly made him come here!
Ugh, that's awful!
Sure,
Just kidding for now!
But Mrs. Kisaragi, you're sure old fashioned.
Yes, I'm fully aware.
Don't get up yet.
But... resting in a day like this...
Don't worry, I've got permission from both Count and Ma'am, so that you can rest with no trouble.
Aww...
Doc, thank ya and stuff!
Is that doctor Yamada?
Who the hell called for that doctor?
You know that I hate those North-East chaps!
Who was it? Who called the quack?
Oh, I apologise...
Whatever,
I've already understood who it was.
There is just one person that would dare disobeying my orders!
Why did you call the doctor?
We needed him so I called him.
Won't you ever listen to me?
Where's Kisaragi?
She is resting.
Huh!? Who authorised her?
I did.
How come!?
I am currently an apprentice bride,
so I have to learn how to take care of a house myself.
Got a problem with that!?
My loss...
This is a commemoration from Ise during the Meiji Era.
It's quite an important piece of history!
Be careful!
Yes, ma'am.
What in the world could be inside this?
So this plate is such a precious thing?
My cat's is better than this- ah!
No!!!
The plate!
Oh, silly me, I broke it!
Sorry!
Hey, what's the matter?
You're all serious right now.
Chill! It's not like I broken the tectonic plate!
We just need to glue the pieces!
Like this!
How's the airing going?
L-Lord.
Where could my plate be?
Oh, there it is!.
This colour, this gloss,
Lord!
Who did this!?
Who broke it!?
I'm sorry, I did I...
I mean, it slipped...
F-F-F... Fi-fi-fi...
Fix this immediately!
Death penalty.
Death penalty?
Benio!
Dear, please wait!
You shut up!
Get ready!
Ack!
Don't run away!
You cunt!
Wait!
Jeez, I didn't think his old mentality could reach these levels!
Benio! Benio!
Wait! Wait!
Count, please quit it immediately!
Getting so furious over a stupid plate...
A plate versus a human life,
which one is more important?
A plate!
Oh well...
That plate is no ordinary plate!
Lord Shimazu of Satsuma in person handed it down to me,
so it's a heirloom for my family!
Be it ten plates or one plate broken, it would ruin my honour as a samurai!
Dear!
Shut the hell up!
I won't back off! My honour as a samurai is on the line!
Dear,
please contain your rage.
Even If I relax, my plate won't be fixed!
You're right, but...
In any case, it could be a cursed plate,
so I would be cautious...
That's right! I won't die completely and my ghost will haunt you forever!
A fashion plate man, a man-
Relax, maid, you won't die alone!
What do you mean by that?
After killing you, I'll commit suicide to set myself free from this dishonour!
Get out the way, Benio!
Or won't you!?
What's wrong, Tenmaru, Chimaru?
Did anything happen here?
Ah, Sublieutenant, just in time!
Ushigorou, what is it?
It's terrible!
Boss and Ranmaru-- err, Ranko, are...
Tenmaru, Chimaru, show us the way!
Dang! If anything bad happens to Boss,
I'll set this whole mansion on fire!
Hey, you...
get out the way!
Are you deaf!?
Can't you hear me?
Get out of my way!
Benio!
Benio...
What have you done, Benio!?
It's better this way.
Why did you break... my plates!?
Kill me too, I beg you.
If you're going to kill someone for a plate,
if the other nine get broken, you'd have to kill nine people.
So, I'll take the responsibility for those nine.
Come on, finish me off!
Benio...
En garde!
I can't take this anymore!
Wait, Ushigorou.
No use in meddling.
But... Boss!
Benio will forge her own destiny.
Damn it!
Hey, old hag!
You creep! How dare you barge into a woman's room with no permission!?
You dumbass! This is not the time to laze off!
But I was given permission by Lord...
You sure don't know anything, ignorance is bliss!
You see, Boss has taken all the responsibility on herself to allow you to rest!
That fool is going to be murdered in no time!
She what?
You better get ready!
As you wish, I'll murder you!
Benio...
I'm coming!
From now on, you'll be part of the Ijuuin family,
take care of yourself.
Father...
I'm sorry for the sadness that awaits.
Shinobu is just going to...
watch me get killed, isn't he?
He can't oppose to his scary grandfather.
Idiot!
I hate you!
The Count from Satsuma's rage has reached its peak,
and is ready to murder the young Hanamura Benio,
who has had enough of Shinobu's lack of resoluteness!
Shinobu, the only person she can count on, is just standing there, dumbfounded.
So, our High Collar Lady has already made up her mind,
oh, how sad it is for a youthful seventeen year-old girl to die like this...
The faint and fleeting contact with Shinobu,
is it just a vanishing dream or an illusion?
Next time on Here Comes the Smart Alec:
Farewell, failed bride
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I'm Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is for me
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I'm Benio
Just a smidgen bit pretentious tomboyish lady
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra