Here Comes the High Collar Lady
Did you hear about it?
Did you ever experience it?
Two shockingly beautiful eyes
A startling romance
All-consuming
Inescapable
With a Taishou Era charming lady
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
High, High, High,
High, High, High, High Collar Lady's coming
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Is he Hikaru Genji or Narihira?
The super-handsome Sublieutenant receives mountains of love letters every day,
however, among those there is someone different from the other girls,
with whom he makes a date in secret.
In an attempt to protect our High Collar Lady,
these two mad lads decide to tail Shinobu.
But due to Benio's unawareness, Ushigorou's plan fails
and she happens to stumble across Shinobu's date of all things!
Was she a fool for being trustful? Or is the deceiving side in the wrong?
Our High Collar Lady is troubled and can't sleep anymore. When will the truth come to light?
This hurt more than I had expected,
I have to do something about it...
It's a bummer that we have to be the first to wake up in here.
It's tough, isn't it?
I know, right?
However, I'm sure that good things await us.
Ah? What's that?
What could it be?
It must be Ranko exercising.
You're right. Let's have her teach us!
Ranko!
Can you teach us how to ex-
Huh!?
Sorry for disturbing you.
We thought it was Ranko...
It's okay.
So, wanna try?
N-No worries!
We're good!
Our apologies!
Working out truly washes all troubles away!
Episode 21
Life is Short, Yet Riddled with Worries
Looks delicious. Benio will surely like it.
What is this?
After
She'll definitely be hungry.
Ah, is that so?
Good morning.
Good morning!
This is going to be yet another lively morning!
My stomach feels heavy and my chest hurts!
Lady Benio, aren't you eating?
I'm not in the mood,
I don't feel like eating.
Oh...
But not eating will be no good for your health.
It's okay.
W-What's wrong, Benio?
You usually eat three bowls of rice first thing in the morning,
did you scavenge and eat something bad?
Oh, I sincerely apologise
for not being hungry all the time!
I'm so mad!
She doesn't seem to be well.
I can't believe it...
This is the omen for an incoming calamity!
I hope it's not an earthquake, though.
Cut it out,
why are you joking about this,
you should worry more about her!
What might have happened to her?
And yet I swore that
I wouldn't think about him.
Benio!
Benio.
Here comes the reason I lost my appetite.
Did something happen?
Going to school without eating
won't be good for your health.
Can't you at least drink some milk?
Boom!
Please, leave me alone!
I can't keep calm when I see your face!
Leave me alone, don't look at me!
Benio?
Benio...
Shinobu?
What happened now?
It seems like she doesn't like me.
It truly hurts my pride.
Even though I
have always been popular among girls.
Moreover,
I've always been serious, yet she hasn't got any closer to me.
It's already been a while
since I first met her,
but that bird keeps flying away from my arms.
Ushigorou, let's finally go back to school.
At your service!
Benio!
Will you be fine, having skipped breakfast?
It's all good.
Boss! You've done your homework this time, have you?
I don't care about homework right now,
I'll be happy just to breath some fresh air
and meet up with all of my classmates again.
Alright, let's go.
Aye!
She seems in a bad shape.
I'm worried... What should I do?
Benio!
Benio, I'll accompany you to school.
Hell no!
Ushigorou.
Yes?
Can't you go faster?
I'm telling you to increase your speed!
Alright, but just so you know, it'll be real fast,
so try not to fly away!
Benio!
Ushigorou! Faster! Don't slack off!
Sure...
She's avoiding me after all.
Shinobu, wait!
Shinobu...
Why aren't you going with Benio?
That was my intention,
but it looks like she just loathes me.
Then why aren't you following her?
If I do that, I'll just end up hurting her more instead.
Don't lie!
If it were me, I'd put my life on the line
and chase the person I love no matter how far.
I'm sure that Benio was hoping that you'd chase her.
Could it be...
If you can't understand such a simple thing,
you don't deserve your playboy title.
Deep down, Benio...
She thinks about nothing but you.
This...
This is why she tells you she hates you.
If you can't understand such a simple thing,
hands off Benio!
Ranmaru!
Idiot... Idiot...
Ushigorou, you're an idiot!
Boss, did ya say somethin'?
I told you to go faster, but why did you actually do it?
What're ya trynna say?
Oh, my bad, my bad.
I always follow your orders...
You're not seeing the point!
I... I...
I'm not saying that we should've been side by side with him.
Then I was supposed to speed up, right?
But.. But I didn't want you to run fast either...
Boss!
Did ya want me to go faster?
Or did ya want me to go at a slower pace? Just tell me!
Can't you understand?
I don't get ya at all.
You obstinate henchman.
Hyaah!
Ouch!
That hurt...
Now I get it!
You have that thing for Shinobu!
N-No way!
Hanamura!
Why, it's you, teacher!
Teacher, good morning.
Oh, right, it's been a long while.
Now that I think about it, it's truly been a long time.
Maybe this is why I'm feeling so nostalgic!
Teacher!
Hanamura being nostalgic? This must be a devilish omen.
Righteous path towards wifehood
I hope nothing bad happens today...
Good morning, everyone!
My!
Benio!
It's been ages!
You haven't gone to school in a while, haven't you?
A lot happened...
But since I'm here today,
let's celebrate with some anmitsu!
I'm sorry, but I have to go straight home.
Oh, why so?
Osono was officially betrothed.
Oh?
But it's not just me, Kanoko too.
Otei too.
Even Shizuko and Matsuya.
In other words, we can't waste any time eating anmitsu.
Excuse us!
Osono, when will you get married?
Uh-huh, before asking others, tell us about yourself!
Hey, listen, who was the first to be engaged?
Shizuko, right?
No, I think it was Kanoko!
Don't forget Matsuya!
No, Shizuko!
Kyaa kyaa kyaa
Wow-wow
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe...
Matsuya for sure!
Not a chance!
Dear me...
It's been a short while since I last came to school,
Left out
but it feels like I've been left behind.
How miserable...
It's time for all of us to decide our path.
We'll graduate soon, after all.
Tamaki...
What's with that long face?
You're marrying Ijuuin, aren't you?
Ah! Speaking of which...
Regarding who was the first to be engaged... Wasn't it Benio?
You're right! It was her!
Silence!
Wifehood
Okay everyone, before checking your homework, I want to talk about something.
Since many of you are brides-to-be by now,
I would like to give you some suggestions.
Excuse me, Teacher!
What is it, Kobayashi?
So, while giving us academic advice
could indeed be profitable,
I think it would be better to listen to the stories
of the ones that already have experience
to receive concrete information.
Please, teacher!
Let's do it!
Silence!
If you want me to share experiences,
you're out of luck!
I put my heart and soul into teaching,
so, as an unmarried woman,
I'm not in the position to tell you anything!
Have you got it now?
Teacher, don't let yourself down.
Right,
We didn't mean to ask you,
we have an apprentice bride in this class,
who lives at his husband-to-be's house.
She is the expert in here!
That's not...
I see. Well, then...
Yes.
I want to hear Hanamura's experience first-hand!
Benio, tell us more!
Please!
Hanamura, please share your valuable experience.
Okay...
Uhm... I... I...
How do you call your future husband?
Have you held his hand?
Have you kissed him?
Mwah, mwah!
I... I...
Alright, Hanamura, tell us candidly
everything about your animated life,
I'll give you my permission.
No, it's an order!
I...
It's not like I...
You don't have to worry!
You don't!
We're waiting!
Please!
Benio, tell us.
Tamaki... why are you doing this too...
I have the right to listen, after all.
You understand why, don't you?
Then, go on.
Got it.
Everyone, then I'll be honest.
Hurry up!
Actually, I don't have any kind of personal experience...
to tell you...
to tell you!
Benio...
Tailoring Club
Shinobu with a geisha?
I can't believe it...
He'd never do such things.
But...
No, you must have misunderstood something!
But I even spotted them together,
and she even sends him letters.
I'm not lying!
If it were a lie,
I wouldn't be crying this much!
Hey, Benio, so you do like Shinobu, after all.
Not a chance! I'll never like him!
Liar, liar, liar.
You wouldn't care this much otherwise.
I told you that I don't!
You crying this much just tells the truth.
As I thought, my best friend sees through me.
In any case, Shinobu likes that geisha.
You loved him too, Tamaki, didn't you?
Isn't this a shock?
Oh, regarding that...
I've already let go.
Tamaki...
I don't want to feel uneasy forever.
I want to be on my own for a while
and do something that I like.
And then, I'll find somebody new to love.
Life is short...
Fall in love, maiden...
Tamaki is elegant as usual,
she hasn't lost heart at all.
Benio, we may end up walking a different path,
but we will both find our way to happiness regardless.
I will.
I'll act as if I've never met
that dumbass sublieutenant!
Here we go again...
There must be some misunderstanding about that geisha,
I know who Shinobu is, he wouldn't do that.
It really seems like she knows him better than me!
So miserable...
Ushigorou, stop!
Stop!
Let's go the opposite way.
What, aren't we goin' home now?
Just do it!
Aight!
Whoa, whoa!
The Ijuuin mansion should be on the right,
but she went to the opposite direction,
as a teacher, I cannot let this slide.
Wait, wait, rickshawman.
I need
Alright.
Hurry up, chase that rickshaw!
Chase?
That's not a good thing to do...
Stop loitering!
Hurry up!
Aight, aight...
Hurry!
Make haste!
Aight, aight...
Can't you run a bit faster, or speed up,
I've said it in a million ways!
Miss, are you planning to keep complaining from up there? Do you think anyone could do this?
If you gotta hurry that badly, do it yourself.
Coward, you're looking down of me just because I'm a woman?
Let's switch, then!
Bonk
Let's go!!!
Get away if you don't want to get crashed!
Make way!
What was that?
That was really wild...
Now turn right.
Go to Yanagibashi.
Yanagibashi? Ooh, wanna beat up those Violet squad dudes?
That's not it.
Then where the hell are we goin'?
Of course we'll be meeting a geisha.
It can't be,
hangin' out with a geisha ain't somethin' for women!
You don't see me as a woman in any case, so...
But... ya see...
Ushi!
Aight!
Oh, I can see them!
Get out the way!
Then, I'll be going.
Have a good time, Boss!
Visiting a geisha!?
Unbelievable...
I must be hallucinating...
May I come in?
The battle will start soon...
Y-Yes!
Good evening...
Oh?
Good evening.
Young Lady...
As much as our High Collar Lady can be modern,
isn't hanging out with a geisha
a bit too much?
Cards are laid on the table
and tonight there is no room for forgiveness.
It's the decisive woman versus woman fight.
Our High Collar Lady is trying to clarify her bond with Shinobu,
and asks Kichiji to marry Shinobu.
This woman-to-woman discussion gets fired up...
However,
what Kichiji says totally,
totally exceeds Benio's expectations...
Next time in Here comes the High Collar Lady:
Falling Flowers, Blooming Flowers and Flowers of Love.
Episode 22
Falling Flowers, Blooming Flowers and Flowers of Love
Don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Please call me High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I am Benio
Just a tomboyish lady with a smidgen of pretension
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation
Encoding & quality checking
Quality checking
Timing
alucardnoyuuutsu
Anonymous
Ziusudra
Perevodildo