Here Comes Smart-san
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Have you heard the gossip already?
And have you made sure yourself with those eyes?
Two shockingly beautiful glazzies
A shockingly overflowing romance
The hottest topic now
It's all about this
A charming lady from the Taishou Era
Here she is, High Collar Lady
With her gentle heart, winning everyone over
Our High Collar Lady got woken up bright and early to learn housework the hard way.
But hold on,
a true High Collar Lady doesn't give up this easily.
However, we mustn't forget that she got all 1s for a reason.
We're left with two guys who have been left alone
and a boy that can't stand to lose-
Err, I meant a lady, High Collar Lady.
This story takes place in London-
err, wait,
we're at Ijuuins' mansion in Tokyo.
Episode 9
The first palpitation
I already know it, by Satsuma traditions,
women eat alone in a corner in the kitchen.
No, today you'll be eating in the dining room.
R-Really, Mrs. Kisaragi?
Certainly. Then, Lady Benio, this way, please.
What a strange turn of events!
Please sit here, Lady Benio.
I'm awful at manners,
but having a nice meal in the morning doesn't sound bad.
Chefs here must be skilled.
Then let's eat!
Hey, hey, you can bring breakfast at any time!
Nay,
you won't eat just yet.
I'll be teaching you politesse.
Politesse?
Sounds delicious, what is it?
It's how you need to behave
when you're eating!
Wha!?
So it's not a dish.
Right.
You need to know table manners before eating.
Ack...
Whoa!
Fancy!
Bon appetit!
Wow!
Lady Benio, Lady Benio!
Why are you so distracted?
Ah, no, it's nothing.
Then tell me all the basic manners I've taught you.
First of all, cutlery must be used going from the most external pieces.
Red wine must accompany meat,
while white wine goes with fish.
Sake!
Also, eating soup must be done silently.
Well done.
Listen, even prisoners
eat three meals a day.
Where did my breakfast go?
Waiter, bring Lady Benio's breakfast!
Excuse me.
I wonder what they prepared for me,
my mouth is watering!
One slice of bread? Just this?
Yes, eating too much is no good!
Got it, then let's dig in.
Lady Benio, where are you going?
Can't you guess? To school.
Compared to this place, school is way better.
It's the first time I really want to go there!
So, I'll be going, Mrs. Kisaragi.
No, wait a minute, Lady Benio!
Ugh,
do you not want me to go?
Exactly.
What,
you don't have the right to do this!
Do you want to go at all costs?
Isn't it obvious?
Any issue with this?
Then I'll see you later.
However, you need to know that it's Sunday.
Aah!
Aw-aw-aw...
That hurt...
This is why I wanted to teach you politesse.
This is bad...
A man?
Huh-uh...
I see. Oh, I see...
The five fundamental seasonings.
Sugar, salt, vinegar, soy sauce and miso.
I should be all set!
It's not that hard, you just need the spirit.
Go ahead.
Sorry to bother you, Lady Benio.
The chef is here to explain how to
bake bread in a stove, please come.
Finally!
A stove, huh.
It's all good!
First of all you need to mix flour, yeast, a pinch of salt and butter,
then you wait until it's fully risen,
after that the butter must be spread on the bottom of the baking tray.
Uh?
I told you'd learn how to bake bread in a stove,
I didn't say I'd teach you how to prepare bread!
Then what should I...
From now on, just remember how to
bake biscuits.
I'm so done!
Next is flower arrangement.
Please, just follow your instinct.
'kay.
Hmm.
This should give it a nice touch.
What,
it's identical to mine!
I have been attending some classes
at the prestigious Ikenobou school.
This should do it.
Oh, my flowers...
Yours is not Ikenobou style at all, it's just pathetic!
Agh, I'm so mad!
In our upper class society, fellowships,
namely, social life, are the most important thing.
Now I'll explain you how to knot-tie a mizuhiki,
an envelope that's typically gifted during ceremonies.
Did you listen, Lady Benio?
Yes, I did.
P-Please go ahead.
First of all, I'll be showing you how to knot-tie the envelope.
Then, let's begin.
You put this like this,
after that you do this.
You bend that thing there, then you keep going that way.
Here, it's done.
Now it's your turn, Lady Benio, do the same.
I could try, but I've only seen it once...
Well, I'll do it, .
let's see...
I bend this here, then I do it like that...
Like this, maybe.
Like this.
Like this!
Oh well...
What in the world is this?
Do it once again!
Only hitting someone's weak points is so unfair!
Alright, the early bird gets the worm,
I'll learn all of the noble words and shock her!
Omawari, akaka...
Iriiri, okabe...
Omawari = vegetables
Akaka = red beans
Iriiri = roasted soybeans
Okabe = tofu
Misomiso = salad dressed with miso
Harihari = dried melon
Surusuru = dried squid
Trying to remember even those things...
Poor thing.
When I see this worn-out visage of yours, my chest hurts.
But you see, I believe in you.
I want you to make a mess of this old-fashioned,
static mansion that's binded by traditions.
It may be tough...
Do your best, High Collar Lady.
Huff.
I'll always watch over you.
What? What?
My heart is beating so deeply.
Get outta my way, go-go-go-go!
Go-go-go-go-go!
Boss, you're looking pretty pale lately, are you okay?
Yeah, I've been through a lot, but I can't give up.
We're late again.
Boss, couldn't you wake up a tad earlier?
It can-t be helped,
I need to wake up early to learn chores,
and many times I stay up late.
Then,
see you later, Ushigorou.
Let's hope I don't snag it this time.
Hop- ah!
Benio!
Benio, hang in there, are you okay?
Today I'm not my usual self.
What are you talking about?
If we don't hurry up we won't make it in time!
Let's go!
Boss! Boss Benio!
You forgot this!
Take it!
Thanks, Ushigorou,
then, I'll be going!
Have a nice day and take care!
So, Benio, how is it going?
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious? Your mission to destroy your engagement.
Not too bad.
Really? That's great!
Do your best.
Alright, everyone.
Please hand me the homework I assigned you yesterday.
So shamelessly honest...
Am I dreaming?
Compared to the housework I have to learn,
going to school is just a child's play.
I can finally rest.
Let's go, go-go-go-go!
Boss Benio, I know it's tough, but cheer up!
Hey, Boss!
Huh? Don't worry,
I'm totally fine!
You see, Boss, whenever I meet your father and Nanny,
they always ask me about you,
but I never know how to answer.
I see.
Could you deliver a letter to Father?
Yes, that's a-okay.
Ranmaru!
Ah, Ushi!
There's a letter from Boss Benio!
Really?
Quick! Give me the letter!
Wait, wait, wait
Understood, I'll deliver it right now!
The Great God
Mr. Hanamura, please read it as soon as possible!
I'll omit all of the introduction,
I'll write this in one go.
I've been spending my days at the Ijuuins' mansion safely,
all of the Ijuuins are deeply tender people,
in particular, the count is incredibly kind,
and I deeply respect him.
Thanks to all of them,
there is nothing I have to worry about.
I sleep like a log and when I get up everything's clean and tidy.
As for kitchen chores, they didn't make me do anything at all.
Moreover, I cheerfully enjoy my meals with the entire family,
so please don't worry about anything.
Yours truly, Benio.
I see, I see,
reading this relieved me.
I'm delighted to read that she's happy.
If Benio is speaking that fondly of her new life,
it might be hard for her to come home.
Oh, Ushigorou,
why are you crying?
I... I... feel bad for Boss.
Ushi, what do you mean?
Hold on,
are you saying that she's lying?
Ushigorou, tell us the truth.
Ushi, what is it?
No, it's that...
Reading those contented words by Boss
made me cry tears of joy!
Oh, is it? Great, great.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Is it true?
Calligraphers have existed for a long time.
It is said that by reading those words,
Poems: Ancient and Modern
you can understand the writer's personality.
This book is often only accredited to Fujiwara no Yukinari, however...
I-I see you're
diligently taking notes.
The three main calligraphers are Fujiwara no Yukinari,
Fujiwara no Sukemasa and Ono no Toufuu.
And you, Benio, will be learning about these three--
Wha-!?
What is that?
Ah-ah-ah, that-!
A character face!
Oh? You didn't like it?
Sorry for the hinderance.
What happened?
I'm here to take Lady Benio's laundry.
Oh,
right!
They're all in my room,
thank you!
You mustn't do that!
You need to do your laundry by yourself!
On top of it, Young Master's too!
And Count's too!
All of this is your duty!
That's the duty of wives in the Ijuuin family!
No!
At this rate,
I could die before Mrs. Kisaragi.
Who will be first?
Hey, listen, what do you think about Young Master's fiancee?
It's such a shame!
To think that I expected Young Master's wife to be as beautiful as him!
She's also pug-nosed, she'll just ruin his reputation!
Right?
Maybe we'd be better than her.
True, true!
How cruel of them!
It's not like I'm here because I wanted to, after all.
He's always trying to act young.
Disgraceful!
What are you doing?
How are you so incautious?
Placing women's laundry on top of men's is an aberration!
Men's laundry is going to be stained!
Throw this dirty laundry away!
What the...
You cretin!
You'd better remember this.
I can't take it anymore,
such chauvinism, such anachronism,
I'm so sick of all of this!
W-Wait, geezer!
What!?
En garde!
Let that be a lesson!
Lord!
Lady Benio!
L-L-Lord, are you feeling alright?
What did you do?
How dare you disrespect me that blatantly!
Get out of my house now!
Go away!
I'm reluctant
to go away because of this,
but it can't be helped,
if you talk that way about women,
let's have a fight!
Huh... she's serious about this.
Let's see if women are as inferior as you think they are,
won't you?
Come on!
Wanna fight?
You bastard...
You're too impudent for a girl!
Yes!
I see that you don't hold your life dear.
Do you think that I'll fall behind just like a woman?
I'll tear you apart!
Get ready!
Bring it on!
This is terrible!
Young Master, Young Master!
Young Master!
Lady Benio and Lord are...
Has it already begun?
You're too relaxed! Please, come stop Lord!
I know that Lord has aged,
but he has mastered martial arts in the Houzouin-ryuu school...
At this rate L-Lady Benio is going to...
Well,
I wonder who's really in danger.
Shinobu, hurry up and stop your grandfather!
Now, now,
just watch and you'll see
my future wife's capabilities.
She'll get murdered!
I-I'm scared!
Take this!
Sorry, Shinobu,
you even told me that you didn't mind if I messed your house up.
I keep remembering it...
The way my heart beat that time.
I didn't want to run away halfway,
but at this stage I'll just take it as it comes, I can't lose!
An elderly, yet still skillful warrior from Satsuma
versus a girl from the Taishou era who's fighting for freedom.
A lot is about to happen!
One more stubborn than the other,
God only knows the outcome of this duel.
They say not to pick up fights,
but seeing a tomboyish combat style
knocking down an old count is great too!
After that, our apprentice bride
will try to pack her things up and leave,
but this Satsuma warrior is not to be understimated,
and will say something unexpected.
Next time on Here Comes Smart-san:
Gulp down the medicine of love,
don't miss it!
How are you feeling? I'm Benio
Please call me a High Collar Lady,
because I'm in that period
When it's getting so hard
to be honest with people I love
I just want to know what's in his heart,
while he goes away I want him to turn around,
to give me once again this loving glance
Ah, how frustrating it is for me
to have this unrequited feeling
How are you feeling? I'm Benio
Just a smidgen bit pretentious tomboyish lady
Translation    alucardnoyuuutsu
Timing    Perevodildo
QC    Ziusudra