People or heirlooms?
That is the question - or so Shakespeare would say.
The count is furious
After vowing to split her open,
Shinobu, who calculated the timing, intervened and stopped the count,
but Benio was already determined to leave the house.
For once, the count's stubbornness
was not approved by the other family members.
So, Shinobu decided to go look for Benio.
I dispatch.
However, there's a problem-
Her father is just as strict!
Do you understand why I brough this here?
This is deplorable! I feel so sorry to the Sublieutenant!
Let me say that
it is Shinobu who is deplorable!
I despise that womaniser!
Womaniser?
He has this many love letters every day,
also he's in really close to a geisha from Yaginabashi.
What? A geisha?
And sadly, on top of that, she's a bit prettier than me!
I can't believe that he'd do such things...
Don't you trust my words, Father?
Shut up!
There is no way an imperial soldier would do such indecent things!
Soldier here and soldier there,
are soldiers such admirable people?
Don't hit the table!
Aren't you the one doing that!?
Shut up, shut up!
Are you affronting soldiers!?
You just trust others more than your own daughter!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Like father, like daughter...
Benio...
My one and only Benio...
Episode 17
Wandering Petals
W-W-What are you doing?
This way, this way.
Please don't hurt me!
Can't you understand?
Father and daughter are finally quarreling again,
so you don't need to hurry,
as it will take quite a while!
Ma'am,
a lovely father-daughter quarrel has started after all this time!
You're still the daughter of a soldier!
I'm your daughter!
What?
Oh, this house's people
seem to truly enjoy family quarrels.
What a nice evening.
Listening to this commotion really makes you feel at home.
Oh,
if it isn't Ushi.
Just in time, I need you to take me somewhere.
You see, I don't want to go anywhere tonight.
What's the reason for that?
Idiot!
Yep!
I'm busy listening to this father-daughter quarrel!
Don't find silly excuses!
So, let me hop in, I'll give you a good tip.
Oh, alright...
Okay, here we are.
Okay, you can start going.
You still can't understand!?
You're the one who can't understand!
What?
Are you affronting your father!?
Professor, Professor Ranmaru.
Oh, Ken, it's been a while.
It was not a while,
you haven't held any lesson in ages,
please put yourself in our shoes!
My bad, my bad,
I simply didn't have the time to do so.
Welcome back, Professor!
Oh, you're beautiful as always!
Hey, hey, hey, when will we rehearse?
Calm down, calm down, one at a time.
I'm not going anywhere, so we can practise anything you want.
So we'll be holding
our spectacle as planned, right?
Of course!
So we must get in touch with the theatre!
Give it a call.
Sure, sure!
Then we must get our costumes ready too!
Yes, I'll leave it to you.
Yessir!
Hey, Professor, since we're all reunited here after a long while,
shall we celebrate by drinking some good alcohol?
Good idea.
Then take some food
and go buy drinks at the liquor store.
Sure!
Young Professor, Young Professor!
Oh my, what is it?
You see, they gave us permission
to use the Imperial Theatre on the 31st!
T
Th
The
The I
The Im
The Imp
The Impe
The Imper
The Imperi
The Imperia
The Imperial
The Imperial T
The Imperial Th
The Imperial The
The Imperial Thea
The Imperial Theat
The Imperial Theatr
The Imperial Theatre
The Imperial Theatre w
The Imperial Theatre wa
The Imperial Theatre was
The Imperial Theatre was o
The Imperial Theatre was op
The Imperial Theatre was ope
The Imperial Theatre was open
The Imperial Theatre was opene
The Imperial Theatre was opened
The Imperial Theatre was opened i
The Imperial Theatre was opened in
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 19
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 191
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911.
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911..
The Imperial Theatre was opened in 1911...
What the hell are you waiting for?
Isn't Benio your fiancée?
Then go get her!
tnaruatseR
Here we are!
Colonel Innen, watch your step!
Why would I? I'm not drunk at all!
Oh, darn!
I told you to pay attention!
Are you alright, Lieutenant?
I'm not the type to collapse after that little alcohol,
to the next bar!
Let's go to yer favourite place this time!
Then let's do it.
I wanna ride that horse! Stop it!
Not a chance! It would be awful!
Any problem?
I'm the Lieutenant Innen!
That's the Sublieutenant Ijuuin!
What, Ijuuin?
Hey, Ijuuin!
Sublieutenant! Stop a second!
Oh, yikes.
Stop there!
Gimme that horse!
Okay, go!
Stop!
Hey you, bastard!
My bad!
Hey you!
Do you have any respect!?
How insolent!
Learn manners,
did you forget military etiquette, you moron!?
Ow-ow-ow...
Ohh,
isn't this where I got on the rickshaw?
So we've only gone round and round from the very start!
Yeah!
I told ya that I didn't wanna leave, didn't I?
Here we go!
What did I get myself into?
Anyway, perhaps because you grew up selfish,
you don't have enough patience.
No, I'm patient enough.
No matter what kind of man Mr. Ijuuin is,
as a bride, you must dedicate him every ounce of patience.
The cigarettes "Golden Bat"
were put on the market ten years prior, in 1906,
and cost 4000 yen per pack.
At home you obey your parents,
as a wife, you obey your husband,
when you're old you obey your sons.
This is how women and children in Japan
have to behave.
You're so antiquated, Father.
Go back to the mansion. Shinobu is probably worried about you.
Oh no... anachronism isn't just a Ijuuin thing.
Benio, go back there!
So you won't care no matter what happens to me, Father!?
Benio.
Once a woman leaves a house,
she shall never return there!
Father!
Excuses are futile!
Understood.
Then, I'll go.
I'll never come back!
Hey, Lady Benio,
Since I knew you'd argue for a while,
I thought about making some noodles for dinner!
I'll never taste your noodles again, Nanny.
Why so?
I got kicked out. This time from my house.
What are you saying?
Wait just a second!
Why does it always end up like this?
Wait here, don't be so hasty!
My dear, I couldn't do otherwise.
It's for her sake,
I have to send her back to the Ijuuins'.
Lord, don't be so thoughtless!
What's the matter? Why are you upset?
Weren't you going to commit suicide?
You think I'm stupid?
If you have a daughter like Benio,
no matter how many times you kill yourself it won't be enough!
You have a point.
How insulting! Alright, if it has to be this way...
I'll go away in no time!
Young Lady, please stop it...
Not happening.
Well then, take care, nanny.
Take care of Father, okay?
This is just the worst.
Hey, Professor,
it's been a long time, huh?
Where were you?
Now that the food is ready
and we have already plans for the next spectacle,
won't you take the lead for this toast, Professor?
Alright.
Then,
to our health, to the Fujieda-style acting
and to the success of next month's spectacle.
Cheers!
Oh Lord!
Ranmaru!
This is terrible!
Why are you such in a hurry, Nanny?
Young Lady has fled from the house once again!
Stop her, Ranmaru!
This is awful!
I gotta go too!
Sorry, everyone, I'm leaving!
Why's that?
Where?
Uh, I don't really know it either.
What will we do with next month's show?
Now it's not the time for that!
I had already booked the theatre...
And I had already ordered the costumes...
And all of this food, on top of it!
Then, see you, bye-bye!
Oh, come on, Professor...
Please wait!
I'm at a loss...
Benio!
Nanny, what should we do?
I didn't mean to disturb your plans,
I just want to stop Benio.
Wait!
Ugh, I can't take this anymore!
You only care about soldiers,
I won't ever come back there,
I don't regret you, stupid dad!
Benio!
Sorry for the wait! Then, let's go!
Young Lady!
She's gone...
Ushi! This is bad! Really bad!
What's it, Nanny?
Young Lady and Ranmaru have fled, please stop them!
Then I'll lend you a hand.
Mister, please get off the rickshaw,
now gimme my tip!
You're kidding me,
I didn't move an inch ever since I got on this rickshaw,
what in the world would I pay you for!?
Now shut up
and get outta here!
Boss!
Ushi!
Lord...
I might've gone a bit overboard.
Maybe you reprimanded her too much,
but i know that it's hard to deal with her.
I would be happy if Benio returned home,
but after all I have no choice but
make her come back to the Ijuuin mansion.
What could that be?
Excuse me!
So he's here after all!
It's you, Shinobu.
Sorry for intruding so late.
Commander Hanamura,
I'm so sorry for what I've caused this time.
No, it's not only your fault.
Benio should be here...
Hasn't she come back to your place yet?
I'm sure I told her to come back there.
She must have not arrived yet,
she went out only a while ago, after all.
I'll look for her.
Excuse me, I'll use your telephone.
Hello, I want to talk with the Ijuuin family in Otowadai.
Yes, Ijuuin.
Hey, Boss, this is the wrong way,
it doesn't lead to the count's mansion.
Who told you we'd go back there?
Ah, I see.
Then, if Benio returns,
lead her to her room and make her rest.
I'll be back shortly. See you later.
She's not home yet.
No need to worry, it might be hard for her to show up after all of this.
Really...
Well then, I'll go home and look for her.
Thank you.
Yes. Sorry for the trouble.
Mr. Ijuuin.
What is it?
You see, Benio told me about
a geisha
from Yanagibashi or something.
Ah, about that thing,
it's nothing you should worry about, Commander,
you can relax.
I see. I trusted you all along.
Thank you so much.
Benio jumped to conclusions right away, so I didn't tell anything,
I'll talk to her about it when the time comes.
I hope so.
Then, I'll be leaving.
Mr. Ijuuin!
Is there something else?
Take care of her.
I know she might be careless-
Not at all!
Benio is the kind of person
I thought she would be,
on the contrary, I think that I'm the one that's worthy of her.
Mr. Ijuuin...
Thank you.
Hey, Benio, what are we going to do?
Stop being loud. I'm thinking.
You've been thinking for a while, haven't you?
Well, I'm out of both houses now, you know,
I can't come back to neither.
After saying those things,
it's too late to come back home.
On the other hand, I would never return to the mansion.
Why does it always end up like this?
I'm sick of it.
Uhm, Boss Benio,
how about, on this occasion,
we drink something and paaarty hard?
You're right! That'd be a great idea!
I might try hot sake this time too!
Please, no!
You know that Benio can't hold alcohol!
Then you can go home on your own.
I'm done with your rudeness!
Ushigorou, let's go!
Hooray! Lessgo, lessgo!
C'mon, Ushigoro, lessgo!
Rudeness, rudeness, why is everyone so rude to me?
I'll keep you company!
What's wrong with Shinobu? That womaniser...
Right, right, right, right.
On top of it, Father was on his side.
Drinking bring so much joy! Let's get fired up!
Sorry for the wait.
Another one!
As I thought, Boss!
Ushi! Don't make her drink any more!
Hey, you,
alcohol is the right cure!
Screw Shinobu, screw Father,
screw soldiers, dammit!
How annoying.
Lieutenant, let's leave.
Don't say nonsense, we've just started, I'm just a bit tipsy.
Whew...
Whoops!
The hell you doin'!?
What was that?
I sat on something.
My hat!
You bastard! How dare you do this to a soldier?
A soldier? You think I care?
Huh!?
Her eyes are glazed!
This is dangerous!
Ijuuin's a soldier, Father's a soldier,
this disgusting guy's a soldier too!
You bitch, respect imperial soldiers!
What's with this?
One, two, three!
That's your sword? It's nothing special.
My precious saber...
Soldiers, soldiers,
stop boasting that!
Our high collar lady is furious,
but she chose a risky opponent.
This man is Shinobu's direct superior
and is like a devil that can control his future.
But of course, she has no clue.
What's for sure is that her future
is black as the darkest night!
The imperial army is no match
for the drunken blooming Benio,
as she stands up against five men.
Benio keeps fighting and Ushigorou calls for reinforcements,
but Shinobu is nowhere to be seen,
while the count comes across the situation!
Benio's surely incurred a lot of grudge!
Next time in Here Comes the High Collar Lady:
Incurring grudge is dangerous!
Don't miss it!