Like a butterfly on a flower,
Ranmaru decided to cross-dress
and came to support Benio, without knowing how she truly feels.
However, this disguise could very well be unmasked,
in fact Shinobu, perhaps recognising Ranmaru,
mysteriously started giggling.
the old and wise count's keen look managed to look through Ranmaru's cover,
and things took a turn for the worse.
However, Benio used her force
and got to dispel all doubts. However...
Enter the bath with Benio and wash her back.
And here we are, with troubles piling up one after another!
Episode 13
Love is a sailboat of reflection
That was awfully close, Ranmaru.
But at least they didn't discover my identity, don't you think?
You're right!
I was so scared for a moment.
Excuse me, Lady Benio.
Count would like you to make tea.
Understood, I'll go make it right now.
Let's go,
Ranko.
Sure, Lady Benio.
Then, I shall leave.
Good night, Benio.
Good night.
Oh, Ranmaru, do you have a room now?
Yes, with only three maids living there.
Three?
Then, you need to be extra careful to keep your cover.
Don't worry, don't worry,
I'll just act as usual,
we'll just sleep, after all.
You're right, today went smoothly.
See you tomorrow!
As usual, with his usual...
flower-patterned loincloth!?
This is bad!
Ranmaru!
Oh, never mind.
Ranko! Ranko!
Ranko!
What's the matter, Lady Benio?
Impressive.
Lady Benio, do you need help with something?
Ah, no, it's nothing important.
Then, you can let us seniors take care of Ranko.
T-Thank you.
Wasn't she kind of panicked?
I wanna eat some grilled chicken...
Here it is.
Pads aren't suitable for people who turn while asleep.
I wonder if Ranmaru tosses while sleeping.
Just as I thought!
Hey, Ranmaru, wake up!
What is it, Benio?
Quiet!
Young Master...
Come to my room, okay?
Uh, why?
Do you really think they won't notice that?
Got it.
Hurry up.
We'll move your things tomorrow morning.
Getting to sleep in the same room as Benio...
I am so happy!
Don't get too excited!
I will sleep here and you will sleep there.
Got it? If you cross the border, I won't let it slide!
Yeah, I'm aware.
Goodnight then, Benio.
Goodnight.
It's so bright...
Okay, I'm ready.
Benio, are you awake yet?
Benio!
Benio... Huh?
Oh, so you were here, Lady Benio.
Hey, good morning!
Ranko, what's the deal with that face of yours?
Benio used to be such a late riser,
I can't believe this is happening.
Lady Benio, what is it you're doing here?
What am I doing... Can't you tell? I'm sweeping.
Masters should not be doing this kind of work!
Why would you have maids otherwise?
But I am learning to become a good homemaker,
so I need to make some practise.
Wait, Lady Benio!
Hey, hey, who gave that order?
It was Mrs. Kisaragi.
Ugh, it's always that hag!
It's not like she's making me do this out of spite,
that woman is just devoted to her duties.
No, I'll just give her hell!
Come on, don't be so rude.
What are you talking about?
Wasn't making a mess of this place
your initial goal here?
Good morning!
Good morning, everyone.
Well done.
Who arranged this flower?
Who was it?
Uhm, I...
It can't be, it is not your style at all.
I was about to say that I had Ranmaru arrange this.
Did you do it all by yourself?
Yes.
It's an excellent job.
Well, I just did what I could.
However, you did something unnecessary!
You mustn't do it for Lady Benio, or she'll never learn!
From now on, don't do unwanted things!
Understood!?
I'm to blame as I was the one giving Ranko the order.
No, it's my fault because I accepted.
You two must know your own places.
Got it?
Mrs. Kisaragi!
There's some lint on your clothes.
Ok, I cut it, sorry for troubling you.
Thank you.
What is that!?
I've been so careless!
This is disgraceful!
Today, you'll learn how to write haiku.
By mixing quiet and simplicity, you can even reach the zen.
This is the essence of haiku.
This is a poem by Matsuo Basho.
Frogs jumped in an old pond and it splashed.
This is a well-known haiku.
Go towards her!
For this reason...
I can't stand frogs!
Whoa!
Ranko...
I made a haiku too.
The old hag jumped in an old pond, splashing all over,
a hypermeter.
Even though I am dressed like a girl,
I still need to meet my physical needs.
Luckily there's no one around, so let's do it!
This must be men's heaven.
Mrs. Kisaragi, you look ghastly!
Aren't you too tired?
She is pi—
In these cases, you need some therapy.
Run away!
I'm certain this Ranko maid was taking a man's piss.
It's too disgusting, it can't be real.
I need to collect myself.
Ever since Benio came here, I've been feeling more and more worn out.
My wonderful roses,
it looks like they've fully bloomed.
No, that place is...
Lord, stay away!
Why should I stay away?
That was... man's piss! Never mind!
You've been quite weird recently.
Maybe you should see a doctor!
No, I'm completely fine.
Such a fine smell!
This is awful...
Ranmaru, aren't you overdoing it a little?
I just listened to my nature calls.
What happened, Boss?
Nothing special,
but Ranmaru needs to learn some basic etiquette.
Benio, aren't you acting strange?
We are doing all of this
in order to break your engagement as soon as possible, right?
He's right, don't you think so, Boss?
Uh, yeah...
Then, we need to be as wild as we can
and we'll be kicked out in no time.
Hell yeah! Boss, to be honest, I can't wait to raise hell!
Hey, look.
It's the best time to execute our plan.
I guess the time has come.
Right! Is there anything you want to do to go out in style?
Yeah, if this is the case, I should.
Yahoo! Let's make a mess of this place!
Exactly! I can always count on you, Ushi!
Well said!
Shinobu... so this is goodbye.
Hm? That sound...
Boss Hanamura Benio's Dwelling
Alright! I'm done.
Oh my! Ushigorou!
What have you come up with this time?
Isn't it obvious? It's a signboard, a signboard, just look!
What is all of this for?
By doing this, the whole world will know that Boss lives here!
This ain't the only one!
Lemme, lemme show you. Here!
Those are to be nailed on doorways, too.
Boss Hanamura Benio's Bedroom
These are for bathrooms.
Boss Hanamura Benio's Toilet
You, unruly man...
Alright! Just kidding, kidding!
Mrs. Kisaragi, I like your style, I really do!
Silence!
Go away immediately!
Oh no, you're so scary!
You bastard! Making a fool of me!
I'll chop your head off!
Time to run away!
Wait!
Ah! Wait, wait! Ah, hold up!
Stop there! Take this, this, this! You coward!
Help!
Boss always tell me it's so funny to kid you!
Don't you dare...
Don't you dare!
Stop right there! Stop!
I won't wait at all!
Here we go!
Stop!
Wait,
insolent!
Stop!
Aw-aw-aw-aw!
Like hell!
There's no stopping me!
Eek!
How'd it come to this?
Oh, my,
Kisaragi, what in the world happened?
Your eyes are bloodshot, what's wrong?
No, it's just that...
Oh my! What you need that for?
No, for no particular reason.
Don't you feel a little exhausted, Kisaragi?
Not really...
Ever since Benio came here,
so many things have changed, so don't strain yourself.
Something this trifling doesn't bother me,
Benio's education is proceeding steadily.
Oh, it's all good, then.
Oh, these must be Tenmaru and Chimaru,
and they're in our garden.
What was happening in the corridor?
Uhm...
These days my eyesight is rather poor,
what did that seem like?
That was... well...
Young Master's dogs are pulling the rickshaw!
Kisaragi! Hold yourself together! Kisaragi? Someone!
I see, I see.
Her mind is fatigued,
yes, she's definitely tired,
she needs to rest for the time being.
Mrs. Kisaragi...
Will she really make it out okay?
I'm so worried!
Alright.
Then, take care.
Thank you very much!
We did it!
We finished that hag off!
While we're at it, we can go home, Benio!
Go home...
Yeah... I could do it...
Going home...
If I return home...
I won't see Shinobu's face anymore...
there won't be any relationship between us anymore.
We'll be strangers...
It's so lonely...
Forget it!
It's too late now.
I came here with this goal in mind!
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me, Benio...
Eek! Who is it!?
Don't come in! Just don't!
Ms. Kisaragi, it's me.
My, Young Master.
Go ahead.
Mrs. Kisaragi, I heard you collapsed.
Don't worry, it's nothing important.
Sorry for being in such a bad shape.
You shouldn't overdo it, you are
my irreplaceable nanny, after all,
you need to take care of yourself.
Young Master, you're such a kind person...
You need to take breaks sometimes,
Nanny.
Nanny?
So Mrs. Kisaragi is to Shinobu
what my Nanny was to me?
Perhaps we really went a bit too far.
Here is your tea.
Thanks.
Here you are.
Ranmaru, your pads are all over your back.
Agh!
What did you say, Ranmaru?
Somebody may have figured your play out?
I'm dead sure! He called me Ranmaru, after all!
As expected!
But why didn't he tell everyone yet?
He knew that I've been with you from the start
and that I slept with you in the same room too.
On top of it, he knew that Ranmaru loves me, not to mention what I risked.
And he was never worried...
Sure enough,
he does not care about me at all.
He loves me,
he loves me not,
he loves me,
he loves me!
He loves me not...
Flowers are scattering and delusions are intensifying.
Love is a sailboat of reflection.
Shinobu!
Even the almighty High Collar Lady
is now lost in thought
for love.
Unable to understand Shinobu's feelings,
our worried High Collar Lady
stumbles across some thugs,
but in the heat of the moment,
no one can match her,
she just needs to use her weapon
and show her tomboyish style off.
All of a sudden, a geisha, who's in love with Shinobu, appeared.
Next time on "Here Comes the Smart Alec":
Two blooming admirers.
Don't miss it!