The socially higher,
yet spiritually rich Shinobu
held a banquet to introduce his fiancee to his friends.
A guest, her best friend Tamaki,
burst into tears as she heard the
marriage break wasn't going well.
On the other hand, the staunch Ushigorou
reported seeing Boss in a bad mood, making Ranmaru feel uneasy.
However, due to an unexpected series of events,
Benio started to win everyone over.
And now, an unexpected m-aid came to the mansion.
So,
how is this going to end?
Lady Benio, what is happening?
Follow me.
Lady Benio, what are you doing?
Uhm, you said that Ranko is going to serve me, right?
So, I thought I could show her my room.
Let's go.
That girl is suspicious...
Wait a second.
I am Ranko, glad to meet you.
Ciao!
Episode 12
Dance! Tormented beauty?!
Don't rush like this, you can take your time!
I've always wanted to visit a noble's mansion!
What even is on your mind!?
Ranmaru, quit it.
Benio, how do I look?
It suits me, right? Look, I even put pads on my breasts.
You idiot! You're being too reckless!
Disguing as a maid...
what will happen if that geezer unmasks you?
What a beautiful room!
It's just like a princess's.
This is cosy to the point
I wouldn't want to go home.
Listen to me!
What the heck do you wanna do, Ranmaru?
This is a bit too much!
It doesn't matter if you're as pretty as a girl.
It's because of this that I changed my coiffure.
I've discovered that western hairstyles suit me well.
Taishou Era, 4th year,
people started using curling iron to style their hair.
This was, in other words, the pioneer of permanents.
Ranmaru!
But, if I don't do this, I will never be able...
to be with you.
What!? Then, do you mean to stay in here forever? As a maid?
Sure!
Oh come on!
It's no good! Just go home, there's the exit!
But, Benio...
Just go home!
But, but, but, but...
I was worried about you...
Benio, you...
Even if you said you'd came back immediately,
with those looks he has,
I couldn't beat that sublieutenant,
so I started to worry that you'd fall for him.
Days and nights my heart kept aching.
I...
couldn't stand it anymore.
Gimme!
Nay!
Just give it to me!
I said no!
Gimme!
It flew away!
Also...
You looked troubled at today's banquet too.
Ushi told me about that.
I couldn't stand still, so I came all the way here.
You did all of this...
Yes.
Ranmaru...
Yes!
Oh, don't cry.
You hopeless child...
When you start crying, you won't stop for an hour.
Benio!
Did you ever meet Shinobu?
Oh-oh... Yes, that time we flew the kite!
He thought I was you, didn't he?
After that,
we met that time at the bar.
You're right... it's no good.
Benio,
what's happening?
If I get found out, we might as well both come back home.
It's not a big deal!
Ranmaru!
Excuse me.
You, wait a second.
Aaah!
H-Hold on.
Shinobu! The weather is so nice today, isn't it?
Yes, today has been a pretty clear day...
Uhm, this is my new maid,
she's called Ranko.
Ranko, huh.
Then, welcome.
Everyone's waiting for you downstairs.
Thank God! He didn't seem to notice.
Ugh, that trademark laugh doesn't bode well.
Could he have noticed?
I don't think so...
If he had, he'd have said something.
But, as long as he doesn't notice, you can go home.
Please, stay with me!
We can't do that.
If the count recognised you, you'd be doomed!
What was that?
Excellent!
Stop it.
Why can't I praise him?
It's not about that,
that old man could get irritated and cut you in two!
Don't you worry!
It's because you don't know him!
I don't...
I don't want to risk my life once again.
Not a problem right now.
Since you came here with
the purpose of breaking the marriage,
getting rumbled is not a big deal, you can pack your bags
and just tell them goodbye, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I've studied my role a lot,
I know many ways to trick anyone!
If I have to deceive people through acting,
leave it to me!
Boss, it's as Ranmaru says.
If we join our strengths,
we can make a mess of this house in no time!
And if we get discovered, we can just run away.
However, if the count finds you, you'll be begging him mercy.
You don't need to worry that much.
Huh, where are you going?
Wait.
Ladies                                    Gentlemen
This way.
Benio! Help me!
I-I-I got it, I got it, I got it.
I have to go the other way, right?
You saw through it.
Oh, I see. What happened then?
Oh, Takayashiki, you came back.
Yeah, I saw Tamaki off,
but she looked somewhat demoralised.
Oh well, let's drink.
Thanks.
Hey, Shinobu, where's Benio, the life of the party?
She should return soon.
A new maid came here, so she's showing her around.
Count, I'm sure you must be worn out after training,
so you could take a shower...
Who's that?
I am Ranko, the new maid here.
You're the one who clapped, right?
Y-Yes.
It was such a spectacle that I forgot myself in such an improper way.
It's all good.
If anything, it's a surprise,
you don't find many youngsters who like martial arts these days.
Yikes, that look...
Did he find out?
She looks pretty.
Pretty lady, pretty lady!
Ranko, right?
From today onward, take care of me
and obey my orders.
Alright?
Dear!
You can't do this,
It isn't the time for such things!
This way!
Hold on!
Your name's Ranko, isn't it?
Yes.
You serve Benio, right?
Things are not looking too good.
Where do you come from?
And who's your guarantor?
Dear!
You shouldn't ask her all these questions!
Yes, I should!
Perhaps you don't know this, but there are many swindlers out there.
I already know this,
they get hired in rich families
steal valuables in the blink of an eye,
and then just abscond!
That's right.
Count, Ranm-
uh, erm,
I mean, Ranko would never do such things,
Her guarantor is...
Ushigorou from Kurumahiki!
...However,
My parents have always been close to hers,
so she's not a bad person.
Nice one!
I'm disguising as a girl,
so it's nothing suspicious!
Then I assume she was sent here by your parents.
Yes! That's right!
So, what can you do?
As a woman, I know everything about housework,
but more than everything else,
cooking is definitely my forte.
What's your speciality?
Let's see...
You don't have one!?
Dear! Please calm down!
Shut up!
If she's close to Benio's family,
she should've been raised well.
Don't you have a speciality?
I have! Potato soup!
Potato soup?
Mhm...
You said this because you know that I am from Satsuma,
are you making a fool of me?
It's not like that, I truly like potatoes!
Don't mess with me, you're being cheeky.
En garde!
Count! Ranko knows nothing about you and your birthplace!
That's true! Don't hit her.
Hey you, my sixth sense is perceiving something.
I survived during the Meiji Restoration
because my sixth sense never lied to me.
Others may be deceived, but my eyes never will.
I can sense it...
I'm sure there's something you're better at!
Don't conceal it!
He's right, do you know any traditional art?
Yes, I know a bit of traditional dance.
I see. What's your school?
Well, uhm...
Fujieda school.
Ooh!
Fujieda school, huh.
Yes, in fact, I'm the head.
What? The head?
I was given the license to teach by the head himself.
A teacher at that age?
Yes, she's been practising since she was this small.
Let's go.
Hold up!
If she's a teacher, it'll do.
Today we're holding a banquet,
and you'll be dancing.
A dance would liven up the celebration!
She can't do that,
To be honest, it's only a nominal license,
so it won't be such a great-
Modesty is futile.
Prepare everything and get a dress.
Dear, we can't do that.
No, today we're holding a celebration to introduce Benio,
so we must be sure to do everything properly.
Go!
Yes.
We're done!
Great job.
Isn't that obvious?
It's the head of Fujieda school,
Fujieda Ranmaru, right?
This isn't looking good!
What? So she's the head.
Lady Benio, what in the world is...
Yes! Well...
Uhm, you see...
If her name is Ranmaru, it's a boy, right?
Then isn't this a transvestite?
This is bad! I have to do something to get out of this!
Hold up!
Right! I'll just make something up!
Count, please forgive me.
Her being Fujieda Ranmaru...
is a complete lie.
What?
This girl looks like Fujieda Ranmaru
and she can dance fairly well.
Even her name is Ranko.
She acts like Fujieda Ranmaru,
it's a bad habit of hers.
They're two peas in a pod, though.
I'll dispel your doubts right now.
Idiot!
You still have this bad habit of yours!
You dumbass!
You want to look like Ranmaru so much, but in reality
you're deceiving people!
Idiot!
Idiot idiot idiot idiot idiot!
Idiot, idiot-idiot!
Benio, cut it down!
Idiot!
Yes?
I'll let you go because the count is saying, however,
you shall never do something like this again, if you don't want the count to use his katana on you,
alright?
Understood.
I've cleared all my doubts now,
Ranko, you can go back to work!
Okay...
It worked!
Taishou Era, 7th year,
All's well that ends well!
Good job, Benio!
Lady Benio, your bath is ready.
Thank you.
Hear me out, Ranko.
Yes?
Enter the bath with Benio and wash her back.
What?
Was that a joke, Mrs. Kisaragi?
When it comes to bathing and the likes for noble women,
leaving everything to the court lady is the tradition.
Come on, Ranko.
Get naked too and bathe with her!
Oh jeez...
Ah, Lady Benio.
Take off all of your clothes!
Hurry up!
Ugh!
It's not an embarrassing thing to do,
all maids are females, after all.
Then-!
But you're wrong!
Ranko is actually a ma—
Benio!
"A ma?"
What does "a ma" mean?
I mean, she is a-ma-amazing person!
I won't be embarrassed to undress in such company!
Right, Ranko?
Excuse me?
Yeah, no problem at all.
I see.
Then, I'll let you do the rest.
Benio!
Ranmaru!
Tee-hee-hee.
As much as we try, we can't do it together.
Just sneak out and hide somewhere.
Yeah, it's not like I want to see your bones.
How do you know if you haven't seen it?
She's always so rough.
I knew that this would've happened!
Go back in!
Ranko!
Don't neglect your orders!
Won't you go back in!?
Enter!
You pervert!
I lost my cool for a moment.
I think I let him see everything.
Good, it seems like she understood.
It's not my fault!
Out of the frying pan into the fire,
boys and girls are forced to bathe together.
Even in hot water...
flowers will bloom- or won't they?
Benio can't help but worry that Ranmaru's identity
could be unveiled,
while Ranmaru and Ushigorou don't worry at all,
leading to even more trouble,
Boss Hanamura Benio's Dwelling
like vandalising shingles.
Oh, by the way, Shinobu discovered Ranmaru's disguise.
Next time on "Here Comes the Smart Alec":
Love is a sailboat of reflection.
Don't miss it!