The most crucial moment in life is during decision making.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace.
But also instilled
numerous lessons on how to live.
Animentary
Decision
Wit is your weapon
Remember to use your head
Repress your anguish,
If you are a man
One decision is enough
To make others cry or laugh
If you win, don't hold your head high,
If you lose, don't cry
Men, don't you ever let other see your tears
Tatsunoko Production
Flower bloom...
At 3:00 am on December 8th, 1941, at the same time as the Pacific War began,
Lieutenant General Sakai, commander of the 23rd Army of the Japanese Army,
who received a coded telegram of the successful landing on the Malay Peninsula,
immediately gathered at the border of the Kowloon Peninsula.
He ordered 30,000 soldiers to attack Hong Kong.
Battle of Hong Kong (Episode Six)
The Japanese army had thoroughly investigated, planned, and prepared for the capture of Hong Kong in advance.
The enemy has fortified a major position named "Gin Drinkers Line".
From Shau Kei Wan to Golden Hill, Shing Mun Reservoir to Lion Rock, to stop our troops on the Kowloon Peninsula.
"Gin Drinkers Line" was a strangely-named line of defense. It means one who over drinks gin.
The enemy commander, Major General Maltby, seems to have recently placed the British 2nd Royal Scots Battalion,
India's 2nd and 14th Punjam Battalion, and the 5th and 7th Radifoot on this Gin Drinkers Line yesterday,
in anticipation of the start of the war.
Yeah, it seems that our army is by far the dominant force.
Let's fight openly in an orthodox method.
How many days will it take for the first artillery to reach the enemy's main position?
It will take a week.
Can it be done in a week?
Lets do it.
Good.
The preparation period for breaking through the Gin Drinkers Line is one week.
The focus of the bombardment is between Lion Rock and Golden Hill.
Please shell the middle of this.
Lets hit those 24cm howitzers with all our might.
If we crush one place, we can attack from the side and the back.
In the meantime, the division's main force will be placed to the east and west of Tai Mo Shan,
and it will break through the Gin Drinkers Line at a moment's notice.
It is exactly the same tactic as the Siege of Port Arthur of the Russo-Japanese War,
Hong Kong is divided into the Kowloon Peninsula, which borders the Chinese continent, and Hong Kong Island.
There were approximately 12,000 troops centered on two battalions each from the UK, India,
and Canada under the command of Major General Maltby.
The Japanese attack was carried out as planned, and the British were immediately hit everywhere.
However, the British Army was also expecting to defend the Gin Drinkers Line.
The Japanese army made a cautious operational plan to completely crush the British position by bombardment,
and then advance the troops.
First, the commander of the front line decided to have his subordinate,
Lieutenant Toichi Wakabayashi,
lead a squad on reconnaissance to search for the British position in the highlands.
Lieutenant, that is...
Yeah. It seems to be an observation post.
Let's get closer.
It is dangerous With this moonlight the enemy will soon discover us.
Look, it's God's help.
This lieutenant had risen from the ranks
and had sufficient practical experience.
There is no one.
Whats going on?
To break through the Gin Drinkers Line, we must first bring down this observation post.
We can do this.
Lieutenant, no way.
Let's take it by surprise.
Don't. It's reckless.
With only 21 soldiers, in addition...
"In addition"? Spit it out.
Our mission is reconnaissance.
This is insubordinate
Don't worry. Just get rid of moles.
However...
“On the battlefield, there are many things that require arbitrary judgment”
Yes.
Flexibility is needed on the battlefield.
There is a great deal of need for dogmatism,
and it is not always considered that dogmatism violates military regulations.
If you know it.
Will you do it?
Roger.
It's an easy job.
Yeah
Gather!
Well, once I jump in first, then you guys also jump in line.
Shoot anything that moves from side to side, they all seem to be enemies.
How many Japanese troops are there?
Maybe 200 or 300, 400 or 500.
There are only 100 garrison members.
Immediately ask the captain for support.
Call him.
Yes
Hello
Hello!
Don't panic.
Be calm.
Captain,
it's an emergency!
What is it?
Calm down.
Yes
Our scouts ran into the enemy,
and are in a terrible firefight.
Damn.
This is not good.
I think they aimed to "steal a march on one's rival."
It is unavoidable.
Immediately, with the support of the 2nd Battalion,
attack with the 3rd Battalion.
Captain,
that would mess up the military's operational plans.
I can't let the scouts die.
However,
the intention of the division leader...
I take responsibility.
This is an order.
They will know military discipline!
Immediately return the scout unit and punish it.
Roger!
The military is always acting on a prudent operational plan.
Do not allow rash actions.
Alright, Let's get in there.
Charge!
Captain!
Please, give me support!
Listen to this sound!
No. The Japanese army has arrived here too! Counterattack is impossible. Retreat!
Even if you say "retreat", all exits are suppressed by the Japanese army.
That's why I hate this kind of position.
Forward!
Captain!
Look
They did it.
Idiot
I thought that it was not necessary to return the occupied position to the enemy.
so I asked the front line commander to stop further attacks and only secure the position we stole...
It they do such things often, our military's operational plans will be ruined.
They should be punished. Violations of discipline are serious.
However, they made the operation, which our army thought would take a week, happen in just one night.
Then, why did we plan and prepare for the operation?
Allowing such a runaway action will only confuse the operation.
Isn't it good? Being flexible.
This took a weight off my shoulders.
How is it sir?
Anyway, the problem of punishing the scouts will be the first issue.
Regarding that,
it is true that they made a big hole in the Gin Drinkers line,
and the British troops are gradually retreating over their front line.
Then, the commanders of the front lines insist that they should take advantage of this period,
and start their advance at once.
Sir
What about it?
I agree
Ok.
We will immediately change the plan
and launch a mass attack over the entire front line.
Let's move the entire British army to Hong Kong Island.
Generalissimo Chiang Kai-shek’s allied forces will attack the Japanese from behind on the Kowloon Peninsula.
It is more effective than defending the Kowloon Peninsula and struggling any further.
Alright,
order all the soldiers on the Kowloon Peninsula to pull up to Hong Kong.
The breakthrough of the Gin Drinker's Line, which was initially thought to take a week,
was completed in just three days.
The Kowloon Peninsula was subdued and Japanese troops entered Hong Kong's Kowloon District.
At 9:05 am on December 13th,
the Japanese staff landed on Hong Kong Island to plead with the British women to encourage surrender.
However,
the British reply was only one word:
"Never"
In other words, they never surrendered.
The Japanese attack was launched again and the air raids continued.
It was more intense than ever.
On December 17th, the Japanese army again recommended surrender. But,
The Governor of Hong Kong and the military commander,
absolutely refused to enter into negotiations regarding the surrender of Hong Kong.
We will also notify you that we are no longer ready to be contacted by the Japanese military regarding this matter.
A squall is likely to come.
The moonrise tonight is late.
9 o'clock tonight, start the landing.
Actually, my division has Lieutenant Reizo Koike, who won the breaststroke at the Los Angeles Olympic Games.
The lieutenant's unit will swim in and confuse the enemy base.
It is not necessary.
With that black smoke, they would not be able to see the sea from the British position.
Besides, in this weather, the sea is completely dark.
Its the same as the Gin Drinkers line's breakthrough strategy.
All right, let's land all at once.
The Japanese army started landing on Hong Kong Island, at 9 pm
However, the British side hardly noticed It,
even as the Japanese army approaching to 90m.
This is the second observation post.
There is nothing out of the ordinary.
They even made such a report.
The Japanese army landed successfully,
However,
the counterattack of the British troops who had been cut off from their escape route was fierce.
The power plant, an important base,
was also protected by 70 British and French businessmen living in Hong Kong.
But despite having military careers, the youngest was only 55 years old.
However,
even after the retreat of the Indian Rajput battalion, their troops successfully held the power plant for a whole day.
At the time of World War I, it wasn't like this.
This medal of mine was given during the Spanish War.
Hmm?
The Indian Rajput Battalion is retreating.
They are pitiful.
I don't mind. We defend here until we die.
Do your best. Chiang Kai-shek’s army will soon attack the Japanese from behind.
However,
the allied army of Chiang Kai-shek, who they relied on, did not arrive.
It moved far beyond the border from west to east and disappeared into the interior.
British soldiers were in despair.
Governor, the reservoir on the east side of Nicholson has finally fallen to the Japanese army.
Citizens are fleeing Hong Kong one after another in search of water and food.
We cannot continue the fight any longer.
If we fight any more, we will kill all the citizens.
December 25th, 5:20 pm
The Governor of Hong Kong and Major General Maltby decided to surrender.
He visited the Japanese military headquarters at the Peninsula Hotel in Kowloon District.
It was Christmas day
The British surrendered in the candlelight, as if celebrating a holy night.
For that reason,
the feeling of defeat in the Governor of Hong Kong was strong.
Stop It!
The Battle of Hong Kong, which was supposed to take four weeks, ended in almost half the time.
These quick victories include problems that the commander of the group must always keep in mind.
The reckless attack of this young junior commander blew away the looseness of command
that was likely to result from overly cautious operations, and paved the way for victory.
When you come into contact with the momentum of your subordinates,
can you further encourage that momentum depending on the situation and exert it over the entire organization?
It always depends on the good decisions of senior commanders.
If you're a man, let's put your strength to test
If you are a man, keep your hopes sizzling
If you are a man, don't lose your heart
Because there's just you and me, a man and a man
With crimson blood flowing in our veins all the same
Brought to you by the Sorcery Party
ѫ~ѫ
"Lux in Tenebris"
Translation by
Quality Checking by
Supplementary materials by
Video by
Perevodildo
Ziusudra and Paul Geromini
History Asian
Moozzi2