The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
The US Navy, which has won the Battle of Midway and gained momentum, was about to launch a counterattack against
the Japanese in order to take control of the Pacific War.
On August 6th, 1942, a fleet of 31 ships carrying 19,000 Marines was secretly heading north into the South Pacific,
protected by approximately 60 escort ships centered on three aircraft carriers and one battleship.
Battle of Savo Island (Episode 13)
The purpose of the Tulagi and Guadalcanal campaigns is primarily to enable contact between the United States and Australia.
Second, it was a stepping stone to control Rabaul. Third, it would prevent the Japanese troops from moving further south.
According to the reconnaissance aircraft reports, no planes have yet arrived at the Japanese airfield under construction at Guadalcanal.
> However, they can come from Rabaul.
> For that purpose, there is a coast watcher of the Royal Australian Navy Intelligence Department.
> These coast watchers are farmers, pastors, officials, miners, etc. who were mobilized to protect the vast Australian coast.
They lurked in the jungle with the local people, and were in charge of informing every movement of the Japanese army .
> The distance from Rabaul to Tulagi and Guadalcanal is about 560 nautical miles.
The enemy can only fly over us for 20 or 30 minutes at the most.
> However, it will take at least four days for our army to complete the landing.
What if the enemy makes an attack?
> We have already lost Lexington in the Coral Sea and Yorktown at Midway.
What if we lose more aircraft carriers? Aircraft carriers are vulnerable to bombing.
> As the landing commander, I cannot kill 20,000 Marines. I need the support of an aircraft carrier.
> I'm not just saying that as a commander of the aircraft carrier fleet.
If two of the three remaining aircraft carriers in the Pacific, or even one, are killed, the war is lost.
> Then, you should cancel such an operation.
> Tell General Nimitz or Vice Admiral Ghormley in Hawaii.
> Well, don't get so excited. The operation has already begun.
> Anyway, why don't you carry out the landing operation as planned and then reconsider after seeing the situation?
> Are you scared? > Are you not seared?
> I try not to think about the future. > We are not Tarzan. Can you fight these guys?
> Japanese soldiers can dive for miles while sucking air from trees.
Barefoot, no noise in the jungle, climbs trees like a monkey.
Evil, ascetic, and able to travel farther than we do. They can survive with a small amount of food and endure any pain.
> I'm really scared too.
> They are not ordinary human beings. They are werewolves.
> On August 7th, at 3:00 am, the American transport fleet approaching Cape Esperance, northwest of Guadalcanal Island,
split into two parts across Savo Island at the entrance of the narrow strait.
Protected by the escort fleet, and Guadalcanal Island. They approached Cape Lunga and Tulagi.
At the time, on Guadalcanal Island, the construction of an airfield for the Japanese army had been completed.
> Today, the 6th Air Group, Misawa Air Group, and Mitsubishi G4M Corps are scheduled to fly from Rabaul to this Guadalcanal airfield.
Until then, the airfield construction team will conduct pilot training, Do you understand?
> Yes > Good. Go.
> Yes
> At this time, the Japanese defense force of Guadalcanal was about 2000 members of the construction team
and 203 members of the Japanese land squadron. And there were 700 Japanese troops in Tulagi.
The US-Australian fleet attacked seaplane bases on Guadalcanal and Tulagi on Florida, and began landing.
The Imperial Headquarters predicted that the US military would rebound in the latter half of 1943, given its military strength,
However, the counterattack was faster than expected.
It was the Rabaul air base on the Japanese side that received this news.
> Immediately raise all troops and attack the invading enemy units.
> I think the enemy's intention is a reconnaissance in force or the destruction of the airfield.
> 2nd unit, 27 Mitsubish G4Ms, 1st unit, 18 Zero fighters for 07:30, 3rd unit, 9 aircraft, start as soon as ready.
> Also, after the Battle of Midway, the 8th Fleet, the combined fleet under the command of Vice Admiral Mikawa,
was about to head to Guadalcanal Island.
> The distance from Rabaul to Guadalcanal is just about Shimonoseki from Tokyo.
We cannot expect much success from our military airplanes. > However, our fleet has just been formed and has not yet take any fleet action.
Besides, since it is such a distance, there is a good chance that it will be attacked by enemy aircraft on the way.
I'm prepared for that too. Since the battle of Midway, our navy has been too cowardly.
> What is the opinion of Chief Yamamoto? > He agrees.
> I will do so with the free discretion given to the fleet, even if opposed by the Imperial Headquarters or the Combined Fleet.
> Chief, let's do it. > How about you, Chief of Staff?
> If the chief is so determined, then I will not dissent. However...
> However, what?
> Decide what to do later based on the result of the land based air reconnaissance and attacks.
> Good. Senior Staff? > We have never sailed the surface of the sea.
> Anyway, it's a rough strategy, so there is no choice but to make it rough.
> Alright, this is the first fleet night battle in the history of this world war. Let's do it roughly.
The flagship, and the 6th Fleet, will sortie immediately.
> for the Japanese side, being deprived of Guadalcanal would be a serious threat to the New Guinea area.
> 24 bombers, head toward Tuvalu and Guadalcanal.
> This information was sent to the headquarters of the Hawaii Pacific Fleet, and was forwarded to
the US operational unit sailing near Guadalcanal Island by strong radio waves.
> The ship is scheduled to be attacked by 24 enemy aircraft at noon.
> The upper right sky, enemy aircraft.
> Good
> The damage suffered by the Japanese side in this battle was five land based attack aircraft five shipboard bombers, and two Zero fighters.
The damage to the US and Australian army was 11 fighters, one dive bomber, and the destroyer McMurdo was sunk.
> The problem is the enemy aircraft carrier. > Therefore, we have to be prepared for an invasion of enemy aircraft.
> If that happens, and there is no aircraft carrier here, then we may be wiped out.
Don't be discovered by the enemy at all costs. The only thing that will beat the enemy is a surprise attack.
> Right front, enemy patrol.
> Alright, pretend to head northwest. > Full port. Hurry!
> Enemy patrol aircraft has disappeared.
> Restore our course. The rest of you gather in the operation room.
> Yes.
> We passed through the Bougainville Strait and broke through the central waterway at high speed. Rush from the right side of Savo Island.
First, a surprise attack will be made to the ships moored in Guadalcanal, then the enemy of Tulagi will be attacked,
and then the enemy planes will hurry back to a point where they cannot be attacked.
> Enemy patrol aircraft, 90 degrees to the right.
> Cruisers three, destroyers three,
seaplane tenders two, course 120 degrees, speed 15 knots,
> Persistent guy. Would you like to change direction again?
> It takes too much time. Don't worry, threaten them with an 8-inch gun.
> With this, there is no doubt that enemy planes will come in a few hours.
> Start each aircraft and scout the enemy's condition. Each ship should have a strict anti-aircraft lookout.
> However, the reconnaissance officer belonging to the Royal Australian Air Force,
who discovered the Japanese fleet, continued to scout the area they were charged with.
At around 2:30 pm, they returned to their base in Milne Bay, on the southern tip of New Guinea.
They then reported the formation of the Japanese fleet, unconfirmed to MacArthur's Command in Townsville, Australia. It's a delay of nearly 8 hours.
> Apparently we are okay. > I have never had a day was as long as today.
> We will surely win tonight. > Good. I'm giving instructions.
> Yes
> Instruction: Win and rush into the night battle, Which is a tradition of the Imperial Japanese Navy. Be calm and do your best.
> Call Admiral Ghormley.
> We have finished the mission of landing support, 21 out of 99 carrier-based aircraft were lost.
> Due to the large number of enemy bombers and torpedo bombers, it seems appropriate for our fleet to withdraw immediately.
There is also a shortage of fuel, so we must request that a refueling ship be dispatched as soon as possible.
> Actually, there was still four days worth of fuel. However, the American side pulled out their escort fleet, including the aircraft carrier.
Admiral Fletcher decided he didn't want to risk losing his aircraft carrier anymore,
now that he lost Lexington and Yorktown in the two battles of the Coral Sea and Midway.
> Report from Aoba's reconnaissance aircraft.
Three enemy cruisers patrolling Savo Island, and southwestern sea.
Alright, from now on, we will rush to the berth on Guadalcanal Island with a speed of 30 knots and a course of 95 degrees.
> 10 degrees to the right, three cruisers. Going to the right. Illumination!
> Shoot!
Fire!
> 10 minutes > It's a major victory.
> Immediately change course to the left and run the troops off Tulagi.
Fire!
> Currently at 00:10. Feel free to give your opinions. > We should withdraw immediately
There are few torpedoes and an enemy task force is believed to be near San Crisbal Island.
> The problem is distance and time.
> It takes two hours to reorganize the fleet and reach Lunga Point, no matter how urgent it is.
> It's past 4o'clock, its morning on the Solomon Sea, so
> it is impossible to escape from the enemy aircraft carrier.
> Two hours > Let's do it. The enemy convoy should be naked.
> The chief also said. If we were discovered by an aircraft carrier, our force would be wiped out.
> Withdraw the entire force. Course 320 degrees. speed 30 knots.
> However, at that time, the American aircraft carrier had left far away from Guadalcanal Island.
> Chief, let's go attack again. If we go only with Chokai, we can escape fast enough.
If you leave the convoy, your enemies will only get fat. Chief, a well supplied enemy will affect future operations.
> We cannot lose an important warship by making a reckless attack.
> Thus, the first night battle in the history of naval battles in the world ended with a one-sided victory for the Japanese side.
However, Guadalcanal’s American convoy was left unharmed.
Given replenishment of troops, ammunition, and food has a major impact on the final victory, was this decision correct?
When making a decision, always look to the future and not lose sight of the big picture, without hesitation about the immediate victory or damage.
This naval battle, which brought victory to the Japanese side, was one of the major causes of the upcoming tragedy of Guadalcanal. When making a decision, always look to the future and not lose sight of the big picture, without hesitation about the immediate victory or damage.
This naval battle, which brought victory to the Japanese side, was one of the major causes of the upcoming tragedy of Guadalcanal.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production