The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
In November 1942, Guadalcanal, which is said to be the most tragic battle in the Pacific Ocean,
could not be approached by the Japanese rescue forces due to the complete control of the sea and air by the US military.
The 30,000 Japanese soldiers left on Guadalcanal Island were racked of hunger, malaria, and death, and were just waiting for help.
The 30,000 Japanese soldiers left on Guadalcanal Island became an island of hunger, malaria and death, and were
For the Japanese side, only covert transportation by submarines was allowed.
Therefore, as a desperate measure, the transportation of supply drums by a high-speed destroyer was devised.
The plan was to connect drums filled with food and medicine with ropes, approach the coast, and drop them into the sea.
Battle of Tassafarunga (Episode 19)
On November 28th, the flagship Nagagami was moored in the hometown of Shortland, ahead of its departure.
In the officer's office a final meeting was held for the commander, Major General Tanaka Raizo, and the captains of the eight destroyers that were organized.
A local staff member also attended from the Imperial Headquarters.
> The total number of drums is 1098. 250 of these will be placed on each of the five ships,
Oyashio, Kuroshio, Kawakaze, Suzukaze, and Kagero, excluding the guard ship, Takanami, the flagship: Naganami, and Makinami.
> That's fine, but as I've seen, torpedoes and cannons are covered by the drums, so they can't be used.
Any fighting will be done by the guard ships. In the meantime, drop the drums safely, and then have the crews show the results of their daily training.
> It's like a express company. The non-commissioned officer said as much this morning as well.
After training so much under Tanaka, they were called the Devil's 2nd Destroyer Squadron, and then, was it a express company?
> Isn't just your saying? But the Guadalcanal soldiers can't eat half of this bread. > Yes. I know it well.
> More than that,
> it is 300 nautical miles from Shortland to Guadalcanal.
If we don't return make it to the halfway point, 150 nautical miles, before dawn, the enemy will chase us from their base on Guadalcanal.
So we have to finish dropping the drums at Guadalcanal by 24:00.
~ I ask that much. I'll' leave the rest to you.
> Commander. > What is it staff officer?
> In the plan so far, it seems that we will not meet the enemy at all.
> That's not what I mean, they may come. No, they will come. > I would like to ask about the strategy for that case.
> It seems irresponsible to not plan.
When you walk, do you command your feet to "put out with your right foot, put out with your left foot"?
If you don't like my metaphor with the legs, let's change the story.
Does the master of kendo command his hand to block when the enemy's sword arrives?
Isn't your hand going there at once? Whether to fight well or not. It depends on daily training.
That's why the 2nd Destroyer Squadron has trained ridiculously hard. They are more than just express company. Look and see.
> Master of the voyage. Is the chart reliable?
> I don't know. It was made in England 15 years ago. It may be a little different.
> Hey, it's a little different? Are you OK? > It will be clear if I can see the sun.
> Well, leave it to me. > Well, if we get on the boat, I'll leave it to you
> If you leave it to me, yesterday's exchange of opinions between Commander Tanaka and the Chief of Staff of the Imperial Headquarters was interesting.
> The imperial officer who doesn't know the local area is like that.
> Master of the voyage. The sun. > Did you see it? Let's get it.
> What is the time? > 1203
> After all it was a little different. I will make a transition. Outbound 175 degrees. Full starboard.
> I want the enemy to come early.
> Enemy aircraft spotted. 331 degrees.
It appears to be one B-17 bomber.
> Prepare for anti-aircraft combat. > everyone, anti-aircraft combat, man your station.
> It Saw us, > That's right.
> At the time, on the American side, the Japanese rescue fleet was called the "Tokyo express", and it was to be attacked and sunk.
A fleet was sent to attack them. Among them, a fleet of 11 ships centered on the heavy cruiser Minneapolis, led by Major General Carlton Wright,
They were to wait for and find the enemy fleet intercepting the supply drums for Guadalcanal Island.
> As mentioned, there are eight enemies. Let's learn from the Battle of Tsushima, which was led by Admiral Togo.
Since the enemy is best at night battles, the water vapor of the cruiser illuminates it with tracer ammunition and destroys it.
> It's "a rat in a trap".
> There is a Japanese proverb, "a cornered rat will bite a cat". Be careful.
Moreover, the enemy is the 2nd Destroyer Squadron, which has been training hard. Even though it is a Destroyer Squadron, I don't know what they do.
But we have radar. Japan has nothing like that yet. They rely on their eyes even when the battle is at night.
As you all know, in naval battles it is better to know the position of the enemy first.
> Of course, the Japanese side also changed course, and approached four nautical miles west of Savo Island, and decided to enter Guadalcanal Island at a 180 degrees course.
> What time is it now? > 22:00
> 2 hours left. > It seems that the enemy will not find us.
> Sir. From 8th Fleet Command. > What is it?
> According to interceptions, the path of your fleet has been discovered. Try to destroy the enemy without sticking to your supply mission.
> I see. If I meet the enemy, throw away the drums and fight. > Yes
> Thanks. Please let everyone know that. > Yes
> I hope they don't find us until we drop the supplies. The soldiers on the island are waiting.
> Until then, well run away. > It is better to sink the enemy than to run away.
We are an express company today. The soldiers waiting on the island are priority customers. Customer first.
> They have made a quick escape. Can't you find the Japanese yet? > We need a while.
They know that 24 o'clock is their time limit. If they are in a rush, they will definitely come.
> God is smiling at us
> In this rain cloud, the visibility in Japan is at most 4000m. We have radar. We can see out to 24000m. The difference, 20000m, can control the battle ahead.
> This is it. > Certainly there is a flagship, but at 6300m. The enemy is eight nautical miles from here.
> Alright, get ready for battle. Man your stations.
Eight. All of them will be attacked and all of them will be finished.
> Another breath. We can see the island soon. > The enemy didn't notice us yet.
> No, we have been caught. But I don't know from where they will come.
> Because it's a fight between blindness and eyes > Let's just prepare to drop the supplies.
> Yes, I understand. Prepare to drop, tell each soldier.
> The Tanaka fleet approached the island knowing that it was being seen by the American radar. It was 23:16.
> 45 degrees to the left. Two black shapes. It seems to be an enemy destroyer.
> Good. This has opened our dark eyes. How far is it?
> 6000m > Alright, I understand.
> Report to flagship. Simultaneous torpedo attack. > Master of the voyage. Mark it.
> Seven ships that seem to be enemy destroyers. Direction 45 degrees to the left. Enemy speed is 24 knots.
> Get ready.
> It's all set. I'll leave it.
> Why do you proceed without breaking formation? At this rate, its like standing naked in front of the enemy.
> Yes. However, the mission is transportation first. It would be a waste to throw away supplies as it is. The soldiers are waiting.
> It is our mission to sink as many enemies as possible. > We will do that too. But now it's transportation.
> What? Moreover, the enemy is in front of us. > Let's do as much as we can. We can see the island. They are signaling.
> Japanese Navy, approach here a little more.
> There are 11 enemies in all.
> Captain. Do you wanna have a drink with the usual one?
> No, I'm standing this time. Until we deliver the supplies to our customers.
> Can I shoot? Captain. > No. Wait. A little more.
> The Japanese side hasn't noticed us yet. > The first ship is showing their side. Let's do it.
> Wait. Pull them all in and then annihilate them.
> It's okay if they come over there.
> But look. They are surrounded by enemies. > Do they not notice?
> Hey! > Idiot. They can never hear your yelling.
> They are becoming prey for us.
> That's ridiculous. Are you still a commander?
This battle is an opportunity. Did you forget about such a rudimentary thing?
> Staff officer, stop it.
> They are attacking. Turn the rudder.
> Commander. It's time to make a decision. > Staff officer. It's me who will make the decision.
> Good. Go. > Simultaneous fire. First of all, target the first ship.
> Isn't it done? But that's not enough.
> Commander. Look at that. Takanami is being attacked.
> Sir, what are you...
> Thank you!
> The food has been dropped. > Good. Tell all ships. Charge the enemy force.
> Begin fire. > Captain. Not yet?
> Do it. > Thank you. Set for 3 meters deep. Third ship.
> The pillar of fire is too much and cannot be seen well. Alright. The one you just shot. Again.
> We can see the face of the enemy well. > Launch concentrated attacks.
> The torpedoes of the trained 2nd Destroyer Squadron on the Japanese side were powerful and accurate.
Hits with one or more torpedoes on all cruisers except Honolulu sank one heavy cruiser and damaged three destroyers on the American side.
> They used to load their luggage. They will do it properly without being ordered, Staff officer. > Captain. We have to save Takanami.
It was hard work, but Oyashio and Kuroshio have already defeated much of the enemy. Please go.
> Yes. I will tell them.
It has became quiet.
> We won. The enemy is almost annihilated.
> Hmm. Did We win? > Of course.
> What was our damage? > Only Takanami
> That is good
> Chief surgeon. Now, the Oyashio and Kuroshio are coming to the rescue with the others.
Thank you for that. I can't handle it anymore. I usually play, so I got a punishment.
> By the way, do you know where the captain is? > Yes. Near the voyage chief's room. He's sleeping. > Sleeping?
> Captain, I came to have a toast with the captain.
> You don't have to stop. I feel relaxed.
> Thank you
> Sir.
> Thank you for your hard work > I'm sorry that I said something insubordinate.
I understand what you mean, "No one will command his right and left feet to walk.”
> I hope Takanami can be saved.
> Thus, the night battle off Lunga was over in just 30 minutes.
It is said that General Nimitz instructed all Navy officers to "train, train, and further train" after the activities and results of the Japanese destroyer fleet.
A strategy that trusts the power of subordinates obtained from rigorous training and leaves everything to them with peace of mind.
What is highly evaluated may be the commander's human decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production