The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
When the Japanese troops withdrew from Guadalcanal in February 1943, air raids on Japan entered their final stage.
The decisive factor in their execution is the B29 long-range bomber.
Its function was to carry 55 tons of bombs and it had an unprecedented cruising range of 5600km.
The Japanese archipelago is 2500kms from Saipan in the Mariana Islands. Considering the cruising range of the B29,
it was necessary to establish a base on Saipan Island for continued air raids on the mainland of Japan.
This is why the US military must capture the Mariana islands.
Battle of the Philippine Sea (Episode 20)
Thus, the American side made Admiral Spruance the general in charged of this operation.
There were a total of 775 ships, including Vice Admiral Mitscher's 58th MTF and Vice Admiral Smith's 5th Amphibious Corps, whose flagships were eight large aircraft carriers.
It was decided to mobilize twice as many troops as the Japanese Navy had once aimed at Midway, and put all their efforts into capturing Saipan.
On the Japanese side, Vice Admiral Ozawa has a total of 73 ships, including nine aircraft carriers, seven battleships, 11 heavy cruisers, three light cruisers, and 32 destroyers.
A combined fleet of 450 aircraft was assembled and set out to recover the Japanese Navy following their recent defeats.
They headed for Saipan from Tawi-Tawi Island with the determination that "the future of the empire depends on this battle" much like during the Battle of Tsushima.
> 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10
> After all it is no good. The shorter the reach, the stronger the punch, but he still lost.
> Are we still talking about boxing now?
> Japanese carrier-based aircraft can fly over 480km. However, our radius of action is less than 320km.
If Japan, which has a long reach, could out range us, we would not have a chance.
> However > A player with a short reach sneaks into the enemy's pocket. In other words, there is no choice but to get in close from here.
> Admiral Spruance did not follow that reasoning.
> Of course, the mission of our fleet is to capture Saipan. Therefore, we cannot leave the sea near Saipan.
However, if nothing is done, we will be unilaterally attacked by Japanese aircraft. Much like a guy with a long reach would do.
Rather, we must proactively confront the Japanese fleet.
> I don't want to kill those cheerful people. Perhaps Lieutenant General Ozawa of Japan is thinking of a long range strategy.
> Enemy troops are more than double our strength, according to reconnaissance photos over the Marshall islands and captured documents.
The only way to win this battle is to attack the opponent from a place that the enemy's spear can't reach.
Fortunately our MTF is equipped with veteran officers who attacked Pearl Harbor and the latest aircraft such as the Suisei and Tenzan.
The crew is inexperienced, but I hope they will overcome it and take the opportunity to win.
> By the wavy, the next time we discover an enemy, will we attack immediately?
> That's right > Finally, we can revenge our loss at Midway.
> It is likely the naval battle will start tomorrow. Let's have a big dinner now and let's listen to the Chief's "Flower Girl of Shanghai".
> That's right > Good! I'll sing
> What is it?
> A communication has been received from Commander Omori of the Third Carrier Division.
> Please read
> An enemy fleet was found at 200 nautical miles west of Saipan. Immediately launch the attack corps.
> What? > We found them! Good. We were just talking about it.
> Good. We are ready to start. > Wait.
> Chief > It's a great opportunity,
> What time is it now? > It's 4:30 pm.
> If you start now, when its evening where the enemy is.
> Then, after flying 150 nautical miles, it will be night. Flight captain.
> Yes
> Can you land at night? You haven't trained for that. This attack is a good opportunity, but we can't kill ourselves. We still have other opportunities. As someone said, We'll be busy from tomorrow.
> I understand
> ♪ Flower Girl of Shanghai
> No one noticed that the warmhearted decision of this subordinate would eventually cause such a big outcome.
At 4:22 am on June 19th, the Ozawa fleet launched a recon aircraft to carry out their tracking of the US fleet, continuing from yesterday,
At 6:30 am, they found the US fleet. It is 450kms from the advance guard unit.
At 7:30 am, starting with 68 advance guard Kurita units, a total of 246 aircraft from each ship, a air raid so large that it surpassed the attack on Pearl Harbor, launched.
> Chief. It's rare. > What?
> Normally, after launching all the aircraft you would said "I have done my job", and drink reading Dostoevsky.
> Master of the voyage. Apparently I don't feel that way today.
> Because of the cancellation of the sortie yesterday? > Maybe so.
> What happened? > Oh, nothing. The laces on my shoes just broke.
This ominous premonition has already begun to play out around this time.
> The Javanese flagship, Taiho. > Launch!
> Chief Surgeon > It's okay. I'm sorry.
> Taiho is 34,000 tons. How could one or two torpedoes do this? They will not even know we vow this revenge.
> Lieutenant General Mitscher, why don't you retrain from smoking a little?
> When did you become my wife? > Your wife left it to me.
> Although I've escaped to the sea. > There is still danger her.
> The Japanese Gum Island Air Corps was on the verge of attacking us.
Our Hellcat fighters defeated them before they hit us. They have to rest a little.
> This means that there will be no more attacks from Gum Island. All that remains is Admiral Ozawa's fleet.
> That's right. > Where are they? If they come suddenly, it will be a knockout.
> Finally caught. A large formation of Japanese aircraft is flying 240km west.
> 240km? Alright. Send out all available fighters. > Yes
> Vice Admiral Mitscher launched 450 ready to go fighters.
Thus, the Battle of the Philippine Sea, which can be said to be the first face-to-face meeting of the US and Japanese fleet since Midway, has begun.
The Hellcat plane, which has a radio, sought out the Japanese plane without hesitation. They flew down like a vulture and attacked the Japanese planes.
The Japanese fighters, which barely reached the sky above the US MTF were targeted by a new weapon,
the Magic Hughes bullet, which explodes in the immediate vicinity of the target.
The American pilots called it the "Great Marianas Turkey Shoot".
> Thus, on the first day of the attack, the Ozawa fleet lost 193 aircraft and the aircraft carriers Taiho and Shoho were sunk by submarine.
As a result of the battle on the Japanese side, only 17 enemy planes were shots down, the battleship South Dakota, and five other ships were sunk.
Vice Admiral Ozawa moved his flag to the aircraft carrier Zuikaku, joining with the remaining ships until the next phase of the battle was resumed.
He decided to evacuate to the northwest at once.
> We should take a rest today. > Please let me call it the "Marianas Turkey Shoot".
> Don't say stupid things. We got a lucky punch in yesterday. We can't predict what Mr. Ozawa will do.
> Besides, your mom is waiting for you in Arizona. > You know this much about me.
> Admiral Mitscher knows all of you. > Yes.
> Lieutenant General Ozawa always mourned the death of his lost subordinates in the form of a letter.
At the same time, the commanders of both the Japanese and US forces loved their subordinates and had the same feelings of regret of their deaths.
> May I come in. > Yeah.
> I'm sorry about being late. > Ah, fine
> I have 330 letters to do so excuse me. > Captain. Do you have the record with Hirosawa Torazo?
> What? Hirosawa Torazo? > Torazo? It is even better if there is.
> What are you doing? > This guy loved Torazo and was always singing.
> Chief. > It's okay if we do not have it. I will sing.
> The United States was desperately pursuing the Japanese fleet in order to catch up with
Lieutenant General Ozawa's who was taking a rest for a day and then taking the opportunity to re-attack.
Finally, Vice Admiral Mitscher’s 58th MTF found the injured Ozawa fleet 350km northwest.
> 350km northwest is this point.
> Yesterday was a lucky counter punch. Even if we're lucky, our enemies are staggering. We need to land a series of hits.
> Alright, let's go. Chief of Staff. Start all our aircraft.
> Chief. Do not do that. From now on, the 350km round trip will return at night.
> I know. > Besides, we have never done nighttime landing training.
> However, if we miss this now, we will lose our chance. Don't give Ozawa time to recover.
> But, the attackers cannot return. It's like sending them to their death.
> No, they will manage to get back. Launch all aircraft. This battle will be tough.
It is not permissible to include your personal feelings. All 216 aircraft will be launched for the attack.
> Yes
> Wait. After you launch all the aircraft, the fleet will heads northwest at full speed, to shorten the return distance as much as possible.
> Chief. > What's wrong with your face.
> There was a correction from the reconnaissance aircraft, the Japanese fleet is 480kms, not 350kms.
>What? Then they will have to fly a longer round trip > Yes.
> Let's recall the attack aircraft. > No, let's go as planned.
> Right 45 degrees, enemy planes.
> The enemy is pretty good.
But can they return safely? I'm sure they haven't done any nighttime landing training.
> Already aware of the approach of American attack aircraft via radar, Commander Ozawa launched 75 aircraft to the sky and waited.
His battleship leveled their main gun and blew up a torpedo bomber, and shot down 20 aircraft in the blink of an eye.
However, the American pilot who have gained momentum did not give in and sank the aircraft carrier Hiyo.
The aircraft carrier Zuikaku, the battlecruiser Chivoda, and others got received direct hits.
> After the enemy planes left, there were 35 planes left in the Ozawa fleet.
Commander-in-Chief of the Combined Fleet Toyoda admitted defeat and ordered Vice Admiral Ozawa to return.
> Chief. The first wave of attack aircraft is approaching.
> Is that so? Did they come back? Alright. Turn on the lights on all the ships. Welcome theme back.
> If you do that, we will be a good target for the enemy.
> That's fine. The pilots launched at the risk of their lives. I'll greet them by risking my life.
> During Operation Bougainville, Lieutenant General Ozawa of Japan turned on a searchlight
in front of the enemy in order to wait for the return of one recon aircraft. I will emulate him now.
> Look for the planes that have landed on the water. > Yes. I will have it arranged.
> Good
> This battle was, in effect, the last of the traditional Japanese Combined Fleet and determined the subsequent battlefield.
Moreover, this battle was also the last opportunity for both Japan and the United States to fight on an equal footing.
This important battle forced both commanders into exactly the same position and forced them to make a decision.
The momentary decisions made by each of them at that time was the major difference that influenced the fate off both forces and their two countries.
It tells us that when we are forced to make a tough decision, humanism determines the right or wrong of the matter.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production