The most precious moment in life
is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace,
but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom, Use your head Keep thinking if you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
In May 1942, the Kokoda Track Campaign, aimed at securing a base in Rabaul and controlling northern Australia,
began with the capture of Tulagi Island by a special land force that assaulted the port of Rabaul.
However,
the Australian Reserve, who knew in advance of the Japanese attack, had already withdrawn and the port was empty.
At 6:30 a.m. on May 4th, Major General Fletcher, the commander off the US Mobile Task Force, who learned of the Japanese occupation of Tulagi Island,
immediately sortied his aircraft from the carrier Lexington, and launched an attack.
Battle of the Coral Sea (Episode Eight)
At that time, the Japanese side was waiting for a report from the front line, with Commander-in-Chief of the 4th Fleet,
Vice Admiral Inoue, taking overall command of Rabaul Island Base.
Damage?
One destroyer, two minesweepers, and one submarine chaser sunk.
The fact that carrier-based aircraft have attacked
means that the US Navy has advanced into the Coral Sea.
Yes...
The enemy task force must be within 200 nautical miles of Tulagi.
However, our task force is currently refueling about 360 nautical miles north of Tulagi Island.
It seems that the enemy knows the movement of our navy
but that is besides the point.
Since they know that the purpose of our navy's operation is Port Morseby,
the enemy will not be able to move from the Coral Sea.
Telegram from the Chief of the Combined Fleet.
We are pleased to be able to destroy the US aircraft carriers that we have been struggling with since the beginning of the war.
On May 6, the Japanese Navy Mobile Task Force, under the command of Major General Takeo Takagi,
advanced into the Coral Sea in response to the order to destroy the US Mobile Task Force.
Major General Takagi, Commander of the 5th Carrier Division, and Major General Hara were staring out from the bridge Of the Japanese Navy's escort aircraft carrier Zuikaku.
Can we find it?
That's what I'm afraid of too.
Tomorrow night, we will pass through the southern tip of San Cristobal Island
and enter the Coral Sea from the east.
It's like looking for a loach in the Pacific Ocean.
That's exactly right.
At that time, the US Mobile Task Force, whose flagships were the two aircraft carriers Yorktown and Lexington,
was gathering together with the Combined Fleet of the United Kingdom and Australia, about 360 nautical miles south of Guadalcanal Island, to meet the Japanese fleet.
Fletcher, commander of the US MTF, held an operational meeting on the aircraft carrier Yorktown.
Japan's Kokoda Track Campaign is expected to pass through the Solomon Sea on the 7th.
So what about the Japanese MTF?
There is no doubt that they are heading south on the west side of the Solomon Island,
but their exact location is not yet known.
Anyways, discover the aircraft carriers before the enemy.
As quick as you can.
A battle between carriers is decided by a momentary difference.
Both the Japanese and US troops were desperately searching for an opponent to launch a first strike on,
but nothing happened during the two days of May 5th and 6th.
Is the enemy's aim to strike us tomorrow, when our troops pass through the Solomon Sea?
No, maybe their aim is the day after tomorrow,
when we are heading for Port Moresby on the Coral Sea.
If it is the day after tomorrow, they will probably act around the south tomorrow.
This is like hide-and-seek.
That's why the one who finds the enemy first wins.
We need to catch and destroy the enemy tomorrow.
What if there are no enemies at the estimated position?
Then, we also head west to the Coral Sea.
At that time, the Japanese convoy carrying the Port Moresby assault units were protected by an escort centered on the carrier Shoho.
They were moving southward in the central part of the Solomon Sea,
but after 9 a.m., it was wary because the enemy aircraft were close.
All crew. Man your stations!
Only one enemy aircraft.
Track it!
Thus, for the first time in history, a battle between aircraft carriers was gradually approaching.
Enemy aircraft carriers are always near here.
Look for the enemy with great care so as not to betray our radio wave detection.
Roger
Report from the reconnaissance aircraft.
Discovered an enemy aircraft carrier. 400 nautical miles southwest of Tulagi Island.
Ship attack, ship bombing, all aircraft take off.
It's an enemy fleet.
Japanese side, at the Rabaul Island base
The enemy is at Rossel Island at 170°, 82 nautical miles.
We observed that the enemy task force is split in two.
First, attack the enemy troops in the direction of Rossel Island with all our might,
while the convoy evacuates to the northwest under the escort of the MTF.
However,
the 5th Carrier Division is already 400 nautical miles southwest of Tulagi,
and has begun a full-scale attack on the enemy aircraft carriers.
What?
That is a refueling ship!
Where are the carriers?
The carriers!?
Around this time, the Japanese side had a convoy escort aircraft carrier Shoho,
under attack by carrier-based aircraft of the US MTF.
Captain. She was attacked.
What?
Damn
It is the responsibility of the 5th Carrier Division for the loss of Shoho.
How was it possible to mistake a refueling ship and a carrier?
Even so, everyone is late.
What are you doing, communications staff?
Throw away the bombs and torpedoes and recall them right away.
At this pace, we can't make it in time.
Assuming that the returning attacking unit is hurriedly collected,
our MTF will pursue and destroy the enemy in the northwest at full speed.
Be sure to take revenge on Shoho's behalf.
However, we have wasted too much time.
Sir, let's do it.
A night attack.
It's dangerous.
It's okay,
The 5th Carrier Division has excellent pilots.
It was no wonder that the Japanese commander was worried.
The 5th Carrier Division was formed just before the start of the war,
and the pilot training was insufficient, especially at night.
However, Major General Hara, the commander of the 5th Carrier Division, forcibly ignored it.
If we do it seriously, we can do it.
Okay, if the commander says as much.
Order:
The main unit will attack the enemy task force in the north of the Coral Sea at night.
The ship has excellent pilots, organize six carrier-capable bombers and nine carrier-capable attack aircraft,
and launch promptly as soon as it is ready.
Make a deadly attack.
Japanese aircraft are unaware of us.
The goddess of victory is smiling at our MTF.
Attack immediately
The North is squalid.
Captain, upper right sky, enemy planes!
Damn!
Damn.
How did they find us?
Throw away all torpedoes.
They are relieved because there are no fighters on our side.
Find that carrier.
I'm sure it's near here.
Find it!
Report from the 5th Carrier Division.
I haven't found the carriers and I am being attacked by the enemy's fighters.
I am engaged with enemy fighters.
My unit is annihilated.
Damn. Where did my home go?
l want to go home early and take a bath.
Captain.
At this rate, we will have to take a ridiculously large bath.
Moreover, it's a cold bath.
Captain.
A friendly carrier was spotted 60° to the right.
What?
That's it.
Immediately move to landing mode,
Captain!
This is an enemy carrier.
What!?
The numbers on the deck and the shape of the bridge are different.
It's an enemy!
They are back!
Sir,
there is an enemy carrier right there.
Is it true?
It is true.
Other pilots also saw it clearly.
Good.
Night attacks are difficult.
It is unfortunate.
How about tomorrow?
The second day of the Battle of the Coral Sea.
The US and Japanese troops, who could not wait for dawn, launched reconnaissance aircraft in search of the others carriers.
It's an enemy carrier.
There was a carrier.
Report from the reconnaissance aircraft.
I found an enemy carrier, I'm approaching it.
205° from our allied position, 235 nautical miles. Course 170°, speed 16 knots
Two aircraft carriers, one battleship, two cruisers, one light cruiser, and six destroyers.
Captain. We only have fuel for the return trip.
We've reported this in detail, so it's okay.
Good.
I will stop approaching the enemy and return.
Almost at the same time, the US reconnaissance aircraft also discovered the Japanese MTF.
The weather is changing quickly.
We have to accurately guide our allies.
Report from the reconnaissance aircraft.
I will stop returning and guide my allies.
I'll leave it to you, the attacking unit.
Captain
our fuel has run out.
Everyone, charge!
Fire!
Full starboard!
Hurry up!
This is exactly the wind of God.
Instead,
Shokaku is taking on the enemy at once.
It was badly done.
Look.
After the battle was over, the aircraft carrier Zuikaku appeared.
Communication staff.
Report to Rabaul’s Fleet Commander.
The attacking force is returning around 11 a.m., and the troops are being prepared, but today there is no prospect of a second attack.
In addition, because of the munitions and fuel consumed, high-speed navigation at night is not possible.
Commander Inoue of the 4th fleet received the report.
It can't be helped if Shokaku was attacked.
Stop the attack and order it to go north.
Operation Port Moresby has been postponed.
What? Was Operation Port Moresby postponed?
Let's issue a pursuit order.
The MTF of the 4th Fleet, which was ordered by the Chief of the Combined Fleet, Yamamoto,
went south at full speed at 2:00 a.m. on the 9th,
but could no longer capture the US MITE.
Upon hearing this report, the Commander-in-Chief Yamamoto immediately removed the MTF from the 4th Fleet.
This was because the day of the next scheduled operation, Midway, was approaching, but at the same time,
he was dissatisfied with the commander who abandoned the attack.
The damage caused by this naval battle was almost the same on both the Japanese and US side.
When you are too caught up in the damage of your allies, the damage to the enemy is overlooked and the operation stagnates.
The 4th Fleet of the Japanese Navy won tactically,
but lost the overall strategy.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Battle of Java (Episode Nine)
If you are a man, test your strength.
If you are a man, burn your hope.
If you are a man, don't let yourself down.
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production Subtitles by History Asian Cleaned up and resynced by Paul Geromini