The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan = (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking if you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
After a successful surprise attack on Hawaii, the Japanese army, which began the Pacific War,
advanced to Hong Kong, the Malay Peninsula, the Philippines, Celebes, Borneo, etc. Next were the Java islands.
The main purpose of Operation Java was to acquire abundant oil resources and to create a line of defense connecting the islands of Sumatra and Java.
At that time, Java was the Dutch East Indies. It is Indonesia now.
First, paratroopers of the Japanese Army descended to Palembang Airfield on Sumatra Island.
Battle of Java (Episode Nine)
The General Staff saw the capture of Java as the most difficult of the Southern operations,
and the oil fields were likely to be destroyed before the Japanese occupied them.
The refinery and airfield were occupied by the paratroopers.
In this way, the Japanese army conquered Sumatra, and started the siege of Java.
On February 27th, 40,000 members of the 16th Army, commanded by Lieutenant General Imamura, began their march on Java.
> The Allied commander of Java Island was Lieutenant General Hein ter Poorten of the Netherlands.
The Allied forces that protected Java numbered 80,000 in total, from the Netherlands, Britain, the US, Australia,
and local soldiers. In other words, it was twice the strength of the Japanese army.
But the Dutch Allied forces could convert as many as 50 million local civilians into soldiers.
Already in Indonesia, under the leadership of Soekarno and Hatta, there was a thriving national independence movement to resist Dutch rule.
Knowing the approach of the Japanese force the Dutch Allied fleet under the command of Major General Dolman, set sail,
but was immediately destroyed by the Japanese fleet in the Battle of the Java Sea off Slavaya.
However, torpedoes also hit four Japanese ships watching this battle in Bantam Bay.
Ironically, a friendly torpedo passed under a US cruiser to hit one of them.
They also hit Sakuramaru, the ship on which Commander Imamura of the 16th Army was on.
Imamura unexpectedly had to swim in the warm southern sea.
However, the General changed ships, and on March 1st, the Japanese army made every effort to begin landing on Java Island.
The main force of the 16th Army was divided into three parts and made good progress, all aiming to take Bandung.
> The entire army has landed successfully. > How is the battle going?
> Very well. No, it's just too good.
> Both the enemy and their allies, want to end this battle with minimal damage. > Yes.
> This is not a battle of attrition. I want to force the other party to surrender, with as little damage as possible.
> Well, it's still a long way off.
> Commander Ter Poorten was frustrated because he did not know the location of the Japanese army.
> He is currently reviewing the situation of each district. The Japanese army has 30,000 to 40,000 troops.
> Isn't it possible to get reliable information quickly?
> Since we are an Allied Forces of four countries, it takes time to contact each other.
> I want more accurate information.
> What are the natives doing? Let's use them to gather reliable information.
> Actually... > What?
> The number of Japanese troops that landed is about 50,000.
> 50,000?
> It seems that the Japanese army in Bandam Bay is 80,000.
> 80,000!?
> What, 200,000!?
> Comprehensive information from the field shows that the Japanese army has at least 200,000 troops.
Information about the Japanese Army was thus extremely exaggerated by the local residents and passed on to the Dutch side,
and it was believed that the 16th Army had 200,000 troops until the end.
> The Dutch army was confused by the information from the locals, so they made efforts to collect information.
Yet the indigenous peoples’ national independence movement favored tie Japanese military in all respects.
> How is the Japanese army moving? Give me reliable information.
> What? Want to know the movement of the Japanese army? That's impossible. The newspaper hasn't been distributed yet.
> The enemy has weekly counter-attacked in various places.
> The less resistance, the less damage to our allies.
> Is that a new tank?
> As of March 3rd, there was a report that the Japanese army had not yet landed on Java Island.
What a load of bull!
> It's a Japanese tank.
> Lieutenant General Imamura made a propaganda broadcast in order to lessen the fighting spirit of the Dutch army.
The Japanese army in Burma seems to have landed in Rangoon.
> What!?
> It seems that the Churchill Cabinet in England has taken responsibility for the fall of Singapore and has resigned altogether.
> The broadcast pleased the natives, and the Japanese army advanced with the support of the locals.
> However, as they approached Bandung, the resistance of the Dutch Allied Forces became fierce.
> At this time, the Japanese army's advance was stagnating.
On March 7th, a unit of more than 700 soldiers was formed. They planned to rush into the suburbs of Bandung.
> If the Indonesians are so hostile, then guerrilla warfare is almost inevitable.
Even if my Dutch troops surrender, the troops of each country may ignore my ceasefire order.
> Commander. As long as your Dutch soldiers fight we, the British and the Australians, will continue to fight.
> The determined words of the British, Australian commanders, and Major General Sitwell were all empty.
> Major General Pessman, who defends the northern central region of Bandung, surrendered quickly within a few hours of the start of the Japanese attack.
> Certainly, it is a messenger from Major General Pessman, commander of the North Central Region?
> He is definitely a messenger.
> Even though they resisted fiercely. Strange.
> I think the enemy is setting a trap. At this time, the city should be thoroughly destroyed.
> It is unavoidable to burn it down.
> Sir.
> I understand that feeling. The damage to the allies are increasing.
> The enemy resists, but does not try to leave the city. Perhaps they will build a defensive position and fight a decisive battle.
> However, there will be many casualties to the local people.
> No, we can evict them as much as possible.
Sir, please make a decision. Time is running out.
> Even if the allies are damaged, the local people must be protected Scorched earth operations are not allowed.
If you damage them here, you will lose their cooperation during the occupation. We did not come to fight the locals.
> Yes > Good. Let him negotiate.
> A Japanese military officer disguised as a local citizen with an interpreter had already infiltrated Bandung as a conspirator and was on standby.
However, on March 7th, before the Japanese troops rushed into Rembang, he immediately departed upon receiving an order from his military commander.
> I am the Japanese Lieutenant General Yanagikawa, and I want to meet the Commander of the Allied Forces of Java: Lieutenant General Tempur.
What!?
> The Japanese army has completely taken the Java Island. The city of Bandung has also been sieged.
Further useless resistance should be stopped immediately and we recommend your surrender.
> On March 8th, the Dutch army finally abandoned the fight.
The Bandung District Defense Commander, Major General Pessman, Governor Chalder, Lieutenant General Telpurten,
and Major General Pakkas, Chief of Staff of the Army, met with Commander Imamura.
> The situation near Bandung is terrible. I don't want to subject the citizens to any more misery.
I'd like to surrender Bandung.
> The surrender of Bandung is not the issue. The Japanese military demands a total unconditional surrender.
> The Bandung Broadcasting Station finally broadcast a stop order to the entire army.
Thus, the capture of Java, which was expected to be the most difficult of the Southern Operations,
was successful with unexpectedly small casualties, due to careful planning and the cooperation of the local people.
>On March 10th, the 16th Army unit, under the command of Lieutenant General Imamura, entered Bandung.
Operation Java is said to have been the only operation that received the welcome support of the local residents during the Pacific War and achieved the desired results.
It can be said that it was compassion that led Commander Lieutenant General Imamura
to protect the indigenous people and reject scorched earth tactics.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength If you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production