The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
Final Decision (Episode 25)
On the morning of April 27th, the UK, the US, China, a trilateral joint declaration was announced.
This is the Potsdam Declaration.
This morning, Kantaro Suzuki, the president of the Information Bureau of the Cabinet
and Hiroshi Shimomura admired the strength of the little bird that came to seek food even in the scorched earth.
> Good morning > Good morning, Mr. Oyadomari.
> Important news has arrived. > Important news?
> At 6 o'clock this morning, San Francisco reported a declaration from the United States, the United Kingdom, and China.
> The US, UK and China? Isn't it the US, UK, and Soviet Union? > It is in the US, UK and China. surely.
> So what? > They demand unconditional surrender by Japan. It consists of 13 items.
>It is almost the same as the Cairo Declaration. > That's right. What do you think? Not as an information officer, but as an individual.
> It is the same as an individual and an Army intelligence officer. I should be silent.
> I don't think so. > Hmm?
> If you read it carefully, it is very hard on the war leaders, but respects the people and human rights.
> It's just a ploy. > They are calling for surrender.
> Do you surrender to the US, UK and China?
> That's right. Looking at the current leadership, no one has the courage to respond to this surrender.
They don't know it's time to surrender.
The Army is in a thorough fight, and the Cabinet is trying to avoid responsibility. If we do that, we lose our chance.
No, not only our chance, but more and more people are being killed while we dither.
The United States, dropped leaflets sown with bombs to inform the Japanese people of this.
However, the cabinet decided to kill this proclamation as a plot to upset the people and claim that the United States was impatient to collect its own station as soon as possible.
> However, perhaps this problem is to well known to kill silently?
I think it would be suspicious to publish this important news in the newspaper without knowing it.
> Is it? If so, I will respect the minister's opinion.
If it is announced, it should be categorically criticized to prevent morale from deteriorating, and raise the fighting spirit.
> However, that would ruin the peace work that is currently underway through the Soviet Union.
> What? Are you still doing peace work? > If you do not show your will to fight to the end, you cannot even make peace.
> Despite the Soviet Union attending the Potsdam Conference, the Japanese government was still hoping for a peace treaty
through the Soviet Union and was negotiating through dispatches to Fumimaro Konoe.
> Captain Harry, Chief of Information for the United States, has declared that:
The entire population of Japan has become a front-line military target.
There are no non-combatants in Japan now. We seek to destroy the largest number of enemies, both men and women, in the shortest possible time.
Despite this, the Japanese people are unaware of the situation. I think we need to let them know.
In that regard, if you have any reason to oppose this, at your own discretion, please let me know in advance. It's a nuisance to the people.
> Sir, What is nuisance? The people are happy to die.
> What an idiot.
> Since you are a private actor, you do not feel worried about the country. 1 don't work for you anymore. Excuse me.
> That's a problem. > There are more problems.
Since the mainland will be a battlefield, it will kill all the old people, children, and sick ones.
I can't think of anyone who is going to be more of a stumbling block then commanders of the Japanese army who says such things.
> What? Do they, want to kill all our people? What do they mean?
> As if to underline this claim, another calamity fell on the innocent people who are killed by both their enemies and allies.
At 8:15 am on August 6th, 1945, the atomic bomb was dropped on Hiroshima for the first time in human history,
In an instant, 240,000 people were killed or injured there.
A plutonium bomb was also dropped on Nagasaki around 11:00 am on August 9th. Here again, more than 100,000 people died in an instant.
What surprised the Japanese commanders more than that was the actions of the Soviet Union, which
Japan had requested to mediate peace. Suddenly they had declared that they would participate in the war against Japan.
The first Cabinet meeting since then was held on August 9th at 14:30.
After explaining the current situation to Foreign Minister Togo, Prime Minister Kantaro Suzuki stood up.
> As Foreign Minister Togo said, things have become desperate.
I would like to ask all of you for your opinions and to decide on a policy regarding the Tripartite Joint Declaration.
> At present, no matter how much the three allied countries talk about the security of the imperial family and give favorable conditions,
unconditional surrender is inevitable. Of course, with the atomic bomb and war with the Soviet Union, there is no prospect of victory.
As we continue to fight for the honor of the Yamato people, we will have some chance.
Ask for the people's cooperation. If you come up with a tactic, I think there is a possibility that the battlefield situation will improve rather than us being completely defeated.
> What is the chance of that? In particular. > A decisive battle on the mainland.
> Only then will you have a chance. It's time to give the Army a chance.
> No, modern warfare cannot be done without the total backing of the nation. It's not a war that the Army or the Navy alone can win.
Prior to the the atomic bomb and the entering of the Soviet Union, there was no material for the war to continue in the current domestic situation.
In fact, the Navy has no chance of winning against the US and UK.
At this time, I am not particular about honor. I would like to stop this wishful thinking and have discussions in line with the actual situation.
> Thus, regarding whether or not to accept the Trilateral Joint Declaration, the group wanting to accept with Foreign Minister Togo and the Navy Minister Yonai
and the opposition group with the Minister of the Army, Anan, and the Minister of Munitions Toyoda will discuss long after 22:00.
However, no conclusion could be found.
> So what happened to the Cabinet decision? > We haven't come to a conclusion yet?.
> By the way, what about you, Governor? Do you want to accept or do you oppose?
> I have a personal opinion, But I'm spokesman for the cabinet. It is my job to give an opinion on behalf of the cabinet.
> More than that, when I came here, I was taught by looking at the cycads in front of the entrance of the Prime Ministers Office.
> That big cycad.
> After all, it was destroyed by air raids, and the leaves and trees were destroyed in bright red.
But when I look at it today, I noticed that blue sprouts are emerging from among the burnt trees.
The Japanese people are cycads. No matter what happens, someday new buds will come out again. We can't take the root. We have to leave them in any form.
> Hmm. I will go soon. > What is it?
> From 23:50, the Supreme War Leaders’ Meeting will be held. > Is it from now on?
> I don't want to kill the buds even a little. > Where?
> In the palace? > In the palace? Then, is it an Imperial Conference?
> There are cycads here as well
> Thus, from 23:50 on August 9th, an Imperial Conference was convened to ask for the Emperor's decision and decree.
The appearance of the ministers at the supreme Council varies, but their thoughts were just the result of the Imperial Conference.
> Mr. Shimomura, I would like to ask you. Has the Emperor ever been asked for his decree like this?
> No. Up until now, even though it was a sacred decision, it was said that the opinions summarized by his vassals would be approved.
His Majesty the emperor himself has not made a decision like this. There is a lot of fear.
> Hmm. After all. > It is unprecedented. The decision the people have made so far will be painful,
> The stars are beautiful. > At this time, what kind of story did you tell?
> Cycad. > Oh, so that's what you were talking about at the time.
> In other words, no matter what happens to the old leaves, if the roots are not withered, new shoots will come out again.
> Whatever happens to the old leaves.
> Thank you for waiting. The Supreme War Leaders Conference is now over. From now on, we will hold a cabinet meeting.
> Each member gave their opinions one by one, and after that, we received a sacred decision.
The gist of the words is that when looking at the situation in the nation, continuing the war not only destroys Japan,
but also makes the worlds human beings even more unhappy. He said that he would accept the three countries declaration, and end the war.
In addition, his Majesty had words of compassion for the Army and Navy soldiers, casualties, and victims of the war.
Thus the decree came down. However, some members of the Army and Navy have voiced opposition to
this decision regarding the conditions under which they would accept the Tripartite Joint Declaration.
Therefore, on the 14th, an Imperial conference was held again with the attendance of all ministers, and unconditional surrender was finally decided.
> Excuse me for the last time. Is this the original plan of an imperial edict?
> Yeah. It is quite difficult to want everyone in the nation to understand what will happen when the imperial decision comes down.
> How will you announce it? > Newspapers and radio broadcasts. I will do both, so it will be up to me.
> That One
> What happened? > Is it Jewel Voice Broadcasting?
> Yeah. > Some officers are aiming to prevent it.
> Is that so? Thank you for letting me know. > Please take some measures.
> There is no countermeasure. If this is his Majesty's life-threatening decree, then I will protect it.
During this time, when I received his Majesty's decree, I was deeply impressed. This final decision is life-threatening.
By the time of the final decision, there will be a lot of commotion.
It means that you can always make a decision to return to the beginning if you risk your life.
> I also made a lot of noise. > However, everyone thinks it's good for the country.
However, there are many things that are good for the country. It is the decision of the highest officer to make no doubt about it.
> Is your future life-threatening job to convey his Majesty's words to the Japanese people?
> Yeah
> 10:00 am on August 14th. An unprecedented in Japanese history "Jewel Voice Broadcast" was recorded.
> Mr. Yabe, you and I are the only ones who controlled the recording board in the basement of the Imperial Household Ministry. We may be caught tonight.
> What? > I wont talk even if it costs my life. I don't want you to break either.
> Of course
> Are you the Minister of State Shimomuria? > It's me.
> Alright, take him to the place.
> Hiroshi Shimomura? Please come for a moment.
> I brought Hiroshi Shimomura > Thanks.
> You are Hiroshi Shimomura, the president of the Information Bureau, right? > That's right.
> I've been checking the car now, but I didn't find the recording board for Jewel Voice. Where did you hide it?
> Why do you want that recording board? > I want His Majesty to spend another three or four days thinking it over and that His Majesty can trust the army.
> Can you do that in three or four days? > Please tell me anyways. Where is the recording board?
> I can't say.
> Then, would you like me to search your body?
> At that time, Governor Shimomura was fearful for his life.
At the same time, he envisioned a defensive mainland operation at the behest of the Minister of the Imperial Japanese Army Anan.
Life-threatening alone is not an accurate decision. What is the decision of the highest level?
> Stop it. It's not good to deal with Governor Shimomura now. He won't open his mouth anyway, so go look for it at the Imperial Household Ministry.
> Yes > Keep all of them in this place until we finish the work.
> Yes, I understand.
> They urged the Broadcasting Association, Director Yabe, to take him to the back of the Imperial Household Ministry
and ask where the recording board was, but he didn't say.
In addition, some rebel officers invaded the broadcasting station before dawn on the 15th and tried to broadcast
by themselves, but they did not succeed. They pulled up to the imperial palace and decided to commit suicide.
<The Jewel Voice Broadcast>
"enduring the unendurable and suffering what is insufferable."
> At the time, the superlative decision was life-threatening. > I think so too.
> But that alone does not seem to make a real decision, Everyone was fearful of course, His Majesty, Anan, Yoneuchi, Togo as well.
But why is everyone making a different decision although they are all fearful?
The difference is the protection of the national polity. Even if we say "Japan", it exists because the country and the people remain.
They haven't grasped this idea.
Without a country, there is no national polity. Now it's important to keep that country. If only the country is left, Japan will surely sprout again.
It's an eye that looks closely at the theme.
What's more, in order to see it, it is important to look forward to the future without being bound by your own position.
It's a real decision.
and a courageous one.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production