The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
> Air raid!
> Start up.
Rabaul Air Corps (Episode 15)
> 50 aircraft passed over the First Observatory. New formations of 30 planes, then the goal.
> There will be over 100 aircraft. > Damn, the number is increasing every day.
> What about our planes? > Already less than half.
> They are here.
> Since the withdrawal from Guadalcanal Island, Rabaul Base on New Britain Island has been on the frontlines, protecting the southern resources.
However, in the summer of 1943, the sea and air superiority around Rabaul had already been transferred from the Japanese army to the US army.
The main target of the US military is to block the Japanese supply line. That is, to destroy supply ships.
Due to their overwhelming quantity, the US military, conducting counter-offensive operations,
launched air raids on Rabaul, the main point of the Japanese military's southern base, every day.
<The 26th Air Squadron Command>
> Commander. Is the Combined Fleet Command still stuck?
> At the moment, it seems that they are not thinking about reinforcements for Rabaul. The Rabaul Air Corps should do its best as it is.
>, It's over optimistic. > Hey, it's a terrible word.
> However, the flight captain's reconnaissance aircraft report hundreds of planes
have gathered at the airfield centered on Guadalcanal Island in New Guinea, and their attack power has been strengthened.
Is it okay to leave them as is?
> Aviation staff?
> I will return to headquarters on Truck Island now. I would like to meet with the
Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet Koga in person and express my sense of urgency at the situation at Rabaul base.
> It's late. It may be too late after the staff returns to Truck Island.
Enemy MTFs and convoys frequently haunt the coast of Bougainville and the Coral Sea.
> Look
> Headquarters. This is the 305th Squadron. I discovered the enemy task force.
Two aircraft carriers, two cruisers, and six destroyers are moving east-northeast in a circle.
> Squad, looking at recent air raids and movement of enemy ships, the enemy is now planning to land on Bougainville or New Britain.
> Let's strike them. If we don't hit them now, it will be a big deal. > Did you find the enemy?
> It is a task force including the southern two aircraft carriers.
> I see.
> Headquarters. I've just discovered another target. I'll check the pattern of the convoy closely.
> Yabe. come back. Don't overdo it.
> After all, the enemy intends to land.
> Bougainville or New Britain has been decided. If this fleet is left as it is, we will be killed.
> Damn. I need an airplane. Do the people in the mainland know this?
Do they think there are hundreds or thousands of planes left in Rabaul?
> Captain, what does the Combined Fleet Say to our plan?
> Strategy discussions are underway. Engage in the given operation.
> What is it? If it was blurred, then Rabaul would also be a repeat of Guadalcanal.
> Headquarters. Another convoys of about 20 enemies.
> Several Grummans are attacking from behind.
> Yabe, are you okay? Don't die.
> Communication has been lost.
> Damn. I cannot stand it any longer.
Wait, Sasagawa!
> Sasagawa!
> Wait! > Captain. Please let me fly. I save Yabe alone.
> No. Do not get ahead of yourself. > Captain, I am not afraid to die. I am ready to die at any time.
> Sasagawa. I understand your feelings well. We are friends who vowed to be together when we die, but the military has must have discipline.
No reckless action is allowed until there is a sortie order.
Hey, Sasagawa, it's easy to die, but don't die in vain.
> Yabe knew he would never return, but he dived into the enemy anyways.
We wall cherish a little more life to reward his death. Someday, we can die together. Alright, Sasagawa?
> Yes.
> Yabe. We will go later.
> I'm Yonezawa, a member of the press team. > Please come in.
> The Combined Fleet on Truck Island is unlikely to move to Rabaul’s request.
> Here have one.
> It is certain that the enemy's target is Guadalcanal and then Bougainville or New Britain.
Are the great men willing to abandon the base at Rabaul?
> I am a fighter. The strategy is decided beyond our reach.
> No, but a strategy that ignores the intention of this front line.
After the Battle of Midway, the Combined Fleet has become stubborn.
> Midway was supposed to be a secret.
> Only the reality of Rabaul is faithfully conveyed. That is the duty of the press.
> Incidentally, please tell the people on the mainland to send as many planes as possible.
It used to be that the Rabaul Air Corps was sung in songs and boasted of its invincibility.
> Pilots longed for this Rabaul.
> Who is it.
> Yes. I am the maintenance manager Yamaguchi. > What happened?
> This was shot in a daytime air raid, but if I replace the engine, it could be fixed. Even one aircraft is precious at this base now.
By tomorrow morning, we will have a great air battle and we need the crew.
> At this time, at the Combined Fleet Command on Truck Island,
> A fleet of two aircraft carriers, three cruisers, four destroyers, and 10 cargo ships are moving north.
> Chief, Rabaul’s patrol aircraft found another fleet off the island.
> Is that so? So how many fleets are there?
> They discovered an enemy fleet of one aircraft carrier, two cruisers, and five cargo ships.
> Well then, next is Bougainville or New Britain.
>Chief. Return the planes and ships on Truck Island to Rabaul. We'll be in time if we act now. Chief!
Rabaul’s soldiers are waiting for the Chief's decision. Morale is also strong.
Now is the time to bring together all the strength of the navy and hit the enemy.
> I also agree with the opinion of the aviation staff. Hit enemies from the sea in the sea. This is the ironclad rule of battle.
What's more, Rabaul makes increasing requests every day. Turn your aviation planes and fleets over to Rabaul.
> The enemy's aim is Bougainville or New Britain, there is no doubt now. After they land, we will regret it.
> Sir. It may be a chance to relieve the black mark of Midway and Solomon. > Sir, let's do it.
Now that the morale of the soldiers is high. Let's beat the arrogant and rude enemies.
> Someone, call Lieutenant General Ozawa.
> The Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet Koga made a decision in response to the the request of the front-line base: Rabaul.
The Third Fleet under the command of Vice Admiral Ozawa and all of his planes were dispatched to Rabaul.
Operational decisions require agility and courage. In that sense, this decision slows the American side slightly.
Early in the morning of the day when the Ozawa fleet arrived in Rabaul, the U.S. military fleet of
18 transport ships and nine escort ships, which had been hidden due to bad weather on the previous day, suddenly landed on Cape Torokina on the west coast of Bougainville Island.
It was November 1st, 1943.
> As promised, I brought in reinforcements.
> 70 Zuikaku attack aircraft of the Ozawa fleet, 70 Chokaku Zero aircraft, and 30 Zuiho carrier-capable aircraft.
In addition, a total of 180 aircraft should be here by the 3rd.
What's wrong? Aren't you happy to see this much reinforcement?
> Ah. It's a pity that we didn't allow the enemy to land in Torokina one day earlier.
> Is that so? Have you been transferred to Rabaul? It seems to be fine and above all. Now, pray for continued luck in the fortunes of war and make a toast.
> I have something to ask.
> I know. You wonder why I didn't order the Ozawa fleet to be dispatched before the enemy invaded Torokina.
> Yes.
> I heard rumors that you are a good pilot, but I'm glad to have such a nephew. > Please tell me.
> These times are terrifying.
even if you aspire to be a lawyer, you look like a soldier now.
How many years will it take to become a full-fledged airplane pilot?
> Yes. It will take at least five years.
> I don't want to waste the excellent pilots who take five years to grow.
From now on, air power will be the most important thing. Do you think this war will end only in Rabaul?
The enemy, who is proud of their numerical quantity are now trying to make a big counterattack.
In such a case, it may be necessary to retreat and rebuild the formation rather than fighting the enemy with all one's might.
> Uncle > Because you are a relative, I just complained. Let's have a toast.
> Chief, please.
> Idiot. even though you used to call me uncle. I may not be able to meet you anymore.
> Ensign Koga. You volunteered for such an assignment, what are you thinking?
Rabaul isn't as easy as the mainland. Like the song now.
> It is encouraging to know that the captain of the 305th is Senior Kamijo.
> Captain. 30 degrees forward to the right, enemy plane.
Enter the clouds in front of you and make a reverse drop. Let's go.
♪ Rabaul air corps
> The Rabaul Air Corps made a fearless attack.
The result of the battle was announced spectacularly by the Imperial Headquarters at that time.
However, Rabaul’s air power was gradually exhausted in the face of the unending amount of American troops.
> Air combat was still going on on Bougainville Island.
On November 13th, 1943, an unbelievable situation occurred in the Rabaul Air Corps.
The headquarters of the Ozawa Third Fleet, who came with reinforcements from Truck Island, suddenly started pulling back toward Truck Island.
> It will be just us in the end.
> Now, with all the aircraft that can sortie at Rabaul Base, an order has been issued to attack and
destroy enemy task forces moving north on the sea west of Bougainville Island.
I have nothing new to do in the sortie. I just pray for your a good fight and your success.
> Captain, Captain, please take me too. I beg you. > Fool! You are injured.
> But, you said we would die together. > I'll wait at the Sanzu River. Come after healing that arm as soon as possible.
> Captain
> Everyone, this may be your last chance to see Rabaul.
> Captain Kamijo. My uncle asked me if I thought Rabaul alone would end the next war.
> Koga. You care about the Ozawa fleet pulling out of Rabaul.
I was expecting it. In the heart of your uncle, Commander-in-Chief of the Allied Fleet.
It is more important for a master to fall back than to attack.
I'm sorry for those of us who pulled the Ozawa fleet out of Truck Island and made your uncle's cool mind go crazy.
> Senior
> Are you all listening? Let's end the battle only for us. But never hurry to death. Live as much as you can and go home.
> Captain, the enemy's mobile unit.
> Upper right sky, enemy planes.
> Let's go, follow me.
> I am engaged with the enemy.
> What about subsequent communication? > Not yet.
> We are going home alive
> Captain Kamijo
> Come back alive. That is the soul of Rabaul.
> On February 1st, 1944, the US military jumped and landed on the Marshall Islands.
On February 17th, the MTF attacked Drag Island. Then, after air raids on Tinian and Saipan, Rabaul was completely isolated behind the front line.
In the midst of this hill-rolling momentum, is any decision useless or helpless? It may just be known only to heaven.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production