The most precious moment in life
is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace,
but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan = (decision)
Use your wisdom. Use your head Keep thinking if you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
December 2nd, 1941, five days before the surprise attack at Pearl Harbor.
The great fortress of Singapore, pride of Britain, was full of joy.
This is because the battleship Prince of Wales and the battle cruiser Repulse arrived at the port as the new main force of the British East Indies Fleet: Force Z.
This was announced worldwide, and no one doubted that Singapore's defense was an iron wall.
The Sinking of the Prince of Wales and Repulse (Episode Seven)
The Prince of Wales is a state-of-the-art battleship called the "Unsinkable Battleship"
because it never succumbed to the attack of the German battleship Bismarck in the Atlantic Ocean.
35,000 tons, max speed 28.3 knots,
armed with 10, 35 cm cannons,
and 16, 13 cm high angle cannons.
The eight-armed anti-aircraft guns, called "pom-pom guns", fired 6,000 shots per minute.
She is also equipped with a number of dual cannons.
Battlecruiser Repulse,
32,000 tons, max speed 30 knots.
Old-fashioned as she was her equipment was almost the same as the Prince of Wales.
At the Japanese military Hainan Island base.
Chief
Prince of Wales and Repulse are at Singapore Island.
If we sortie, they will come out.
We must make our landing a surprise.
However,
there is no guarantee that we will be able to hide ourselves from the enemy and land.
As long as the British East Indies Fleet exists, it will be dangerous to supply the Army from the sea.
I want to destroy the British fleet as soon as possible.
Commander,
Prince of Wales and Repulse will be destroyed by our Air Squadron.
Ok, I leave it to you.
I am prepared to safely deliver the landing party even if my escort fleet is wiped out.
I will do it
We will definitely protect our fleet.
When they come out, be sure to hit them from the sky.
"Sunrise is Yamagata". This encrypted telegram announced the decision to open the war on December 8th,
and the Japanese troops secretly advanced toward the Malay Peninsula and Singapore.
Above the fleet. One British aircraft!
They are finally coming out.
The enemy will be sending telegrams such as "Discovered the Japanese Navy's Grand Fleet" by this time.
It would be bad if the British East Indies Fleet came out now.
I don't mind. If the Prince of Wales comes out, it will be in the sea west of the Anambas Islands, where mines have already been set.
If they mistakenly come from the east, they will only find the eyes of our submarines.
However,
if the British realize the purpose of the surprise landing, it will hinder the entire Maylayan campaign.
No problem.
As planned, the course will be north-northwest and we will be shown to be heading for Thailand.
Sir
The Japanese fleet is heading for Bangkok, with 25 transport ships, one battleship, five cruisers, and seven destroyers.
However,
Air Force General Brooke-Popham General Commander of the British Far East force in Singapore,
did not take any measures because the purpose of the Japanese fleet was still unclear.
The Japanese convoy suddenly changed course to the west at 00:45 on the 8th.
Some of them have begun landing on parts of the Malay Peninsula.
Upon on receiving this information, Phillips, Commander-in-Chief of the British East Indies Fleet, gathered his staff.
The only target of the Japanese army that landed last night, is Singapore.
It is impossible for the Japanese army to bring Singapore down from the sea.
The British Force Z will make a surprise attack
with the support of the Air Force
and destroy the Japanese fleet.
There are 20 warships escorting the Japanese fleet.
The whole world knows that Prince of Wales and Repulse are in Singapore.
We are no longer hesitant.
Whenever we meet an enemy, we fight and hit it.
This is the pride and tradition of our Royal Navy.
5:35 p.m. on the 8th. Force Z of the British East Indies Fleet, whose flagship is Prince of Wales,
has set sail from Singapore's military port to launch a surprise attack on the Japanese fleet.
Sir,
a telegraph from the Air Force.
My fighters are heavily damaged by the Japanese force, and it is impossible to escort Force Z.
What?
Alright, let's make a surprise attack without the the Air Force.
Go around the east side of the Anambas Islands and proceed north.
The Japanese know that if we pass, it will be on the west side. It's impassable if mines are set up.
Force Z safely avoided a swarm of mines on the west side of the Anambas Islands and moved north.
However, on the afternoon of the 9th, Force Z was completely unaware that a Japanese submarine was waiting in its way.
The telegraph of the discovery of Force Z was sent to the base of the 22nd Japanese Air Squadron.
An emergency telegraph has been sent from the 5th Submarine Squadron, the 30th Submersible, I-65.
Read it
I saw two enemy Repulse-type battlecruisers.
Where?
Read it
Course 340°, speed 14 knots, 1515.
Impossible!
What does it mean?
Prince of Wales and Repulse have just been seen by our reconnaissance planes this morning when they were in Singapore.
Hmm, which one is correct?
Develop the reconnaissance photos. It's urgent.
This is a large merchant ship.
It is neither the Prince of Wales nor Repulse.
If so what about the telegraph from I-65?
I can trust it.
The enemy is heading here.
Alright. Sortie.
At 5:34 p.m., torpedo bombers were launched from the air bases in Saigon and Tudomo for an attack on Force Z.
The Japanese convoy on the eastern side of the Malay Peninsula immediately retreated to the coast of Thailand.
and the heavy cruiser and other escort ships proceeded to destroy Britain's Force Z in cooperation with the aviation unit.
We have no regrets if we fight against Prince of Wales.
Stop them from getting closer until the entire fleet of troops has landed.
It is impossible in this storm.
Should I turn back?
At 8:10 p.m., the torpedo bombers that took of from the Tsudomo base discovered a fleet that looked like Force Z.
Discovered enemy ships. 150°, 140 km
Unbelievable.
They mistook our ships for the enemy.
It you do not contact them quickly, we will be attacked.
Immediately send a telegraph. "We are the allies who are illuminated."
Reconnaissance is impossible due to bad weather. There is also a chance of mistaking friendly ships for enemy ships.
I understand.
Return the attack force.
We will try again tomorrow.
At that time, the British fleet thought they were found by the Japanese side, and they quickly turned back.
However,
the Japanese side did not discover Force Z.
Thus,
both the enemies and the friendlies turned their backs at the same time and parted.
Force Z, who abandoned the surprise attack, is returning to Singapore at 00:52 on the 10th.
Sir, an emergency call from the Singapore headquarters.
It says that the Japanese army is landing on Kuantan.
Sir, you can make a surprise attack.
Hmm, 640 km from the Japanese military base in Saigon.
First of all, there is no need to worry about being attacked by Japanese aircraft.
We can crush the enemy convoy and escort the fleet at the same time.
Alright, I can do it this time.
Let one destroyer scout ahead first.
Force Z sent the destroyer Express to Kuantan first,
and started advancing with the hope of ambushing the Japanese fleet
However,
although Force Z was completely unaware,
Its actions were discovered by the Japanese submarine I-58.
Never let it go this time.
Thoroughly find out the movement of the enemy.
If you find them, hit them with the whole force.
I'll do it.
Sink Prince of Wales and Repulse by plane.
You can definitely do it,
Immediately send the reconnaissance aircraft.
At 4:55 a.m., nine Mitsubishi G3M planes took off for reconnaissance from Saigon base.
However, the Japanese side was still searching for British Force Z.
It's been five hours already.
Damn.
Where did the Royal Navy go?
Captain.
We have passed the planned 600 nautical miles.
Idiot!
Do you think we can go home as it is? We looked for them thoroughly.
Captain.
You can see the Malay Peninsula.
Yeah, it's Kuantan.
At that time, a shadow was reflected in the captain's eyes.
Hey, look.
It is an enemy ship.
Alright, check it out.
Use the clouds to get closer.
It is definitely Prince of Wales and Repulse!
I did it!
Congratulations
Send the telegram
Sir
Discovered Prince of Wales. 4° north latitude, 3° 55' east longitude, 60° course.
They are shooting at us.
I wish we brought a torpedo!
Reconnaissance is boring
Idiot!
War cannot be done alone.
Reconnaissance and sinking enemy ships are the same mission.
Roger
Alright.
Keep an eye on them until our attack aircraft arrive.
I won't let you go.
The third reconnaissance aircraft discovered the enemy's main force off the coast of Kuantan.
Don't let it escape,
be sure to sink it by plane.
Every attack aircraft is rushing to Kuantan.
I wish you good luck
Japanese attack aircraft will definitely come.
Prince of Wales is not afraid of airplane attacks.
The enemy is also desperate.
Make sure the counterattack plan is perfect.
It's okay to attack at any time.
It's time to show the bravery of the Royal Navy.
Knock all enemy planes into the sea.
Enemy main force, change of direction. Course 60°, speed 20 knots.
What is the attacking unit doing?
Come on.
Captain.
There is no fuel.
Alright
Everyone. Throw away your belongings.
Huh
It is to save fuel.
Weapons and clothes.
Hurry!
At that time, eight Japanese air squadrons reached 3,000 meters above Repulse.
For the first time in naval history, the battle of airplane vs battleship began.
A bomb hit the Repulse.
It won't sink in one shot.
It's the torpedo bomber unit.
Two torpedoes hit the Prince of Wales.
The engines have stopped.
Fire!
Fight until the last soldier.
Telegraph to Singapore.
We are being bombed by the Japanese Navy.
The enemy is also doing a good job.
As expected, it is an unsinkable battleship.
Eighth company with eight aircraft.
I'll leave it to you.
This time, I'll leave it to you!
The battle of the British fleet was tremendous.
But first,
the end came to the Repulse.
Put on your life jackets!
All crew gather on the upper deck and prepare to leave the ship.
God save you.
The Repulse is sinking.
It's fine. She fought well.
Next, Prince of Wales.
Fire!
Sir!
All crew abandon ship!
All crew have left the ship.
She fought well.
This is the knight of the British Empire.
Sir, let's go to the lifeboats right away
No, I'm fine.
Sir! Captain!
Prince of Wales is sinking
Captain,
there is not enough fuel to return.
Report the results of the battle.
Watch out!
Are they out of bullets?
No, its Bushido.
Did you do it?
Yes
An unsinkable battleship was sunk by airplane.
The successful capture of Singapore is only a matter of time.
The next day, a Japanese plane flew to the sinking site of Prince of Wales and Repulse to drop two bouquets.
The battle between the Japanese and British forces in the Naval Battle of Malaya was spectacular and imposing.
One bouquet is for the British soldiers and the other is for the Japanese soldiers.
These were for their devotion
to fight to fulfill their mission.
However, the Japanese Navy did not fully asses the arrival of the aviation era, and eventually went on the road to a major defeat.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Battle of the Coral Sea (Episode Eight)
If you are a man, test your strength If you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production Subtitles by History Asian Cleaned up and resynced by Paul Geromini