The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom Use your head Keep thinking it you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
Operations Midway and Aleutian were carried out in June 1942 with the main force of the Japanese Navy.
Operation Midway has been a major defeat for the Japanese since the beginning of the war,
but the Aleutian Operation was able to occupy Attu and Kiska without any resistance from the US.
Kiska Withdrawal (Episode 16) but the Aleutian Operation was able to occupy Attu and Kiska without any resistance from the US.
Kiska Withdrawal (Episode 16)
Kiska Island is about 40km long and about 10km wide and is closed to ice and snow all year round.
Even in the summer, it is often covered with thick fog and the temperature is below freezing.
In the first place, the purpose of the Japanese Army's Operation Aleutian was to stop the advance of the American MTF from the north.
On Kiska Island, there were about 5,600 Army and Navy soldiers under the command of the North Sea garrison commander and Major General Mineki.
> Sir. According to reports from Northern Command reconnaissance planes, the enemy unknowingly built an air base on the neighboring island of Amchitka.
> What?
> It seems that the United States is on the offensive from the battle on Guadalcanal Island in the south, but has it finally reached the north?
> Approximately 90 nautical miles from Amchitka Island to Kiska Island. Naturally, Attu Island will also be hit harder than it is now.
Kiska Island and Attu Island are important bases in the north for us. We absolutely have to protect them.
> It's an air raid
> The Imperial Headquarters immediately began transporting reinforcements to Attu Island and Kiska Island.
On May 11th, Approximately 11,000 US troops escorted by the US North Pacific fleet under Major General Thomas Kinkade began landing on Attu Island.
The garrison captain, Colonel Yamazaki, and less than 2,500 Japanese soldiers fought back fiercely,
but on May 30th, they were finally wiped out. This was the first Japanese army to die via banzai charge.
The US military, which regained Attu Island from the Japanese army, set up a fleet blockade in the North Pacific to block the isolated island of Kiska.
The Imperial Headquarters finally ordered a submarine withdrawal from the isolated island of Kiska,
but the US Pacific Fleet's scrutiny made the withdrawal operation difficult.
> Enemy attacks are becoming more intense day by day. The landing on Kiska Island will begin shortly.
Before that, we have to complete the withdrawal without leaving any soldiers.
> The enemy's vigilance is strict. Several submarines have already been sunk.
> How many have successfully withdrawn via submarine? > 820 out of 5,639.
> Hmm. It is 15%? > Only about 80 people can be loaded on a submarine at a time.
> Staff officer Fuji. > Yes
> Please go to Paramushir. I would like the you to advise the Northern Command to withdraw everyone at once by surface ships.
And as soon as possible. This will be the final meeting on the withdrawal.
> On June 16th, the submarine carrying Staff officer Fujii escaped Kiska Island safely. On the 20th, he arrived at the Chishima Islands, Paramushir.
The Northern Command of the Navy was anchored at the port of Paramushir Island under the command of Vice Admiral Kawase's 5th Fleet.
> The local commander strongly desires to withdrawal by surface ships.
Currently there has been a lot of damage to our submarines. Withdrawal by submarines must be stopped.
> Can a large number of ships escape the eyes of the enemy's strict surveillance and go to Kiska Island? That is the problem.
> Besides, we cannot expect the support of the aviation unit,
> This is clearly reckless.
> On Kiska Island, 5,000 comrades are holding out under the fierce attack of the enemy. Do you want to make the same mistake we made on Attu Island?
> It takes at least 10 days to go to Kiska Island and come back. It is almost impossible for a large fleet to act without replenishing by tanker.
> I am not confident in the Navy.
> If there is something that can protect the ships of our large fleet, it will be solved.
> Unfortunately, our fleet.
> There is one way.
> Call Beard of Kimura.
> Beard of Kimura is the captain who assumed command of the flagship Abukuma 10 days ago.
A sailor who just assumed command of the First Destroyer Squadron: Major General Kimura.
> Let's accept it.
> Thank you.
> It's a big role. The enemy has an excellent radio detector. > There is also a strategy here.
> I see. > One of the ancient Japanese ninjutsu techniques, the technique of fog.
> What?
> Kiska Island is a foggy place. It is advantageous to act using the fog. > I see.
> Thus, the Kiska Island withdrawal operation, which relies on the fog of the North Sea, proceeded steadily.
> The greatest weapon of the withdrawal operation is fog. In August, the fog will fade. If we do this, we should complete it by mid-July.
> How many Daithatsu-class landing craft are there? > About 10 ships can be used.
> It takes time to transport by itself, Alright, let's load 12 ships.
> The biggest problem is the meeting point and meeting time of the local army.
> Even if we can approach Kiska Island but make a mistake in our meeting time...
> The meeting point is Kiska Bay. The meeting time is five days after the day from when our rescue fleet sails. It's about 3 hours after sunset.
> What if the fog clears and we can't get close that day?
> Have them try again every day. At that time. The withdrawal operation is a covert action.
> Be careful when contacting the local army.
> The rescue fleet decided to set sail on July 7th. Our garrison will meet at Kiska Port at sunset on the 11th. Do not leave a single soldier.
> When will the rescue fleet arrive? > They can't come so easily. Will we suffer the same fate as Attu Island?
> July 7th, 1943, the rescue fleet under the command of Major General Kimura is two light cruisers, ten destroyers, one tanker,
and one landing ship. With a total of 14 ships, they left via Kuril Islands, rather than the port.
> The fog condition looks good. > No, optimism is not allowed.
> Even in the fog, if the enemy finds us, everything is over. > Stay outside 500 nautical miles from the enemy air base.
> The rescue fleet reached 500 nautical miles southwest of Kiska Island on July 12th,
as scheduled. It finished refueling, and turned its course to Kiska Island.
However, at the time of the decision, the fog cleared up. It's an ironic prank of nature.
> Sir. We've come this far with a preparedness for death. Let's do it.
> Sir, they are urging you to come all at once.
> If we approach Kiska Island, the fog may come out.
> Why don't you go back to the waiting point and wait for that time?
> We can't. There is not enough fuel. > Then, why don't you turn back and try again?
> We won't be able to do that either. The current issues is fuel shortage. Even trying twice is too much for this big family.
> Then, are you condemning the Kiska Island garrison?
> Sir
> Sir, please make a decision.
> Lets go home. We can come back again if we can.
> That day, the Kiska Island garrison, which was waiting for the rescue fleet, soon received
a brief description of the cancellation of their withdrawal operation. Kiska Island was once again in despair.
What came to their mind was the appearance of their comrades smashed on Attu Island.
> Good. How is it? > How about taking advantage of this Opportunity?
> Then, do you want to attack this one? > At that time, it was already too late.
> No, I'm here. I was just a little careless. > The key to winning or losing is to be a little careless.
> Sir. > What?
> Fog is occurring from Paramushir to Aleutian. > How many days will it last?
> 5 days probably. > Good.
> Is that so? What day is it today?
> It is July 19th. > Hmm.
> Here, let's skip the story to July 30th, about 10 days after July 19th, and explain the situation on the US military's side.
From this day, the American North Pacific Fleet began a naval bombardment on Kiska Island every day.
The landing of the US military on Kiska Island is finally approaching. The area around Kiska Island was
completely blocked by the American North Pacific Fleet, making it completely impossible for the Japanese fleet to approach.
On August 14th, US troops finally launched a landing operation on Kiska Island.
The number of participating ships was 91, and the number of troops exceeded 34,000.
> Where did the Japanese army go? > I think they escaped into the mountains.
> On Kiska Island, there were only three stray dogs and no Japanese garrison.
At that time, 25 American soldiers were killed by friendly fire and 31 were injured due to anxiety and fear.
How about 5,000 Japanese garrison soldiers escaped under US military surveillance and withdrew into the North Sea fog was a mystery.
Lets return to the Japanese military side on July 19th.
> Sir > What?
> Fog is occurring from Paramushir to Aleutian. > How many days will it last?
> In any case, I think this is the last fog > Good.
> Is that so? What day is it today? > It is July 19th.
> On July 22nd, the rescue fleet for the second withdrawal operation left Paramushir in the thick fog.
> It's a great fog. > I don't want it to clear up as it is.
> On the light tour ship, Staff officer Fujii prayed for the safety of his comrades on Kiska Island.
> I will show you success this time. Please wait.
> If the enemy lands, I am sorry. > Only you guys will be alive.
> The rescue fleet has left Paramushir. > Is it true?
> This time, I can finally go home > Is it true? Good.
There was a telegram saving that they would leave today.
> The Kiska Island defenders were delighted. However, two American destroyers were still watching at the entrance to Kiska bay.
Around that time, one US military reconnaissance aircraft caught sight of seven ships that seemed
to be the Japanese fleet on radar 200 nautical miles southwest of Attu Island,
and the US North Pacific fleet gathered at the point indicated by the reconnaissance aircraft on July 25th, preparing to ambush the Japanese fleet.
However, they were actually bombarding a Japanese ghost fleet. The American side was unaware of their radar error.
What radar thought was a Japanese fleet was an echo on a nearby island. The bombardment fired more than 1,000 shells into the cold North Pacific waters.
At that time, the Japanese rescue fleet was waiting while replenishing at a point about 500 nautical miles, far southwest of Kiska Island.
> Damn. The fog cleared up again.
> Same as the first time.
> The foggy season may have passed. It was late to begin with.
> Sir, if nothing is done, we will be immediately discovered by enemy reconnaissance aircraft. If we are attacked, everything is over.
> Sir, the Kiska Island garrison contacted us. They have reported that the weather on the 29th is definitely foggy.
> However, I can't believe that fog will come out in this weather.
> No, it's a great opportunity. Start towards Kiska Island.
> Sir, then it's like jumping into the enemy's pocket.
> When an enemy fleet comes out, we will fire and withdraw then.
> On July 29th, fog miraculously covered the North Pacific Ocean.
The US North Pacific fleet, which bombarded the Japanese ghost fleet and consumed fuel, gathered at 105 nautical miles south-southeast of Kiska Island to refuel all ships.
As a result, Kiska Island's surveillance disappeared and at this moment,
Major General Kimura decided and the rescue fleet rushed into Kiska Bay in the fog.
> A ship has arrived. It's a Japanese ship,
Look. We can go home.
> Please see, Sir. The happy faces of those soldiers. > It was good
> The last landing craft has arrived.
> Sir, thank you for your patience.
> It was hard work.
> Approximately 5,000 Kiska Island garrison members have completed their withdrawal. It took only 35 minutes.
Is this lucky withdrawal of Kiska just a coincidence?
At the time of the first withdrawal operation, if Kimura made a reckless decision and made the decision to go in,
he would surely be under the scrutiny of the US military and there is no doubt that he would be wiped out.
In the worst case, a commander must not lose his composure.
A calm decision maker that should always look at all possibilities and lead them to success can really be of value.
On August 1st, the rescue fleet safely arrived at Paramushir Port.
After that, as before, US troops continued to bombard the ghost defense forces on Kiska Island, astonishing the three dogs.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength It you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production