The most precious moment in life is the time of decision.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
Ketsudan (decision)
Use your wisdom, use your head Keep thinking if you're a man
Whether you cry or laugh, it depends on your decision
Don't be arrogant even if you win Don't cry even if you lose
Man does not show tears
Tatsunoko Production
The purpose of Japan's southern operation in the Pacific War was to acquire oil.
This operation, which seeks to cross the sea and land on enemy territory, was unprecedented in the history of warfare in terms of its scale.
Therefore, the 16th Army, under the command of Lieutenant General Imamura, was joined by other land, sea, and air forces in joint operations.
January 2, 1942, Japanese troops occupied Manila in the Philippines. With that momentum,
they launched an operation to capture Celebes Island across the Makassar Strait, east of Borneo.
As part of this Celebes Island operation, the Navy's Southern Forces planned an attack with paratroopers.
The commander was Vice Admiral Tsukahara, Commander-in-Chief of the 11th Air Fleet.
> The main body of the Japanese Navy Land Force will land in the direction of Manado on the west coast
and partly in the direction of Kema in the east. They will attack the enemy from both sides.
At the same time, paratroopers will land in Langoan to capture Langoan's airfield and Kacas's port.
> The paratroopers will descend into the middle of the enemy. > They will divide the enemy and weakens their power. That will be our first win.
> This operation by the Japanese paratroopers was a challenge for the untested Japanese forces.
Japanese Marine Paratroopers (Episode 10)
> Winning the battle is the highest priority
> Although it is out plan, isn't too reckless to suddenly descend into the middle of the enemy's position?
It they become besieged by the enemy, the few paratroopers will be at great risk.
> I am fully aware of the risk. > Please reconsider their point of descent.
> lam not afraid of death. I just want to do my best.
> The attack by the paratroopers was decided to be the best plan to capture Celebes.
> It is still possible to change their descent point.
> It is important now to carry out our plan. Now our priority is the plan. That's it.
The tactic of using paratroopers to surprise the enemy and take the initiative has already been used by Germany and other countries.
Following that, the Japanese Navy's paratroopers were created in secret in 1941, with life-threatening training.
On January 11th, 1942, at 4:00 am, the landing in front of the enemy began when the Navy paratroopers descended.
> Hurry to the airfield. Go to the airfield as soon as possible,
Don't kill the paratroopers. Don't isolate the paratroopers.
♪ Sora no Shinpei (The Divine Soldiers of the Sky)
January 12th, 11:30 am. The ground troops and the Navy paratroopers finally link up.
It was 31 hours after the start of the battle.
> Murai, you. > Tateno, you.
> It was a wonderful descent.
> You guys led a wonderful attack too. I wanted to see you as soon as possible.
> We were waiting.
> It's been a long time. > It's been too long since the academy. We used to look at the sky like this.
> Hmm, I miss those days.
> Thanks to you for the success of our paratroopers.
>What are you talking about? This is because we, the Navy and the Special Army Squadron, cooperated with each other.
> For that reason, the paratroopers were immortalized in the song: The Divine Soldiers of The Sky
> The paratroopers are popular wherever they go. > Because they are now the divine soldiers of the sky.
> Because their parachutes are gorgeous. > Hey, don't be jealous.
> I'm not jealous.
> That makes the ground crew look pitiful.
> Aren't we comrades who share the same blood and flesh? What do you say.
> Are you a paratrooper? > No, I'm not. This is the paratrooper,
> Please come talk about parachutes. > Hey, stop It.
> Please? The children are waiting.
I am contused.
> It's good. Think of it as an act of goodwill.
> Hurry up. > Murai. sorry.
> Well, I'm getting used to it. > What?
> Alright.
> Not just paratroopers. The blood of our ground forces also seep into the land of Celebes.
> Who is it? Stop!
Which unit do you belong to? > The Paratroopers.
>Is it a paratrooper?
> My unit is... > I know.
Go back to your unit. Go!
> I am... > T fully understand your feelings.
> The paratroopers are thinking of occupying this area on their own. I can't stand it when I think of my dead comrades.
> I understand. So what should I do?
> If you leave it as it is, it will only hurt both sides. Is there any other way?
> I understand what you mean. But we just came down from the sky with a parachute.
> I'm sure something is wrong somewhere.
> We, who were exaggeratedly praised like “divine soldiers of the sky", are quite a nuisance.
>I didn't say. that, but when I think of my subordinates, I can't stay still.
> Hey, Murai. It's nothing to be angry about. Time will solve this.
> Is that so? You can't understand my feelings.
> Hey, this is a battlefield. Tomorrow we may be at the forefront with each other. We're are risking our lives here. Such a thing...
> Wait. Murai.
> "Divine soldier of the sky?"
Is this a military hero?
> Hey, are you great because you are a paratrooper? Do you think that only paratroopers are soldiers?
> This hero is pathetic.
> Chief, if you leave it as it is, the gap between the two branches will only deepen. We have to think about countermeasures as soon as possible.
It may have a significant impact on future operational plans.
> The parachute operation was successful. Don't worry about the little things.
> I understand. But,
> Captain. I don't need that story anymore, We must prioritize the plan.
> Yes
> Unexpectedly, the operation went smoothly.
> With this, the capture of Java was completed one month earlier. This is the result of planning first.
There is no need to make a decision on this issue. The paratroopers will move to other operations.
> Will the paratroopers move?
> The strategy is the priority. Captain.
> The paratroopers stayed on Celebes Island for about a month and set out for a new battlefield, Timor Island, and Turban further south.
> With the departure of the paratroopers, the conflict between the ground forces and the paratroopers seemed to disappear.
> Hey, please tell me: Do you have any interesting stories about paratroopers?
How about this? Please give us your impressions when you shook hands with the paratroopers at Kakas Airfield.
> No
> Hey, if you want to write about the paratroopers so much, why don't you ask them directly?
> Let me go! > What if you chased them?
> I would like to write about the friendship between the paratroopers and you, the ground forces.
> Friendship? > With the world-class paratroopers.
> What friendship?
> Stop it.
> Excuse me.
> Apologize
> However. Ensign.
> Apologize > Excuse me.
> Please take a look. The graves of the paratroopers are full of bouquets. The graves of the ground troops have no flowers.
Do you understand the meaning of the soldier's tears?
> I know. A soldier who landed with a parachute. He gave me 5 cigarettes.
A very nice soldier who held my child and and was kind. Please write this story.
They were brave. The paratroopers were strong.
> If you ask the press, all the people on the island talk about is paratroopers.
Because they know you guys are happy with it.
> You may just choose a flashy story. However, we ground troops also fought.
Can't you understand why the same people hate each other?
> Come in.
> Were you fighting again? > Yes
> Why do soldiers who have fought soberly have to hit each other almost every night?
> It is said that the guerrillas are considerably well trained. Be careful.
> Yes. > Wait.
> Looking at your eves, I'm very worried. I think you're well aware, but don't get drawn in too deeply.
The purpose of this mission is not to destroy the guerrillas all at once, but to gradually weaken their power.
Yes
> It is also important to decide when to stop pursuing. Never chase too deep.
> Ensign Murai was instructed by the Captain of the battalion to subdue the Dutch troops who continued guerrilla
warfare in the interior of Central Celebes.
Remember that soldiers are human.
> It's a strange atmosphere. > Isn't it because it's been a long time?
> This time we are the protagonists.
> Now write about us.
> The battle is like clearing up the past. What was hidden in the chests of the soldiers suddenly bursts out.
It was a tremendous guerrilla war.
> This time we are the protagonists.
> The plan is the priority. Is there a way to do something other than prioritize the plan?
> Because there are no paratroopers. > This time, they write about us.
> They were not afraid of death and their assault was so violent that no one knew what to say.
> Even if you chase the enemy, you cant chase deeply.
> This subjugation operation, which killed seven people, including the platoon leader, was too severe for such a battle.
What was it that made his subordinates forget their judgment and motivated them to rush to this brutal death?
The brilliant success of the capture of Celebes Island gave the Japanese troops great confidence in the subsequent Southern operations.
But in this battle, we must rethink the meaning of the commander's words: prioritize the plan.
The Pacific War taught us the preciousness of peace, but it also leaves us with many lessons to live.
If you are a man, test your strength If you are a man, burn your hope
If you area man, don't let yourself down
I and you are men and men bleed the same bright red blood.
Tatsunoko Production