I would be sad if you thought
That I can do anything on my own
I heard the wind carry someone's "Good morning"
Into my room through the open window
Ito Aki
As the sunlight
Comes flying to my unkempt hair
Tanaka Kumi
It's nice weather for soccer
But I'll have to control myself
Fujimura Saori
It pains me, but I'll put off dating for a while
Aida Sachiko
On that Sunday when we can't meet
Don't look at other girls, only think about me!
If you just give me a call
You've been cast in a TV drama.
To tell me to keep doing my best
What? I'm playing the lead?!
Then I'll feel a lot more energetic already
This is our guest star, Aida Sachiko-chan.
Nice to meet you!
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
Special TV drama
Love on Tiptoes
Script
S-So many lines to remember...!
That's right!
I dream that I'm more beautiful
Okay, action!
Than anything else in the world
So, Aki, what's your cat's name?
You know, it would make me happy
Uh, that's...
Uh...?!
If you thought so too in some corner of your heart
Okay, let's retake!
Take 13. Action!
Geez, I can't eat any more!
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
Birth
Debut
Orphan Fansubs presents
I'm off!
Love on Tiptoes
Ah, Mike.
How's it going, Mike?
Oh, you're doing well too, Chibi?
Looks like you've grown a bit.
Kaori Girls' High School
CLASS 2-C
If there were no cherry blossoms in this world
How much more tranquil
our hearts would be in spring.
This "mashi," the last word of the poem,
is the counterfactual auxiliary verb "mashi" in its final form.
I explained the counterfactual auxiliary verbs last time.
With the binding particles "seba" and "setto,"
they make a supposition
that is contrary to reality.
Counterfactual
Verbs
We use them to make a conjecture,
Counterfactual
Verbs
"If something were true,
what would happen then?"
Counterfactual
Verbs
Tanaka-san.
Yes! Good morning.
Have you tried sneaking in quietly when you're late?
Well, you'd find out anyway.
"Be light and bright. Don't worry,"
is my motto, after all.
Hurry up and take your seat!
Okay.
I looked at you with a start
And I couldn't believe
Welcome.
Are you ready to place your order?
How about our new curry rice burger?
That I could smile like this again
So you feed the stray cats every morning, Aki?
The beginning comes as a surprise
Yeah. If the locals from the apartment complex
see it, they'd probably get upset,
so I have to feed them
under the stairs secretly.
I see. Maybe I should try feeding stray cats too.
Like a flash of light in my heart
What're their names?
The cats?
Yeah.
Oh, nothing fancy.
I call the kitten Chibi, and his mother...
Mike!
Hey, Mike?
You're just kind, you're just fun
Yes?
Be here at 5 o'clock tomorrow.
But you're also sad
Okay!
Thanks for your help.
I'm off!
Before I knew it
All I could think about was you again
What's with you, Aki?
No matter what I look at...
No, it's nothing.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Tomorrow at 5, right?
Kumi!
Let's stop at Joe's on the way home.
Um... I'm running out of cash
from going there every day.
I'll buy you a shake.
Oh, Kumi...
I couldn't help it, all right?
Sure, sure.
I'm sorry!
Thank you.
Who's that?
Fujimura Saori from Class A.
You didn't know? She's a third year.
I didn't know.
Please enjoy your meal.
I was dumped
Whew, that was good.
A month ago
Ah, Mike! Small fries please.
Coming up!
And I didn't want to go
Here, thanks for waiting.
That reminds me. That guy...
Through that pain again
I wonder why they call him Mike.
I want us two
Oh, that.
His full name is Miura Kenichi.
So they nicknamed him Mike
by combining the first letters.
To laugh together again
He's needs to redo his entrance exams.
Wait a minute. How do you know so much about him?
So much so that
When I look at these scars, I feel nostalgic
Well, I have the details
on most every guy
in the vicinity of our school.
Wow, sounds admirable.
You're just kind, you're just fun
Admirable, that's me.
But seriously, nicknaming Miura Kenichi "Mike"...
Isn't that a bit disrespectful?
But you're also sad
Not really.
I had a classmate in middle school named Goto Masako,
Even when I try to cast it off
All I can think about is you
and everyone called her Goma.
Oh, I see.
But he's nothing spectacular as a man, is he?
You think so?
It's the power of love that makes towns
and people love each other
I-I think he's okay.
Speaking of that, I wanted to tell you something.
What's with you?
Those sparkling eyes are sickening.
Actually... Recently, I've fallen in love.
Again? How many times
is that this year?
LIBRARY
Book: The Grass Radical by Naoyuki Ii
I think I'll go with this one.
I'll take this one, please.
Okay.
Fujimura-san?
Oh, we met yesterday?
Here, it's due Tuesday.
Library Preparation Room
Thanks.
Sorry I'm late!
I want to see you now
I want to see you right now
Hurry up and change.
Oh, where's Mike?
But I can't
He's off today.
What? It's boring without him.
Before I knew it
Maybe I should go home too.
This is no time for jokes!
All I could think about was you again
Welcome!
Next counter, please!
So she's from our school too?
No matter what I look at...
Well anyway,
you should've seen his face.
So?
Can you understand how I feel?
For instance, when I call his house, he's inattentive
and doesn't even listen to me.
And if I stop talking, he immediately switches to talking about other girls.
And when I tell him to stop, he says,
"Why, are you jealous?"
And laughs it off.
Do you understand?
I don't.
You're so insensitive!
Hey, Aki! Let me tell you something this once, just in case.
What?
About that boy you like.
Which one?
Mike!
Don't say that out loud.
What?
What about him?
He has a girlfriend.
Really? Is that all?
It doesn't concern me.
Are you sure it doesn't?
She's from our school, you know.
It doesn't concern me!
Don't even wanna know her name?
No, I don't!
See ya.
Bye-bye.
Aida Sachiko
Class 2-F, Aida Sachiko.
I'm off for today!
Thanks for your help!
Welcome.
R-Right... Th-Thanks.
Your fish burger and ice coffee.
Sorry to make you wait.
Thanks.
Really?
No way!
Why, you!
I wonder if she's really Miura-san's girl.
The Grass Radical
Naoyuki Ii
Are you into tearjerkers like this?
Yeah, I guess I am.
I'm the kind who tends to cry
when reading a novel.
So then, have you read
Flowers for Algernon?
No. Is it sad?
I borrowed it from a friend.
I cried so hard!
Then I'd like to read it too.
Do you have it here?
Yes. Let me get it for you.
This is it.
Flowers for Algernon
KICHIJOJI
Sorry to disappoint you,
but your prediction was wrong.
She's not Miura-san's girlfriend.
You think so?
My information is never wrong
when it comes to relationships.
Sorry, but not this time.
You sound rather happy about it.
Let me know if you decide
to mount an attack on him.
I'll be sure to come and watch.
Not a chance! Anyway, Kumi-san,
are you going to summer school?
I haven't decided yet,
but eventually, I'll have to go.
What about you?
I will.
Which one?
The Daidai Seminar.
I wanted to get the application form tomorrow.
Maybe I should go there too?
Hey, quit talking
on the phone from the bath.
Your voice reverberates,
and it's distracting.
Aki, I love you.
Majestic Princess
In theaters this July
KICHIJOJI
Daidai Seminar - Summer School
Now accepting applications
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
Huh?
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
The textbook is a collection of seminar
papers and will be provided to you.
'94 Summer Course
Textbook Distribution
Miura-san!
You joined this seminar too?
Yeah. I see you at our place a lot.
You wear the Kaori School uniform,
so I figured you'd be here.
Yeah, I like our uniform a lot too.
Why'd I say something so stupid?
You're Ito-san, right?
How'd...
Well, it's pretty easy
to notice you in our joint,
so I asked my Kaori School friend for your name.
I don't really stand out that much.
Ah! I've read that one too.
Huh? O-Oh, this?
Flowers for Algernon
Do you prefer science fiction?
Y-Yes, I read it every now and then.
Here.
Thanks.
Then, perhaps you like movies by Viluncas too?
Offices→
←Cafeteria
Yeah, I do.
Offices→
←Cafeteria
Are you going to Majestic Princess?
Offices→
←Cafeteria
Yeah, I want to see it if I can.
Offices→
←Cafeteria
Actually, it opens in theaters this week, doesn't it?
Offices→
←Cafeteria
You're right. I bet you have someone to see it with.
Offices→
←Cafeteria
N-No! I don't, actually...
Personally, I've decided
to see it on opening day
during a morning showing.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
See?
Daidai.Seminar
Two tickets.
Ah, time for class.
See you later, then.
I'll be waiting at the joint.
Yeah... What?
I'll be waiting at Joe's.
On opening day... At Joe's...
LIBRARY
Opening day...
Hm, opening day...
Hey, what're you looking for?
When this movie starts.
The attack was a success?
No comment.
Whatever it is,
it's rare to see you like this.
You have the face of a maiden in love.
Oh, is it that obvious?
I can't wait to become an adult.
I'll wear a red dress.
I'll walk through that gate,
all dressed up in red,
fluttering the hem of my dress.
And I'll see so many things with my own eyes that I've never seen before.
Right...
Ito-san!
Fujimura-san?
Have you read Algernon yet?
I'm about two-thirds through.
It's really interesting.
Good to know!
Here you go.
This is good, Mike.
You should eat well too, Chibi.
Say, Aki, you were really friendly with Fujimura-san yesterday, weren't you?
How come?
Why shouldn't I be?
I don't mean that you shouldn't.
I was just surprised.
Why's that?
It's my turn.
This one, after all?
I'm not that desperate yet!
Let's see...
In the Tokyo area tomorrow,
the probability of precipitation over 1 mm is 0%.
An up-train will be arriving on track 3 shortly.
KICHIJOJI
Mike!
Morning.
Do we have time?
I wanted to get some coffee.
Huh?
Ah, if it isn't Ito-san!
What a coincidence.
How come?
Oh well...
I get it. You were going
on a date too, weren't you?
Oh well...
If that's how it is...
Ito-san, you don't mean
to say you came...
Stop.
No, I mean... Surely, it can't be you expected me...
Enough already. It's my own fault.
But, that is...
That day, I...
Never mind, okay?
Look, I dressed up like this.
The reason I was...
so quick to jump to conclusions...
is because I'm an idiot!
Hello?
Kumi, let's go see
the Majestic Princess movie.
Really? Like, now?
It must be awfully crowded.
It's on me.
Thank you very much!
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
NOW SHOWING
COMING SOON
Majestic Princess
Waiting for someone?
NOW SHOWING
Majestic Princess
COMING SOON
NOW SHOWING
Majestic Princess
COMING SOON
NOW SHOWING
Majestic Princess
COMING SOON
So you did have a boyfriend, after all?
I...
Actually, I've secretly admired you for a while, Ito-san.
I'm a bit envious.
Anyway, see you later.
Let's go.
And here I am!
Sorry I invited you out like that.
Don't mention it. I was a little bored myself this morning.
Then, have you read
Flowers for Algernon?
I borrowed it from a friend.
I cried so hard!
Student List
Kaori Girls' High School
Hello?
Who is it?
I don't know. A silent call.
It's the season when the rows of poplar trees are beautiful
I can't see you anymore
But are you still well?
After that, I took a little trip
To cheer up my broken heart
That feeling from meeting you for the first time
That enchanting face on the photograph
The more you smile, the more painful it becomes
But the wind can't erase
the footprints of my memories
You had such kind eyes
whenever I looked at you
Really... He had the nerve to come there!
Can you believe it?
I, for once, can't believe he's that kind of person!
I'll break up with him for sure.
I really mean it.
Hey, Aki, are you listening?
This time I'll make sure
to find someone better!
Oh, right! I've applied for the Daidai Seminar summer school too.
We'll spend summer vacation together! Right?
I'm not going to the Daidai Seminar.
I'm going to Mitaka Academy.
What?! You can't do that to me!
I only applied there because I thought
I'd go there with you!
That's awful!
Today it's only you, Mike?
What happened to Chibi?
See you.
There you are, Chibi!
You've grown so big.
You climbed up there on your own?
I suppose you're not a chibi anymore, are you?
Kaori Girls' High School
Oh? So Chibi's gone, huh?
Yeah.
I wonder where he went.
He leaped into the crimson sunset
and disappeared in it.
Listen, Kumi.
Yeah?
I gotta go to the library now.
I know. You have to return
that book, right?
Yes. So could you wait here for me?
Sure. I'll pray for you.
Thanks.
LIBRARY
Don't look down. I need to look her
right in the eye.
Here you go.
Okay.
I still...
haven't finished reading it, but it's due.
I could extend your term.
I dislike putting things off.
I'll come borrow it anew later.
Okay. I'll be waiting, then.
Kumi.
You didn't lose?
I didn't lose.
Then you gotta listen
to what I have to say!
Actually, I'm in a new romance right now.
What? Again?
How many times just this year?
The Tale of Genji has a volume titled "Wakamurasaki."
Let's take the first ten minutes of class today
to read it on our own.
Let's see...
Page 53 through 56.
Sound good?
During our casual small talk
You sound more excited than usual
You quickly brush it off, saying that
It has nothing to do with that girl
I know I have to believe that it's all in my head
That I'm imagining things
And I really want to keep looking forward
Whenever I looked at the menu or ate my meal
I felt a sense of unease deep in my heart
Please understand, as you always understand me
Because I love you more than anyone else
We both wanted to ask it, but we couldn't
So we swallowed our anxiety that night
Translation
Check
Timing
Editing
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Mushin
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Collectr
WasteOfHair
anonymous