Hannya
Is that you, Niomaru?
You're mine, starting today.
It looks like you're not familiar with a woman's body yet.
Let Lady Hannya
give you a good lesson in love.
What's going on?
What does it look like?
Hey, guys! You said no woman
has set foot here in 300 years, right?
Well, you can have your fun
with this hag, then.
What makes you think you're in command here, you dimwit?!
Niomaru! What's the meaning of this?!
It means I refuse!
Think I'll let an old bag like you
suck the life out of me?
What?!
Now you've said it, you punk!
You'll pay for this!
W-Wait a second, Grandma!
Shut up!
I'll kill you!
Hold it!
Annio
Not so fast, Hannya.
Niomaru is still a child,
he meant no harm.
What are you talking about, Annio?
He turned out this way
because of your poor upbringing!
For how long have you been groping me?
Oh, guess I have. My bad.
Don't try to laugh it off,
you ungodly pervert!
Enough, Hannya!
You'll strangle me!
Niomaru! Leave this to me and flee!
Thanks, uncle! Please relay this to my dad when you see him: I'm going on a journey!
Journey?
Bye!
Hey, wait!
Niomaru!
C-Cut it out, old bag!
I'm suffocating!
Niomaru
The universe is centered around the Earth.
The one who maintains the overall balance of things is Buddha.
Above the observable universe,
there is Mount Meru, where gods dwell.
Mount Meru stands 560,000 kilometers above the human realm.
Two dragons guard the entrance at its base.
Above that, one of the Four Heavenly Kings
Four Heavenly Kings
guards Mount Meru in each direction, gazing sternly down at humanity.
Mount Meru is home to the gods,
who battle evil spirits
Twelve Heavenly Generals
and rebellious deities that defy the Buddha.
In other words, it is where
the Buddha's warrior gods assemble.
Twenty-Eight Protectors
The gods' total fighting force numbers in the millions.
Thirty-Third Heaven
That's right, the gods are the Buddha's Army.
This tale recounts the journey of a lone human
who dared to challenge the gods.
Climbing the Clouds
Come on, Kai!
How long are you going to just sulk there
like some spoiled wench?!
Isn't it about time to wake up?
How long are you going to sleep
just because some sparrows laughed at you?
Look, while you were sleeping, the ashes accumulated,
the soil piled up, and the grass and trees grew into a mountain!
Who are you?
I am Niomaru, the son of Unnio!
And I'm nothing like you—a spineless wimp who loses his spirit over a few harsh words!
Niomaru?
Don't talk like you know everything!
How could you possibly understand the heartbreak
I've endured by believing
in and following this philosophy?
"If a sparrow can’t grasp the motives of a swan,
why bother caring about what it says?"
What you say is true.
But the irresponsible words of the sparrows...
I must confess, have pierced deep into my philosophy.
Their words hit the mark of truth!
Great philosophers are easily hurt
because they deeply believe in this truth.
All right, I understand your logic!
Still, wouldn’t 2,000 years of sleep
be more than enough for anyone?
2,000 years? I see.
It's already been 2,000 years since then?
Then why did you seek me out
to awaken me from this slumber, Niomaru?
I ask you to become my servant!
What?
That old bag Hannya
almost turned me into her boy toy!
Without any status here,
making a pact with Hannya
would trap me as a Yaksha forever!
I don't want to languish in a place like this,
as Buddha's gatekeeper,
disallowed to enter the heavenly realm!
I have yet to see the big world!
Take me to Mount Meru!
Kai
It seems you're serious about it.
This might be fate, so I shall join you
in your foolhardy adventure!
Get on, we're going!
All right!
Niomaru?
Yes. He united with Kai
and is headed towards Mount Meru.
So the destined time has finally come?
Then, what you said...
It was true.
The Buddha once said:
a day will come when Niomaru will try to reach Mount Meru as a human being.
But if Niomaru goes to Mount Meru,
Sakra's domain...
Exactly. I still remember it like it was yesterday.
Unnio
What happened back then...
I still don’t know what possessed me
to do something so thoughtless.
Soothed by the safety of the clouds,
I forgot how quickly humans evolve and what their science can achieve.
I caused an indescribable tragedy.
That accident wasn't supposed to happen.
I frantically searched for survivors.
It was an incredible sight.
A young boy struggled desperately
to save his sister.
I rescued the two.
Then I fed them the juice from the Quince of Life
that I stole from Sakra's palace.
Yes, I squeezed into their mouths
the quince that can heal anything.
Unnio! Do you even realize
what you've done?
I beg for forgiveness!
At the time, it seemed like only
the Quince of Life could save those children!
You fool!
Don't you know what happens
if a human eats the fruit of that quince?
Wait, Sakra.
Buddha... The Great Buddha!
Sakra, Unnio.
I have descended now
to pass to you the Buddha's decree.
Sir!
I'm prepared to accept any punishment!
As your faithful servant,
I shan't have peace until I've atoned for my oversight with the Nio brothers.
Unnio, I command you to bring the human boy with you to our Sea of Clouds.
Certainly... I will.
Entrust the other child to Sakra’s care
and let them live on Mount Meru.
S-Sir?!
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
When these two reunite in the future,
all the heavenly gods will no longer be needed.
That is all.
Such is Buddha's decree.
A-All the gods...
No longer needed?
Is that true, Buddha?
The Buddha is willing
to end our existence like this?
All the gods, including us,
will no longer be needed.
We don't know for sure yet.
Will one puny human
really be enough to convince
the Buddha that he no longer needs us gods?
It's too difficult for me to understand as well.
But what if Buddha has truly grown weary
of the gods' idle existence?
So then, the gods will have to take the fall for the humans' foolish and self-destructive nature?
Probably.
While the gods slumbered in complacency,
man ventured where he was forbidden.
We tied this noose around our own necks.
But the gods have been
doing their best for the Buddha,
chasing away evil spirits and demons
as Buddha's Army.
That’s why Buddha is testing us: do humans have the mettle to take the gods' place?
So Niomaru is...
It's Buddha's gamble.
When Niomaru climbs Mount Meru, Buddha will have to acknowledge
humanity’s strength and independence, bringing an end to the gods.
I can't imagine Sakra and the other gods
just watching enviously as he climbs.
I'm going to do my utmost
to help him get to Mount Meru.
Including fighting other gods?
Yes, I will. If such is Buddha's wish,
I believe that is also a part of his plan.
All right, I'm going with you.
I've been shirking the gods for the past decades that I've been a gatekeeper.
He may lack the strength to back it up,
but he has no fear in facing the gods.
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
Ready!
Kai! Mount Meru is not in this direction!
Don't worry, soon we'll reach the Valley of Wind
where the Wind God lives.
I see why it's called Valley of the Wind!
Fine by me, bring it on!
Simply put, braving this wind
is no trivial undertaking!
Hold tight!
Hey! Who the hell's that?!
You came here knowing that this is the Valley of the Wind, where the Wind God presides?
Kinkaku
Who's that bozo?
Probably Kinkaku, the Wind God's son.
Kinkaku! We're heading to Mount Meru!
Please show us the quickest route!
Shut up!
You dare to address me without due respect,
so you'll pay for it!
Did you truly think I’d open the path to
Mount Meru for a complete stranger like you?!
Insolent fool!
Niomaru!
There's your quickest route,
you dumbass!
Wh-Who are you?
And why are you in the Wind God's flower garden?
Sara
Ran
Sara, what were you doing? We didn't have
the flowers ready in time for the princess's bath!
I'm sorry.
You're sorry!
Is that all you got?
Enough, don't reproach her.
Sara stays, everyone else, leave.
Certainly...
Get naked, Sara.
Soak in the hot water with me.
Okay.
How did this happen?
The blemishes that always bothered you
have disappeared from your body altogether!
A man held me in his hands.
Kinkaku makes his body small
and embraces you all the time. Why now?
No, it wasn’t like the way celestial men
rest their hands on my shoulders.
He looked me in the eyes
and hugged me gently.
And his man thing
penetrated deep inside my body.
What?
At first it hurt so much it was unbearable.
But then I quickly started to feel like I'm melting.
It was so sweet, so intimate, and hot...
In the end, the man's body
exploded deep inside me.
His man fluids mixed with mine...
and made my blemishes disappear.
That's ridiculous!
Please believe me, Princess.
I'm telling the truth!
Princess Ran, we have a problem!
The Wind God...
What is it about my father?
He ordered us to catch a human.
But that human is too nimble!
His name is Niomaru.
Princess, please help us!
He's the man who held me!
Don't let him escape!
Catch that rogue!
What a clingy geezer!
Think I'll let you catch me?
Let go!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Who the hell are you? Aren't you the hornless Oni who came here on a giant eagle?
Look, you prick! It's thanks to you
that I got yanked off my eagle!
Give it here!
This guy isn't Oni,
they're called humans.
They're a delicacy, with skin and meat
far more tender than the Oni you just ate.
Then let's hurry up and have a bite!
Wind God
Give me a minute. I'll prepare it right now.
When eating, it’s best to shrink our bodies and savor the flavors.
Hold it, you two!
Long time no see, Wind God.
Nio!
N-Nio?
I don't get it!
What's the meaning of this?!
That human is my son!
What?
So it's him—Niomaru?
That's what I'm saying.
I'll have to ask you to give him back.
I see now.
I've heard rumors.
He's heading to Mount Meru, isn't he?
He's the man who holds in his hands
the fate of the gods you despise so much.
Hand it over?
It's the first human
I'm able to eat in 3,000 years—
the privilege we've lost because of you!
If you want him back, try to take him!
Dad!
I have personal scores to settle with you!
You condemned me to 3,000 years of suffering!
You're a vengeful man.
Yes, we joined forces with the God of Thunder
and descended to Earth
3,000 years ago, causing the havoc that led to this remonstration.
But you also had a change of heart back then.
Isn't that why you joined
the Buddha's guardians?
I'm going to eat that human!
I'm not taking orders from you!
So it seems you want to do it the hard way...
That's something I should be saying!
Ready?
Yeah!
Kongo Rikishi
Back then, when we attacked with the 28 deities
as part of the Thousand-Armed Kannon's ultimate force, we avoided uniting our powers...
But when we're united,
our strength is unmatched!
Oh! Just what I wanted!
Is that the rumored result
when the Nios fuse, Kongo Rikishi?
I don't care!
When brothers Annio and Unnio combine,
Kongo Rikishi appears!
Our combined body
is as strong as a diamond!
Your blade is no match for it!
Oh? So you're serious about it, pops?
Damn you!
Why? Why do you stare at me so intently?
Don't you care about your father's battle?
No. Even if blood is spilled,
I'm too enthralled by your beauty.
Mine?
I want you to show me that sweet,
melting pleasure that you let Sara feel.
What are you going to do?
Just enjoy yourself.
I'll make you my woman now.
It hurts! Let's stop! No more!
Bear with it.
It's necessary to make you my woman.
Damn it!
D-Dad!
Wh-What is he doing, brother?
The Wind God inhales!
Even with a body that's
as sturdy as a diamond,
without any special abilities,
even Kongo Rikishi cannot stand up to me!
Die!
Die, Kongo Rikishi!
This hurricane will hurl you away
and scatter your body to the four winds!
Hey, dad...
For an enemy, you're quite
the formidable one, Kongo Rikishi!
You didn't budge even in my whirlwind!
The formidable one is above you right now.
What?
Ra-Ran!
With this, I've truly become
your woman, haven't I?
Yes, that's right.
You're my woman starting today, got it?
So he screwed her?
So it seems.
Niomaru, if you, human, are to reach Mount Meru
within your lifespan,
you'll have to go this way.
What does he mean, Kai?
Truth be told, even if I carry you
on my wings through the gods' main hall,
it’ll take 300 years to reach Mount Meru.
You can't be serious!
I'll die of old age before that happens!
That's why
you have to use this path.
Beyond this door lies eternal time.
Stop, Niomaru!
Hell awaits you there.
Hell?
That's right.
Dead humans can get by,
but to those who are still alive,
that place is millions of times more painful.
Isn't it funny that the shortcut to Mount Meru,
where the gods live, goes through hell?
Let's do it!
Niomaru, why are you that hellbent
on getting to Mount Meru?
I don't know,
but something's calling me there.
Something I've known for a long time.
Go ahead and open the gate, Wind God!
Brother?
Please open the door to the underworld.
All right. As you wish.
Off I go then, dad and uncle.
Thank you for raising me all these years.
What are you saying, Niomaru?
This could be my farewell to this world.
Niomaru...
Ciao!
Don't! Let him go, Annio.
Such is the Buddha's will.
Buddha's will.
Brother...
Dammit, what is this hole?
How deep can it be?!
You're in the Hole of Depravity, leading to hell.
I know that voice.
When did you...
Just before you jumped in,
I shrunk myself enough to hide in your ear.
Are you stupid? Go home!
This isn't your battle!
I'm your woman! And I'll follow you wherever. That is my resolve.
Tsk. Don't say I didn't warn you, you wanton.
Is that how you talk now?!
Quit it! Don't mess with my ears!
It seems I've reached
the bottom of the abyss.
But is this really hell?
I've never seen a place so beautiful.
This is neither heaven nor hell.
When the dead come to this world,
this is the first thing they see.
The border between life and death
is a flower field of Datura.
Hey, what's with these guys?
They all have the pallor of death!
They are dead!
Huh?!
They're on their way to the Sanzu River.
Man, that stinks.
The Deep Ravine is where the Sanzu River rages most violently, fed by the blood of the dead.
You there!
Where are my six coins?! C'mon, pay up!
Datsueba
The fare for crossing Sanzu River!
They were supposed to put it in your coffin!
No...
Man! Everyone is so greedy these days!
Ken'eoh
I really can't stand it!
You humans let money blind you!
Damn it! Those without a fare
will go for a swim!
Who's next?
Those seeking judgment from King Enma
must pay the toll here!
Hey grandma!
Uh?
What's that over there?
Who are those women?
Whee! Women!
The foolish men who get enticed by these women fall straight into the Avici hell!
The Avici hell?
The lowermost hell,
the most painful one!
Once you fall there,
you'll be tormented until the end of times!
That's right. But it's good for us.
We're just sparing Enma the hassle
of judging everyone by the Book of Sins.
I see.
By the way, Ran,
who are these two?
Datsueba and Ken'eoh. They oversee helping people cross the Sanzu River.
But being greedy,
they always strip the dead bare.
Young man, why are you mumbling to yourself there?
Decide whether or not
you're crossing the bridge already!
Here's my answer!
Niomaru, what are you thinking?!
Do you think I can face Enma
after leaving such beauties to their fate?
Datsueba, look!
Unlike the other dead,
that one is actually making progress!
He's not dead!
He's a living human!
What?!
You slackers! How can you drown yourselves in this creek? Just put some effort into paddling!
'Sup!
What?
What's going on?! What is this commotion?
Ox-Head           Horse-Face
Insolent fools! Even after arriving in hell, you still refuse to abandon your lecherous behavior?!
R-Run!
Are you the originator of this outrage?
Guessed it, you creeps!
What was that?!
King Enma
Are you quite certain he is still alive?
Yessir! No doubt about it.
The dead lack the strength
to swim across the Sanzu River.
How did you come to hell while still alive?
I asked the Wind God
to open the door to the underworld.
What was that?!
Ridiculous!
I'm the son of Unnio, Niomaru!
I'm taking the shortcut through hell
to reach Mount Meru!
What?
You're going to Mount Meru?
Through hell?
Y-You punk...
Wh-Who do you think you are?!
King Enma?
What's so funny, Enma?!
That's interesting!
In Avici hell, the living endure suffering millions of times worse than the dead!
No human has survived that pain
since mankind's dawn 1.5 million years ago!
I'm going there!
Don't you look down on hell!
If he claims he can pass it with flying colors,
let him try! Bring him there at once!
Yessir!
That Niomaru?
The man fated to come into conflict with all gods, as decreed by Buddha?
I was the first human to set foot in hell
since the dawn of mankind.
And that man might very well be the last.
The last human to come to this hell...
Ran, are you there?
Do something!
No can do. Even I can't defy Enma's orders.
Enma is the Great King of Hell—
angering him is pure folly!
Tsk. I knew I shouldn't have counted on you—
should've brought a bow or a gun.
What is this place?
Meet the first of the great hells—
the Quartering Hell!
This is the hell where murderers are sent.
People who loved to fight during their lives
are forced to keep fighting even in hell.
No doubt, the pain at the moment
of death is unbearable.
But whenever a cool breeze blows here, they're brought back to life and have to resume fighting.
They're revived over and over,
forced to taste the terror before dying again.
Agonizingly, they endure
the same torment on an endless loop.
What a nasty place. And to think it's all
the work of the heavens and gods...
Shut up! What makes you think you're better?
Dammit!
What the...
What are you doing, you dumbass?
Can't you see that you're being played
by Enma and the gods?
Come to your senses!
We're on the same...
Motherfucker!
That stung...
Th-The lights are fading...
Crap, why is everything the same color now?
Is this what it means to die?
Is that it?
What are you doing, Niomaru?
What happened to your insurmountable drive?
R-Ran...
It's just a hallucination. A spirit without a physical body can't possibly kill you.
D-Don't be stupid.
What is this pain, then?
A convincing hallucination
that addles your mind!
Look, Niomaru!
Come on, touch me.
These are my breasts,
my body.
You have such nice boobs...
I'm glad to have known you. This is it...
I can't believe it!
How inert can you be?!
Uh, what can you do...
Huh?
R-Ran?
C-Can you feel it now?
This is my body, Niomaru!
My real body!
Now, start moving.
Penetrate me!
O-Okay...
There, see? You're still alive.
Your pain melts inside me!
You're right!
I'm feeling alive!
I am alive!
Niomaru, your body...
Won't you cut it out, you troglodytes?!
There's no such thing as hell!
So how can you let this phantom trick you
into spilling more blood for no reason?!
Open your eyes!
Is that true?
What's going on?
Watch me as I level this useless place!
Niomaru, you need to stop!
Shut up, Ran!
What's the good of this place?
That's enough, Niomaru!
As the King of Hell, I won't tolerate any more chaos from you, you puny worm!
Don't get cocky, Enma!
I've had enough of your "hospitality!"
You have to stop, Niomaru!
You can't rebel against King Enma in hell!
If his hell has to be that irritating,
I'll just blast it away here and now!
You jerk... Die!
What's going on?
Are you made of stone or something?!
Niomaru!
Wait!
Don't worry.
I'm not going to kill him.
What is that?
The Ring of Yama.
Even if you try to make him bigger,
this ring won't allow it.
This ring is absolute and immovable,
so his skull will be crushed first if you try!
D-Damn you!
Kid! What does a punk like you know
about the true nature of hell?!
Just hearing the name of this hell
should make you writhe in agony!
But King, aren't you the one who despises this hell more than anyone else?
Nonsense!
Who ever said that?
I did.
King Ashura!
Long time no see, Princess Ran.
King Ashura
And yes, she heard that from me.
Rubbish!
I am the King of Hell!
Why would I hate my own domain?
Is that so?
Yet for some reason I can't see it any other way.
As proof of this, you led this infernal army against Buddha for exactly 137 crusades.
I'm sorry, but I can't shake the feeling
that you did it just to rid yourself of this hell.
You're overthinking, Ashura.
Just like our friend Niomaru here,
you detest this hell created by the Buddha.
Am I wrong?
Quiet! I've had enough of this nonsense!
Oh, but King!
How should we deal with the human?
Even Quartering Hell is too soft for him!
He deserves to be sent to the Robbers' Hell!
Yessir!
Sounds interesting!
King Enma, ​​bring on that hell you hate so much,
and I'll make sure to enjoy it thoroughly!
I'll face it head on!
What happened, Niomaru?
Why do you keep silent?
I should have said even more. In this battle between me and Enma, I intend to win!
I will face head on
his filthy tricks!
Look at this guy's face.
The more you try to hurt him,
the more resilient he becomes.
No one has ever taken this hell head on
and successfully climbed out of it.
None of the many celestials living on Mount Meru, let alone their countless retainers.
Is he really the one destined to climb Mount Meru, as decreed by Buddha?
The gods must be in an uproar right now—
especially Sakra.
With every step Niomaru takes toward Mount Meru,
he chips away at the ground
beneath our feet.
So he is Buddha's great gamble?
The one whose mere existence
will question the need for all the gods?
Even I am discontented
with the gods these days.
So I also wondered what would happen
if the gods disappeared.
Just like you did, I'm sure.
Just like I did?
Looks like that brat Niomaru
really has the guts to break through hell!
Sakra!
You know of Buddha's decree as well as we do!
Sakra
Is Buddha really going
to wipe us out because of him?
I refuse to believe this!
Why does it have to be either us or him?
It's downright absurd that some clueless human
gets to decide the fate of us gods!
What's going on, Sakra?!
Let us hear your thoughts!
I'm going to break away from Buddha.
B-But Buddha has already recognized
that humans have the power to become gods.
I don't know what's on Buddha's mind.
But I don't intend to let that Niomaru
come and take our place.
Therefore, my army will fight anyone
who recognizes Niomaru.
Sakra!
The balance of the universe
rests solely in Buddha's hands.
He can cause or avert
any conflict that arises within it.
And yet... Yet you want us
to fight this battle, Buddha?
What's wrong, Maya?
You look like a rainy weekend.
I'm scared, but I don't know why.
Something is coming towards me.
Step by step, steadily...
Damn it! Think I'll lose that easily?
Mount Meru... I need to get to Mount Meru!
To all the newly admitted souls in our paradise,
Mahasthamaprapta
behold the suffering of those consigned to hell.
Although you in paradise are untouched by it,
during this sacred time,
feel free to mock those whose evildoing and bad karma condemned them to the land of suffering.
You, with good karma,
can laugh at them to your heart's content!
Where the blazes is that prick Enma?!
Is that the purpose of hell—to give heaven dwellers something to point at and laugh?!
Come out, you!
Come out and answer me, Enma!
How dare you mock those
who can't even defend themselves!
Damn you, you self-important prick!
That's the sea of sinners' blood
and piss for you! How'd you like it?!
Now I know what your hell is all about!
Bastard...
And it let me realize
nobody needs this kind of thing!
You guys fight too!
B-But...
Are you still hesitating?! Don't you have a shred
of pride left to oppose this humiliation?
Fight!
Even if they kill you over and over,
you'll keep reviving—so keep fighting!
That's it! They're not making fun of us ever again!
Damn it!
Let's fight back!
Niomaru, now's your chance!
The road to Mount Meru is through the viewing crack, opened by Mahasthamaprapta!
Oh, I see.
That's my way to go, then!
Just hang on, you dead!
When I reach Mount Meru,
there'll no longer be any hells for anyone!
What's wrong, Enma?
Won't you try to stop him to protect hell?
I... I...!
Is that it, Enma?
Even you won't try to stop him?
But whatever Buddha's will may be,
my view of it is the same as Sakra's!
Niomaru, a lout like you
is fit for only one fate!
What's the matter, Maya?
I don't know. But I just felt a tremor deep in my bones—someone's coming!
But who is he?
What just happened to him?
K-Kai! Ran!
Well done, Niomaru!
They tried to stop you, but you went through hell!
Really?
B-But what is this place?
The Underworld Dunes.
The road to Mount Meru
on the other side of hell.
I see. Even so, that hell is one wretched place.
Is it just me, or did you grow a size bigger?
Probably. Either way, our first move is heading to Mount Meru and wiping out hell!
Naturally, Mount Meru
is where they'll fight me the hardest.
But I won't lose. How can I!
Niomaru...
Let's go, Ran, Kai!
Fine by me.
But there are still countless hurdles awaiting!
You could say our real journey only starts now!
I know.
However, I'll make sure to blow away
anyone who stands in my way!
Mount Meru...
I must climb Mount Meru!
Maya?
What's going on, Niomaru?
Who is this Maya?
My sister.
Now I know—I'm going there to meet her!
Let's go, Ran!
Okay!
Buddha,
is this also part of your design—
that I'm destined to fight the gods?
Isn't that right, Buddha?
All right... I don't care if they're gods!
Fly, Kai!
RAW
Translation & TS
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
True Noobow Gamer