Kai, what is this enormous tornado?
It's a tornado of fire too!
Kai
This is the Demonic Tornado,
which has been guarding
this key checkpoint to Mount Meru
for 7,500 years.
This tornado is sucking in all the air around us!
Niomaru
Worry not, just hang on tight!
It appears the tornado is stronger than me.
At 300,000 km tall, this tornado makes flying over it impossible.
How about going around it?
Just avoid the tornado?
Ran
That'll take 30 years.
30 years? Out of the question!
You gods can afford that, but I...
Wh-Who is it?
Here, here!
It's the Louse speaking!
The Louse?
Correct!
The Louse that's been living
in Kai's feathers for 5,000 years.
How about we go meet the four demons
running this checkpoint?
Meet?
Technically, they're devils, but their power is formidable even by celestial standards.
Louse
You can't defeat them, so you need to negotiate.
And how do we do that?
Well, just leave it to me!
Hey, demons! Together with Niomaru,
the son of Unnio, we're heading to Mount Meru!
We absolutely need to pass through here!
Could you calm the Tornado of Fire
for a moment and let us through?
Of course, we don't want it for free!
We'll bring you anything you want—anything!
So what do you say?
Anything we want?
Don't make us laugh!
It's our duty to stop the infidels beyond Buddha's salvation—
those on the five paths besides the celestial:
humans, Ashura, animals,
Demon of Five Scandhas
ghouls, and hellish beings—
from entering the Pure Land!
Demon of Temptations
Demon of Death
Why should we let pass a louse or a human?!
Demon of Worldly Desires
Keep pestering us,
and we'll roast you to charcoal!
You'll pay for this!
Wait, Niomaru! But what about a woman?
You don't want a woman either?
What did you just say?
What if we found wives for the four of you?
You're not teasing us, are you?
We have protected
this checkpoint for 7,500 years!
Due to constantly living among the flames,
we were charred to this state!
Are you saying there are women
who'll come to live here as our wives?
Yeah!
They're totally sold on the idea!
Huh?
With an unparalleled kind
and beautiful smile?
Women who'd love us
from the bottom of their hearts?
Yeah, got it!
I'll find them!
Niomaru!
These guys aren't rotten to the core.
A truly rotten heart
holds no high hopes for women.
I'll find them—perfect wives for you!
Make sure you deliver on this promise!
Bring us women who smile at our faces
and pour out their love,
and we'll open this gate
and guide you to Mount Meru!
So, Louse, do you know anyone like that?
I got you covered!
Hey Kai, break through dimensions
and descend to the human world!
South of Jomolungma,
there lies the old country of Shakyamuni!
All right!
Climbing the Clouds
Ran, what is this round world?
I've never seen anything like that.
This is your birthplace—
Earth, the human world.
My birthplace?
Ryutaro! Ryutaro!
Ryutaro       Mayumi
There... Look at that!
Remember I told you about a giant feather I saw from the roof of a housing complex?
And this must the bird that dropped it!
There are people...
People are riding it!
Th-That must be Tatsumaru! After them!
Okay!
S-Say, what?
You want me to drink up this pond?
Yes! Karnaya's drowned body
rests at the bottom of this pond.
You can't be serious!
How am I supposed to drink up a whole lake?!
And look at that water—it's rotting!
Karnaya was the wife of Kohanama,
the king of Buddha's tribe.
2,800 years ago, their tribe was attacked and defeated by Virudhaka,
the tyrant of the Kosala tribe.
"Spare the people inside the castle?"
No deal! Kill them all!
That was when Karnaya, the wife of King Kohanama,
made an unexpected offer to Virudhaka...
There's a pond next to the castle.
Please let me dive in, and only let people escape the castle for as long as I stay underwater.
Karnaya
Only while you dive? I like it! How many
do you think can escape in such a short time?
I accept that wager!
You have only dug yourself deeper!
It's a deal.
But Virudhaka was gravely mistaken, granting her only a few minutes,
Karnaya still hadn't surfaced hours later.
In the meantime, all the people in the castle were able to escape.
Are you saying...
Precisely.
Karnaya took her own life by tying her hair to the roots of the willow at the bottom of the pond.
What an intrepid woman!
Furious, King Virudhaka ordered Karnaya's body to be raised to make an example of her.
However, Hermit Vasu, living in this area,
rotted the water to prevent it.
Hermit Vasu
The water poisoned anyone who tried to dive for her, making their bodies melt.
Even knowing that,
you want him to drink it, Louse?!
But then Hermit Vasu also said:
"He who will drink up this lake
will get Karnaya's body."
Niomaru, you're the only human who can drink this water since you tasted the Quince of Life.
I'll drink it.
Niomaru?
She took her own life
to let the people escape the castle.
How can we leave
such a good woman rotting here?!
I'll drink it!
Niomaru! Please, stop! That water will burn your throat, fester your stomach,
and wrack your whole body with agony!
Yet I'm going to drink it!
I've decided to drink it!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes!
Hang on, we're almost there!
It's my little brother Tatsumaru!
I'm certain of that!
Look, the lake's water is receding.
Yes...
Our Niomaru really is a god.
No doubt about it—
he's the man destined to become a god.
Niomaru?
Silence!
You've got a fever—you're burning up.
Like that can stop me, dammit!
Hang on, Karnaya.
I'm coming to save you!
Niomaru...
Niomaru, I can see it now!
Karnaya's corpse!
Ravish her, Niomaru.
If you come inside Karnaya's mummy,
she'll come back to life.
What is wrong with him?
He can even get hard for a mummy?
Don't be Jealous, Princess.
Niomaru may seem cocky,
but deep inside, he's a good guy.
Humph. Or maybe just too horny.
Maybe climaxing would be a bridge too far for him?
After all, Karnaya's mummy
has been rotting here for 2,800 years.
I wince at the mere thought
of intercourse with her.
No, look! The mummy...
It's coming back to life!
So good...
He did it!
He came inside...
Although you've just been revived, we need to ask you for this huge favor without delay.
We'll accept a "no," Karnaya.
But since they're so ugly,
I'm sure they'll treat someone like you kindly.
Niomaru-sama,
you lifted my rotting corpse from the bottom of this lake
and loved me sincerely,
never once looking at me with contempt.
Why should it bother me, then,
if they're beautiful or not?
Yeah... From the moment I heard how you died,
no matter what form you take,
I could only see you as infinitely beautiful.
I was just a woman who spent countless millennia at the bottom of that poisoned lake.
I never imagined there could be a man
who'd drink that rotting lake dry.
Yet you drank it for me.
To pay you back, I would happily marry one of the demons and serve him well.
Karnaya...
Ta-Tatsumaru!
We're in trouble! It's a human!
Hurry up and get on my back, everyone!
Tatsumaru! Tatsumaru! Tatsumaru!
Tatsumaru! I'm your brother!
I'm your long-lost brother!
Tatsumaru!
Dammit!
Ryutaro!
Ryutaro, are you okay?
Shit... I lost them again.
Now there's only one way for me...
A suicide won't do!
Oh?
Death is, without a doubt,
the gateway to the otherworld.
However, a suicide won't lead you to the world where Niomaru is.
Are you the hermit?
Hermit Vasu.
The plane collided with a giant!
Co-pilot's last words
The investigators dismissed
the co-pilot's words as hallucinations.
But I believed in the giant
who rose up among the clouds.
She also believed it.
Our parents' bodies
have been confirmed with certainty.
But they never found
my little brother and sister.
The police confirmed that everything there
was destroyed by the airplane fuel.
But I couldn't help feeling
that they were still alive somewhere.
I knew that that giant took my brother and sister to the otherworld.
So you two had the "bright" idea of committing
a double suicide to meet them in the otherworld?
Please don't tease us!
Ryutaro had already tried every other way!
The reason we came here
was to meet you and maybe...
Yeah, I know.
Don't underestimate my foresight.
The reason I appeared here
is to help you two project your astral bodies
and guide you to Niomaru's world.
You guys are the chosen ones.
As singular enlightened humans, you'll be able to watch Niomaru's fight to the end.
So, are you coming or not?
Y-Yes, certainly!
Hermit Vasu, where is Niomaru now?
The Pomegranate Castle, Hariti's residence.
Pomegranate Castle?
That's right. Fetching Hariti's daughter
that one of the demons longed to meet.
Hariti was originally the wife of a demon god
and mother to 500 daughters.
She was once a vicious woman
who snatched and ate human children at will.
The Buddha admonished this atrocity
by kidnapping and hiding
one of her own 500 daughters.
Hariti turned the world upside down,
desperately searching for her child.
Buddha then appeared before the crying Hariti,
holding the child in his hands, and said,
"If losing just one of your 500 daughters fills you with this much grief and despair,
imagine the pain of all the parents
whose only child you've devoured.
I want you to remember this lesson."
Ever since then, Hariti turned to Buddha
and became the guardian deity
for safe childbirth and children.
The daughter he hid back then was Juri.
Hariti
I'm sure you already know that.
That's right.
But do you know the reason why he chose Juri from among my 500 daughters?
I heard she was your most beloved daughter.
She must be a good woman, then.
I see. You've got some nerve.
As expected of Unnio's son.
I like you, Niomaru.
In that case, try to find Juri
from these 500 girls.
If you succeed, you can take her with you.
Wh-What?
H-Hey, Lice, you know
what Juri looks like, do you?
Don't be stupid! How would I know?
Wait, what?
Now then, what do you say?
Are you confident you can find her?
If you're not, leave at once.
For if you make a wrong pick,
I will eat you on the spot!
It's a deal!
Let's go and find her, then.
H-Hey, Niomaru, where does that confidence come from?
I have no choice—I've got to do it!
That said, they all look
like stunningly fine women.
Hey, babe. What's your name?
It's Juri.
And yours?
I'm also Juri.
Damn... Does anyone here ever tell the truth?
You're Juri!
You're Juri! No doubt abo—whoa!
Too bad, kid!
That isn't Juri!
Hey, quit shitting me!
Gods aren't supposed to tell lies!
How could you tell?
Because she's your most beloved daughter.
While the other girls laughed freely,
she alone had a different expression.
Striving to be a good girl before her mother at all times.
Can you tell why, Hariti?
Your selfish love is chaining this girl,
hand and foot!
Juri
Juri, is that true?
Not at all, mother!
My mother's wish is my wish, at all times.
That's a lie too!
If you don't believe me, ask your own heart!
Your life is yours alone!
It doesn't belong to your mother,
it's your own!
Juri...
I'm sorry, Mother.
I really wish to go out into the world.
This may be a splendid palace, but the waiting maids take care of everything for us!
Don't you wonder what the outside world
is like and what other people do there?
I want to see it
with my own eyes.
Juri!
Please forgive me!
My love was detrimental to you!
It was actually suffocating you, wasn't it?
Mother!
Listen well, Niomaru!
If anything unfortunate
happens to my daughter,
I'll chase you to the ends of the heavens
and earth and make sure to tear you apart!
All right, I get it!
She's in good hands, you have my word!
That's what I said...
But really, I brought you here
to be the demons' wives.
Ugh, I don't like this!
Let's not do it.
What do we do, then?
Unless the demons open the checkpoint for us,
we can't go to Mount Meru.
It pains me to break a promise,
but it's also such a waste...
Niomaru!
I don't really mind.
The way Niomaru conveyed my feelings
to my mother so strongly,
he must be at least as powerful as Buddha.
If Niomaru tells me to do so,
I will go and live with the demons.
Damn it, what a pain in the ass!
Juri! I don't want to give you away.
Karnaya, I don't want to give you away either!
Niomaru.
I know, I know.
Hey, demons!
Come out!
I brought you your wives as promised!
Hey, what now?
What's wrong, guys?
It's the first time ever for us, Niomaru!
Huh?
In the 7,500 years
that we've been demon gatekeepers...
You, Niomaru, are the first person ever...
To take us seriously!
W-Wait, what are you, guys?
The Demon of Five Senses,
One-Horned King.
The Heavenly Demon,
General of Gods.
The Demon of Death,
White Dragon King.
And I am the Demon of Earthly Desires,
King-Entertainer.
Please forgive us.
We were testing the limits of your willingness to put up with our whims.
You passed this test. You are a god.
You're the man who we can entrust with our dreams.
One-Horned King and I will accompany you.
Once you pass through here, the gods on Mount Meru will definitely attack you.
All right, you can pass
through the Demons' Gate, Niomaru!
What? The Four Demons
let Niomaru through the gate?
Insolent brats... Go, Skanda!
Show them the power of heaven!
Skanda
Understood, sir. Leave it to us.
Everyone get ready!
Sakra
May I, Sir Sakra?
Vaisravana?
Sakra, I'm concerned that Skanda
is getting ahead of himself.
Vaisravana
This way, he might lose to Niomaru, who passed through hell and the Four Demons' Barrier.
If you want to be sure, you should send me...
Oh, it's reassuring to hear the strongest
of the Four Heavenly Kings reason this way.
In that case, I must ask you to do it.
Sir.
Buddha... What are you thinking?
Do you really believe in humans
and think they can antiquate us gods?
Buddha...
Wow... These guys are something else!
Dammit... If it wasn't for this ring of Yama...
No... I just can't hold back!
I'll help too!
Whoa! Are you stupid!
Don't do it, Niomaru!
What the hell is this bug?
Kill him! That bug is Niomaru!
Don't let him escape!
Niomaru! Don't be reckless!
Just watch from Kai's back as we...
One-Horn!
And that's what awaits all who side with Niomaru and humanity!
We wiped them out!
Damn you...
Stop! Don't do it, Niomaru!
If you try to transform, the Ring of Yama
that King Enma put on you will crush your skull!
Silence!
He shattered the Ring of Yama!
Just how powerful is Niomaru really?
He, who comes from Yama Heaven
in the Desire Realm,
can become bigger than even King Enma?!
Bullshit! He's bluffing!
Attack! Attack him, you cowards!
Just how much stronger
is Niomaru going to become?
Don't tell me...
Vaisravana, we would have
to ask you to decline this fight.
It would be foolish for you to fight this battle alone—no one will benefit from it!
I'm a warrior!
But sir...
Among the four Heavenly Kings
of the Heavenly Army,
I am the strongest general in charge of the northern quadrant!
I'm a warrior even if I'm alone.
And my warrior's blood is boiling right now!
Monks, I thank you for serving me
for so long as advisors.
Vaisravana!
Vaisravana...
Oh no... I have a bad feeling about this battle.
Vaisravana?
You mean the one with a sword in his left hand
and a pagoda in his right, where monks
and high priests live, reincarnating eternally?
It seems you've done your homework.
He is also the most knowledgeable
and discerning of all the heavenly generals
who listened carefully to the Buddha's teachings.
Vaisravana set out to repel Niomaru's march.
It's going to be a fabulous battle.
Isn't that Niomaru, brother?
That's right.
My son-in-law, Niomaru.
Tatsumaru!
Hermit Vasu, I would like to talk to Tatsumaru.
No can do! You've barely been initiated,
there's no way you could speak to Niomaru!
That's so cruel!
Forget it!
Vaisravana!
He beat him!
Wait. Look over there.
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
A god will not die until his lifespan runs out.
Even if you rip off his arms and legs,
or pierce his heart, he will still live on.
And Vaisravana's lifespan is 9 million years.
Dammit!
Th-That's ridiculous!
At this rate, Tatsumaru will never...
When the god is injured in battle,
he simply lies still and waits
for his wounds to heal—
it's the usual course of action.
What's more, his body grows bigger
each time you hit him.
Hm?
That's the Four Heavenly Kings' Army—
Vaisravana's allies.
And here are the gods of Wind and Thunder with their armies, probably to help Ran.
But right now, both sides are baffled by the abnormal situation and Vaisravana's tenacity.
With this Staff of Evil-Busting Righteousness,
I will strike down the wicked
and protect all things in the universe,
created by the Buddha.
With this heavenly strike,
I will wipe out Niomaru's murderous intent!
Neckside Strike to break his violent spirit!
Chest to defeat his lust for power!
Stomach to crush his desire to steal!
Navel to stop him from lying!
Then finally, his pelvis!
Pelvis to eliminate his wont for adultery.
Spectacular.
His divinity is spectacular!
Is Tatsumaru dead?
He's not dead.
But this is sure to make him a tame Buddha's servant.
Hm?
Get up.
Oh no! Vaisravana is intent
on hitting Niomaru on the top of his head!
What does it mean?
If Niomaru is hit on the top of his head,
he will disappear.
Maya
This pain...
What is this pain?
This heartbreaking sadness...
Who is it calling for me?
Ah... Who are you, the boy in my memories?
Ryutaro? What's wrong, Ryutaro?!
He's calling for me...
Niomaru needs his brother!
Brother!
Niomaru! Surely, you didn't expect me
to just let you stay as Buddha's servant?
I'll get rid of you for good!
Tatsumaru!
Brother!
Meet this ultimate strike!
It was a divine power!
He summoned their souls.
Humans, lacking physical or mental strength,
have only each other's souls to rely on.
That unleashed divine power
strong enough to overcome Vaisravana.
Holy radiance!
The Buddha is coming down!
We are blessed by this chance to see the Aurora Bodhisattva from the Second Zen Heaven,
far above the Mount Meru realm,
who arrived in the light!
Buddha
Please tell us, what happened to Vaisravana?
Vaisravana has attained enlightenment.
I-Impossible! We, the Four Heavenly Kings,
don't even dare to dream about attaining it!
It's unreachable even for those who won military honors protecting the Buddha!
What did Vaisravana do to earn the right
to be enlightened after letting Niomaru,
a human, strike him down?!
Vaisravana will ascend to the Tusita Heaven.
Under the guidance of Maitreya Bodhisattva,
he will train to become a Tathagata.
What the hell is this battle?
Is Niomaru a manifestation of Buddha's will?!
Bullshit! If that was so, why did Vaisravana,
who fought him, become enlightened? Fight on!
Fight him to reach enlightenment!
No, wait! We mustn't fight him!
Now, then, Niomaru,
what are you going to do about this kerfuffle?
Where's Ryutaro anyway?
He's inside Niomaru.
Right now, he is one with Niomaru,
his consciousness sedated.
Th-These footprints!
These are Gotama's feet.
His footprint is perfectly flat!
It is one of the 32 major characteristics that only Buddha can have.
If even one of them has appeared,
that means Niomaru will become Buddha too...
No, it's more than that.
There can only be one Buddha. For the human world, it was Shakyamuni. Which means...
He'll be the Buddha of Power,
the Universal Ruler!
Vaisravana and the Heavenly armies clashed with Niomaru and the armies
of the Wind God and Thunder God.
And then... All the armies dispersed.
Dispersed?
What do you mean?
Niomaru has taken refuge in the waters
of Rahula Sea within King Ashura's territory
and is now heading here alone.
The Heavens...
The Heavenly Realm will be gone!
Is it Mount Meru I'm seeing beyond that sea?
No. That is Mount Nimindra.
Mount Meru is surrounded
by eight mountain ranges and eight seas.
Each has a fortress, guarded
by a veteran general of the heavenly army
who will come out to face you.
Are you still going?
I am.
My little sister is held on Mount Meru.
I must bring her back—
she's my sister, my flesh and blood.
You've grown so big you can now easily
carry me on your shoulder.
My role in your story ends here.
Ran and the demons are injured too—
I’m afraid they’re out of the fight for now.
Thank you, Kai. You did well carrying me all the way here.
From here onwards...
I'm going alone!
The root of Niomaru's actions
is a human emotion called affection.
King Ashura
That emotion is born from the universe
within every human.
Wait a minute... What was it you said just now?
The universe within humans?
However... A universe equals God!
Are you saying the humans are gods?
That's right.
That's the way Buddha created them.
And Buddha has patiently awaited the day when each human becomes a god in their own right.
It falls to us gods to see to that.
When humans grasp the universe within them,
they’ll no longer need us, their guardian deities.
Niomaru will be the gauge for Buddha
to determine whether that time has come.
Then, Sakra rebelled
against Buddha's wishes?
That's what happened.
If humans discover the universe within,
they'll realize they can be their own gods.
Sakra still insists that that is unthinkable.
Why?
Why is Sakra so hellbent to oppose it?
That, I don't know myself.
Is he looking for personal enlightenment,
or pursuing some agenda in relation to humans—
I can't tell what's on Sakra's mind.
But Buddha already ruled it.
When Niomaru reaches the peak of Mount Meru,
humanity will become self-sufficient and the gods will become obsolete.
King Ashura, sir!
A-A report:
Niomaru crushed Vaisravana and the Heavenly Army,
went past the 500 Disciples,
and invaded the Garden of Delights!
Niomaru also smashed Vaisravana's staff to pieces.
We needn't to worry about his fate
in the Garden of Delights.
Got it... Well, then.
God of Delights
Your husband, Vaisravana—
a god who shouldn’t die until his lifespan ends—
has disappeared, Kishoten.
Throughout the vast heavens,
no wife has ever loved her husband
Kishoten
as faithfully and devotedly as you.
To live up to that reputation, you will surely thwart Niomaru's advance, won't you?
Very well, God of Delights.
What? He sent Kishoten?!
That's enough.
You let me enjoy your company
to my heart's content and catered to me well.
My body is properly rested now.
You have my gratitude.
How can you say that?
No god has ever rejected these pleasures after experiencing our entertainment.
What on earth is this man?
Very well.
It seems we cannot keep you
entertained here any longer.
But at least grant me
one final night with you.
You don't smell like all the other women here. Who are you?
Vaisravana's Wife.
Kishoten.
D-Don't do it, Niomaru! You absolutely cannot share a bed with that woman!
Who is she?
Kishoten, who contains in her body
the Womb Realm Mandala.
It was created by the Buddha to teach about bodhicitta, or the state of enlightenment.
Mingling with that woman
clouds your mind with pleasure—
Sakra's night with her lasted 7,000 years,
5,000 for King Ashura.
That infinitely deep and soft vulva...
Her body melts you and beckons you in.
All the sounds disappear.
You lose touch with reality,
embraced by this soft warmth.
It let's you experience enlightenment exactly as it is.
I didn't regain myself until I too
was awakened to Buddha's mind.
Even to this day, I still miss the comfort
of the Womb Realm whenever I remember it.
If Niomaru enters it with his human lifespan,
we'll never see him again.
To think Sakra would go to such lengths
to block Niomaru’s advance...
Sakra? Not the God of Delights?
All 33 heavens encompassing Mount Meru,
including the Garden of Delights,
are ruled by Sakra!
Why? Why are you crying?
I don't really know myself...
But what a sight...
Such beautiful tears.
Kishoten.
No need to pout like that.
Ryutaro is still unconscious.
Still...
Instead, look at that.
Take a look at that face,
the face of the God of Delights.
But really, it's just Sakra in another form.
All 33 gods of this realm are a blatant lie.
They all are just different forms
of the same Sakra.
So then, Sakra effectively monopolized
the whole of Mount Meru?
Right now, Sakra really wishes he could enter Kishoten's Womb Realm Mandala himself.
He's extremely jealous.
Before I took refuge in Buddha's wisdom,
I was the mother of Kamadeva, the God of Lust...
The purest of instincts...
Lust.
Only in lust lies Buddha's salvation.
Love is natural.
Only when indulging in lust
can you experience the true Nirvana.
A union of two sexes.
Only at that moment
can you feel what Buddha feels.
Now, come...
Join me on a Journey to Buddha's Realm.
It's infinite...
You can go as deep as you want.
Don't hold back!
Put it in! Deeper!
You can go deeper!
Put it in deeper!
It's over, sir.
No...
What?
How did this happen?
Are you saying his power even transcends
Kishoten's Womb Realm?!
Even Kishoten's Womb Realm Mandala can't fool him...
Does he possess a stronger Diamond Realm
than even Vaisravana,
who had not once embraced her?!
Bastard...
I'm grateful to you.
You can't imagine how lonely I've always felt,
cursed with the Womb Realm Mandala.
Through contact with your Diamond Realm,
I was able to experience
the pleasure of being a woman for the first time.
I'm also grateful to you.
I feel that I've grown one size bigger
through meeting you.
Thank you.
So he has Gotama's feet.
And he has Dharma wheels on his feet.
The fingers that touched my cheeks...
Were divinely slender too.
He keeps manifesting the 32 characteristics of Buddha one after another.
So he really is the one...
He's the one who can become
the Universal Ruler.
Damn it, that asshole Sakra
even stopped the nectar rain now.
Louse told me that as long as the nectar rains,
even I—a human—won't feel hungry.
That's right! You look yummy!
Hey! Wait, you!
Damn it, those little jerks are fast.
Wh-What the?
Oh, but it worked!
Just when I need it!
It even threw itself
into the fire without my help!
What a stupid bird!
I've never tasted anything like that.
But it's good!
Wh-Who the hell are you?
I am Sakra, Niomaru.
You did well coming this far as a human.
I'd like to express my admiration once again.
However, you committed
the greatest sin known to humanity.
Take a closer look
at what you just took a bite of.
H-How did this happen?!
Have you finally noticed?
The bird of paradise you've decided to eat
was your own mother reincarnated in heaven!
Wh-What did you say?!
Recognizing your closeness in life,
Buddha's grace allowed your mother to live with you forever on Mount Meru in this form...
Yet you had to eat her?!
Are you mortified?
Eating your mother's meat
is worse than eating your own!
Repent and suffer for your sin, Niomaru!
You're destined to wander this wilderness
as an imp who has lost any humanity!
You'll wander it forever
until you finally kick the bucket!
King Enma! A report, sir!
The bloody pond of hell is boiling!
The Sword Mountain erupted in flames!
The dead are rioting,
and it got completely out of hand!
King Enma
If this continues, hell will be reduced to ruins!
King Enma!
The era of destruction.
Indeed, that era has come.
All as it should be. Let chaos consume everything,
so a new order may rise from the silence.
All as it should be!
I've been waiting eons for this time to come.
Wh-What's this, an earthquake?
Niomaru...
Niomaru!
Dad? Uncle?
Niomaru...
Niomaru.
Tatsumaru.
M-Mom!
Tatsumaru... No, Niomaru, please hear me out.
I'm happy right now.
Even while living a dream-like life
in this heavenly world,
I still regretted how fate treated you and your siblings.
And now I was finally able
to make myself useful for you!
Tatsumaru, I am your big brother.
It wasn’t because of moral decay or wickedness that you ended up eating your mother's flesh.
As Mother just said, she was glad to become your flesh and blood
and to know she raised you
with such compassion in your heart.
Stand up. Stand up, Niomaru!
That bird of paradise is your father.
Eat it! Eat it and live on!
Eat to fight another day!
Don't seek stability.
Eat the meat!
You are the Buddha of Power!
The Universal Ruler!
The heavenly gods forgot how to fight.
They only seek stability.
That's what brought about
the total destruction of the universe
unfolding right now.
If humans also become complacent,
the end of times will come then and there.
Fight on!
Fight, fight, and never stop fighting!
Only by continuing to fight can humans
avoid repeating the same mistakes as the gods!
Sunja!
Maya! Where are you, Maya? Only you can stop this! You have to stop them, Maya!
Maya...
Ma... Maitreya Bodhisattva!
Sakra! Please stop this, Sakra!
If this continues, Buddha will have to...
The eternally troubling question, "What can Maitreya Bodhisattva do to save mankind?"
was revealed to me today, and my soul was burdened with that worry as well.
Yet, with every step you took toward Mount Meru, that worry inside me gradually faded.
Are you my sister?
Yes. And I am also a servant to you.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Maya.
Brother!
Niomaru,
you did well.
The earthly world of humans is in your hands.
The final kalpa of destruction is upon us.
Indra's Arrow will keep radiating for 7 minutes.
Niomaru, if you are to protect the humans and the new order you'll build with them,
you'd better protect them from Indra's Arrow.
Whether or not to preserve
the earthly human realm is up to you.
If your body overcomes this light
and doesn't get evaporated in it...
Then you truly are worthy to be the Universal Ruler!
You are now the only god in this universe.
As the Universal Ruler in this age of destruction,
work with your followers to govern wisely the new universal balance of this realm.
Are they here?
RAW
Translation & TS
Editing
Quality check
Piyo-Piyo Productions
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
True Noobow Gamer