It's beautiful!
So pretty!
I can't wait!
Yeah, I wanna ski already!
Must be fun!
Yashagatake
We're approaching Yashagatake now.
We'll be there shortly.
It's quite a chilling name
for a place like this.
Akimoto-sensei, did you know
this was the site of an old battlefield
from the Sengoku era?
An old battlefield?
They say it was named after the ghosts of soldiers
who were burned alive in that castle and became wandering Yaksha.
Everyone, we're not here
for a test of courage.
Jouka Academy
This is a ski training camp.
Hagiwara-san, that's enough.
Sorry.
Snap, Makeup
Episode 4
The Cursed Ski Slope
Jouka's Mountain Villa of Terror
That concludes the room assignments.
Whew, finally!
Now then, everyone,
carry your luggage to your rooms!
Okay!
I'm looking forward to skiing,
but also this year's ritual.
Me too!
I see.
So they're finally here?
It's hot!
I'm already drenched in sweat!
Ah, feels great!
Oh geez, Manami!
So bold!
Ah, and this is even better!
Wow! Me too!
Even better!
What about you, Saori?
No one's watching.
B-But I put on my bra and shorts.
That's too bad. It feels amazing!
M-Manami!
Wow! Teach me too!
Manami-san, honestly...
Ugh, just do whatever you want!
No! I-It's so cold!
I can't hear you!
No self-respecting man would go in
for wimpy skiing with the girls!
Let the cold wind refine your spirit!
That is the tradition of Jouka!
Damn it!
Saori and the others sure have it easy.
There's a world of difference
between boys and girls!
Clear your mind, Sakazaki.
Y-Yes, sir!
Next! Begin the cold-wind endurance!
Man, this is unbearable!
Huh?
Come on! I wanna look too!
Just a little more.
Oh! Classic briefs.
Come on, give it here!
I'm not done looking!
Enough already!
No, I want more!
Just a little more!
I said, stop!
It's my turn now.
I suppose...
Ah! A flag signal.
"Es-cape is im-pos-sible."
Honestly, Yuji-kun...
Yeah, this is hopeless.
Then let's get into the bath
one more time and wait for him.
Yeah.
Hey, let's go wash each other.
Sure. Lend me the soap.
Lend me your shampoo.
Yeah, sure.
When it comes down to it,
we'll have to do it, the three of us.
It's a bit lacking in impact, though.
Finally, the annual hazing
of the new teacher is upon us.
And this year's target is Akimoto-sensei.
Half-hearted stuff won't work on her.
If we can make that sexy teacher who
toys with the boys cry uncle, it'll be a huge hit.
Yuji-kun promised to help, though.
Or even better, if a real ghost showed up,
it'd really liven things up.
Yuki, don't say weird stuff like that!
No!
Squish, squish...
S-Sakazaki-kun!
'Sup! Did I make you wait?
Well, when there's a worthy goal,
nothing is impossible for me.
Geez, you're impossible!
Ow! That hurts!
Don't you know I've got frostbite?!
Hey! Hey, who's there?
Fukuike-sensei!
Everyone's back already.
Shh. I've got an idea.
So, listen... and then...
So you do this... and that...
Teacher…
Y-You kids?
Did you hear some strange voices
from deep inside the building just now?
No.
You know the rumors, right?
That this lodge was built
on the site of a razed fortress.
I... know.
If you're too nosy,
you might even summon some old spirits.
More importantly, teacher,
I really wanted to ask
for your advice on something.
H-Hey, now!
What is it? I could advise you
just fine in the lobby.
But the others might hear us there!
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
Hey! Stop that! You're on a
school trip, and th-that's improper...
I just want to talk to you
about something, that's all!
K-Kobayashi!
Teacher...
Am I really as childish as they say?
Do I have no feminine charm at all?
No... you're very charming.
More than enough.
Cappy! I'm so happy!
Everyone always makes fun of me.
And it kept bothering me... so much!
Yes, now h-hurry up
and put your clothes on! Hurry!
Gotcha!
Oh, teacher, how naughty!
I-It's a misunderstanding!
R-Right, Kobayashi?
That's right. You just said you'd raise
my makeup test score a little if I do this.
H-Hey, what are you talking about?!
That's favoritism if I ever saw it.
H-Hey, give me that photo!
Then come and take it, Fukuike-sensei.
Actually, while we're at it,
maybe I should ask for a favor too?
I'll give you special service, teacher.
H-Hey...
Teacher! Here, water.
This stuff sure is strong!
All done here.
Saori?
Must be my imagination.
Uh... this one!
What, again?!
Good, good.
This blizzard will be over by morning, it seems.
You girls should go to bed soon too.
I brought your dinner.
Thanks.
By the way, how is Fukuike-sensei?
Just a cold, I hope?
Yes, apparently he suddenly
developed a fever of unknown cause.
He took some medicine and turned in early.
Really?
Could it be the curse of the spirits?
Spirits?
Yes...
On stormy nights like this,
the restless spirits go wandering around.
That's what I've heard!
Don't be ridiculous.
That's just superstition.
B-But Fukuike-sensei was drenched in sweat,
like he was being haunted by something.
I've heard this lodge was built
on the ruins of Yashagatake Fortress.
I don't know why, but I feel…
Come to think of it, strange incidents of an
unknown nature occur here from time to time.
It's an open secret among the graduates.
Ah! Then that mysterious case
of the suicide jumper too...?
Huh?
Yes. Aside from the academy's higher-ups,
only a few people know.
E-Enough already!
But don't you see it can't be explained
by anything else but the curse?
Even last year, in the bathtub...
That razor suicide, right?
And isn't that the room
Akimoto-sensei is staying in this year?
Huh?
No! I'm scared!
I-It's just a coincidence.
Yes, obviously just a coincidence.
All right, that's enough for tonight.
We have an early morning tomorrow.
Hey, we should definitely sleep together tonight, the three of us!
To be honest with you, I'm scared too!
Hello? Fukuike-sensei?
Is he really that sick?
Whew! It's cold.
I should've left the heater on.
Weird... Maybe it's because of this blizzard?
W-What am I even scared of?
It's just some kids' ghost stories.
I... I'm just hearing things...
As expected, I'm seeing things too.
I'm only freaking out
because I tend to overthink things.
I need to warm up and calm myself down.
That's more like it.
Of all times to be alone...
Huh?
W-What's this?
O-Of course, it can't be...
S-Someone help me!
Help! Someone help me!
It won't open!
The door won't open!
Someone help me, anyone!
You'll pay!
You'll all pay for it!
I am the lord of this fortress.
Why has a shameless young woman
such as you come to this place?
Your wicked deeds are plain to see!
Dissatisfied with toying with countless men,
you dare, while holding
the sacred post of teacher,
to seduce innocent young lambs as well?!
I... I would never do such a thing!
Fool! Even now you still feign ignorance?!
I... I understand!
I swear I'll never do such things again!
Never shall you dare think of it!
Did we go a bit too far this time?
Huh?
S-Sakazaki-kun?!
So this was all something you set up?
N-Not at all. In fact,
I'm just a special guest today.
Teacher!
You girls…
Just what is the meaning of this?!
Sorry! This is actually
our annual “new teacher scare” ritual.
This year, it fell to us to carry it out.
What?! Then the door not opening
was your doing too?!
Still, not bad, Akimoto-sensei.
You're the only female teacher
so far who didn't faint.
Congratulations on passing it!
It was just a joke, see? This is where you
laugh it off and forgive us. Right, teacher?
By the way, where's Saori?
No! Don't tell me she's still on the balcony!
Help! Someone!
Hey! Saori, are you...
Help!
S-Saori!
W-What was that?
That wasn't in the script...
Saori! Saori!
No!
Saori! Where are you?! Hey!
I'm here, Yuji!
Here?!
Th-This is Saori's costume!
Help!
Yuji-kun!
Over there!
Is this...
an old escape tunnel from the fortress?
Hang on! I'm coming!
Yuji!
Saori!
Damn it...
Not so fast!
Yuji!
Y-You?!
From back then…
Bargain-bin playboy Hoi Hideki!
You really hurt my
pride back then, y'know that?
So I treated you to some real
American-style special effects makeup.
Wha... What are you doing?!
H-Hey!
H-H-Hold it! Are you for real?!
That look suits you perfectly.
Damn you...
H-Hey, let go!
Let go!
Boss!
No! Give that back!
Idiot! Don't let go of the controls!
Ah! My bra!
Good! Keep her steady!
Good! They're the mummies I've discovered.
Let's put them on display in our hotel lobby!
Isn't this prank going a little too far?
I made sure to use plenty of adhesive.
Serves them right for that amateur makeup stunt.
Hold it!
Well said!
Now I've finally found you two!
Crap!
Saori, quick!
Wait! Stop right there!
Hey! No slacking off! The heptathlon's
next after the snowfield running!
Vice Principal! Don't move!
Sakazaki!
Nothing personal!
Get him! Get him now!
Hey, you! Stop! Now!
We can't! Please forgive us!
You're starting to turn your eyes
to something you never even tried to see
"I'm sorry," you said, bowing your head
And I no longer had anything you could believe in
I can never hold
those shaking shoulders again
Because I miss you, Baby
I won't look back
Your smile is flashing through my eyes now
Because I miss you, Baby
I can't see you anymore
My love, my dreams, and even my voice won't reach you
Because I miss you, baby
I'm getting smaller
I can't see you anymore
Because I miss you, baby
Raw provider
Translation,
typesetting
Editing
Eternal_Blizzard
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies
Paul Geromini
imatu
Because I miss you, baby...