Right? It's an incredible presence,
wouldn't you say?
I need to film this scene!
Just one more take!
Please! Let's go and
film it real quick, Saori-san.
As if!
Snap, Makeup
Episode 3
There! And Here Too?
A Snappy Love Triangle
That splatter flick again?
If I keep having to work on it,
it'll be the death of me.
Oh? It's Father.
He's home early today.
Oh? W-Welcome home, sir!
Oh, Yuji-kun?
Are you going out at this hour?
Y-Yes, sir! I was going
to a friend's to study for a test.
I see. Do your best.
I hear your grades haven't been great lately.
Y-Yes. Excuse me.
Man, freeloading at
the director's house is tiring.
Just the other day...
Father was talking about dropping
by your room for a surprise inspection.
You'd better be careful with the film.
If Saori hadn't tipped me off,
I'd have been seriously screwed.
What?!
The film I left with you got confiscated?!
B-But with Fukuike-sensei
threatening me like that...
Imbecile! I spent my entire
summer vacation shooting it—
Throbbing Alien: Intestine Carnival!
I barely got Saori on board with it!
You know how hard that was?!
S-Sorry... But after all, you did cast the director's
daughter as the star of a risque movie—
if that went public,
it'd be a huge scandal for Jouka Academy!
H-He said he had to check it.
Damn you, Fukuike!
But the film's with Akimoto-sensei now.
H-Huh? With Akimoto-sensei?
Crap...
What's she doing with my masterpiece?
M-More!
This is Sakazaki.
Akimoto
Y-Yes?
Dear...
S-Sorry, I didn't mean to!
Figaro su, Figaro giù...
No way!
Honestly, Manami-san...
What's wrong, Saori-san?
Oh no... I forgot something.
Sorry, go on ahead without me.
Geez... I guess it can't be helped.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
You came all that way for nothing.
Don't be shy, lean a little closer.
If it's about the film,
I might give it back to you.
R-Really?
Fukuike-sensei confiscated it,
but he wasn't sure whether to officially
submit it to the school, so he entrusted it to me.
I-Is that...
It's the key to the coin locker
where it's stored.
Y-Yuji-kun...
P-Please, give it back, Ma'am!
Please... I'm begging you.
A-Akimoto-sensei?
I... I'm sorry!
It's fine. I understand how you boys feel.
A teacher always wants to know her students.
Ah? N-No, that's not why I...
You only get one shot at youth like this.
You should do whatever you want
with all your might.
But it'd all be pointless if you failed
the next English grammar test, wouldn't it?
M-Ma'am...
I wouldn't mind helping you out with it.
Here.
I'm heading out!
'Sup, Saori! What's the matter with you?
Tsk.
Hey, what happened?
Don't touch another's shoulder so casually.
Just because the boys at Jouka
are desperate for female attention,
doesn't mean a teacher and a student
can cross that line!
GULP
So she saw what happened
at the parlor yesterday?
No! You're wrong! Saori!
And the best part comes after that...
Hey, wait up, Saori.
Calm down and listen to me, okay?
What's going on with those two?
Something didn't sit right about them yesterday.
Something? Ah!
You mean they did that?
Oh geez!
It's a misunderstanding, you hear?
How long do you plan on following me?
The boys' building
is over there, remember?
Saori-san, what's wrong?
You don't look well at all.
If you're always flirting with him,
things like this are bound to happen sometimes.
Who was ever flirting with him?
Sorry, but don't ever mention him
in front of me again.
He's nothing to me anymore.
This is getting troublesome...
What do you have to say for yourself?!
We just made a vow to protect the students from the academy's obsolete customs together!
And now this?
Surely, you must
have an explanation for this!
That's why I haven't told anyone yet...
But depending on how this goes, I...
Very well. I'll provide an explicit explanation
until you're satisfied. Just the two of us.
Okay...
I can't believe Fukuike-sensei saw us.
Even though I was only planning
to quietly help Sakazaki-kun.
At this point, there's only one way forward.
She saved me from suspension
when I sneaked into the girls' building,
and now she's helping me
through this new crisis?
But it's also a problem if Akimoto-sensei
takes this odd liking to me.
Saori
Even if I know it's just a misunderstanding,
the real issue is how Saori feels about it.
What's it to Saori, anyway?
Exactly! It's not like she's my girl or anything.
I don't owe her a thing!
Come to my place and I'll teach you.
I can do whatever the hell I want!
Oh? Fukuike-sensei?
Sakazaki, there's somewhere
I urgently need you to come with me.
Okay...
I don't like using this method,
but if I want to settle everything cleanly,
I'll have to make full use of a woman's weapons.
Akimoto
This is Fukuike.
The door's unlocked.
Please let yourself in.
I'll do that, then.
Hey!
B-But I specifically said just the two of us...!
Well, in matters like this, it's only fair to hear both sides at once. So I brought him along.
For instance, a teacher and a student together at a parlor after school, cuddling like this...
is certainly scandalous!
But also, I understand that accidents do happen.
So Saori wasn't the only one
who saw that scene at the parlor...!
Goodness... this is really screwing up my plan
to seduce Fukuike-sensei into keeping quiet.
O-Of course, I believe this is all a misunderstanding.
O-ho! So Fukuike's got a thing
for Akimoto-sensei?
That's one hell of a love triangle.
But if I play my cards right, he'll be the perfect witness to clear Saori's misunderstanding.
Since we're talking about misunderstandings...
I mean, I know it's only hearsay,
b-but some say that you seduce
the male students you fancy and then...
Of course, I don't believe any of that!
The Akimoto-sensei I know is not about that—
she's a model teacher devoted to education!
Since Fukuike-sensei has said that much already,
I suppose I must tell the truth as well.
If what you said were true,
what would you do?
Y-You can't be serious!
And my current favorite is Sakazaki-kun.
You little...!
One side of my personality is a teacher,
but the other side is a woman.
A woman?
That's what I hope to be.
Fukuike-sensei...
Oh, no... Wait, I can't hold back...
Yuji-kun!
My, oh my... Men these days are so feeble.
Are you okay?
Come by alone this
Saturday afternoon, won't you?
Come!
Dammit... what's going to become
of our educational system!?
Maybe I went a bit too far this time?
You idiot...
Why should I care about Yuji at all?
S-Saori-san...
Right!
Manami-san!
Yuki?
Bad... This is... very bad!
Huh?
Please, just come with me!
It's nothing to worry about!
Men and women getting a little too close—
it happens all the time.
But I really don't like Saori's mood.
At times like this, only you know what to do! I'm totally lost...
You're being too melodramatic, dummy.
Whoa! It's so good
to have you as a friend. Yay!
He called, says he wants to talk and apologize.
Why would he ever
ask you for advice on this?!
I don't know either. But hey, if a guy's bowing his head, why not hear him out?
I think he wants to ask for your help.
What?
It's about the next test—if he fails,
people say he's done for the rest of the term.
Saori-san, hurry!
But at this point, all we can do
is cram like crazy for the exam.
That's fine.
So, he's waiting at the library or something?
No, no, no! You need a place
where you two can be completely alone!
H-Hey, where are you taking me?
Didn't you hear me? The place where Saori
can teach you properly, step by step.
Step by step?
Stop dragging other people into this.
Handle it yourself from here on out.
What are you dawdling for?
Here, you can talk things out
without worrying about anyone seeing you.
H-Hey, are you sure
Saori wants to meet here?
Ugh, just come!
Now with Manami too?!
Oh, leave me alone!
I guess this place was a bad idea, after all.
You can never guess
what's on someone's mind.
You've gotta be kidding me!
Yuki and I chipped in to rent this place for you!
Huh?
I'll go get Saori.
Really, so you two set the whole thing up?
Don't be such a crybaby!
Saori's too quick to jump to conclusions. Guess there's only one thing left to do, Sakazaki-kun.
I've been curious anyway.
H-Hey, Shimizu?
What must a guy have in him
to make Saori fall for him that hard?
G-Give it a rest!
L-Look, I...
Are you really that faithful to Saori?
I-It's not that...
Then why not?
Sh-Shimizu...
Hey! So it really is you!
Takashi-kun?
Yeah. Long time no see.
I think since my family moved... right?
What's wrong?
You look kind of down.
Want a ride?
Seeing the ocean might clear your head.
Good idea.
Let's drive as fast as we can!
Saori-san...
Taxi!
Follow that car!
Ever since we moved, I couldn't stop thinking about you for some reason.
We've been friends since kindergarten, after all.
T-Takashi-kun!
Huh?! What, that too?
All right, better brace yourself.
Tonight, I'm really in the mood
to do it with someone like you.
Come.
W-Where to?
Come on now, hurry...
I can't take this anymore!
H-Hey, are you okay?
Pull yourself together!
No way...
Maybe I took the teasing a tad too far.
Shimizu! Can't it go any faster?
Shut up!
What? Saori left with some guy in a car?
Come quickly! Please!
I'll be there soon, Saori!
No... Stop!
You've gotten so beautiful, it's killing me.
No! Don't!
Relax, I won't hurt you.
Be gentle, okay?
Sure.
W-What's with this fog?
W-What's going on?
I don't know.
What's wrong?
Th-There's something in the rearview mirror...
There's nothing there.
Hey, Saori...
Help!
'Sup!
Yuji!
Hey, now...
Oh, wow, looks like
they're back on track already.
No!
Nothing happened between me and Sakazaki.
It was a whole lot of worrying for nothing.
Lies.
You think so?
Stop making mountains out of molehills.
How do you know that the first incident
wasn't a misunderstanding, too?
Yeah, yeah!
All right!
Akimoto-sensei, I’ll take the exam
on my own merits, just you watch!
He's late!
And I was all set to give
him some special tutoring. Jeez!
Nope... can't understand a thing.
No visitors
You're starting to turn your eyes
to something you never even tried to see
"I'm sorry," you said, bowing your head
And I no longer had anything you could believe in
I can never hold
those shaking shoulders again
Because I miss you, Baby
I won't look back
Your smile is flashing through my eyes now
Because I miss you, Baby
I can't see you anymore
My love, my dreams, and even my voice won't reach you
Because I miss you, baby
I'm getting smaller
I can't see you anymore
Because I miss you, baby
Raw provider
Translation,
typesetting
Editing
Eternal_Blizzard
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies
Paul Geromini
imatu