I can’t hold it anymore...
I'm out of my mind...
D-Damn...
I'd heard rumors, but to think this kind of stuff
really happens in the girls' section of the school...
Is this for real?!
Who's there?!
A boy! A boy's here!
Oh crap...
Somebody!
A boy snuck into the school!
That klutz!
No way!
Wasn't that Kuroiwa from Class 2-G?
This'll get him expelled for sure.
Good thing it wasn’t Yuji-kun.
Snap, Makeup
Episode 2
Infiltrating the Girls' Building!
Catch it on Film!
A new laxative?
You dummy! It’s the pill.
The pill? You mean that kind of...?
Yep. You never know when
you’ll end up making love, right?
It's up to the girl to
take that kind of precaution.
Hey, Manami-san, is the pill salty or sweet?
Look, you...!
The pill isn’t candy!
But I kinda wanna taste one... just to know.
Look here...
The pill only works if you take it every day!
Really? That’s such a hassle.
Goodness! This is why
I can’t deal with late bloomers!
If you’re not having sex, you don’t need it!
That’s kinda boring.
Don’t mope, my friend.
Infiltrating the girls’ part is practically tradition
for us in Jouka Academy's boys' department!
Still, it pisses me off, Yuji!
I finally got that perfect focus shot!
Ugh! You guys never learn!
Whassat?
Saori! Let's get this straight. You girls get all excited 'cause we’re barred from your building,
and do all sorts of risque stuff in secret,
so of course it fires up our craving to sneak in!
What risque stuff?!
I know all about it!
You girls grope each other
and twist it around and stuff, right?
Lesbians. Total lesbians.
What’s that vulgar pinky for?!
Okay, maybe some of the girls,
but we definitely don’t do that kind of stuff!
Oh, really?
What do you mean?!
Whoa, you two have gotten so close!
Won't you stop making a show of it?
W-We weren't trying to!
If you two get too chummy,
it’s irritating!
We’re not!
Oh, really?
L-Like I’d ever get all buddy-buddy with Saori!
Anyway, knock it off with the borderline criminal infiltration games. It’s for your own good!
That's true.
All of you’ll get exposed for it sooner or later.
At this rate, the boys’ side
will be drowning in suspensions.
Like a little suspension
can scare a man from Jouka!
It’s all about how you do it.
I’ll prove it to you within a week.
No way!
You three, especially Saori,
go wash your necks... no, wait—
better wash your underwear real good!
And be extra careful when you change!
W-What the...?
Damn, the enemy's not messing around either.
This just stokes the fire
of my craving to sneak in.
STAFF ROOM
Another troublemaker from Class 2-G?!
Fukuike-sensei!
How do you explain
your homeroom class’s behavior?!
Vice Principal!
What is it, Akimoto-sensei?
Even though this is a co-ed school,
the girls’ and boys’ buildings are walled off!
It’s practically railroading any two kids
who love each other to jump straight to sex!
W-What are you implying?!
I'm just asking you to be lenient
with Kuroiwa-kun this time.
Absolutely not!
There is no need to even
bother the Director with this!
Our rules are ironclad, airtight, and absolute!
Really, Akimoto-sensei, your courage
amazes me every time.
It really should’ve been me,
as their homeroom teacher, saying that.
It is our duty as teachers in our twenties
to protect those kids
from the decrepit old customs of this school.
Let’s keep supporting each other, okay?
Yes!
Oh?
Oh no, it’s spreading.
Teacher, your fly is undone.
PINCHED
Fukuike-sensei, when you’re flustered, it only digs in deeper. Don’t move. I’ll free it for you.
My, someone’s full of life today.
So... I’m sure you all already know
about yesterday’s incident.
And the girls’ side
isn’t entirely blameless either.
What do you mean, sir?
What I'm saying is,
don’t give the boys any weird ideas.
Act like proper, modest high school students.
That's what I want you to be mindful of...
Fukuike-sensei is oddly refreshed today...
Ouch!
It definitely feels like
he just beat off somewhere.
Huh?
Hey, what do you mean
by "beat off," Manami-san?
Y-Yuki!
H-Hey! Kobayashi!
Don’t say stuff like that in class!
Huh? But Saori and Manami were just...
It's that kind of explicit talk and behavior
that arouses the curiosity of the boys!
Oh, no! I've never aroused anyone yet!
And when they say "boner,"
what kind of bone is that?
When they say "it stands up," what is "it"?
S-Seriously, you don't understand at all?!
So explicit is like... this?
Oh my, you snapped!
Really? If that’s explicit,
then this is explicit too, right?
Like that!
M-Make it stop!
That’s nothing.
Real explicit stuff is more like this.
Study on your own
for the remainder of class today!
Yay!
And thus, we've secured an early dismissal.
We really did!
Who goes there?!
Yikes... No way we’ll ever get
to the other side at this rate.
Did you hear, Sakazaki?
Even if you’re a genius at special makeup,
you’re not gonna fly over there like some fly-man.
You think so?
Idiot. Why would I ever try
something that conspicuous?
Don't screw this up, Sakazaki.
We’re really counting on your heroics here.
Leave it to me!
But you know, aside from hopping over the fence,
the only other route is that one connector path.
Welcome back.
I-I’m back.
You are now entering the boys' building
The girls’ classes sure are exhausting.
Wow! Our school's girls are second to none!
That was a close call...
Infiltration successful!
All righty, then...
Hiding in plain sight, ain't that right?
And in the world of women,
you've gotta be a looker, right?
Whew... The girls’ section of the school
has these kinds of facilities?
This is pure discrimination!
How could I ever leave
without capturing this on film?
Akimoto-sensei!
She’s the girls' swimming coach too?
Crap!
Okay, once you’ve learned the ropes, try it.
Okay!
Whoa, can't miss this!
You there.
Sitting it out because of the cold?
Oh, my! You can’t even speak?
You don’t have a fever, though...
Go to the nurse’s office
and get some medicine just in case.
Whew! That was close.
I gotta bail before she figures me out.
All right, now hold it!
That’ll be it for today.
Now everyone hit the showers.
I thought for sure she caught me.
SHOWERS
Ugh... It was going so well so far!
If I go in now, it’ll be the biggest scoop
in Jouka's history. I'll be the boys' superhero!
All right...
Oh, it's you!
You still haven’t gone to the nurse’s office?
You’d better hurry and go now.
Where on earth is Saori’s classroom?
After that declaration, I’ve gotta get solid shots
of the 2-C crew, or my infiltration’s pointless.
No! Cut it out!
Ah! Look at that cute bra you've got!
Let us see it too!
No way! I said no!
Oh, quit struggling! If you don’t behave,
we'll undress you completely!
Oh, what adorable undies!
No!
They've gotta be third-years, for sure.
PUBLIC MORALS
Oh, crap! The public morals inspector.
Your tie’s crooked.
I don’t think I’ve seen you before.
Are you a second-year?
You can't wander around the third-year floor for no reason! Go back downstairs.
I see! So it's one floor below?
But does Yuji really have the guts?
No way. He's totally bluffing.
So I figured. The next boy caught here won’t just get suspended—he’ll be expelled!
Heh! My makeup work is flawless.
Even Saori and the others didn’t bat an eye.
What did I tell you? Don’t come crying later!
Saori, what are you so worried about?
Huh? N-Nothing.
Come on, even if he is coming,
it won’t be so soon.
He gave himself a whole week, right?
That's right!
There’s no way he’d show up
on the same day he warned us.
You're too naïve, my dear!
Don’t you know that infiltration works best
by exploiting the enemy’s psychology?
I-I suppose.
All the lockers are already in use,
and the curtains are all shut tight...
It’s stupid to keep worrying
about every little thing.
Yes, good!
That's the spirit!
Nobody would suspect that a girl sitting out in PE class is secretly filming them!
What's more, Shimizu’s totally got
a full-on woman’s figure now!
Meanwhile, Kobayashi still looks
like a middle schooler.
But in the end, Saori’s got
the cutest body of the bunch!
All right, with all three of them together,
it's time for a commemorative snapshot.
I did it!
Guess I had nothing to worry about.
I told you.
If he really had the guts,
I'd show him this myself!
Manami!
In that case, I’d give him a real treat too.
Here!
Y-Yuki!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5! 6! 7...
Now, look here!
That's way too bold!
Everyone! Hurry up!
Today’s the vault test!
No way!
A surprise test?
That sucks...
Huge success!
All thanks to my go-getter attitude.
Didn't I tell you to go to the nurse's office?
NURSE'S OFFICE
Huh? That was pretty rough, wasn't it?
That was pretty reckless, wasn't it,
Sakazaki-kun?
You can drop the act now.
No matter how good your makeup is,
you can’t fool a teacher's eye.
I had a vague feeling about it back then.
Sure, you look like a girl, but...
That inconspicuous mark of a boy—an Adam’s apple.
Even a genius makeup artist can slip up.
If it’s come to this,
I’m ready for suspension.
Not bad. I admire your courage.
Huh?
You poor boys...
M-Ma’am...
If you're that desperate
to see a girl’s naked body,
I’ll help you as much as you like.
Wait, what?
N-Not at all! That’s not the real reason
why we sneak into the girls’ building!
No need to pretend anymore.
M-Ma’am...
I’ll teach you gently,
so go on, do whatever you want.
I’ll protect the pure boy in you
from suspension.
There—what you boys yearn for the most
is this garden of flowers.
You’re trembling.
Go on, right here.
Protecting our pure boys
from suspension is our duty as teachers!
I didn’t tell on you for sneaking in, so please...
Boobs! Boobs! Ah, boobies!
Ah... N-No, ma'am, please, h-have mercy...
Bear with it. Not yet.
H-Hey...?
Look, I'm not the only one
getting excited. You're stiff as a rock.
start!
Th-The film...
S-Stain... A stain! But that's...
Saori-chan, goodbye!
Yuji’s voice?
Oh, come on!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Of course not!
You're starting to turn your eyes
to something you never even tried to see
"I'm sorry," you said, bowing your head.
And I no longer had anything you could believe in
I can never hold
those shaking shoulders again
Because I miss you, Baby
I won't look back
Your smile is flashing through my eyes now
Because I miss you, Baby
I can't see you anymore
My love, my dreams, and even my voice won't reach you
Because I miss you, baby
I'm getting smaller
I can't see you anymore
Raw provider
Translation,
typesetting
Editing
Eternal_Blizzard
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies
Paul Geromini
imatu
Because I miss you, baby