Oh, I'm losing my mind...
Wow... The rumors were true.
No way!
Somebody!
A boy snuck in!
Yeah, that’s definitely gonna get him suspended.
Don’t get depressed...
Today again, a boy from our school got suspended.
To be honest, our school is not normal.
“Co-ed” is just a name—we’ve got completely separated boys’ and girls’ buildings.
So I kind of get why boys try to sneak into the girls’ side just to peek on the maidens...
Well, there are things girls can’t exactly talk about out loud.
And then Yuji goes and declares it:
“I’ll steal a look at you naked.”
Just like that!
Total puttsun!
It’s all about how you do it.
I’ll prove it within a week.
No way!
And so, a beauty appears within the girls’ garden. Right?
Saori, what are you spacing out about?
Huh? N-no, nothing.
I mean, even if he comes,
it won’t be yet. He said a week, right?
Exactly. There’s no way he’d show up
on the very day he warned us.
You’re too naive!
Don’t you know infiltration is all about messing with the enemy’s expectations?
Disguised as a girl sitting out PE class, snapping photos—no one would ever know.
See? Saori’s still the cutest one.
Well, that was anticlimactic.
Told you.
If he had that much guts,
I’d want to show him this myself!
Manami!
T-teacher!
I will protect your innocence from suspension.
There—what you boys yearn for the most
is this garden of flowers.
Are you shaking?
Come on, come to me.
See you again on Puttsun Make Love:  Infiltrating the Girls' Part of the School! and Catch it on Film!
Honestly, it's so one-sided.
Someone’s gotta wake Yuji up.
Saori, do it once in a while.
Why are we stuck with this
horror-movie-maniac freeloader?
And now I have to wake him up too?
Don’t say that. A woman should know
how to make a man rise.
Golly, Mother!
Are you saying you do that for Yuji every morning?
How shameless!
Hey!
How long are you gonna sleep?!
No wonder it vexes me so much!
The freeloader at our place—that’s Yuji.
They call him some kind of special-effects genius or whatever, but he’s just gross beyond belief!
I even see him in my dreams.
He's totally perverted!
And then, out of nowhere, Father brings up an arranged marriage.
What? No way!
The whole thing starts feeling like a nightmare alien movie.
An arranged marriage?!
Looks nice.
H-hey, wait.
Marriage meetings are a woman’s training for life.
You’re lucky. The candidate is the nephew of Master Hori, ninth-dan of the Kendo Federation,
a respectable young man who'll eventually inherit his family’s trade company.
Tonight?
Yes.
Your father just called.
That can’t be...
What about my feelings?!
You said it’d be this Sunday!
But the boy you were supposed to be meeting
suddenly has to fly to New York tomorrow.
That’s not my problem!
B-But when he saw your photo,
he insisted on meeting you before he leaves.
Looks like he’s totally smitten with you.
Father is simply incorrigible.
He sounds like a servant
carrying out his lord’s orders.
Really, our Hideki-kun has got a grand future.
I think he fears nothing in this world!
If he’d just master the Old Master's kendo,
then he’d really be invincible.
What’s wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
You should lie down for a bit.
You’re quite the curious one, aren’t you?
Following me this far
wasn’t just the drugs talking.
I’ll take you to even nicer parties someday.
Help! Yuki! Manami!
The night of the arranged meeting goes totally puttsun!
Puttsun Make Love.
See you again on Matchmaking Meeting Scramble!
Product promotion
I am the master of this fortress.
Swallowing our hatred for hundreds of years, we have wandered this land.
The grudges of our clan—
now is the time to settle them!
Just kidding!
Sorry for scaring you out of nowhere.
We’re girls from Jouka Academy.
We came here for a ski camp, and this place happens to be the legendary Yashagatake.
Believe it or not, this lodge was built on the ruins of that fortress,
and it's where the girls
of Jouka Academy are staying.
Every year, it’s tradition
to haze the new teachers.
This time, Manami, Yuki, and I were on duty.
Our target was Akimoto-sensei.
A worthy opponent.
Inviting Yuji as a special guest was fine and all, but then a real monster appeared right in front of me!
Volume 4: Puttsun Make Love.
Cursed Ski Slope, Jouka's Mountain Villa of Terror.
Someone help me, please!
Product promotion
Sorry about yesterday.
You came all that way, after all.
Come on, lean on me more.
It’s just film—I might even give it back.
Th-that is...
Hey, listen, listen, listen!
Our freeloader—you know,
splatter-obsessed Yuji—
of all people, he was making out
with Akimoto-sensei!
I saw it all, clear as day. What a jerk.
But the fact that I care
kind of means I’m weird too.
I mean, don’t you think it’s unforgivable for a high schooler to cross that line with a teacher?
But then Fukuike-sensei, who secretly has a crush on Akimoto-sensei, witnessed the whole thing too.
The incident spiraled into an unexpected trip.
Manami betrays our friendship
and invites Yuji to a love hotel.
Akimoto-sensei plays men like toys.
And on top of that, my childhood friend Takashi starts coming after my maiden heart.
Everything’s blowing up left and right—total puttsun!
Volume 3 of Puttsun Make Love.
There! And Here Too? A Snappy Love Triangle.
I don’t care what happens anymore!
Product promotion
Jouka Academy’s annual big sports festival is approaching.
Us girls, under Akimoto-sensei’s guidance,
train and train for the mass games.
One night on the way home from practice, Yuki got molested.
You never know what might turn out to be a blessing.
That incident ended up giving Yuki her first love.
She was completely lovestruck.
But then... It turns out this guy only just transferred to Jouka,
and now he has to transfer again.
Yuki is devastated.
And it seems, the Norimatsu Gang, some scary friends of that guy are on the move.
Manami and I, and Yuji too, decided to step in and somehow make Yuki’s first love come true.
Puttsun Make Love, Volume 5.
Big Sports Festival With Yuki's First Love!
You won’t be able to look away.
Product promotion
It’s summer—it's the beach—a day at the seaside!
Manami booking a one-night trip to Izu was great and all,
but thanks to an unexpected twist, it turned into a one-night trip with just me and Yuji.
We’re usually fighting all the time,
but somehow it felt strange.
Fidgety, restless, my heart pounding.
And then, on that train, we met a mysterious girl.
It’s like there’s a shadow of uneasiness about her—or maybe she is that shadow.
Her left wrist is wrapped in bandages, and the things she’s carrying?
A knife, rope, pills.
No matter how you look at it, she gives off a dangerous vibe.
But this was my precious
make-love chance with Yuji.
The sea at Izu brings an unexpected puttsun.
Puttsun Make Love, Volume 6.
Saori and Yuji's Summer Story.
This time, I’m doing it for real.