Fight! Fight! Fight!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, let's go, let's go, Jouka!
This is awesome, isn't it?
The barrier between the girls' and boys'
buildings gets lifted just once a year—
during the big sports festival!
And then...
Snap, Makeup
Episode 5
Big Sports Festival With Yuki's First Love!
Saori, want a burger?
Maybe a donut? Or udon?
Hmm...
Udon today. I'm starving.
Yay! Yuki agrees!
Ah!
We Spring Team girls
are on decoration duty today.
Thanks for your hard work.
Then we can help ourselves
to your portion, right?
I'm totally late, and in this crowd too.
Yuki's got no luck at all.
And besides...
What? I can't believe it!
Ignorance is bliss—
especially for teachers.
Hey, hey, what are you talking about?
Well, look...
It's not good for your eyes—or ears.
No way! Really?
It's true.
Basically, once a year, on the sports festival day, the boys and girls who are usually kept apart
end up having their own little “festival”
in the shadow of all the excitement on the field.
Kyaa! I had no idea.
Those thrilling little adventures only happen
if you've got the right guy, though...
If only Yuki had a wonderful boyfriend too...
No, we'd probably do something even bolder.
Oh my god, you pervert!
What on earth is Yuki thinking?
A­... A molester!
I... I can't speak... I can't move!
No!
Ah!
Bastard...
Molester! A molester!
What the hell!
Who do you think you are?!
I-It's not me! I swear!
That's not him!
Huh? Wrong guy?
Damn, so it's not him?
Aw, rats. Let's skedaddle, boys.
I'm so sorry! Are you okay?
I'm really sorry. This is my fault.
Don't worry about it. It's fine.
Just go home already.
Okay.
You're damn clingy, ain'tcha?!
Look, I said it's not a serious injury, so cut it o—
Yuki... Yuki...
L-Look, I appreciate you worrying
enough to follow me, I really do, but...
It's getting dark, see?
But this is Yuki's way home.
It's them!
Are you sure you saw Satoshi around here?
Aye-aye!
That prick! If he thinks he can run somewhere I can't see, we'll prove him wrong!
Find him no matter what! Got it?
Yep!
M-My heart's pounding...
Is it because a man is touching Yuki?
Oh, geez... W-What am I to do?
This is embarrassing...
Did they leave?
W-Well, bye now.
Sorry, but I'm really not in a position
to walk you home right now.
Bye!
Cappy!
Huh? Really?
That's great, Yuki!
That's right.
Our chests were pressed together...
Yuki's heart was racing!
This is what they call first love, right?
Huh? His name?
Ah!
Yuki's so stupid!
And it's all my fault for
only thinking dirty thoughts!
Ah... Yes, Manami-san?
Yuki, I heard from Saori.
You're really thoughtless, you know that?
Yes... But I didn't realize I liked him
until after we parted.
Calm down and think back carefully, come on.
Even if you say that...
Ah!
So you say you saw Satoshi around here?
Satoshi... Satoshi...
They called him Satoshi-san!
But his friends looked kind of scary.
Hmm... So things are
more complicated than it seems?
That guy goes to Jouka Academy.
He was wearing our uniform.
You should've said that sooner!
Kobayashi!
I heard! So you've finally gone into heat, huh?
Good for you. Good—
WHACK
Don't talk about her like she's an animal!
Oh... I was just phrasing it differently.
How can you say something that tramples
on a maiden's feelings like that?
Do it again and we're through!
Okay, okay, I get it.
Oh, by the way, Kobayashi, that guy's gotta be
a transfer student named Kogure Satoshi.
Kogure... Satoshi?
Hey!
He was absent today.
Huh? Is it because of yesterday's injuries...?
Nah, apparently he's barely shown up
to school since transferring.
Then there's that flashy group
looking for a guy named Satoshi...
Sounds like there's something shady going on.
Yuki can't just sit around!
Sheesh... Does she really have to go
change clothes for something like this?
Yes, she does.
A girl's heart is delicate, you know.
Right?
Help!
You didn't have to run away, you know.
We just wanted to ask you something, is all.
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Seen this guy?
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Kogure
Satoshi
If this face rings a bell, call the Norimatsu Gang
Lying to us will only make it worse.
Who-ah Twice as Nasty Fruit Ninja
Looks like these ladies
really don't know anything.
Hey!
Always take care of your informants!
Here you go!
Compost Barrel Crushing
This is the May Queen potato
we carefully cultivated at school!
Help yourselves!
And if you see this man...
call us at once.
H-Huh? That guy they said they're after...
Looks like Yuki's first love
is turning into a life-or-death matter.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Cappy!
It's lovely!
Mori
So he was freeloading at a relative's place, huh?
No wonder we couldn't find
a nameplate that said “Kogure.”
Guess you'll see me in a better light now, huh?
Saori...
Get a grip!
Oh no, is nobody home?
Ah! It's open!
Excuse me!
Ow-ow...
A-Are you okay?
Ouch...
Who are you?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I came to thank you properly.
I'm Kobayashi Yuki,
Class 2-C at Jouka Academy.
Huh?
Are you really in high school?
I thought you were my
cousin's elementary school friend.
E-Elementary school...?
N-No, no, actually, it suits you so well!
I mean it! So cute!
Cappy!
But still, how'd you find this place?
Oh, a friend of mine happened to know it.
Oh? Sorry, but I'm kind of busy right now.
Yuki can help!
H-Hey... Hey!
This is part of my apology.
Your room's on the second floor, right?
Ah! Satoshi-san,
what month were you born?
A-April.
Then at the sports festival,
we'll be on the same Spring Team. Cappy!
Oh no, you're almost finished already?
Yuki was all fired up... Too bad.
I-Is she clueless or just forward?
But this feels more like moving out than in.
Yeah, I'm moving.
Huh? You are, Satoshi-san?
Yeah. I'm changing schools.
What? But you just transferred here!
N-No! Yuki hates that!
She had just found her first love!
First love?
That's right. It's the one sweet chance each year
when boys and girls get to be together.
A sweet chance?
Ah! If Yuki and Satoshi got together,
we might even advance to a first kiss!
No, I actually prepared myself
to go way farther than that!
H-Hey! You've prepared yourself,
but what about your partner?
Then... could you please not transfer
until after the sports festival?
That sports festival
is exactly why I have to transfer.
What? Yuki doesn't get it!
I wanna go to the sports festival too!
I want a girlfriend too!
But... But you see...
As long as Norimatsu Kintaro from the Norimatsu Gang is around,
the springtime of my youth
will never blossom!
The people from last night, right?
Yeah.
Did something happen between you and them?
They're coming for revenge.
What?
If I show up, the sports festival'll
fall into total chaos.
I-It can't be...
So transferring is my only option.
H-Hello...
Nice to meet you.
We couldn't help overhearing.
Please let us help you.
Manami-san!
You don't know how relentless those guys are.
They just don't give up.
Jouka has its own way of doing things.
Are you really planning to spend your whole life
running away from sports festivals?
Please...
Transfer after transfer...
I never even managed to make any real friends.
This means the world...
Let's do it! My last sports festival...
in the name of first love!
Cappy!
What? You've found out
where Satoshi's transferred?
Aye, sir. Jouka Academy.
And they've got a big sports festival
the day after tomorrow.
What?
He's planning to compete.
You're too naïve, Satoshi!
I'll never forgive you
for the incident which changed my life!
Gather every member of the Norimatsu Gang!
We're going in.
63rd Jouka Academy Big Sports Festival
Ready!
Excuse me. Is there anyone here
with naturally curly hair?
Good luck,  Spring  Team!
A scavenger hunt?
These items are brutal!
Look at this!
“Tightly curled hair?!"
All right, wait right here.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
Good luck,  Spring  Team!
Do your best!
A sports festival, huh? Nice stuff.
NORIMATSU
GANG
Satoshi, you were fast, all right.
No matter what you did, you outshone me.
Satoshi-kun!
You can do it!
But... But... But...!
Satoshi! Lose, why don'tcha?
No way! That's sneaky, Kin-chan!
You brat...
Yay!
Ugh! You stink, Kin-chan!
Ah! He pooped his pants!
It's not true! Shut up!
He totally pooped his pants!
Unbelievable!
Poopy pants!
Ever since then, I've hated sports festivals
out of sheer humiliation.
So there's no way I'll ever let you
have a fun sports festival
for the rest of your life!
Thanks again. I can’t believe
I’m actually able to take part
in the sports festival without them finding out.
I just hope nothing bad happens.
If the worst happens,
a smoke signal will go up from the roof.
Ah!
They're here.
W-What on earth is going on?
Could this be an elaborately staged
costumed demonstration for showmanship?
Ah, the times we live in...
Norimatsu Kintaro!
His lackey, Red Pine!
Likewise, Black Pine!
Yezo Spruce!
Sakhalin Fir!
On the boss's wish,
the Norimatsu Gang is here!
Now drag Satoshi out here!
Yuki and Satoshi are hiding.
All right, start the operation.
Alley-oop!
Your clever tricks won't fool me!
How's that?
Now then, where did you hide Satoshi?
Be a good girl and tell us!
No! Pervert!
Damn it, I'll have to crush all of you!
Stop it, Kin-chan!
I found you, Satoshi!
Just stop ruining our festival already!
Huh? Eh? What?
Please!
Kin-chan!
Th-This is going too far.
Stop them!
All right, I'll go tell them off myself.
Don't let a single one escape!
Find the real one!
How about it? Those are the skills
of makeup genius Sakazaki Yuji for you!
You...! Where's the real Satoshi?!
No idea...
You little...
Satoshi! Where did you go?!
Don't go!
Kobayashi...
What about Yuki?
What's going to happen to me?
I'm even wearing
my brand-new bra just for today!
So? Does it look good on me?
My panties today are super-special too.
H-Hey, h-hold it now!
H-Hold it, you hear?
Sorry! I gotta try
to talk some sense into Kin-chan.
Satoshi-san...
There!
You've always been good at running, right?
Hey! Stop that!
This is between the two of us men!
Stay out of it!
Enough already!
BROADCASTING ROOM
Now I've got you cornered!
K-Kin-chan! That's going too far! Let's stop!
Shut up! You're the one person
I'll never let enjoy a sports festival!
Let go of the past already! I...
I already forgot all about you pooping your pants
at the kindergarten sports festival!
Now you're saying it again!
Please stop!
It's all Satoshi's fault!
What?! You're the one who decided
to ruin the sports festival! You poopy pants!
Say that again, I dare you!
You poopy pants!
Why you...
You're a poopy pants, so what can I do?
Let's go home.
Yeah.
I'm kind of exhausted.
Me too.
Shut up, you poopy pants!
Do you really have to go?
Yeah. I can't keep causing trouble
for you any longer.
What a messed up fate to carry.
So that's what you are—
a fateful transfer student?
Well, I'm off.
Yuki, go ahead.
B-But...
Fine, I'm not looking!
Satoshi!
Crap! Be well, folks!
Stop!
Like I'll ever stop!
Ah, Yu—
He'll come back to me someday, right?
Yuki's getting hungry!
Ah! Sir, one pork ramen, please!
Hurry up, guys!
Delicious!
Cappy.
You're starting to turn your eyes
to something you never even tried to see
"I'm sorry," you said, bowing your head
And I no longer had anything you could believe in
I can never hold
those shaking shoulders again
Because I miss you, Baby
I won't look back
Your smile is flashing through my eyes now
Because I miss you, Baby
I can't see you anymore
My love, my dreams, and even my voice won't reach you
Because I miss you, baby
I'm getting smaller
I can't see you anymore
Because I miss you, baby
I'm getting smaller
Because I miss you, baby...
Raw provider
Translation,
typesetting
Editing
Eternal_Blizzard
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies
Paul Geromini
imatu