They're late, damn it!
Ah! Here they are!
Awful! This is awful!
Yep. Fukuike and the
other teachers are in the area.
If we're spotted, they'll suspend us all
for breaking the school rules!
Come on, scatter, people!
Here, for you two.
Come on, skedaddle!
Ah!
It's Fukuike!
H-Hey...
And they're off!
Looks like it worked.
Sheesh, getting them alone together
really takes some doing.
They're together all year
and still haven't even made it to their first kiss.
No way!
Hey, there's no Fukuike anywhere!
What are you guys all doing here?
No... we, uh... were just...
Ah, Kuroiwa and the others decided to take you
up on that thing you were recruiting for earlier.
The official English training camp?
Yes!
We just came to see them off.
Oh, I see, I see. And here I thought not a single applicant would show!
As the person in charge, I'd be screwed!
Ah, Sensei. Vice Principal!
Hurry, hurry.
Snap, Makeup
Episode 6
Saori and Yuji's Summer Story
I wonder if Manami and the others are okay.
It's Shimizu, after all.
They'll pull through somehow.
More importantly, a trip with just the
two of us sounds pretty stylish, doesn't it?
Yes, I guess so.
Oh, crap!
Watch out!
P-Perfect weather for the beach, isn't it?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, since we're going there anyway,
should we stay over?
But you told your parents
it was a day trip, didn't you?
Oh, come on. I can say that
as many times as I want. Right?
S-Sure.
No! Not on the train...
Why not?
Machida, Machida Station.
I... I'll go grab some juice and bentos.
S-Sure.
Ah, so chilly!
True! I feel rejuvenated.
Hurry, hurry.
I couldn't buy them in time.
Ah, I forgot!
I made sandwiches already.
R-Really?
Upsy-daisy...
Gee, I'm drenched in sweat.
True. I feel so gross.
Why don't we change?
Whoa, so bold!
Then I will too.
Ah, me too.
Oh, come on.
Don't be stupid.
Saori's right here!
Found them!
I-It got caught in the zipper!
If this turned into spending the night
with Saori, that'd be the best!
Looks like Manami and Yuki
haven't returned home yet.
Did they get caught by Fukuike-sensei?
All right, baby!
Huh?
N-No, I just meant being alone together
is kind of nice, and all that.
You're not thinking anything weird, are you?
What kind of weird?
Geez...
Here it is!
At last! The blazing sun,
the sea breeze filling our chests...
That sea breeze is nice...
H-Hey!
Watch out!
Odoriko
You idiot!
Yuji-kun...
Phew!
Ah! The guy's okay.
Yuji-kun!
What about that girl?
She's fine.
Now, give me a hand.
Sorry about earlier.
My contact lens slipped behind my eye.
But that was awfully close.
You heard the train coming, didn't you?
Yeah, but I was too focused
on looking for my contacts.
It happens a lot.
Ah, it's back.
Because of it, I end up falling all the time.
See, this one's from the day before yesterday.
This is from five days ago.
And this one's from a week ago.
And then?
This is from ten days—no, eleven...
Maybe even two weeks ago?
So we ultimately went
to check up on them, huh?
Think those two are making
any progress right about now?
Vice Principal, look.
This car's almost empty.
Yes. Looks like a good place
to teach the fundamentals.
Hey, what do you think about that girl?
Honestly? I'm creeped out by her.
She's gloomy! And hard to read!
We sure picked up a weird tag-along.
But do you really think
she just fell on the track by accident?
Actually, it didn't seem like that at all.
Right? There's too much that bothers me.
Did you see the bandage on her left wrist?
Yeah, but…
N-No way, you mean this?
And those fresh wounds—aren't they
hesitation scars from failing over and over?
H-Hey, Saori...
She's taking a long time.
Didn't she only go to the restroom to change?
Crap! You think she jumped?
Huh?!
I can't believe I dropped it again.
H-Hey, aren't you hungry?
Would you like a sandwich?
Sandwiches feel kind of lonely.
Then how about some fruit?
Yuji-kun!
R-Right...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Well, I've got this,
but not the can opener.
Ah...
Did you forget it?
Um, if this works, how about it?
"Th-This"?
Y-You can't open a can with that.
You take the knife away from her. Got it?
Oh, that's a godsend!
Yeah, really. You saved us.
Then, don't hesitate and let me have that.
On second thought, this is a little too much.
Then let's buy frozen oranges
at the next station, right?
Ah... Good idea!
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I suddenly felt overwhelmed by sadness.
Thank you.
Th-That medicine just now, wasn't it...
I really am in the way, aren't I?
O-Of course not!
The more the merrier, right?
I'm having loads of fun!
Tahama Station
That's strange, I thought we got off together.
Exit
Entrance
Maybe we should ask a policeman
to walk her back or something?
Exit
Entrance
Let's just enjoy the beach alone!
Exit
Entrance
We can't leave it at that! First it was
the knife, and now it's the rope and pills!
She might be wandering around now,
looking for a place to die.
Seriously, much ado about nothing.
Oh, geez!
Yuji-kun, you jerk!
Girls are sensitive, you know!
Would you just leave her at that
if that were me?
I-Idiot! Of course not!
It's because you've been so cold to her!
That must've pushed her over the limit!
O-Okay, okay, I got it.
But if she's gone already,
there's nothing we can do.
Geez! You really don't have
a shred of sensitivity, do you?
Hey, look at this! This is Kojima Island—
apparently it's famous for its love knots.
Oh, really?
It's right by the beach we're going to!
Is that so?
Oh, come on, why so cold?
Um… would you like any of this?
Y-You…
I bought enough for you two as well.
TAHAMA SOUVENIRS
I suddenly got my appetite back.
Maybe it's because I met you two.
TAHAMA SOUVENIRS
Y-Yeah, sure! We'll take it, won't we?
Y-Yeah, give it here!
I know about Kojima Island too.
Huh?
If a couple stands on that historic cliff,
they become blessed by the sea.
You two might benefit from it.
Huh? Y-Yeah, it's just the thing for us!
Oh...
Disgusting!
You should go there too.
Huh? I don't know yet...
They say the shape of that
lone pine tree's branches is amazing.
It's also a great spot for diving...
if you don't mind the rocks below, that is.
H-Hey, if it's something you're into,
would you wanna swim with us?
Some of our fun-loving friends
will be joining us soon.
Is that really okay?
It's not...
Of course it's okay!
Right, Yuji-kun?
Yeah! You bet!
This stuff is great!
I can't stop eating it!
Hold me, hold me, hold me tight,
There!
wrapped in the morning light
Yuji-kun! I'm going to change now, but you—
don't take your eyes off that girl, got it?
Burning, burning, in these heated arms,
Sure, I'll go all the way
with your boundless compassion.
like a nimble jive dancer
Don't get all stubborn about it.
Once she gets her energy and brightness back,
we'll have some time all to ourselves, okay?
Really? Really?
Re-a-lly!
Feeling gentle love through a smile,
shimmering, supple, we dance on
Your love and my love
melting together, dazzling bright
And seeking happiness forever and ever...
Oh my, Sakazaki-kun?
Huh?
Ah! Akimoto-sensei!
Did you follow me all this way?
Aren't you adorable?
N-No, I mean... excuse me!
Goodness, Sakazaki-kun!
No need to be shy!
I'd rather not!
Sakazaki-kun!
Help!
6th Seaside Madonna Contest
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's here again this year!
The Seaside Madonna Contest!
6th Seaside Madonna Contest
Who will claim the title of our New Madonna?!
Now then, contestant number one, step right up!
It really worked!
Whoa, I'm falling!
WOMEN'S SHOWERS
It was an accident!
Yuji-kun!
I dropped my contacts!
Huh?
Oh, geez... Where are you looking?!
There!
This is exactly why
I begged you to watch her!
Huh?
She's disappeared again!
What?
What if something happens to her?!
We finally talked her out of it
and were just becoming friends!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Gosh...
Don't worry, just leave it to me.
I'll find her, no matter what.
What? A girl?
Beats me.
Nah, doesn't ring a bell.
We didn't see her.
Oh, that girl?
That lady said she went this way.
Ah!
Look! It's her! What do we do?
This is bad!
Saori, go get help!
Okay!
Beautiful…
We finally made it.
Where do you think Saori and Yuji are?
Right in the middle of the action, I imagine.
Huh?
Saori, I want all of you...
I've treasured myself until today,
only for you, Yuji-kun.
Saori!
Yuji-kun...
Ah, not there!
Come on, why not?
Yuki, are we two really
that corrupted by his influence?
No, I don't think so at all.
Really?
All right, then I'm going
to find myself a fancy guy too!
S-Someone!
Someone come!
Saori! What's wrong?
Manami! Yuki!
Yuji...
Yuji went to Kojima Island
to stop a suicidal girl!
Huh?
Wow!
When a girl wants to die in a beautiful place,
she always believes a wonderful prince
will come to stop her.
Y-Yuki?
So I bet she thinks that until
Yuji comes to save her, she can't die.
And if anything,
she'd rather they both go together.
Yuki!
Don't say things like that—you'll jinx it!
Sorry.
No! It's an earthquake!
Ah! I-It's a big one!
Huh? W-What?
Looks like it's over.
Tsunami warning issued!
Everyone on the beach, evacuate immediately!
What do we do?
My, it's you girls!
Evacuate now!
What if this tsunami hits?
Oh, if it isn't Akimoto-sensei!
What a coincidence.
Oh, you're here, Fukuike-sensei?
And the vice principal too?
Please! Help save Yuji-kun, everyone!
Huh?
Huh? No way!
The mission to save Sakazaki
is proceeding in perfect order!
One-two-three, this is the Yamagawa Style!
The Jouka's trademark strategy!
I repeat:
Everyone on the beach,
please evacuate immediately.
The earthquake has subsided, but a tsunami has occurred! This is not a drill!
H-Hey!
Stop! Don't do it!
Don't stop me.
I finally found the perfect place.
You idiot! Don't do anything rash!
W-Wait!
Yuji-kun!
Saori!
If you're doing something stupid, stop!
Huh?!
Hold up!
Whoa... I'm saved!
No! Don't grab me there, geez!
There's nowhere else to grab!
Did you know?
Couples who get splashed by the high waves
on this cliff are destined to never again be apart.
Yuji-kun!
Saori!
Yuji-kun, hang in there!
S-Saori! Thank God you're safe.
Are you all right?
Please stay with us!
Love me gently, without being noticed
Quickly turn off the light in the room
The city is already deep in dreams,
and the spare key is in the milk box
Love me softly, like rippling waves,
a small throbbing, repeating
Feeling our way, these hot hearts,
the scent of passing midsummer
Please, don't turn warmth into sorrow
Please, casually, love me in secret
Go for it, my heart!
A happy-sounding conversation,
pushing through at last, the waiting ends—
an aggressive style that makes everyone turn
Walking around all flashy,
but when your heart really hurts,
that's one more beat added
An airhead like me—hurt, but it can't be helped
Don't talk to me about human ambitions,
just start moving your body like a fool and DANCE!
Dancin' on the street
My playful heart
DANCE!
Dancin' on the street
My extreme heart
DANCE!
Dancin' on the street
My precious heart
DANCE!
Dancin' on the street
Go for it, my heart!
M-M-My heart
M-M-MY HEART!
Raw provider
Translation,
typesetting
Editing
Eternal_Blizzard
Perevodildo
MartyMcflies
Paul Geromini
imatu