Whoa!
So this is the city of Toras?
The sun is setting.
We'll rest here tonight.
Well, Silver? You must also be dying
to smell a woman again after all this time, right?
Right, Silver?
Well, I'm dying too!
Heya, Silver!
He came down to us from the pages of a children's book, the legendary knight Yamato Takeru.
A hardworking hero, who was born as a child of the gods, but must now wander the human realm.
Though he himself does not know it,
the fame of his many heroic deeds has already spread across the land, and his name is known everywhere.
The people await his arrival
with eager anticipation.
Hero of the Sun, Yamato Takeru.
The Flaming Swordsman, Yamato Takeru.
Who hasn't heard of Yamato Takeru?
Dragon Knight
Side Story
Oh? So that's the famous Toras cathedral, huh?
Really is a prosperous city.
Hey! Stop right there!
Somebody grab that brat!
Thief!
Sorry, coming through!
You punk...
Hand back what you stole.
I don't know anything about that!
Don't play dumb.
Hurry up and hand it over.
I said I don't know!
You little street rat,
always picking the pockets...
Let him go!
You guys get your kicks roughing up
kids who can't defend themselves, huh?
Don't get cocky, pal.
You might get hurt.
We're just trying to get
back what this brat stole.
That so?
Asshole...
No sudden moves.
You amateurs won't be able
to take me on for as long as you live.
If you stole something, hand it over now.
Otherwise I'll let these
scary gentlemen deal with you.
There, that settles it, right?
Or do you want more?
N-No... As long as we get this back... Right?
Ah... Yes, the Bishop'll be happy.
Idiot! Don't say more than you have to!
Let's go.
Out of the way! Move it!
Hold it, you brat!
I never let my guard down,
so I'd like my wallet back.
You noticed?
Of course I did. You haven't been in this business long, have you?
Am I really that bad at it?
Yeah. Since even I could catch you.
Keep that up and one day
they'll catch you and lop off both your arms.
You hungry?
Yeah. Haven't eaten in three days.
All right, I'll get you something to eat.
Huh? Really?
Yeah,
but you gotta promise me one thing.
What? Promise what?
As long as you're with me, no stealing.
Fine! I won't even look at your wallet again.
Not just mine. Nobody's.
Got it?
Yeah. I promise.
What's your name?
Jody.
I'm Takeru.
Whoa! That looks great!
I could eat her here and now!
Hey, Takeru, what about the food you promised?
Yeah, just gimme a minute.
We'll eat after.
This one's even yummier!
Takeru, when are you actually gonna feed me?
Later, kid, later! It's women! I haven't had
a woman in ages! Look at her sticking it out!
Lord Incubus Leonardo...
Lunther, I enjoyed this last selection.
Keep the flow of women for me steady!
Yes, sir.
Thanks to you, Lord Leonardo, the city of Toras
will soon be completely under my sway,
a den of pure debauchery.
Keep at it.
Leave it to me.
Who's there?
It's us, Bishop.
Oh, you found him?
Yes, sir. Here.
Deliver these women
to Vanessa the moneylender.
Top-quality goods.
Understood.
No... it's gone!
I swear we didn't pocket a single coin!
Idiot! I'm not talking about money!
The special potion I kept here—
the packet is missing!
The special potion?
Then that brat must've...
Ugh! Find him. Find him no matter what.
He knows too much,
we can't let him live.
Kill him if you have to, but bring it back.
Find the one who stole the potion immediately!
You seem troubled, Bishop.
Th-That voice... Shade!
Shade?
Creepy as ever, I see.
Lord Leonardo send me to keep an eye on you.
Can't let you out of my sight.
Then you should understand,
if I don't get that potion back,
my true identity
will be exposed to the whole city.
I haven't reported anything
to Lord Leonardo as of yet.
I beg you, recover that potion for me.
Sure, as long as I can handle it my way.
Fine. I'll leave it to you.
No time to even breathe...
Man, you sure eat a lot.
Thanks for the meal!
This'll last me for two or three days.
For a kid who's supposedly had it rough,
you sure can pack it away.
Did you really come here to worship
and get separated from your sister?
I wonder where she is now?
I know she's somewhere in this city, but...
All right! Guess I'll lend you a hand.
Huh?
Toras is big, but if you still can't find her,
something must've happened.
Maybe some bad guys
tricked her and snatched her.
No way...
Your sister... she good-looking?
Wh-What are you thinking, you perv?!
I get it.
I knew what was on your mind
even before you bought me food.
That so? Then this'll be quick.
Even when I look at your face, it's not half-bad,
so your sister's gotta be pretty decent too.
And if she's not pretty,
you won't go looking for her?
Don't tell me your sis...
is too ugly to even look at!
No way! I'm telling you, you won't find a girl
in this city as gorgeous as my sister!
All right, then it's settled!
But even if you find her,
I can't pay you back or anything.
Don't worry about that.
If we find her, I'll get plenty of thanks from her.
Th-Thanks, Takeru.
Though I'm not sure if that's kindness
or just ulterior motives...
Don't you doubt me like that,
partner. Hey, hey, hey!
I saw how you helped that kid earlier.
You've got real skill.
Not at all, that was pure luck.
Oh no. I can swing a sword myself.
I can tell you're no amateur.
I could use your help.
Well, sorry, but I just got hired by this kid.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
I see. Too bad.
Then some other time.
Sorry.
My name is Julius.
I'm Yamato Takeru.
Yamato Takeru?
You're not... the one who lifted the curse from Strawberry Fields?
N-Nah, wrong guy.
Do I really look that strong to you?
True...
the hero Yamato Takeru
is said to be a towering warrior,
an absolute legend,
beloved and respected by all who meet him.
Especially women,
who are overcome with an urge to throw themselves at him the moment they lay eyes on him.
Nothing like you.
Tsk. Damn it, that rumor's taken on a life of its own.
Is there something on my face?
You look just like someone I knew.
But she's already dead,
so you can't be her.
That has to be just an accidental resemblance.
They say every face has got
three or four lookalikes in the world.
Yeah, I guess. But...
Well then, Takeru. When you finish your business with him, come to see me about this job.
Yeah, if I feel like it.
Okay, Takeru. I'll also head out then.
Where are you going?
Well, to find a place to sleep, obviously.
What if those thugs from earlier see you again?
But...
Hey, shopkeeper.
Yes, what is it?
We'll be staying for a bit.
Here.
Certainly. Thank you very much!
Also, find some used clothes that'll fit this kid.
Anything's better than what he's wearing.
I've got my son's old clothes.
Hold up!
I don't wanna share a room with you!
Relax, bro.
I'm straight as an arrow—
I'm not swinging that way for as long as I live.
Come on, let's go.
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
Let go, Takeru!
Certainly. Your room is on the second floor.
Come on already, Jody.
Jody?
So he's here?
What do we do, boss?
That guy's stupidly strong.
We'll wait till he's asleep, and then...
Hope this works...
Don't worry. Once he's out, he's ours.
That door leads to the bath.
Enjoy your stay.
Jody, go take a bath first.
N-No way, I'm not taking a bath!
If you clean up, nobody will recognize you.
And this inn doesn't want you dirtying up the bed.
B-But... I kind of have a cold, so...
Keep whining and I'll strip you naked
and toss you in myself!
No... W-Wait...
Come on, move it!
O-Okay, okay! I'll do it myself! Just let go!
Then hurry up and get in.
All right, but don't you dare open the door!
Who the hell wants to see you naked, idiot?
I swear, who raised that guy like that?
Skittish like a girl.
Innkeeper.
Y-Yes?
I'd like a room as well.
Is the one next to those boys vacant?
Yes, it is. I'll show you the way.
Who is it?
I brought a change of clothes.
Come in.
It's not much, but it's all I have.
Yeah, this is perfect.
Even Jody'll look presentable in this.
Make yourself comfortable.
Yeah, thanks.
Jody!
Your clothes are here.
No!
W-What?!
Don't look! Don't come in!
Y-You...!
Stupid Takeru!
Hurry up and get out already!
Y-You're a girl!
Takeru?
Takeru! Get it together, Takeru.
Takeru!
Takeru, talk to me.
Takeru. Takeru?
Takeru!
Ow...
You okay, Takeru?
B-Boobs...
Ah, Jody, y-you...
Thank goodness!
I thought you were dead.
J-J-Jody, calm down.
I—I'm fine.
I'm sorry! That must've hurt, right?
Never mind that, Jody,
just put some clothes on.
Hey...
Get yourself together, Jody...
Make love to me, Takeru...
H-Hey, hold it...
This isn't right, Jody.
You can't be doing stuff like this yet.
It's all right.
You saved me, didn't you?
Still... This and that aren't the same thing.
And you said you'd help me find my sister.
Y-Yeah, I did, but still...
Also...
I told you my sister's a real looker, right?
Y-Yeah...
I don't want my sister stealing you away from me.
Oh? Didn't see that coming.
That filthy little brat was a girl?
If we'd grabbed her earlier,
we'd be the ones with her now...
Look at that nice ass on her.
It sure is.
Are you two that much into that little girl?
Lady Shade!
Is she the one who stole the potion?
Y-Yes.
What about the man?
Seems he's a wandering headhunter.
He's damn good with that sword.
Oh, no! You can't stop
in the middle of it, silly Takeru!
W-Wait, hold on.
I can't even breathe like this.
Sorry...
you must think I'm shameless.
That's not it, Jody.
Oh... My bad.
So what's your actual name?
Jodice.
Jodice, huh?
Nice name.
Jodice, I've already gotten
plenty of advance payment.
Huh?
We start searching for your sister tomorrow.
So tonight you're going to sleep.
But...
A mercenary taking full payment
before the job even starts is weird, right?
But...
So what happened earlier
was just the down payment for the job.
You hate me, don't you?
Of course it's not because hate you.
You're cute, Jodice.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Once we save your sister,
I'll come for the rest of the reward.
That work for you, Jodice?
Takeru, you're mean.
Sorry.
You know I like women, Jodice.
But taking advantage of a girl I saved to get in her bed?
That'd weigh on me a bit.
Please, take just a little more down payment.
Come on...
W-Well... if you insist...
Kiss me, Takeru.
I like you, Jodice.
M-Me too...
Takeru!
Ta...
Takeru! Takeru!
Takeru...
Nice view.
Sure is.
Don't move.
That's our line!
Make one wrong move and the girl
gets a pretty red flower blooming on her throat.
That what you want?
Jodice!
Takeru...
Did you say "Takeru"?
Put the sword down, or else...
I'm scared...
W-Wait!
All right.
Now, set it down nice and slow.
Fine, just don't hurt Jodice.
Takeru!
Don't make such loud noises.
Close the door.
Yes.
What happened?
Speak up, girly.
Where's the stuff you swiped earlier?
Tell us quick or I'll slice your ear clean off.
Stop! I don't know anything about that!
Then maybe you'd prefer a pretty red flower?
Help me, Takeru...
Still nothing?
S-Sorry...
Where the hell did she hide it?
What's wrong? Something happen?
Tsk. We've been interrupted.
We're pulling out.
We're taking the girl and her clothes. Got it?
Aye.
Let's go.
Hey!
Stay with me! Hey!
Damn it, where'd she hide it?
No!
No...
It's too early to start screaming.
You two find anything?
Is that so?
Looks like we'll have
to work it out of your body then.
There, see?
It... It hurts!
Please, stop...
Then speak up!
Wh-What are you doing...
No... Please, stop it!
Go on, talk.
Where's the item you stole from the Bishop?
I—I gave it back.
It hurts...
You took something out of it, didn't you?
Tell the truth or...
It hurts!
Help...
No! Stop, don't twist them!
I'm sorry, I didn't take anything!
Ugh. What a stubborn girl.
Don't worry, this won't even scratch
that pretty skin of yours.
Please... anything but that!
P-Please...
Take this!
Well now, pretty sensitive, aren't you?
But it wouldn't be any fun if you faint too early.
Next I'll work up that cute little butt of yours.
Warm it up properly, you know.
Please...
Let me go...
I don't know anything...
But please... stop...
Once I'm done with you,
you'll be the filthiest little wench in this world.
The girl doesn't really know a thing.
Yeah? Then why...
Probably wants to keep her as a toy.
After she breaks her, she'll use a potion
to make her completely addicted to pleasure.
Do that long enough, and you get a girl
who obeys everything you say like a doll.
I know, but Shade's really taking it especially far.
Shade's taken a liking to the girl.
I bet she won't even let the Bishop
lay a finger on her.
Like that chick the other day—
Shade hogged her all to herself, didn't she?
Yeah. Well, thanks to all the weirdos in charge,
we'll never be out of job, I reckon.
Too true.
My head's splitting...
G-Give me water...
Is this... Takeru!
Wh-What is it, Julius?
My head still rings.
Just give me the water already—ah!
Wh-What's the meaning of this?!
Why do you have this here?!
Speak up! Why?!
Forget that, where's Jodice?
Answer me!
Why do you have the forbidden potion?!
Depending on your answer, I might kill you!
Forbidden potion?
The Magic Herb Mandragora.
The potion made from it drives women mad.
It makes them slaves to desire,
obedient to anything.
Oh? It's that strong?
Sounds convenient.
No, that's not what I meant...
Humans cannot produce this potion.
Eh? Then how come...
You really don't know, do you?
There are agents of demons in this town.
Julius, where's Jodice?
We have to find her fast!
Leave it to me.
I've got a lead.
Hey, Julius,
why do I have to dress like this?
They've got a hostage.
We can't just storm the front door.
That's not the problem!
Why are you the noble lady
and I'm the younger sister?
Just look in a mirror and you'll know.
Humph! Figured as much.
Don't do anything that stands out.
But are you sure Jodice is in that cathedral?
I'm certain.
I know the Bishop of that cathedral, Lunther,
like the back of my hand.
And I know he's hiding something in there.
But if they think we're just two ladies
here to make an offering, they'll drop their guard.
I see. If that's how it is, fine...
What is it?
Well, you see, we lost our family in the recent plague,
so we're left all alone in this world.
We came to ask the Bishop for his blessing
to prevent any more misfortune from falling on us.
Man, Julius is not half-assing it.
Well, that's truly unfortunate indeed.
We'll make an exception
and speak to the Bishop directly for you.
Thank you very much.
W-We're so lucky to have you...
Oh my, oh my.
My men already told me everything.
I'll grant you a special prayer.
Take these two to the underground chapel, Shade.
Shade?
This way, please.
You...
Shade! So it really was you.
What's going on?
My big moment's finally here!
P-Please stop.
So you've sold your body and soul
to monsters, Shade?!
Wh-What are you hesitating for,
Shade? Kill them! Kill them all!
I...
Right.
I knew you couldn't do it.
It's a pity, but die!
Shade! What are you doing?!
Julius! Leave her to me!
You go make the Bishop spill where Jodice is!
Stop!
Against someone like you,
I won't be pulling any punches!
Bring it on, you monster!
Show your true self!
You freak of nature!
Bastard...
That reaction...
So you really are that Yamato Takeru!
I don't give my name out to monsters!
I've already figured out your moves!
Arrogant fool.
This is the end!
What're you looking for?
Right here! I'm right here!
What...
There!
Julius.
Lunther! Where's Jodice?
Prepare to be sent to Lord Incubus Leonardo.
What can a worm like you possibly do?
The girl's barely breathing in the cellar.
But you won't make it to her—
you're being sent to Lord Leonardo first!
Prepare yourself!
Julius!
Huh? What the...
Damn, that was such a waste!
Takeru!
Oh, right...
This isn't the time for that.
You bastard...
This is the end!
That's what you get for staining your soul.
J-Jodice...
I just wanted to see Jodice once...
Could she be Jodice's sister?
I can't believe it.
I won't let your sorrow go unanswered.
Jodice!
Takeru!
Are you okay, Jodice?
Ah... Takeru... you came for me.
J-Jodice, what's wrong?
Make love to me, Takeru... please... do it!
W-Wait, Jodice...
Pull yourself together... what's going on?
Your body is burning...
H-Hey, Jodice?
If you don't do it to her now, she'll go insane.
What did you say?
It's the Mandragora potion.
Jodice... they used that on you?
Please... I can't... take it anymore.
I'll wait outside.
Even to an innocent girl like her...
I'll never forgive that Incubus Leonardo!
Jodice...
Takeru...
Hurry, please!
My body's on fire.
Yes, you'll feel better soon.
N-Not there!
S-Sorry. Did it hurt?
No... It's not that.
Touch me down there too...
You came already?
I don't know...
But it feels so good!
Touch me more down there...
Yes, there...
I'm glad... I managed to make you so wet.
Yes!
It's embarrassing...
Don't talk like that!
It's because you're too cute.
Takeru... give it to me soon!
I can't... take it anymore!
Are you sure?
Takeru, I love you. Do it.
It hurts!
Are you okay?
Don't stop. I want you to do it.
No... It's in!
Jodice...
Takeru, I'm so glad!
I've finally done it with you.
Does it hurt, Jodice?
No! It's irresistible, Takeru!
Do something... Anything!
Yes! So good!
More! More!
Takeru, please... Give me more!
Ravish me!
Takeru...
Takeru! This feeling...
Please... do it with me!
We'll do it together... this time.
I'm so glad, Takeru...
O-Oh my God, what's happening to me?
Ready?
It's here... I'm coming, Takeru!
I—I'm coming!
Get Jodice to safety.
Were you able to neutralize the potion?
Yeah. Looks like she's back to normal now.
I'm heading out on a journey.
Then, won't you come with me to the town of Rona?
Seeing as you're taking care of Jodice now, please!
The town of Rona, right?
I'll do it.
I'll go on ahead and wait for you.
So you really were the princess.
And you're the daughter
of the palace forest watchman.
Yes. Do you remember now?
Your sister suffered so much,
it makes my heart ache.
With the Bishop dead,
this town should know peace again.
Stay here for a while.
What about you?
I'm returning to Talos Castle.
Until Leonardo is defeated,
there will be no peace in this world.
Where is Takeru?
He left on his journey.
Though I hope to ask for his help once more.
I understand.
Thank you.
Free-spirited and hungry for thrills, the wandering swordsman Yamato Takeru keeps traveling on.
Not knowing the truth of his own birth,
he continues his journey, carrying the star of fate.
He is also a hero who chases romance and pleasure—the ultimate adventurer.
What new trials await Yamato Takeru
on the perilous road ahead?
Let me dream a little, even if it's only for tonight.
Hold me tight, don't let go.
I never knew I could feel something this wonderful
until I met you.
So for now, let me keep dreaming.
Tell me more about yourself.
When the time comes for me to leave this place,
you can forget about me, it's okay.
The happiness I get, the embarrassment I hold, it's always like that.
Things slip through my fingers, and nothing good ever stays.
But tonight, somehow, I feel like I can change.
ProxyMan
Perevodildo
Paul Geromini
Raw provider
Translation
Quality check