Starvation will kill me before
these stupid monsters will!
I'd better find a town soon.
Weird...
Hey! Anybody home?
Talk about weird towns.
Not a soul around.
I can't believe even the bars are closed.
This is ridiculous.
Can't a guy even buy a meal in this burg?
What a pathetic excuse for a city!
Could this castle be empty too?
Hey, take it easy, won't you?
Some woman you are!
Who might that man be?
Yes, Your Highness.
After breaking into the palace kitchen,
this knave proceeded to ravish the royal pantry.
Stealing food? How vulgar!
Now, wait just a second!
I was out there yelling until I turned blue,
and nobody saw fit to answer me!
My stomach was rumbling,
and my eyes saw food on the table,
so my arm decided it was time to act!
And that's exactly what the law
calls "stealing food."
So that makes you a petty thief.
Not at all! Yamato Takeru's the name,
seeking a life full of excitement,
from journey to journey.
I suppose you could call me
a free-spirited swordsman?
We have no need for such
unreliable swordsmen in our state.
Especially since we're a women-only nation.
Drive him away at once!
Right!
Please wait!
I beg you to wait, Your Majesty!
Luna?
Your Highness, have you forgotten
the words of the prophet?
This man must be the hero
who will deliver Strawberry Fields.
We can't risk expelling him!
A man's our hero?
The hero?
Ah, I remember now.
"In the season when flowers bloom
and leaves take on color,
with the full moon shining brightly overhead,
a young man shall come from the southern range.
Though his appearance would be wretchedly shabby,
you must not be deceived."
Well, excuse me for my "wretchedly shabby" appearances.
There can be no doubt
he is the promised hero.
I see.
Yamato Takeru, seeing as we consider you a hero,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Our nation was once
a bountiful and beautiful land,
founded upon the Fountain of Happiness,
with the Goddess' blessing.
But one day, dark clouds gathered
above the tower where the Goddess dwelled.
Suddenly, the water from the magic fountain
ceased to flow into our country.
Then one day, our Goddess
was delivered to us... in this form.
Sealed in stone?
This is the work of the Dragon Knights,
the incarnate evils.
Dragon Knights?
Indeed. The Dragon Knight Overlord
made a proclamation...
Dark clouds are trendy!
The age of good is over.
Embrace the advent of evil with us
and enjoy it to the core!
...and other stupid things!
A showdown between the Good and Evil, huh?
What's the deal with these holes?
They are the symbols of the Goddess' power.
Six holes for six jewels.
To restore the Goddess,
we must retrieve these jewels.
And those were taken by the Dragon Knights?
That's right. The Overlord
and five of his Dragon Knights.
To make matters worse, they've also captured
all the warriors we sent after the jewels
and subjected them to terrible torture!
Ah! Tears!
Even sealed in stone, the Goddess still worries
about her people... and pities them.
Brave Takeru, it is your destiny
to rescue our captured warriors.
To restore peace and tranquility to our land.
Do that, and not only shall we forgive you
for stealing food, we will grant you any wish.
You want me to bring them back, but isn't that tower
filled with all kinds of monsters or something?
Are you scared?! Aren't you a man?
No, that's not it, exactly...
So you wish to abandon
all our beautiful warriors?
Beautiful?
Indeed. Some are even prettier than me.
Really?
I see now.
Your Goddess getting sealed really moved me,
so maybe I'll go for a little walk to settle my stomach.
Will you do it for us, Brave Takeru?
Just don't get too mad if I fail!
There's something I've been
wanting to ask you...
84, 58, 83!
Not that! What's the deal with all those swords and helmets scattered around?
Ah? Ah... Those mark the graves of the men
who've gone into the tower before you.
The Dragon Knights are pretty disciplined,
gotta give them that.
They dug a grave for every single one of them.
Yikes. I have a bad feeling
about this whole idea.
What are you saying?
You can't turn back now!
I guess not.
But since it's babes we're going to be saving out of captivity, I brought my trusty instant camera!
Jeez... What are you even thinking?
This way.
Hey!
If you knew the way all along,
you should've said so from the start.
Use your head!
Why do you think I came along?
Swayed by my awesome good looks, of course?
Jeez, what a wimpy monster!
He really is the hero!
He's incredibly good!
What's that?
Stop it!
They're going that far with her?!
So, where do you want it next, sweetie?
Please don't do this to me.
If you want me to stop, you have only to reveal the secret of the jewels to the Dragon Knights.
That...
Since you're still refusing to listen,
I guess I'm going to have to do it again!
Hold it!
Wh-Who the hell are you?
I don't give my name out
to dungeon fodder like you.
Prepare to die!
Are you all right?
Thank you so much!
I'm Sheela, a warrior
from Strawberry Fields. And you?
He's Yamato Takeru,
the hero from the prophecy.
The queen sent him here
to defeat the Dragon Knights.
Well, that's very nice, but...
Could you please untie me?
Ah, oopsy daisy...
Not before I take a commemorative photo.
What are you doing?
Untie her already. Don't be a jerk!
Sure, sure. Boy, do you get scary!
Um... I'm sure there's a better way...
Oh, don't worry, it's nothing!
Hey...
Not there!
Hurry up, please!
WHACK
The five Dragon Knights and their Overlord
have one jewel each.
Each Dragon Knight lives in his own personal level of this tower.
Well, I'll head back to the castle now
to report back to the Queen.
Good luck!
H-Hey, wait! I still need your three sizes
and your phone num-
Please, you can't do this to me anymore.
Of course we'll stop,
once you tell us the secret of the jewels.
I don't know nothing about it...
What a stubborn little bitch.
All right, let's take it from the bottom again.
No problem!
You'd better be ready,
'cause I won't go easy on you!
S-Stop...
Not there...
Stop!
That looks like fun!
No, don't!
What's this enviable thing you're doing?!
It's a filthy human!
Did you come to interrupt us?!
I wouldn't care about that.
I'm only here to slay all of you!
Serves you right, you dirtbags.
Commemorative photo secured!
Hey, wake up!
Right, there's a surefire way to wake up a girl...
You're here to rescue them, nothing else.
But of course!
It was just a bit of mischief.
Who are you?
Takeru's the name.
The queen sent me to rescue you!
I'm Jane.
But why are you putting your hand there?
My, when did it get there indeed!
Come on, lighten up!
I'm not mad at you, though.
That's exactly what someone
who's mad would say!
And it's not like I have to please you
with everything I do, anyway.
Isn't that right?
I don't...
Luna?
Luna!
I'm sure Takeru is doing his best.
After all, he is the hero of the prophecy.
My prophecies have never been wrong before.
Only three jewels left to go.
Godspeed, Takeru.
We await your safe return.
Who's there?
She's just as beautiful as we were told.
We are serving the Dragon Knight Overlord.
I am the Dragon Knight
who commands the Green Dragon.
We have come to put some questions
to the queen.
Give us the answers quickly,
and nothing too repulsive shall befall you.
Takeru...
This is getting rather repetitive.
YOU       LOSE
Now, why don't you tell us everything, Queen.
What is the secret of the jewels,
and who is this upstart hero Takeru?
I have nothing to say to lowly filth such as you!
Spoken like a queen.
Still, I cannot help but wonder
how long you'll hold that regal pose.
Do it!
What do you think you're doing?
Your bosom is magnificent.
I wonder if it's just as nice to the touch.
Go to hell, you stupid jerk!
My, oh my, such uncouth language!
Let's see what you say to this!
A splendid sight indeed.
Are you going to start talking now?
Ow...
What the hell is going on here?
Takeru! Save me!
So it's you, the hero Takeru?
Your escapades have really caused a stir
at the Overlord's tower.
So you came all the way here to try and stop me this way? You've got too much spare time.
Will you please stop talking and do something?
I'm blushing to the tip of my toes here!
So I see.
Get on with it!
I could use a little exercise before lunch!
Now you shall experience
the true power of the Dragon Knights!
Green Dragon!
The notion of a pathetic human
taking on one of my kind is laughable!
To battle, Green Dragon!
Hey! Enough jumping about!
He's slow, but that fire could be dangerous.
Okay...
Your Majesty! I'm coming to rescue you now!
How is holding onto that column
going to rescue her?
Dragon, to the right!
He fell for it!
No, left!
Eat this!
So you've done it?
I'll take out the big one first!
You're next, asshole!
What, you're still here?
Strike!
Takeru!
How dare you treat a priceless jewel like that!
Come on, chill. You're not exactly dressed to look commanding.
Still, one can't help but notice
how impressive your "qualities" are.
I should thank the Dragon Knights
for showing that to me.
Get back to the tower
and rescue the remaining warriors!
Man, talk about a harsh mistress!
And I'm hungry again...
Her Highness sure doesn't know
how to show her appreciation.
I never even got a chance to ask about Luna.
Now what?
I know they're ugly,
but attacking one of their own?
Hold it!
What the hell are you? A human?!
You're another weakling, so why even try?
Are you all right?
There. I don't fight the children. Run along now.
You can't come with me!
I'm a hero, here to defeat your associates!
That makes me your enemy, got it?
Suit yourself.
What? That way?
You'll show me where to go?
I need to get to the upper levels.
The monsters on the fifth level were tough!
I just need to give myself a bit of a power boost
with these picture of cuties I collected.
I think... this one is Ann.
Her bust was something else.
And this is Annie. An intelligent beauty with the most stunning curves from her hips down to her feet.
Tina. Boy, was I surprised when I lit
that match! She was right there, stark naked!
Poor Maria-chan, forced into such a disreputable line of work.
That's when sympathy turns into love, isn't it?
So, what do you think?
See anything you like?
H-Hey, what's the matter?
Why are you so angry?
You're not jealous, are you?
Hey, hey, hey!
Say, I bet you're female!
Hey, little one! It's all right. I'm right here!
I can't believe we're actually inside the column.
I found this hidden in here too!
What? Is it really that important?
The so-called hero Takeru, who snuck into our tower, has proven to be
an unexpectedly strong adversary.
In only a short time, he has already
defeated four of our Dragon Knights!
You worry too much.
He is only human, after all!
Never could he hope to match
an incarnate evil such as I!
But My Liege, he has already
recovered four of the jewels!
Worry not!
The one in a million chance he might have
would be to find the White Sword.
A human, who trusts only what he can see
with his eyes, will never find that!
Rest assured, Black!
Now where do you suppose
the stairs to the sixth level are?
The staircase we used earlier dead-ended here at the fifth. Do you know?
I see.
Oh? Something smells good.
I was hungry anyway.
Let's stuff our faces already!
What a spread!
This part looks particularly appetizing!
Why are you grabbing it with your hands?
Don't you have any manners?
Yeah, ain't you got no fuckin' couth?
Huh?
What the hell?
Wake up, men! It's a human!
You don't suppose he's the human
who's been carving up the Dragon Knights?
That's right!
Now it's your turn to be served on a platter!
So, you're going to cook our goose, huh?
How about we slice you into bacon instead?
Damn, I can't keep an eye on all of them!
I think I got motion sickness.
Thanks, you saved us!
Oh man, that was nasty! The demons licked our bodies all over, so now we're sticky!
Thanks for saving us!
I'm Lara, and this is Leila.
You're Takeru, right?
How did you know?
The demons were talking about you.
And you've found the White Sword as well!
You're talking about this?
That's right. You'll need it to defeat
the Dragon Knight Overlord!
But the White Sword alone
will not be enough.
Only Luna, the child of the priest
of Strawberry Fields,
can unleash that sword's power.
But I haven't been able to find her.
That's too bad.
So she's missing now?
In any case, Black Dragon and their Overlord
are still waiting above. Won't you go face them?
Well, you see, I can't find the stairs.
Oh, but the way up is there,
through the aqueduct.
Why is it an aqueduct,
if there's no water in it?
The water used to run here before.
On the top floor was the Goddess's Spring,
from which beautiful water gushed forth,
streaming down here and cascading like a waterfall
through that window into our country.
But now, with the Overlord occupying it...
All right! I'll take care of it!
I'll bring that wonderful spring water back for you!
If you promise to go out with me later.
All right!
That so-called hero's not going
to show, it seems.
You think he's turned tail and gone home?
Humans haven't got the guts
to follow through with their claims.
That's certainly the truth!
Hey!
This human's come to finish the job!
Prepare yourself, Overlord!
Whoa! He's really here!
You escaped us once, but never again!
Dang, I knew I should've finished you off earlier.
Overlord, please let us deal with him!
Idiots!
You idiots let a human get so far!
I beg your forgiveness, sir!
You worm...
Looks like the old magic is having an off day!
He's got the White Sword! But without
the priest's daughter, it will avail him naught!
You're going to die!
You call yourself a hero?
I ought to commend you for getting this far.
When I send the queen to meet the ancestors,
you'll be waiting there to greet her!
You...
How did you survive?!
My Lord, you must escape!
The priest's child...
What did he mean?
Takeru...
Luna!
Don't look, you idiot!
S-Sorry...
It's just that you're even prettier
than the warriors I've saved here.
You mean it?
I mean it...
Let's be reasonable, hero.
Your human soul is inherently evil too.
Why not join up with me now?
You'll have all the booze and broads you want!
Unlimited wine and women?
With me, Takeru already has
all the women he needs.
O heavenly spirits in your infinite variety!
Grant us your power!
Shine upon this White Sword!
Foolish hero! Someday you'll regret this!
That's not too likely, is it?
Hey, Takeru!
We've been waiting for you!
I never thought I'd regret it so soon.
I can feel
my heart
giving me a command.
From the moment
I met you
there in the outer cosmos,
I've been sending you
this thrill, telepathically.
There's someone else
whose laser beam
is aimed at you.
There's someone else
whose feelings
ran silver through me.
You slipped past me without answering.
Please remain the same, unchanged.
Shooting Lover, warrior of love,
until I capture your love.
Shooting Star,
I want you to watch over me in this battle.
Even if I get hurt, it's better than doing nothing.
Yes, now is my chance,
but for some reason I'm trembling.
Right before my eyes, there's a love
I've seen far away that I want to capture.
Raw provider
Original Translation
Translation check
Quality check
ProxyMan
Official R1 DVD subtitles
Perevodildo
Collectr, Gervaise Macquart