You're going to learn about poverty today.
Here.
And after that, about illness.
Okay.
Let's go.
Is this still the town?
Yes.
There! There! Get this! There!
Hey, why do all these people live in a place like this?
Because they haven't got any other home to live in.
Why haven't they got any other home?
Because they haven't got any work.
Why haven't they got any work?
Because they haven't got any luck.
So without luck, you can't have anything at all?
That's what real poverty is.
Here.
Good, one more bucket!
Okay!
There!
Oh, so you're here?
I used morning glories this time.
Yes, it turned out quite well.
But the district is somewhat lacking in scent now.
Next time, give a thought to jasmine.
It's a quick climber, and it smells good.
Will do.
You're saying I resemble Mr. Mustache?
That is no doubt because we are
both concerned with tending life.
Mustache tends to the lives of plants,
and I tend to the lives of human beings.
There are thousands of kinds of disease,
and only one kind of good health.
Moreover, diseases wear all kinds
of disguises in order not to be recognized.
Finding and chasing those away,
as well as helping people take good care of their health, is our job.
I brought you a friend.
Come and find me later in my office.
Hello.
Who are you?
Tistou.
Dr. Ayling said that your legs won't walk.
Are they better since you've been here?
No, but it doesn't matter
all that much.
Why?
Why? Well...
Because I have nowhere to go anyway.
I have a friend named Gymnastique.
Gymnastique?
It's a pony.
We play together in the garden.
You're lucky. If I had a garden, I might want to get well so I could walk in it.
Aren't you bored here?
Not terribly. I look at the ceiling and count the little cracks in it.
At least, you're not unhappy?
To know that you're unhappy,
you need to have been happy once.
I was born sick.
Everyone here is kind to me.
Dr. Ayling, the nurses, and the doctor who comes to look at my legs
all assure me that I’m going to get well.
But I just look at the ceiling.
At least, it doesn't tell me lies.
What are you doing?
I-I think you're going to get well.
I'm sure of it.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Give my regards
to Gymnastique.
Sure.
What did you learn today, Tistou?
In order to get well, one must want to live.
Doctor, aren't there any pills for giving people hope?
You've found out for yourself
the first thing a doctor must know.
And what's the second thing, Doctor?
Is that to be a good doctor,
you must love your fellow men.
Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
What...
What on Earth is going on here?
When I woke up,
everything around me had bloomed!
Doctor, look, I can move my legs now!
Oh my...
Look, they're moving!
No! It is absolutely unacceptable!
We must pull up all the flowers!
I agree! Anything that defies the rules
cannot be left as it is!
Hear, hear!
Exactly! Those flowers are unnatural!
That's unnatural!
Flowers are suddenly blooming all over the place! This is preposterous!
No, this is certainly abnormal!
Gentlemen, fighting flowers won't do us any good.
Moreover, when the cause is unknown,
fighting flowers can be especially dangerous.
What made those flowers suddenly bloom
all over the place? Not one of us here knows.
You can't predict where flowers might bloom tomorrow, so you want to pull all of them up.
But in reality, we must admit
that these flowers
are doing us more good than harm.
The prisoners are no longer trying to escape.
The slums have prospered.
All the children in the hospital
are getting well.
Let us make use of the flowers wisely.
Instead of trying to undo things,
let us look to the future with optimism.
What are you suggesting?
I am putting forward a daring suggestion.
We must change the name of our town
and call it Mirepoil of the Flowers.
With a name like that,
flowers sprouting everywhere—
even the church steeple transforming
into a cluster of lilacs by tomorrow—
would simply seem
like part of our long-term urban greening plan.
Yes, I like it!
Yeah! I agree!
Mirepoil of the Flowers!
Please have some beautiful flowers
from Mirepoil of the Flowers!
Mirepoil of the Flowers!
Can I have one?
Sure.
Mrs. Mother was worried.
Her Tistou has been silent all day lately.
What are you thinking about, Tistou?
Hey... Please tell me.
I'm just thinking that the world
could be so much better than it is.
Those thoughts are not suitable for your age yet.
Now, why don't you go over there
and play with Gymnastique?
Gymnastique thinks the same.
Don't tell me...
Do you really value your pony's opinion over your parents' advice these days?
It's no laughing matter.
That educational system of yours made Tistou take himself too seriously.
If this keeps up, he'll turn into
an odd, grown-up child.
My Tistou...
Why don't we show him
other animals, then?
Is this what they call a zoo?
Yes, indeed.
I thought zoos are where all kinds of animals live together happily.
Where do these animals come from?
From very far away.
Did anyone ask their permission
to bring them here?
No...
They have no grass or trees in there.
I feel sorry for them.
Oh, so now you're even working
with tropical vegetation, are you?
That's very good indeed.
Those poor wild animals were so bored
because they're far away from their homes.
Anyone would want
to do something for them.
For the past few days,
Mirepoil has been rife with gossip.
And children are always interested
in secretive gossip.
Oh no...
They're about to go to war again.
How very unfortunate.
At this point, a conflict between these two countries appears inevitable.
Next, the local weather forecast...
It looks like they're about to start a war.
Poor people.
Hey, Mr. Mustache.
What do you think about war?
I don't really understand.
I'm against it.
Why?
Why? Well...
Because even a little, unimportant war can annihilate a very big garden.
Annihilate?
It means destroy, abolish, reduce to dust.
And have you actually seen gardens annihilated by war, Mr. Mustache?
Yes, I've seen it happen.
I saw a garden full of flowers die in two minutes.
I saw the greenhouses smashed into a thousand pieces.
And whose garden was it?
It was mine.
Once a war starts,
everyone loses what they value most.
Here it comes!
Okay! Got it!
Man, I have no time to spare.
Mr. Trounadisse,
where is this war happening?
Right here, in the desert between Vazys and Vatens.
Just a desert?
Yes, but there's oil underneath the sand.
And oil is an essential material
for fighting wars.
It seems far away, so the war probably won't come to Mirepoil, right?
Who knows?
Once the war starts, the two parties will ask different great powers for support.
And then the war may engulf the whole planet.
So, in other words,
war's like some appalling sort of crab grass
growing on the face of the globe.
Come to the factory with me.
It'll be an instructive lesson for you.
These cannons are the source of Mirepoil's prosperity.
Where are these cannons going?
That left one is going to the Vazys.
The people of Vazys have been our loyal allies for a long time.
So you'll keep the other one?
No, it's going to Vatens.
Vatens have been our good customer too.
That's business for you.
Something's wrong.
What was that?
I think that your business is wrong.
After all...
The conflict between Vazys and Vatens suddenly extended to Tistou's cheeks.
Lower it!
Well done, my diligent Tistou.
Trying to make up for your failed lesson.
Hello? Mirepoil Star speaking.
You wouldn't believe what happened.
It's a miracle!
Mr. Mustache!
Oh, so you're here?
Tistou, you did a wonderful job.
I have nothing left to teach you.
You already know far more than I do.
You can work much faster too.
Tistou...
Mr. Mustache!
It's wonderful.
I've stopped a war with flowers!
By the way, a bundle of white clover
would not be unwelcome.
It's my favorite breakfast dish, and there seems to be less and less of it in the field.
Try to remember it some time.
So you knew I have green thumbs?
Ruin! Dishonor!
Bankruptcy! Unemployment!
Conspiracy! Sabotage!
Ah, my cannons... My beautiful cannons...
Oh, if I could only find the wretch
who sowed flowers among my guns!
If only we could catch him!
But what if...
it's not the work of a human?
There must be an inquiry.
It's high treason, sir!
I sowed the flowers among the cannons.
The slums and the prison—
that was me too!
The girl with the bad legs—
I gave her flowers!
At the zoo too!
I'm not joking! Look!
There. I've got green thumbs.
Mr. Father was usually a decisive person.
But this time,
he had to think about it for a full week.
I'm concerned about the factory,
but right now, Tistou's future concerns me the most.
Yes...
I followed in my father's footsteps.
And I had hoped that Tistou would also follow in my footsteps.
But it's clear now.
Our son isn't cut out for this job.
Yes. I think so too.
Therefore, I have made a decision.
Let's turn that factory
into a flower factory.
Mirepoil of the Flowers
has truly become a city of flowers.
Use as many flowers as you need!
Make it lovely!
Yes!
Wow, it's beautiful!
Like a chip of sky.
This sunflower is the color of dawn.
And this one contains
all the hundred colors of dusk.
All the flowers here are so beautiful!
It seems my work here is done.
Are you happy now?
Of course. Very happy.
Do you want to live with us
like this forever?
Of course. Why do you suddenly ask such odd questions?
You'll see. Soon enough.
A few mornings later,
a piece of news shook Tistou's house.
Mustache had failed to wake up.
I'm going to see Mr. Mustache.
Mustache has decided to sleep forever.
Can I go see him sleeping?
No, you can't see him anymore.
Mustache's gone on a long, long journey.
But he never said goodbye to me!
You don't go on a journey
while you're asleep.
They're hiding something from me!
Poor Mustache is in the sky now.
He's now happier than we are,
who remain here...
If he's happy, why do you call him "poor"?
Mustache is buried in a cemetery
under the ground.
Under the ground?
But Amelie said he is in the sky.
Mustache is dead.
Mustache died
from old age.
Every life comes to an end like this someday.
I wonder if Mr. Mustache is in the sky?
Or is he under the ground, after all?
Mr. Mustache!
Ah, Mr. Mustache's grave
is in the third row on the right.
Maybe more scented flowers will do the trick.
Gymnastique...
Yes, I know.
"Death is the only sad thing that flowers can't keep from happening."
You've just discovered it.
It's death.
That's why humans are very stupid
to try to kill each other.
They do it all the time, you know.
I'll build a ladder.
This ladder will need to have strong roots.
If Mr. Mustache really is in heaven,
I'm sure he'll come down this ladder.
Even if it's just for a little while.
I have to see Mr. Mustache.
I want to know where he is.
However, Mustache didn't come down.
You're up very early.
I didn't go back to the stable last night.
I see.
I must confess that I've been trying to gnaw through your trees all night,
but the wood is too hard.
My teeth aren't strong enough.
You mean you wanted to cut down my beautiful ladder?
Yes.
Why? Was it to stop me climbing it?
Gymnastique, there's no need to cry.
What are you worried about?
You know I never feel giddy.
I'm only going up and coming down right away, okay?
I must be back in the house before Carolus gets up.
I knew it.
I knew this was bound to happen one day.
I'll bring you a small star as a souvenir.
I'm going now, Gymnastique.
Goodbye.
Wow, it's high!
And the fields all look so green!
I must hold on tight.
It looks just like Mr. Mustache's mustache.
Oh, so you're here?
And with that, Tistou disappeared forever into the invisible world.
Tistou was an angel.
Flowers blossom in the meadow
Stars shine in the sky
Flowers are the little sisters of
The stars in the night sky
We should learn the joy of living
From the flowers
The stars and the flowers
Are the symbols of happiness
Translation &
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Encoding
Perevodildo
Collectr
ImAWasteOfHair
Paul Geromini
Nemesis
WOWmd