Selected by
the Ministry of Education
Commemorative Work for
the World Horticultural Expo '90
Children always want to work for the happiness of all.
Tistou did it through the medium of flowers.
I believe you'll understand from this story.
From the preface of "Tistou of the Green Thumbs" by Maurice Druon
I now baptize you, in the name of
the Father, the Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
You're lovely!
Oh how lovely,
my Tistou.
Tistou
of the Green Thumbs
Based on a book by Maurice Druon
(Academie Française)
Flowers blossom in the meadow
Stars shine in the sky
Flowers are the little sisters of
The stars in the night sky
We should learn the joy of living
From the flowers
The stars and the flowers
Are the symbols of happiness
Tistou. Tistou!
Papa!
Good morning, Grandpa.
Good morning, Tisti.
Good morning.
Oh! Be careful!
Yahoo!
This garden and that mansion
will all be yours.
Strive to become a worthy successor.
Okay.
Good, good.
Whoa!
Master?
Good, good girl.
Come down now.
There we go.
Our horses must always gleam
with cleanliness, like precious jewels.
Okay.
This is your pony. Your very own.
So make sure you treat it well.
My own. My very own!
Really?
Yes, indeed.
I've got a name for you: Gymnastique.
So? Do you like it?
My wonderful Gymnastique
My friend to whom I can talk about anything
He will answer me with magic words
My good pony, Gymnastique
We're going to the ball.
Good night.
The town where Tistou was born was called Mirepoil.
Come on! This way!
Hey! Wait for me!
At first sight, it was like any other town,
yet it was known throughout the world.
It was because Mirepoil was home to the cannon factory owned
by Tistou's father.
You must eat your soup.
Come here, Tistou.
Look there.
How many chimneys are there?
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine.
That factory will be yours someday.
And you will be the master of Mirepoil.
For that, you have to eat well
and grow big.
We can't afford weaklings in our family.
When Tistou turned eight,
he was sent to school.
Before that, his mother used
to educate Tistou herself.
Tistou already knew how to read and write.
In math, he was also able to add,
subtract, and even divide.
7 times 7 is 49.
8 times 8 is 64.
9 times 9...
If you split a swallow in four, will it still fly?
If it has only one wing or one leg,
will it still fly?
Oh, poor swallow split in four
You can still eat a tart
if you cut it into fours
But the swallow cannot fly
if it's cut into fours
Oh, poor...
Tistou!
Yes?
Please repeat what I just said.
If you divide four tarts
by a quarter of the swallow...
That's an F!
All right, two hours have passed.
You can go home.
Okay.
Also, give this letter to your parents.
All right?
Yes.
Unfortunately, studying at school
always made him sleepy.
The school sent Tistou back home.
Hello, Tistou.
"Your son is not quite like the other children.
We cannot keep him here. Principal."
How troublesome.
Not quite like the other children...
What did he mean by that?
I wonder what'll happen to me now.
Indeed, raising our son seems to be more difficult than running a whole factory.
How can you teach anything to a child
who always falls asleep in class?
Being a little too sleepy is preferable
to bronchitis, of course.
Still...
Ah, right, I know of just the way to do this.
It's quite simple, actually.
What do you mean?
We're going to try out an entirely new system of education.
He's not like all the other children, right?
And what is that new system?
He will learn the things he needs to know
by direct observation.
He will learn about stones, gardens, and fields on the spot.
He will learn the management
of the town and factory by example.
That's right. Life itself is
the best school there is.
I love it! It's a wonderful idea.
Why aren't there more schools
with such a delightful educational system?
Listen, from today onward, your teachers will be
Mr. Mustache, the gardener,
and Mr. Trounadisse, the factory manager.
You'll start today with studying the Earth.
The Earth is the origin of everything else.
Ask your teachers to write down their opinions
of how you studied in this notebook.
Not to keep score,
but because we want to understand
the kind of man you are growing up to be.
Okay, you can go now.
Mr. Mustache is waiting for you.
I'll try not to fall asleep.
Excuse me...
Oh, so you're here?
Good morning.
Listen, Tistou.
You fill these flowerpots
with humus from the heap.
Then, you make a hole
in the middle with your thumb.
When you've finished,
arrange the pots along that curb.
Okay.
Once you're done with it,
we'll plant the seeds.
Okay.
Here.
I've finished.
And I'm not one bit sleepy!
Good.
Let's plant the seeds now.
Tistou, do you see what I see?
A flower blooming in this pot?
Yes.
It's unbelievable.
It takes at least two months to grow begonias like these!
But I didn't plant any seeds yet.
It's the truth.
Very mysterious indeed.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong with my fingers?
Something extraordinary
happened to you.
Tistou, you have green thumbs.
But they look pink to me.
Rather dirty at the moment,
but certainly not green.
No, it has nothing to do with the color.
This is a special quality
that the heavens have granted you.
What do you use green thumbs for?
Green thumbs can revive dying flower seeds with their touch.
On rooftops, wedged between stones in a wall,
or buried in the ground, seeds are everywhere,
often perishing without ever blooming into flowers.
Hundreds of millions of such seeds.
But if a green thumb lights on one of them,
wherever it may be, the flower grows at once.
Is that true?
Believe me when I say I envy you.
I still can't believe it.
Oh no, if someone finds out my thumbs
have that kind of power,
they'll say that I'm not like the others again.
There's no shame whatsoever
in being different from others.
But if you're worried, let's keep this a secret between the two of us.
Okay.
"The boy has the makings of a gardener."
As you can see, a town consists of numerous streets,
large buildings, small houses,
and the people who live in them.
What, in your opinion, is the most important thing in a town, Tistou?
The gardens.
Not at all!
The most important thing is order.
Without order, a town, a country,
or an entire society is like chaff in the wind.
Where were your eyes looking, huh?!
You were supposed to let me through!
You got a death wish?!
That's what happens
when we fail to maintain order.
Pay attention!
This is where those who disrupt order are sent: the prison.
Why did they put
those spikes everywhere?
To stop the prisoners from escaping.
If the prison were less ugly,
perhaps they wouldn't try to escape.
What are those people doing?
Taking a break, since it's their recreation hour.
That's their recreation hour?
Then, what must their school hours look like?
I feel sorry for them.
"The boy needs to be watched closely.
He asks too many questions."
That night, Tistou had a scary dream.
Thank goodness it was just a dream.
What can we do?
Tisti, the sun is up.
Mr. Carolus.
Yes? What is it?
No, nothing.
What's the matter?
You need to be calm when you read.
Madam, you won't believe what happened!
The whole town is talking about it!
I give up.
Mr. Mustache.
Oh, so you're here?
Not bad, not bad.
I'd say you made a dazzling debut.
Really? It makes me happy when
even you praise me, Mr. Mustache!
After all, without you, I would never have known I had green thumbs.
That said, you used a bit too much honeysuckle there.
Next time, try to use
more morning glories.
It'll add a note of gaiety.
Okay.
This mysterious event gave the adults a perfect chance to make a fuss.
But can you believe...
Ma'am, when did you find out?
When I woke up in the morning and opened my window, I was so shocked that I fainted!
What can you tell us about it?
How very surprising.
It's a perfectly normal flower.
Following the press came the botanists.
If they discover that I did it,
it's going to lead to a lot of trouble.
Don't you worry.
They don't even know how to pick a nice bunch of flowers, so they'll never find out.
I'll stake my mustache on it.
And just like that,
the commotion continued for a week.
But since they weren't getting anywhere,
everyone had to return home, eventually.
But it was the prisoners
who were the most surprised.
The inside of the prison was nothing like it used to be.
That's right. Nobody considered escaping any longer.
Everyone's soul was transformed...
thanks to the flowers.
Are you busy, Mr. Mustache?
Yeah, it's repotting season.
I see...
But secrets are very difficult things to keep.
When you feel happy,
you want to tell someone about it.
Gymnastique, listen carefully...
but don't tell anyone.
I've discovered a most extraordinary thing.
Flowers prevent evil things
from happening.