Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
An unexpected reunion with Lotte helped Luise
overcome a crisis, through changing places with Lotte again.
But immediately after that, both - Lotte with mother
and Luise with father - retired in the different directions.
Lotte and Luise will remember
this fleeting moment of happiness.
But what's coming to the two now?
Episode 16
Quirk of Fate
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Long time no see, Munich breakfast.
Long time no see, our flat.
And of course...
Long time no see, mom!
Which reminds me, mom last night...
She seemed oh so happy.
With a radiant smile.
The prettiest of moms!
Mom and Editor Bernau seem to be advancing
towards each other by leaps and bounds...
Lotte?
Something happened?
I was just thinking about how mom
was even prettier than usual, last night.
True?
Yes, true.
Wow, glad to hear.
In that case, maybe I should try finding my love,
to start a spring in someone else's soul, too?
I lied!
Don't scare me like that!
Your dad made me realize,
I had my share of men in this life.
Was he really that wicked a person, my dad?
Well I may be exaggerating it a bit,
saying I had my share.
There are wholesome marriages, sure,
but even those seldom coincide with happy marriages.
I will never in my life
need anyone else as long as I have Lotte.
Ah... By Jove, it's so late!
Lotte, you also gotta hurry!
Ah... Wait. Wait!
Lotte, hurry up!
Give me a moment!
Ah... This Luise! My desk is a jumble because of her!
Where might the arithmetic textbook be?
Ah, right, right.
I'll be home late today.
Go ahead and dine without me.
Okay. Work?
Yeah. With Editor-in-chief,
we're putting together a report about the concert.
Frau Annie, if we don't come in now,
the classes would start without us!
I said we're waiting until Lotte comes!
Today, I'm definitely telling her what I think!
We're not letting her put on airs,
just 'cause she can play some lousy piano!
Also, I need to figure out,
how do I make contact with Luise now?
The phone is out of question, right?
Lotte!
What was that?
Picking a fight again?
I bumped into you because I wasn't paying attention.
I'm sorry, Annie.
Exactly! You're the one at fault here!
Look at you - barely learned some piano,
but thinking you're the cream of the crop already!
I am truly sorry.
Pay attention next time!
Pay attention!
Right, right.
I can swear they expected me to start a brawl just now.
Even Annie looked scared at the sight of me!
I swear, Luise, what kind of monster
have you been molding out of me?
Miss Körner.
Yes?
For tonight's event, I got us three tickets just in case.
Feel free to bring Lotte along.
Ah, Lotte?
Personally, Palfy's alleged impeccability in arts
rubs me the wrong way.
But well, there would also be Prosofsky,
said to be number one pianist in the world,
so Lotte might be interested in listening to it, too.
Ah, thank you then.
I see, I might bring Lotte along for his concert.
This can actually do her good -
watching her dad work, even if she doesn't know it's him.
Munich Hotel
Lotte should soon be back from school, I think.
Somehow, I'm sure she'll try to call me then.
Luise, are you ready to go out yet?
No, not yet.
Then, you'd better hurry.
I'll need you to meet Herr Prosofsky,
whom I'm also introducing to musicians today.
Who is that man?
The number one pianist in the world!
At tonight's concert, he is making a guest appearance.
I deemed it necessary to let him listen to your piano.
What do you think? Awed, aren't you?
After all, good ideas are my trademark, yes!
Wait, though...
Might as well go ahead
and ask him to take you as an apprentice.
Exactly! That's what we do.
Oh my, you gotta be kidding!
Lotte!
Yes?
Yes, this is me, Ludwig.
Ah, Frau Irene.
Yes, what is it?
Inviting me and Luise to your place?
Oh? A home party?
Yes, I like it!
Luise is also delighted.
He's talking to Frau Irene.
Lotte's observations were right, after all.
And dad is also willingly playing courteous with her.
Yeah, we'll be looking forward to it!
Then, I'll see you when we're back.
Yes.
Good bye.
Dad.
What is it, Luise?
Say,
the person that just called...
Oh, you mean Frau Irene?
You know her too, don't you?
Do you love her?
Could it be, you're marrying her?
Now, how do I put it...
For your dad, life consists of loving things.
An imposing city street, or beautiful flowers,
then, there are also mountains, seas and even skies.
Without a doubt, pretty women are among those, too.
In the world such as ours, all the art is born
from either loving someone, or being loved.
Surely, when you grow up,
you'll also give your love to great many things.
That's not what I meant!
Ah, you were asking about the marriage?
Alas, I've had my share of marriage.
Had your share?
At the very least, for the moment,
I don't need anyone else's love, as long as I have my Luise.
But well, I guess I'll have to reconsider,
once you find someone you love yourself.
I'll answer it!
Yes, this is Luise Palfy.
Ah! Luise, it's me!
Lo—
Oh, I'm so glad!
I was afraid you won't be able to answer.
Lotte?
Mom!
Mom?
Ah, wrong number!
They just apologized.
Mom? You said you'd be late today.
I came to pick you up.
Pick me up?
Turns out, when buying tickets for tonight's concert,
our Editor-in-chief also took you in account.
Tonight's concert?
Big concert of the Munich Symphony Orchestra.
The guest tonight is the world's number one pianist,
so it would only be beneficial for you to listen to.
Now, the taxi is waiting for us. Presto, presto!
Okay.
Mom is going to attend dad's concert...
And she brings me along.
I wonder, in what feelings mom is going there?
What feelings?
A majestic sunset.
The sunset. It's absolutely majestic.
You're right!
After that, I never had a chance to call Lotte again.
We finally meet after such a long time,
and yet we've not even a moment to sit down and talk.
Yes?
Luise, the car is here to pick us up.
Okay!
Ah, Herr Chauffeur.
Could you make a short stop
at the gates of that hotel?
Ah! That's the hotel where dad is staying!
What for, mom?
A critic from France had arrived,
so I need to hand him over the manuscript originals.
I hope it all goes well.
Luise might come out at any moment!
Luise, sure you didn't forget nothing?
Wait! The score, the score!
Thank you.
Excuse me, I am Körner
from the Munich Graph magazine.
I can't help wondering,
what may Lotte be up to now?
Luise! Need to hide!
Lotte and mom... here, of all places!
Take care.
Dad!
Forgot something, after all!
Really? Even as I told you to make sure!
My bad. I'll go get it in a moment.
You just wait for me in the car.
Thanks a lot.
Okay, Lotte, I'll be back in a minute.
Wait here for me, will you?
Yeah. Take your time.
Let me help you.
Lot—
Hey, hey, don't you think,
mom might have a thing for Editor Bernau?
And our Editor also
seems to be rather fond of mom.
They say, women that are in love
can even become prettier, without realizing it.
And mom last night looked the most radiant!
Well, maybe it was
because she knew dad is in Munich, too!
That would have been fine by me.
Think they're considering a marriage?
This doesn't seem likely.
After all, she said she had her share of marriage.
Huh?
Dad put it in those exact words, too!
So there's no hope at all...
Since both are so resentful
of their previous marriage experience.
Artists are whimsical beings.
Refusing to put up with it,
mom went on to pursue her own way of life.
There's more to it than meets the eye.
Life is not making it easy for us...
But at least, dad said,
he doesn't need anyone else's love, as long he has me.
Mom said it, too!
Just loving me is more than enough for her.
Then, at least we know, that for the moment,
they both don't have a special someone.
Yeah!
At any rate, both for mom...
And for dad, we need to keep an eager eye
so that they don't end up on a slippery slope.
Yeah!
Until we know for sure
how dad and mom actually feel about it...
...The fact we two ever met
should be kept a secret at any cost.
Do your best.
We'll do our best together.
Ah! Mom!
Well, I'll go with mom then.
Luise, no! I'm the one going with mom now!
Ah, right.
I'll call you again tomorrow.
Mom!
Ah, sorry I made you wait.
Now, shall we go?
Now that I think of it,
where might Lotte be heading to now?
My, we'll be late, Luise.
What's taking you so long?
Look, Editor. The interviews we need to take
are with Herr Prosofsky and with Palfy.
Well, about that...
I wonder if that'll be enough.
Still, I'd never think I'll get to attend
dad's concert, looking like this.
Right!
What are the chances Luise is also around?
Ah, and we could include a photo in this one.
Then, the other photos...
Of course, I hope for some good answers,
but just getting them to speak would be a feat already.
Right, right.
But that's exactly the kind of thing
you've acquired such a knack for.
I'm pinning my hopes on you.
Even thought I know
they're merely talking about the work...
Then, I guess, I'll go take my seat
in the auditorium now.
Yeah. Your seat would be
the third in the A section on the second floor.
Don't let Herr Prometheus overshadow you.
It's "Prosofsky."
Well, I'll be trying my utmost either way!
See you!
Ah, when it's over,
we'll go get something delicious to eat.
Okay!
Section A, seat three...
There! Found it.
Lotte...
How come you all are also here?
Luise...
Don't tell me this is your seat...
What else do you call this,
if not an ironic quirk of fate?
Four people - the entire family
ended up together in a place like this.
Will they prevent this
from escalating into a kerfuffle?
With bated breath, I pray that Lotte and Luise
are spared the woeful fate.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode
Hey, Lotte, something really bad happened!
What is it?
We happened to be sitting
next to each other on the concert!
Eh? No way!
This is a disaster! After all,
mom and Editor-in-chief are also here!
But there's more. There's more to it!
The worst thing of all -
Annie is sitting to the other side of me!
Oh no! What do we do, Luise?
We're screwed!
Totally done for!
Next time in I and Myself:
Munich in an Uproar!
Episode 17
Don't miss it!