Because of the commotion
that Lotte and Luise inadvertently caused,
dad's grand concert
was reduced to shambles.
In the wake of that, mom is seriously considering
marrying for the second time, possibly her boss.
Just as they had escaped one quandary,
yet another, bigger problem is on their hands already.
Episode 18
Dad and Mom Meet Again
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
I wonder if mom really set her mind on marriage.
One would think,
"Well, Herr Editor is a good man."
And I quite like him, too.
But we have a dad of our own!
We don't need anyone else but our dad!
It's cold tonight.
Thank you.
At this rate, mom can really
marry her Editor-in-chief...
There has to be something we can do
to make dad and mom start getting along again.
And yet, what can we do?
That - I'd like to know myself.
One way or another, it seems, ever since they day they parted,
they haven't talked to each other, not once!
If they would have at least talked today...
I know! We make them talk, instead!
You think they can reconcile, then?
Come one, we gotta try, Lotte.
We'll take it in our own hands
and make dad and mom meet when they least expect!
Please make it work this time.
This is bad!
I overslept beyond possible!
Good morning, Lotte.
Why didn't you even try to wake me up sooner?
Good morning.
But you came home so late last night!
You looked like you need plenty of rest.
Really? Thanks, then.
I hope I wasn't too much of a nuisance
to Editor last night...
He had to spend an entire evening
listening to my endless quibbling.
You'd never tell he can actually be that attentive, too.
So you love him, after all? Our Herr Editor.
Huh...
What's this?
Well... A letter had come.
From who?
That, I don't know. But this morning,
I found it slipped into under our door.
"Let's lunch together today.
I'll be waiting at Don Giovanni restaurant at two o'clock?"
What's this thing?
Who would make such a joke?
But it shouldn't be a joke.
Probably, some terrific person sent it.
I mean, he knows Don Giovanni
is mom's stamping ground!
Well, it's true...
Please-please, mom.
Go to Don Giovanni today!
Can you do it?
Good morning, dad.
Ah, Luise? Good morning.
You don't feel well?
My last night's concert
was turned into a trainwreck.
As you'd expect, my head
is still quite heavy this morning.
Ah, well...
A letter had arrived.
From who?
Don't know. There's no return address.
"I wish to have a lunch with you.
At two o'clock, come to Don Giovanni's.
I'll be waiting for you at the third table.
I still wish to surprise you,
so I shall keep my name a secret..?"
What's the matter, dad?
You'd need to come up with a better ruse to trick me.
Because as of now, it's as plain as the nose on your face,
just who would such a thing.
But...
This is Irene Gerlach's prank.
By appearing in Munich when I least expect,
she plans to catch me completely by surprise.
That sounds just like something she'd do.
Well, either way, you'll go there, right?
My, oh, my.
It doesn't sound like she's giving me a choice.
Right, like this.
Well, I'm off, Lotte.
I hope I'm not getting lectured for coming this late.
Mom... Mom!
This was in the living room.
Ah, Editor must have forgotten it last night.
He's so careless sometimes!
I'll be sure to return it.
Which reminds me...
The man who wrote that letter -
you know him quite well, don't you?
Eh? No! I mean...
Fine, then. Tell him I'll be there,
at Don Giovanni's.
I look forward to meeting whoever it is.
Really?
At two, remember?
Sure, sure. The third table, right?
Then, I'm gone.
Last night...
Was I too rash?
Oh? Then, Editor, have you ever considered
getting married yourself?
Most naturally.
I had no idea.
Who could she be?
That...
For instance, Miss Körner,
that could be you.
Don't you ever think about entering a marriage?
I'm dreading the moment
when I have to see Miss Körner today.
An article about Herr Palfy?
Need to cover last night's concert.
I've heard about it, too.
The way it got ruined was a sight to behold...
Yeah. To see the concert destroyed so spectacularly
is a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
Maybe that'll serve to bring him
down a peg or two.
Ah, good morning,
much obliged for the yesterday.
No, it's nothing...
Here. Forgot something, didn't you?
Right...
Editor-in-Chief, what is it?
Well...
We might need to discuss something...
Discuss?
No, not quite...
How about we meet for a lunch?
I knew it!
Yeah, sounds delightful.
I will gladly join you at Don Giovanni's, at two today.
At two, at Don Giovanni's?
Yeah. Third table, isn't that right?
I remember!
Third table, then...
He came. Dad's here!
So far, everything is according to plan.
It's almost two o'clock.
Just need to wait for mom.
Oh, I see!
Don't hold back, Annie.
Be it a lamb, or a veal,
anything you like - I'll get it for you!
And for dessert, you can get
as much plum pudding as you want!
Super!
Those two are here, too!
Screwed!
A reservation for the third table...
We were waiting for you.
This way, please.
Ah... Thank you.
Huh? Isn't that the guy who was swinging the stick
at the last night's concert?
Yeah! Something like Rudo...
It was Ludwig Palfy!
Right, right.
That dope Palfy.
He has the nerve to show up here
after bungling a concert so miserably!
Not a hint of shame!
Luise!
I won't tolerate that slander!
Not now!
Someone is waiting for me at the third table.
Understood. This way, please.
Why?
How come?
Welcome, your table is over there.
Isn't it... Herr Palfy?
Do I know you from somewhere?
I'm sorry, but I don't recognize your face.
Did someone invite you to wait at this table as well?
Yeah...
At this third table.
How peculiar...
Who in the world might be behind this?
Hey, boy! Come here.
We didn't mix things up at some point, did we?
No clue!
But we're in trouble now.
Mom is also coming!
Must be someone special to you,
the woman you're waiting for.
Well...
I may have given her some trouble last night,
so I'm apologizing with a present.
I'd wager, she is very pretty.
Do you intend to marry her, too?
No, that's not...
We still have a rather long way to go.
It doesn't take a clairvoyant to know -
you're poised to propose to someone.
Yes, marriage sure is a nice thing.
Moreover, if your beloved one is just as honest a person
as you are, you'll be certain to have a happy marriage.
You think so?
That's interesting.
Why...
Dear guest, on your request, we have prepared
another table for your own rendezvous.
Ah, thank you.
Still, I'd like to stay here for a bit more.
At least until I get a chance to take a quick glance
at the world's happiest woman today.
Could you be talking about the woman over there?
Long time no see.
Yeah... Quite some time.
You two know each other?
I can't believe it was you all along.
That's right.
Why would Editor go to the trouble of writing a letter?
I see.
The letter didn't actually come from Frau Irene.
Why are you playing innocent now?
What's the point after coming this far?
That's what I should be asking!
Making me come all the way to here...
No! I would never...
Save your breath!
I know you did it to make me listen
to this man's vaunting about his love.
Vaunting about love?
You're the one playing innocent here!
Frau Körner!
You're at it again!
Herr Habersetzer...
Oh? It appears, this place is swarming
with the invitees of yours.
My, my, isn't that Herr Palfy himself?
May I express my admiration for your concert last night?
That was some of the finest cacophony I've ever heard!
Now it's clear to me. From all sides,
I'm besieged by the pawns in your scheme.
That's why you invited me here - intending to make fun of,
to affront in the most insulting manner!
I've had enough!
Why...
I swear, do they really call him
Palfy, the great musician?
Yes, so far, I'm utterly disappointed with him.
You've got to be joking...
With a head as dense as yours,
appreciating his music is unachievable even in a lifetime!
It was an unforeseen trouble,
that made his concert go wrack and ruin!
His music is only born out of genuine kindness!
Nobody but me is destined to ever truly understand it!
"Nobody but me?"
Miss Körner?
No clue what's this all about,
but our lunch is ruined!
I'll file a complaint!
Ah! Daddy!
Mom's manuscript!
"Even though his last concert
had ended in such a grand-scale fiasco,
the inhabitants of the Earth
will soon let it fade into oblivion.
After all, it's still Herr Ludwig Palfy
who they call the best musician of our time."
I may have said too much earlier.
After all, I know perfectly well, you're not the kind of woman
who'd ever be so gravely vindictive.
He doesn't seem like a half-bad guy either,
your new man.
I believe, you're a really good match.
Fare thee well.
To you as well...
"Whenever you listen to it,
his music is capable of evoking
this ever-changing love,
that usually just lies dormant in our chests."
Just like that!
Even to this day, mom still remembers dad
with such warm feelings!
Dad, too, probably only got so worked up
because jealousy was searing him!
This means, they can start getting along again!
Hey, Lotte, it's been some while
since the last time we swapped.
I'd really like to stay with dad for a little longer.
I also feel that there's a hundred and one thing
I still need to discuss with mom.
Still, it's saddening
that Munich and Vienna are so far apart.
We'll definitely meet again!
Definitely.
The train is leaving soon.
Hurry up to join dad.
Please look after mom.
I'll write you a letter soon.
Bye.
"It'll be quite a while
before I get to see dad and Lotte again" -
in Luise's chest, the feeling of loneliness
was on the rise again.
At the same time, Lotte
was experiencing the exact same thing.
This time, however, the two part,
firmly resolved to set their sights on an even higher peak.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Luise, I was anxious to know
how dad actually feels about mom,
I went to atelier to check!
And then?
The glass frame that mom's photo was stored in, was now...
Don't tell me it was broken!
I think, could it be that dad
had come to hate mom now?!
You're overthinking again! Cheer up, Lotte.
Next time, in I and Myself:
Dad Doesn't Know Himself!?
Episode 19
We Can't Understand Dad!?
Look forward to it!