Upon discovering that her mom
had never forgotten her, Luise
was on the verge of shouting "Mom, Luise is right here!"
from the bottom of her lungs.
However, Luise wouldn't break her promise to Lotte.
Not of her own accord, at least.
Episode 10
Birth of a Genius Pianist
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Luise, we've been invited
to give an opera performance in Berlin.
I will be away for about a month.
If you need help with something while I'm away,
feel free to consult with Doctor Strobl. Deal?
Yes.
You can leave with an easy heart, Herr Palfy.
I'm also going to come by every now and then,
to make sure the girl is doing well.
Oh... In that case, please let me bring you
some dazzling souvenir as a "Thank you."
Well, I can but to look forward to it.
What's the matter, Luise?
Won't you give me a chock-full list of souvenirs
you want me to bring back this time?
A list?
Rather than souvenirs,
I'd like you back soon and in good health.
Oh, Luise! Those words stem
from the genuine goodwill.
To return to you possibly sooner
and in good health is my wish, too.
As soon as we finish performing,
I'll take a plane to fly back to you!
Maria Therese.
Some say she has the world's number one soprano voice.
World's number one in putting on airs, too.
I hope they hold contests in that.
As luck would have it, I have reasons to think
you will conduct her performance, as well.
Well, we'll see what comes out of it.
Luise, I'll be back soon!
Please do, dad!
In good health!
Impressive!
Yeah, he's darn good!
Wow! Amazing.
Thank you very much.
Much obliged.
Thank you very much. Thanks.
Here.
Hold there, little one.
You don't have to pay.
How come?
Not accepting money from those younger than me
is one of my policies.
But I also had a lot of fun,
on the same level as all the grown-ups.
So I should pay up.
Besides, our household budget
easily allows for that.
Household budget?
Yeah. I should still have enough here to buy meat,
vegetables and bread from the market on my way home.
Then, wouldn't it be better to use this money
to return home with a bigger piece of meat instead,
Frau Little Housekeeper?
But how?! How do you know?
Did we... meet before in Munich?
Munich, huh?
I considered visiting it at least once.
They say, street performers there always eat their fill.
Eh? But why, then,
would you call me a little housekeeper?
Well, you said you're managing
your household budget and doing groceries.
And that's something housekeepers do.
That's all?
Don't you mean to say
you're working as an actual housekeeper in your age?
Of course not!
That's what I'm saying!
They call me Hans of the Winds.
Nice to meet you.
Hans of the Winds?
Because it sickens me to reside in just one place,
I'm always on the road, just like the wind.
Born as Hans Stefan.
And I'm Lotte.
Luise Palfy.
Palfy?
Any chance you're a daughter of Ludwig Palfy?
Oh, that's straight-up silly!
Why so?
Well, imagine - a daughter of a famous conductor
and composer hanging out with me just like that!
Or is it..?
I mean, as a fellow musician,
I hold Herr Palfy in highest esteem!
If you happen to actually be his daughter,
would you, by any chance,
let me see his atelier just for a second?
Oh, I can't do that!
To my dad, his atelier is a sacred ground.
Hey, I'm begging you!
Just for a second or two, to breathe the same air,
same scent as the great master would be enough for me!
Even if you're asking so earnestly...
I could let you take a peek.
I'm in luck!
Herr concierge, good morning.
Hey, Fraulein Luise. Good morning.
This here is my friend,
his name is Hans.
Good morning.
Likewise. Good morning.
Well, here it is.
Is this...
Is this Herr Palfy's atelier?
And here is where Herr Palfy
sits while composing?
This is a first-class piano!
I bet, it sounds wonderful, too.
Hans, you play piano?
Yeah. Just a bit.
Want to try?
Why, of course... Ah...
No, I'm good.
I should be sufficiently content
just being let into Herr Palfy's atelier.
I don't mind, try it.
You gotta be kidding!
To have me, some street performer, play this...
Seriously serious?
Most seriously serious.
But for me, to play this piano...
I get to play a real piano...
You're good, Hans.
Bungled the last part.
It's been a while since I last played it.
For a first performance in a while,
this sounded amazing!
Luise, I'd rather listen to you doing it, now.
Eh? Me?
You can play, right?
Just... not now.
Not now? Why so?
I'd like to, but at the moment, I'm my other self -
Luise who can't play the piano.
That's a pity.
Pity?
When you got a piano that exceptional,
and you got the teaching from your dad who is a composer,
refusing to play it for someone is a real waste!
If I were you, I'd be playing it for days on end,
to be perfectly honest!
I wish I could play it, too. However...
Thank you.
It was my pleasure.
Now, then.
I need to make some more coin today.
Hans...
Yes?
Dad would be away for about a month.
Until then, feel free to come play piano anytime!
For real?
Man, that's a godsend!
By then, I hope Luise lets me hear her play, too!
Now I'm convinced!
Mom's cooking is better every time!
Just letting you know,
flattery won't help increasing your allowance.
Saw it right through!
Still, mom, you should let me
do the cooking sometimes, too.
Don't you get so hung up on it.
You need to let go of your sense of duty sometimes,
spending time in leisure.
I would only resort to asking you for help
when I'm too busy myself, okay?
Ah! The phone.
I'll answer it.
Could it be a call from Lotte again?
Hello?
Lotte Körner listening.
Hey, Lotte.
A thorn in your mom's side is calling.
Editor-in-Chief Bernau!
I'm giving you mom right now.
Here.
Hello? This is me.
Recent development of things suggests
making next month's issue an opera-focused special.
In three days, I want you
to go to Berlin for the field work.
Need you to interview
Maria Therese and Ludwig Palfy.
I know you have to take care of Lotte,
but we really have nobody else that suited for the job.
Sorry I'm having to bother you for this.
Very well.
I don't see why I shouldn't be able to do it.
Whew, you're a saver.
I'll book two tickets, then.
I'm coming as a moral support, too. See you.
Yes. Understood.
So sorry, Lotte.
It seems, I'll be away for some time
due to a work assignment.
You can leave with an easy heart!
I hope you do your best
during that assignment.
Thank you.
What's the matter with Hans?
He never came today.
Good evening, and pardon the intrusion.
Ah... But who might the Frau be?
Eh? What... What's all of this? Eh!
Oh my goodness,
what's this sumptuous feast?
Well, little Luise. As you can see,
I'm not taking a promise I made to your father lightly.
Fraulein, you know the Frau?
She's a friend of dad's.
Master's friend?
This dinner has been prepared for Fraulein Luise
by my best cook on my request.
But a dinner for Fraulein
is something I can handle myself.
Well, aren't you happy
to be relieved of your duties tonight?
We have included your share, as well.
Eh? Included my share? My, my!
That is the most welcomed favor, then!
Well then, Luise. I will come again
with another one of those in a matter of few days.
I hope you look forward to it.
Take care! We would be happy
to see you on our doorstep again!
Fraulein, let's get to eating right away!
I don't feel like it.
Resi, you can have it all to yourself.
Would you really let me
eat all of that myself?
Yes, go ahead.
Just heavenly!
Of course, Master's friend is a noble person!
Can't believe Hans is not coming today either.
Peperl!
Can't you find Hans with your nose?
Hans!
Here you are.
Say, Hans, why didn't you
come over to play the piano again?
You see, after I played it once,
I've come to realize one thing.
Which one?
In the end, I won't be able
to part with this fellow.
Ever since I was small, I was toiling as a bootblack,
saving some coin day by day, until finally, I could buy this.
Ever since then, he is a friend of mine.
Now we do everything together, even sleep!
Noble! Becoming friends with your instrument.
Thank you.
But that's also why I won't be able to dump this friend
to replace him with a piano.
I know, one day, us two
will be playing on the stages of the world, too!
On the very same ones as your dad.
I know, for Hans, it's doable! Certainly!
You really think so?
They say, the key to music
is being passionate about it!
If I'm passionate enough about it,
nobody can stop me.
Mozart, Beethoven, Strauss -
the great composers of the past,
all raised by Vienna.
One day, I might stand alongside them!
I believe in you, Hans.
Call me somehow odd,
but I'm the one who's envious here.
Luise, I can never be sure
which exact approach would work for you.
But as long as you like it,
you should keep playing.
And then, the piano will become your friend, too.
Hans...
Well... See you around, Luise!
Berlin performance cancelled?
Sudden illness?
Or did someone get in an accident?
That'd be petty, compared to reality.
Palfy and Maria Therese seem to have had a beef.
Indignant, she threw a tantrum and left.
Ah, which means, Palfy is to bear the blame?
So it would seem.
Palfy is playing an important part of a conductor,
so getting along with Maria Therese is among his duties.
But isn't this duty mutual, for Maria Therese as well?
Her snobbishness makes up half of her fame by now.
Do you happen to be a fan of Palfy?
Quite the opposite!
I find him rather sickening.
But I will always keep saying that conflicts
should be judged from a position of impartiality.
If you excuse me.
Maria Therese, someone has to teach you some tact!
How can you be so snot-nosed?
To be taken seriously as an artist,
you learn some modesty first!
Well, at the very least, I get to return home so soon.
Can you even imagine Luise's rapture when she finds out?
I cannot tell for certain,
which approach would work for you.
But as long as you like it,
you should keep playing.
Hello, Herr Palfy!
Young Fraulein is also here.
Oh, that's highly convenient.
Need a hand with this luggage?
Ah? No, no, I'm good.
Take care, then.
Who could that be?
Did Luise bring along some friend?
Ah... Keep going!
Okay...
Right, very soothing.
The warmth channeled straight into your heart.
Whoa! Bravo! Bravo!
Dad, I...
You were practicing in secret, didn't you?
Not just that, even without my teaching,
you managed to become that good!
"When a child is a genius..." No,
"Exactly because the child is this way!"
The change that the summer camp
caused in Luise is miraculous!
It emancipates the mind, makes a new, better self out of you,
both as an artist and as a human!
Then, you don't mind me
playing piano from now on, too?
Not for the life of it.
After all, you're daddy's dear girl.
Dad!
"I am daddy's dear girl."
This little thought, seemingly so obvious
had only now been grasped by Lotte.
The delight of just being able to keep playing the piano,
was soon to be displaced by an even greater joy.
But for now, in her little heart, Lotte is merely praying
for this moment of happiness to last forever.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode preview
We switched places!
Lotte, I had this thought haunting me lately.
Why did our dad and mom break up?
Eh? I've also been thinking the exact same thing!
Really? Then, there's a quick solution.
What do you mean, Luise?
The reason for dad and mom's break-up -
we'll find it out ourselves! We'll become detectives.
You mean we'll interrogate them two?
Exactly. We'll get the answer out of them!
Next time in I and Myself:
Little Detective Agency. Don't miss it!
Episode 11
Little Detective Agency