After realizing they are actually blood-related twins,
Luise and Lotte became so close,
as to the point of their hearts beating in unison.
"I wish to meet my dad."
"I want to meet my mom."
The result has been a plan
of unthinkable magnitude.
Luise as Lotte, and Lotte as Luise -
they will swap places to this way return home.
Episode 4
Onset of the Operation
Translation: Perevodildo    |    Timings: Sub-RoRo
Ready, Lotte?
What a waste.
Took a lot of effort to make this photo.
But keeping it would mean
risking to blow the gaff.
Before long, we'll be able to take a new one,
even better picture. I promise!
How should we stay in touch?
I guess we'll have to stick to letters.
A General Delivery would do.
Every day, on our way home from school
we'll be checking if there's any post for us.
But for how long?
How about we start with one month?
After one month, we'll arrange a rendezvous
to decide our further course of action.
I hope, by then we know enough
to unravel the mystery of their parting.
Stephie...
Poor little soul Stephie.
Let's show her our support.
Good morning, Stephie.
Good morning.
Good morning, Luise, Lotte.
Cheer up, girl!
Exactly! Gloom is unbecoming of a girl.
At a time like this,
easier said than done.
But still, my soul is empty,
and somehow, my belly, too.
You probably think I'm weird.
Nothing of the kind.
However, overeating is also insalubrious.
My, would you look at who is being admonitory!
I remember, when I first arrived here,
someone was so mad, she was eating until she bursts.
But I wasn't really eating to the point of bursting!
Not eating! It was gobbling so vigorous,
I thought you'd swallow the spoon, too!
Even the memory of it is still amusing!
That's the point.
Still think you're weird?
But come on!
You both suddenly felt unwell
and want a leave from swimming?
Yes.
Well, I guess your mental link is strong.
Very well, you can spend this afternoon
getting a good rest in the room.
Okay!
Are you sure it's okay?
They are clearly feigning it.
Those girls only have one week left
before they have to part ways again.
You've no idea how much those two
need to talk over in that short a time.
In that case...
You shouldn't be entering the water so suddenly!
You need to warm up first!
Everyone is away.
Now, let's get to learning.
Here's the layout of the house.
Make sure to remember it really well.
You can trust our servant Resi
to tend to all the housekeeping work.
But you should always be on the alert with her.
Why so?
Resi is a big fat liar.
What she says and what she does
are two different things.
And dad still hasn't noticed?
Men are some very oblivious creatures.
I'll keep that in mind.
But still, this looks like a spacious and gorgeous house.
Oh, but where's the dad's working office?
His atelier is elsewhere.
He rents a room along Kärntner Ring​
expressly for that purpose.
Let me show you the way. You start on Rotenturmstraße,
pass by St. Stephen's Cathedral,
after passing by the Opera House, you turn left
and find yourself on Kärntner Ring.
That's where his apartment is located.
Mom works for an illustrated magazine
"Munich Graph."
Their phone number is highlighted in the list
right next to the phone.
Her Editor-in-chief is Doctor Bernau.
A very hearty old chap.
But you can only ever call him
when it's a matter of life and death!
Doctor Bernau, right.
Mom works as an Editor there.
She chooses topics, sorts out photos
and even writes articles.
Chief puts an infinite confidence in our mom.
That's why she is always so busy.
Amazing. I'm so delighted.
My mom is that capable a person!
Be mindful, though. There are times when I'm the one
having to act momly towards her,
like whenever mom throws a tantrum!
For real? How peculiar!
When this happens, it means she is very tired,
so you should react in the most caring manner.
She'll get better after just one night's sleep.
Uh-huh. Got it. Not letting you down!
I'm starting! Get it!
Come, this will also be on the test.
Hey, can we join, too?
Really? Don't you two have something better to do,
like jawjawing to one another?
Christine is at it again, like a broken record.
Come on, let them join!
Right, let them.
As long as everyone else is okay with it.
It'll all good, come on in!
Thanks.
Alright, everyone. You ready?
I'm going in! Monica!
My! Of course I couldn't catch it.
It was Luise's ball.
Impressive! No way I will ever be able
to throw that strong a ball!
There!
Lotte is a complete bungler in sports!
I'll also have a hard time pretending to be that weak.
Doing the cooking? Me?
That's right.
Don't tell me, cleaning and laundry, too?
Naturally! There's no housekeeping duty
out of your reach.
That's what mom calls me
her little housekeeper for!
You can't be serious. No way I do that!
I don't even know how to turn on the gas properly!
You don't?
Told you. For that, we always had Resi, the servant.
Then, see it as an opportunity
to learn some new skill for the future.
Put that in the memo.
Can't believe it's actually a thing.
Mom's favorite dish
is beef soup with macaroni.
Beef - you buy that from Huber's.
Get half a pound of filet with a lot of marbling.
Huber, family butcher, corner of Max Emanuel Street
and Prince Eugene Street.
...corner of Prince Eugene Street.
The cook book is in the kitchen cupboard drawer.
That book has in it all the recipes I know.
...kitchen cupboard drawer.
Even if Lotte could do something,
doesn't mean I'll ever be able to repeat it.
No excuses! You do everything to the letter.
Won't make a convincing me otherwise.
Hey, even if I bungle it, I can just say
I've forgotten how to do it while I was away for vacation.
Would do for a plan B.
After all, if things go wrong, you can write me at once.
Omelette...
Your favorite dish is omelette?
Whenever we eat at the Imperial Hotel,
I always ask for multiple refills.
Dad's always so pleased when I eat a lot.
Multiple refills?
The very thought of eating that slimy omelette
makes my stomach turn over.
Could I get away with only eating one?
You will eat it!
Won't make a convincing me otherwise.
But I suppose, if you eat four or five refills
of omelette on the very first day,
you could say you've had enough omelette
to last you the rest of your life.
Impossible!
Just why does summer vacation
have to come to an end so soon?
Already on the day after tomorrow,
it would be time to go home.
Even after I've made so much good friends here...
And I'm looking forward
to returning to Vienna, because...
...you can't live without mama!
Ah! Truda, how coarse!
Sorry, sorry, Monica.
I'd really just prefer
to stay here for the rest of my life.
But the life never stands still.
Cheer up. And dive headlong into your new life.
Your happiness is our concern, too, Stephie.
Thank you. I perked up.
People! News, news!
A big package arrived!
A package?
Farewell party gifts
from Brigitte's dad!
A surfeit of big boxes with toys!
Also a lot of lanterns, streamers, and the like!
Great!
Tomorrow evening,
we'll have a farewell party!
With a lottery to distribute the presents!
First prize is roller skates!
Let's take a look!
Luise, Lotte, I'm going, too!
A farewell party.
Just what we need, right?
Let's put it to try.
If nobody notices, it's a complete success.
We'll make the party a dress rehearsal,
before returning home this way.
Okay?
Braiding your hair isn't easy.
You'll get used to it,
after doing it every morning.
On my part, it's the ordeal of adjusting my character...
Hey, Lotte, this countenance is nothing like me.
Really? But you have it all the time,
you just never notice it.
Eh? I don't think so.
Look at it!
Let me introduce myself: Lotte Körner.
Nice to meet you.
And I am Luise Palfy. Hey, you!
A Munich girl who thinks she is the cat's whiskers!
Was it out of character?
Not at all. Bull's eye!
It just feels so peculiar
to be watching myself from the side.
But I actually quite like
that exemplary candor of yours.
Yet if I'm not cautious,
I might casually let slip what's on my mind.
Starting today, we're to swap places
along with our whole lives.
Our names, our belongings,
our homes and friends - everything!
Oh, I know!
This apron - I got two of them,
so I'll take one with me.
I'll tell dad it's a souvenir from a friend.
It's the same I was borrowing the other day!
Mom bought those
for my birthday last year.
From Oberpollinger's.
A department store on Neuhauserstraße.
Next to Karlstor.
Right, it is my most treasured memento.
As well as mine.
Don't give up.
We can do it.
I sure am going to miss you all after today.
But at least tonight's farewell party spells fun.
That's right. As soon as we finish the breakfast,
we need to start preparing.
I wonder who's going to win the roller skates.
If you show a thing you want it real bad,
you shoo away the luck.
You think so?
Truda, hold the ladder for me, will you?
Okay.
Counselor, let me help you with this.
Luise? Right, I could use your help.
Climbing on trees is not my thing.
Now, Truda. Let's help the others now.
Okay.
Luise, be careful, will you?
Sure!
That's a good start.
Nobody has got a clue.
So far, being you just means being reckless.
Don't you know I'm just as afraid of the height
as Fraulein Ulrica is?
My knees are shaking like crazy.
Breathtaking!
It's like a dream come true!
Remember - all of that my papa sent to us!
He runs a department store.
If there's something I like among papa's goods,
I can get it in a snap of a finger!
You're so lucky!
Ah, Brigitte. Not even Munich girls
have been spared her bragging.
But hey, at least Brigitte has one redeeming feature,
which is her generous papa.
You can say that again!
Lotte, come join us.
This Punsch is delicious.
Coming!
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's really good!
Nina, did you put any alcohol in it?
Of course not!
It's a drink for children.
Somehow, it's strangely intoxicating.
I'm feeling so much livelier!
Hey, Luise, are you doing it this year, too?
Huh? Doing what?
Why, this thing we did last year!
Wasn't it fun?
Oh no, I forgot to tell her.
Excuse me?
What are you talking about?
My, what's wrong with you?
Have you forgotten already?
Ah! You mean this thing?
I decided to stop,
we're not children anymore.
Good thinking, Lotte.
What? What was it, Luise?
What did you do last time?
A magnum opus! She brought in some fireworks
and set them on fire right behind the counselors!
They soared up with a whoosh!
Fraulein Ulrica was so scared,
she shrieked and fell off her chair!
Eh? That much?
Such a pity I had to leave for home early last year!
Staying for a day longer
was worth that kind of show.
Everyone, we're starting to draw the numbers!
Please come closer.
Okay!
They are my favorite!
Such roller skates are all the rage these days!
I was born to win them today!
First set - an eraser and a pencil.
Seven sets in total.
Here, person with a number 33.
Eh?! Me? Out in the very first round...
See? What did I tell you before?
Next, person with number 18.
Oh no! Now it's me.
Next are 10, 5, 29, 11, 3, 15, 35...
Four letter sets - 32, 4, 13, 7.
It's me!
And me!
I'm so glad!
We'll write a million of letters!
Thank you.
You have become so close,
even the fate now binds you two together.
Okay! The first prize, roller skates
go to number 23!
Who has number 23?
Didn't you have that number?
I got my prize already.
Me too.
Maybe it's a mistake?
How odd. Did we forget to give someone number 23?
Number 23, congratulations.
They're all yours, Stephie.
Ehh. You couldn't have chosen a winner more unfit
for something requiring a physical exercise.
You can't be saying things like that.
Oh well.
When papa and mama
are breaking up behind her back,
this would at least provide some distraction
so I guess it's a fitting prize.
Christine!
Luise is doing it again...
I didn't want to slap you, but...
But you should apologize!
Sorry, Stephie.
It's fine. No problem.
Cheer up, Stephie!
Your happiness is our concern, too.
Right! I'm sure things will start looking up soon.
Our hopes are with you, Stephie.
Right, Christine?
You hope for her happiness too, don't you?
Stephie, you heard how hard Luise just slapped me -
that's how hard I will be hoping for your well-being.
Don't lose hope!
Christine...
What a convoluted way to put it.
Truly convoluted!
Say, Lotte. When you slapped Christine just now,
was it to live up to the character?
I don't know.
I only knew back then -
it hurts Stephie to hear something like that
and before I knew it,
I slapped her.
Just a minute, mom.
I'll get you dinner in no time!
Herr Pot, please wait!
My mom is starving after the work!
Please, come back!
Herr Pot...
Dad!
Dad?
Not the omelette!
I don't want you, Herr Omelette.
No! Don't come near!
Egern Station
No way, Luise. I don't think
I'll ever be able to make a convincing you.
Lotte! Make sure to write to me from Munich!
Sure. You too, Truda.
And of course, you, Lotte.
For the next time we meet,
let's try to bring each other some good news.
Luise, I trust you to take care of mom.
I know, we'll meet again soon enough.
We'll be waiting for you next year!
Goodbye!
Goodbye, Seebühl Village.
Goodbye, my summer vacation.
The two embarked on a journey.
Luise had become Lotte,
to stay with her mother in Munich.
But Lotte also had become Luise.
Soon, she'll be living with her father in Vienna.
Two young actresses head to cities they've never seen,
so as to use them as a stage for their secret little play.
A miserable Romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next Episode Preview
We two switched places!
It starts! We finally meet our dad and mom.
Lotte, you can't bother dad when he is composing!
He becomes very grumpy and short-tempered,
so don't you even try to talk to him!
Luise, don't you think our mom's perfume is the best?
Oh, I wonder how it feels to be kissing our mom.
And I hope me and dad manage to get along!
Next time in I and Myself:
Long Day for the Twins. Don't miss it!
Episode 5
Long Day for the Twins