Upon returning from Munich,
with Lotte in tow, her dad attended
a party in Frau Gerlach's house.
There, Lotte, having taken a glance at dad's world
that was obscured from her up until this day,
starts to feel the crevice
between her and dad widening rapidly.
Before - the broken frame of mother's photo.
Now - Frau Gerlach's imposed amicability.
As Lotte feels being left out completely,
a sharp pain runs through her little chest.
Episode 20
New Ally, Herr Gabele
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Should I tell her about all of this?
The broken frame of mom's photo...
I can't be entirely sure what had happened to it.
But it may seriously trouble Luise if I tell her...
Fraulein Luise!
If you don't hurry up now,
you'll be late for school!
Okay!
Yes, I know what you mean, Peperl.
I'll get ready now.
Today, on my way from school,
I'll try to drop by dad's atelier.
Maybe I'll thus learn something new.
The letter can wait until then, too.
Oh, right! I should also
write her about the painter next door.
Oh my, you've been through some torment, that's for sure.
I could tell by the Imp of Sorrow
sitting on your shoulder.
Imp of Sorrow?
Yeah, with this fellow around,
you'll never get your good night's sleep.
It's fine. This Old Herr would look after him for you.
Look! He's caught.
There, you'll be fine now.
It was Herr Gabele, isn't that right?
If it wasn't for that man,
who knows if I would have gotten any sleep last night.
Should say my thanks, next time we meet.
All right, that sounds a lot more like it.
I ought to give Frau Irene my thanks.
The party yesterday
provided for a fine change of mood.
Why is it here?
Oh? The frame is broken.
How did this happen?
But the picture is intact.
Indeed, our adorable Luise
is your daughter.
She had inherited that elegance of yours in full.
I thank you and pray
that the happiness follows you closely.
Ever since that evening,
I can't bring myself to talk to her directly about it.
I swear, it takes an idiot
to make a drunk confession like that...
Editor-in-Chief!
What's the meaning of this?
Meaning of what?
Please don't feign ignorance!
The special project for the next issue!
How come you let Karl do it all by himself?
Is that what you wanted to know?
This project has been my brainchild all along!
Right, but look at it...
"The path of a divorced woman."
You can't find a better writer for it!
I'm the only one around
who went through an actual divorce!
Ah... Well if it's all right with you,
then of course, it must really be so.
What's the matter with you, Editor?
For the last few days,
you're constantly talking in a roundabout way.
Recover sooner and become vocal and forthright again!
Well, then.
Boisterous as always.
It seems, I'm the only one here getting hung up on it.
Let's see... A General Delivery letter from Vienna...
It appears, none today.
I see...
Thank you.
This is odd.
Lotte, as soon as you're in Vienna,
you'd send me a letter - that's what you said yourself.
I wonder if dad is still here.
Maybe I could ask him directly about the photo?
I wonder if he even returned here last night...
Not here!
That photo frame...
But I was sure I left it somewhere here...
There's the frame. But...
The photo is no longer in it...
It means, dad returned here, didn't he?
And then, this...
But what became of the photo?
Not here... Could he have hidden it somewhere?
Or maybe...
Our engagement is a matter of time...
No!
I need to calm down.
I still don't know for sure.
Neither about it, nor about dad marrying Frau Gerlach.
That's right. It's not decided yet, right?
Luise... Luise!
What should i do now?
Peperl.
Thank you.
You are my only consolation these days, Peperl.
Herr Gabele... I wonder what his room is like.
Peperl! Where are you going?
Behave, Peperl.
Peperl, you can't go there!
Peperl!
Don't do this to me, Peperl.
Are you telling me, this here
is Herr Gabele's room?
Well, here it is.
Not home, see?
Let's return, Peperl.
It's open! I didn't lock the door.
Come in whenever you want.
Sure is an amiable pup, you.
You won't make a good watchdog this way.
Excuse me, Herr Gabele?
Oh? A bit too soon for me
to be seeing angels.
It must be last night's Fraulein.
Yes. My name is Luise Palfy, Herr.
I live in the house next to this.
I know.
You moved here when you were very little - like this.
However, we never spoke until last night.
Thank you for what you did last night.
Thanks to it, I could sleep.
Well, that's a relief to hear.
Now... I should offer Little Lady some tea...
Herr Gabele, something happened to you?
No, nothing.
Maybe just caught a cold from strolling at night.
Oh no! You have a terrible fever!
Never mind it, just some cold.
Nothing a good share of sleep can't cure.
Still, if you see a doctor, maybe...
I'm fed up with doctors.
They make a fuss over anything.
What about a meal?
It's fine, I would gladly do it.
In the meantime, return to sleep.
Agreed?
My, my, I thought you're a crybaby at first,
but suddenly you're a real nurse!
I'll be right back.
Peperl, sit.
Fraulein, is there really any need to do all this?
Well, he is ill, after all!
He has a cold, a fever, and just feels drowsy.
In case of cold, the best treatment
is hot food and good sleep, isn't that right?
This is all true and stuff...
But why be so attentive to some
second-rate painter you don't know?
Herr Gabele is a decent person.
That's why he had also been attentive to me before.
Resi, where's the medicine?
Been there last time I checked.
But regardless, letting you go all alone
into some oddball's room is a no-go.
You'll have to bring me along.
Sure, sure.
It's open!
Sorry for the wait.
We've got you a whole pot of hot soup.
You'll have a meal now, then drink the medicine
and get all the sleep you can.
This would make anyone's cold vanish!
This is a special soup Fraulein made just for you.
Make sure to taste it thoroughly.
This here is Resi.
She is a housekeeper living with us.
Well, what do you know, today is my lucky day!
Immediately after Luise,
I'm seeing another angel, armed with a broom.
Angel?
Do you suppose that could be me?
There's this terrific glare to your personality
that sends a painter's imagination soaring.
The fact I'm feeling better already, I owe solely
to my determination to paint a picture with you as a model.
Oh, not in your life!
Being a model is embarrassing...
Is that so?
Well, it's a pity to hear.
There, your meal.
This is delightful!
It warms the body to the core!
But most of all - the heart.
Fraulein, now that I think of it,
maybe he is not that bad a person...
Told you!
Dad didn't come home today either...
Whenever I need to talk to him,
dad is never here.
Was Luise also feeling that lonely here?
With mom, I could discuss anything, any time...
That's right... A long time ago,
mom must have been feeling lonely, too!
Dad...
Why can't you do your work from home?
What's going on?
Ah, Fraulein Tiny Angel?
Well, dear, my cold vanished just like you said.
To celebrate that, I figured I'd clean my room.
It's gone already? That's great!
Now let me help you with that, too!
Splendidly done.
With your help, this place is mighty cleaner now!
Let me thank you with tea.
You have a good many of your paintings stored up here.
Yes, I'm not selling those.
Or rather, I can't sell any of them anyways.
What's this picture called?
That would be "Twilight of Gods."
What is pictured on it?
Good question! I was hoping you'd tell me.
But that's for later,
you tea is getting cold.
It's a bit convoluted.
Herr Gabele, you're not married?
Don't you feel lonely?
I'm a lot more relaxed, staying alone!
Can just paint however I like it.
Say, Herr Gabele...
For an artist, having a wife and kids
is a mere hindrance, isn't it?
Who knows. One always decides it for himself.
For creatures such as artists,
the happiness in its ordinary sense is unattainable anyway.
The artist's idea of happiness is at odds with the idea
of happiness that an ordinary woman aspires for.
Then, Herr Gabele, do you mean to say being able to paint
is more important than anything else to you?
I guess so. Perhaps, painting is the reason
why I've been born into this world, or so I think.
For dad as well,
is music more important than anything else?
What's the matter, Luise?
Something else is worrying you?
As long as it's not a secret,
I'm curious to know.
Herr Gabele, will you hear me out?
What is it?
I have a friend, whose parents
broke up a long time ago.
Initially, she had a sister.
But upon parting,
dad and mom split their kids apart as well.
It wasn't until recently that them two
had finally found out about each other.
So now, those two sisters decided to try
to get their parents make up and live together again.
Can you think of any good way to do it?
It's easy to understand how you feel,
but it's not easy to solve that riddle.
What do you mean?
Marriage is never anything plain or straightforward.
The human emotions are a conundrum,
only existing in an incomprehensible realm.
But if they broke up,
perhaps that's for the sake of everyone's happiness.
But...
But what if the two parents
still love each other, even to this day?!
Then, those sisters also act
for the sake of the family's happiness, right?
Is there really nothing children can do about it?
After all...
I'm sorry, I just...
I...
It's all right.
It's all right, you hear?
You are such a caring child, Luise.
Fine, then! Why don't I join those sisters' cause as well?
I'll try to advise you in any way I can. Don't hesitate
to tell Luise that she can count on my help as well.
Okay.
Deal? Whatever befalls those sisters, this guy Gabele
is henceforth their faithful ally for life.
Thank you, Herr Gabele.
Now then, how about we focus
on something brighter, for a change?
Luise, I might also have
a certain favor to ask of you.
Of me?
Are you tired?
No.
It's getting too dark here.
It's because the windows in your room are so small.
Yeah. It's about as bad
for a painter's atelier as it can get.
You should try looking for a more suitable place!
Those are not thick on the ground.
Can you turn a bit more to the window?
Say, isn't it better for a painter's atelier
to also have a high ceiling?
Yeah, if possible.
This way, the light that comes through big windows
can come from above and lie evenly.
It sounds an awful lot like dad's atelier.
But...
Herr Gabele, would you be allowed
to bring piano into this room?
The fellow that lived here before me
was a pianist, I think.
You don't need as much light for composing music
as you do for painting, do you?
Well... You could do with less, I suppose.
But those questions... Something on your mind?
Nothing serious.
That's right. If dad and Herr Gabele exchange ateliers,
that would only benefit everyone!
If they do, nothing would stand in the way
of Herr Gabele's work.
And dad also would be able
to return home at any moment!
Maybe we'll even start dining together!
One of the finest ideas I ever had!
Resi!
Along with the tears she was shedding frantically,
Lotte managed to expel from her chest
that pain of the last few days.
Thanks to finding a new ally in Herr Gabele,
Lotte had regained her spirits.
How would she make use of this advantage,
as our story progresses?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Luise, we're in trouble!
Dad told me, he is proposing to Frau Gerlach!
Eh? You can't let this happen!
You absolutely can't!
Dad has been completely alone
ever since he broke up with mom, right?
Well, now, I think he had decided
he no longer wants to be alone!
Lotte, you must at any cost prevent that marriage
from coming to fruition! I believe in you!
Next time, I and Myself:
Dad, Don't Get Married!
Episode 21
Look forward to it!