Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
Thanks to mother and Luise,
who rushed all the way from Munich,
Lotte's illness was gone
before you can say Jack Robinson.
A once-in-a-lifetime chance -
"Dad and his partner should definitely reconcile,"
was the new aim that Luise and her partner
set their sights on.
In turn, father and mother also realized that the schism
in their feelings was caused by a simple misunderstanding.
One last push!
That's when the unforeseen complication takes place.
Episode 26
Saying Goodbyes? No!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Today, I come here with an important favor to ask.
Ah, about that? Unfortunately, let me see...
We have an emergency, Herr Palfy!
Becker? What is it? You look flustered.
Just a moment ago, our leading actress
Yvonne Janowitz suddenly got hospitalized!
What are you saying?
The director wants to see you immediately.
Got it. I'll go there right away.
Apologies, Frau Irene.
I'll call you some time later.
Herr Palfy!
My!
Things look dire.
Should either postpone or cancel the concert.
No, no, Herr Palfy.
If I were you, I would have considered
a postponement or a cancellation unfavorable.
Isn't that so, Becker?
Yes...
There already exists an unfortunate streak of two concerts -
in Berlin and in Munich - cancelled one after another.
If this concert ends in a cancellation as well,
it may deal a fatal blow to your reputation in media.
Never mind the media.
They don't understand a thing.
Here's what I think, why don't we double down
and reassign the leading role?
You're thinking Lenz?
It's true that there's an undeniable potential to her.
But making it until tomorrow...
If we don't push it to the extremes,
we might arrive to a pitiful fiasco.
It will be all right.
I know her, and I have faith in her.
As well as in you.
Let's go for it, Herr Palfy!
Can't know until you try!
Fine, then.
Tell everyone to gather on the stage.
Roger!
Ah?
Oh, my bad! I've forgotten.
Becker, sorry to bother you,
but I need you to go to Cafe Schubert for me.
There, find a woman by the name of Körner
and tell her this from me,
"Today, I have some urgent matters to tend to."
Understood. Miss Körner, isn't that right?
Yeah, counting on you.
Herr Palfy, everyone's ready.
Körner?
Could it be...
You're his manager, Herr Becker, isn't that right?
Yes.
The message you were just asked you to convey -
I'm actually acquainted to that person.
Is that so?
Then, would you do it for me?
This place is currently a kerfuffle,
you'd really help us out!
He's quite late.
In the bygone times,
I would have gone home already.
Mom's quite late.
Must be that she's chatting to dad heartily.
Leaving us two out?
Right. Make no mistake,
it's an important talk just for two.
Then, you think they're...
Definitely, Luise.
The dream is coming true!
In five days from now, it's our birthday.
We'll celebrate it as a family of four!
Right!
Of four!
Is this Frau Körner I'm seeing?
Yes.
You may know me as a certain Irene Gerlach.
It appears, dad have been seeing some woman
named Irene Gerlach quite frequently.
You mind if I join you?
Not at all...
May I take your order?
I'll have Sherry.
Sure.
As a matter of fact, Herr Palfy intended
to come here personally to introduce me.
But then, some others matters
demanded his immediate attention.
If that's how she puts it,
it must really be so.
In addition, we two were planning
to celebrate our engagement here.
Engagement?
Oh my... You were never informed up to now?
Well, that's Herr Palfy for you.
The other day, he made a solemn proposal to me.
Proposal?
Ah, in that case, accept my congratulations.
Thank you.
But I must apologize, too!
We made you wait for so long.
You know him - when it comes to music,
it's like the rest of the world can wait.
This is so troublesome.
However, out of deference for his music,
we could forgive him this little oversight.
After all, his genius is probably
the God's gift to humanity.
He does all that to bestow
more of his amazing music upon us.
Personally, I intend to prop up Herr Palfy
in all his endeavors, whatever they might be.
For that purpose, I'm going to leverage my father's
numerous influential connections in the most diverse fields.
However...
I believe, nothing surpasses in importance
being understanding and caring towards your partner.
Even when the world of music
infatuates him to the point where he stops looking at you,
it's best that you step away
and let him roam it freely.
My, a piece of educated portending?
Rest assured. I have my own ways
of conferring my love on him.
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to say that...
Well then, may you both be happy.
Bon voyage, sweetheart.
How could I actually be that foolish?
An unforgivable mistake.
Mom!
Welcome back. Where's dad?
Lotte, how come you forgot to mention it?
The fact your father
and Frau Gerlach are engaged.
He isn't! It was one big misunderstanding!
Dad wasn't being serious!
So you knew, but didn't tell me either, Luise.
That's something you two
should have mentioned earlier.
I should now congratulate your father, shouldn't I?
I protested it!
My own mom...
Is the only mom for me!
Mom, will you really let it slide?
You think it's fine for dad to marry Frau Gerlach?
As long as it makes your dad happy,
it's the finest thing ever.
Your dad's unhappiness
is something I want to avoid seeing at any cost.
Dad's unhappiness?
Having attended some more of your dad's concerts
after we broke up, I've been able to discern it clearly -
his wound had been much deeper than mine.
But attending his concerts even after you broke up,
means you loved him still, didn't you?
Even now, you're still very fond of dad, aren't you?
It's too late.
Way too late.
I'm sorry.
Your mom had overstayed her welcome here.
Mom?
Mom?!
Resi, where's mom?
It would appear to me that she went out.
But where to?
That letter might hold some keys to it.
"I just remembered about some job
I absolutely need to get done.
I shall return to Munich now.
My best regards to your father.
I'll call you soon."
But why?
Did it without even saying goodbyes to us!
This is so unlike her...
Resi, has dad been here?
Nope, not to my knowledge.
Sleeping in his atelier, perhaps?
Lotte, we'll call him right away!
Not there.
Oh, right! I think, he conducts a concert
in the Opera House today.
Must be there!
On our way, then!
We can't see our dad?
Regret to say it, but I can't help you.
I'm instructed to not let in anyone but the staff.
But we're here for a reason!
Can't we peek in just for a second?
Today, it's explicitly forbidden.
The director looked mighty stern, ordering this.
I know! You can try writing a note,
and I'll see if I can pass it at some point.
What now?
I feel that it's something
we need to ask dad directly.
Are you absolutely sure?
Sorry, girls.
I see...
Thanks for your service.
Hey... Hold it, Fraulein!
Off-limits for anyone but the staff!
That won't be a problem.
I'm the fiancee of Herr Palfy himself.
Hey, wait! No, you'll get me in trouble!
OK! Let's take a short break.
Intermission - one hour!
Lenz, this one was perfect just now.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you very much!
But in the final aria of the first act,
try to restrain your emoting.
Okay!
Conductor, would you be able to listen to me
during this intermission for a bit?
Sure, no problem.
Herr Palfy!
Frau Irene?
Could I confer with you for a few minutes
about our mutual affairs?
I'd be glad to, but some other time, please.
Hey, Becker!
Herr Palfy! This is an urgent matter!
Becker, do you know where director is?
Holding a conference in the next room.
Director, could you summon Schwarz here as well?
Herr Palfy!
It's about the accompaniment for Lenz's aria.
Understood, I'll arrange it immediately.
Herr Palfy, I need to ask you
about the engagement announcement party...
Becker!
Yes?
For one hour starting now,
see that our practice is uninterrupted.
Understood.
What should I do about your meal?
Later. Not until Lenz's aria is polished.
Herr Palfy, the date for the ceremony...
Actually, director!
I'd like to do some parts of the second act, too.
Summon Meyer as well.
Very well. Anyone else?
No need, that's enough for now.
Herr Palfy, we also need to finish choosing the dress!
Becker, what else is in the program?
One more rehearsal in the evening.
Got it.
That's quite rude, Herr Palfy!
Between me and the opera,
which one is more important to you?
The most important thing is being understanding
and caring towards your partner.
Be it even at the expense
of him paying attention to you.
It's not something I can't figure out myself.
Not there?
I'm sorry.
If I hear your voices right now,
I'll break into tears!
What's going on?
I know! Editor-in-Chief is the one
who might have some leads.
Yes? Bernau on the phone.
Oh, Luise? Is Lotte feeling all right?
About your mother?
No, we've not seen her in the office.
Ah, I got it!
I'll try looking into it.
Worries aside.
Thank you, it'd be of great help.
Don't worry. When Editor-in-Chief finds her,
we'll know everything.
What a relief!
With Herr Palfy, I can excuse a lot for the sake of music,
but the way he treated me today... Does he have any limits?
I ought to have a word with him about it.
If today's concert is not plagued with contingencies,
Herr Palfy's reputation would be once again on its peak.
Right. I'm also concerned about how'd it go,
after that streak of disasters he had lately.
But say, during the daytime rehearsal, Herr Palfy had
this look on his face, saying "don't get in my way, or else..."
That is very true.
Even while Frau Gerlach was clinging to him,
it was as though she is is invisible to him!
Right, right.
At times like that, Herr Palfy
is pretty much deaf and blind, not just to her.
Let's say, the president himself suddenly shows up -
Palfy still wouldn't condescend to look at him.
The most important thing
is being understanding and caring towards your partner.
When he flies off to the world of music,
you don't try to restrain him.
Even if he ends up completely forgetting to look at you.
I have a feeling that Fraulein Lenz
had some of Herr Palfy's passion rubbed off on her,
so we should expect
a terrific leading role performance.
It's true what they say about Palfy -
must be that his genius is the God's gift to humanity!
My...
Hey. Welcome back.
Editor, but why?
I didn't feel like dining alone tonight.
Would you keep me company?
The girls sent you, didn't they?
Leading two adorable Frauleins a merry dance -
quite unbecoming of you.
Come on, need to defeat my growling stomach now.
I'll hear your explanations later.
The wretch now thou knowest,
Who sought my betraying,
And vengeance thou owest
My father's, my father's foul slaying.
For justice I sue thee;
I ask of thy troth...
I'm home!
But why, so suddenly...
We're the ones asking that!
Dad, did you say anything to mom?
Last night, she went to Cafe "Something,"
to see you, didn't she?
No...
Yesterday, I was too busy...
It's your fault!
It's because you didn't show up!
I see.
She must've been waiting until the very end. And then...
...Mom returned home,
when she found out you're marrying Frau Gerlach!
This is unthinkable!
Unnatural and unthinkable!
Dad, we only wish... We only wish...
...That our dad and mom...
reconcile!
Just as they were this close to opening their hearts,
father and mother end up parting ways again.
Lotte and Luise can't help wondering,
"Is our dream really coming true?"
As well as, "Will we be able to finally come together
to celebrate our birthday as a family of four?"
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Eh? No way it's true? Lotte should also return to Munich?
Did mom really said so?
I guess she wants to return
to our old life as soon as possible.
And I also have to go to school.
So mom said, "return tomorrow," just like that.
I hate it! I can't part with Lotte yet!
I hate it, too! I'm not parting with Luise!
Next time, I and Myself:
Two People, One Wish.
Episode 27
Two People, One Wish
Don't miss it!