With Annie's instigation,
the mini-concert at school
is to be held with Luise in the vanguard.
Alas, the girl doesn't know
the first thing about playing the piano.
Being at a complete loss, Luise
tried to reach out to Lotte via the phone,
but this time, nobody answered.
Episode 15
Lotte, Help!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Lotte being able to play piano
was one big lie all along!
Lotte screwed everyone over! She is a liar!
Liar!
Lotte, help!
Lotte!
Lotte? Lotte?
What's the matter? Are you okay?
Good morning, mom.
You were moaning in your sleep.
You don't have a fever, do you?
Ah... Not at all!
Just had a slightly unpleasant dream.
Well... Glad to know it's nothing serious.
But now, come on, wake up.
I'll take care of the breakfast today, Lotte.
Okay!
"Slightly unpleasant" doesn't do it justice...
Still, Lotte, where could you have gone to?
There's nobody in the house to even answer the phone.
Lotte!
Could you come here for a moment?
Okay!
How about this, Lotte?
What do you mean, mom? This...
I just thought, you need to look appropriately
for today's concert, so I bought this.
But it's just a mini-concert in school,
it'd be wiser not to spend too much on it...
Never mind that, Lotte.
You shouldn't concern yourself with such matters,
just do your best.
Ah... I'm deep in trouble.
Running away is getting too difficult to pull off!
I'll try to leave early today to cheer you on.
And I'm sure, Editor Bernau
would love to come listen to it, too.
Don't let him down!
Eh? You're relying too much on me!
Besides, I've just barely renewed the practice,
and I still make a lot of rookie mistakes!
So it's better if he doesn't come!
I know my Lotte would handle it.
Mistakes won't blemish a talent such as yours.
I'll leave this in the bedroom,
so once the classes are over, come and change.
Malingering is still an option for me,
but that'd be a dead giveaway to mom.
Ah... What can I even do about it?
In the Alps, the temperature
remains rather low even in the summer,
so countless clusters of perpetual snow
eventually form into glaciers.
Germany is located exactly to the north
from the main alpine ridge.
Ah... Things turned from bad to worse.
How do I talk my way out of it?
Consequently, the highest peak on the German side of it -
resting at 2,963 meters, Zugspitze.
All this is happening to me
because of Annie's stupid instigation!
It is a popular attraction for ski enthusiasts,
that climb to the top in a cable car.
Lotte!
I think you need to calm down a bit.
After all, the mini-concert this afternoon
would be attended by the principal, as well as many parents.
You should refrain from misbehavior.
Okay.
Lotte!
I'm excited to hear your mini-concert today!
Ah... Okay. Thanks.
You think she'll dare to show up for the mini-concert?
What's the point of showing up
if she can't play?
Say, how do you think,
what'll Lotte do?
What would you have done in her shoes?
I'd try to make a run for it!
She might pretend to fall ill, too.
And we're here to prevent any of that!
Whatever she tries to pull, we'll expose Lotte!
She'll bear the brunt of embarrassment!
Could it be because Annie
also suspects I'm not the real Lotte?
But she doesn't have any reason to.
Ah, this doesn't help...
What are you doing?!
Luise, you can't tell? It's me!
See? None other, Luise.
Lotte!
And the real one at that!
You're a saver!
Saver from what?
Something happened?
This is bad, Annie is still on my tail.
Eh?
Put on your mask, Lotte!
Must be some of Lotte's friends.
Where could I have seen her...
Nowhere to hide around this place.
Annie and others won't be able to get close.
That sure was startling.
You materialized in front of me out of thin air!
But it was you who didn't show up
for the rendezvous.
So I had to intercept you on the way.
Eh? What rendezvous?
The one I appointed in the letter.
Oh no!
Those few days were so hectic,
I forgot about checking in the post office!
My, Luise, you're always like that!
Hear this, dad recently got an offer
to conduct the Munich Symphony Orchestra!
So he brought me along!
Eh? Dad is also here?
So that's why nobody was answering
your phone in Vienna.
The phone? Did something urgent happen?
The mother of all urgencies!
I got myself involved in something big.
Something big?
But now, we're in the clear -
Lotte showed up to save the day!
You're a godsend!
Wait, Luise!
What could they be talking about?
Moreover, the way they cuddle each other,
you'd think they've a foot in both camps!
What's having a foot in both camps?
Huh? You don't know?
If I knew, I wouldn't be asking!
I don't really get it myself.
Gosh, you're useless.
No "rewrite it once again?"
This time, it's good enough as it is.
My, how peculiar.
I hope it doesn't snow today.
The event is peculiar indeed,
so you'd better be sincerely glad about it.
Sure, will do hereafter.
Your next assignment would be
the field work at the Munich Philharmonic.
I'm told, for the upcoming series of concerts, the same Palfy
we discussed before, had come to do the conducting.
He is currently in Munich?
His previous performance in Berlin -
why was it cancelled?
Does he regret letting down the audience
that has been waiting for him eagerly?
I'm counting on you
to unravel those mysteries.
Okay.
Really? A mini-concert on piano?
You must really feel troubled.
To the point of seeing nightmares about it! I was already
considering coming clean and just returning to Vienna.
But now, the true Lotte is also here,
so we're on the right path again!
Which means, we just need to exchange places again,
in a way inconspicuous to Annie.
But say, isn't it weird?
Lotte no longer looks troubled!
Hm! Must be just pretending.
It seems, Lotte isn't running away.
We can't know for sure yet!
Not until she comes out and goes there.
But if she doesn't, I'll drag her there, even if by the hair!
You're playing piano today, like it or not!
Lotte, what is dad up to now?
Went to the theater.
He expects me to return to the hotel by six.
Mini-concert starts at three,
so you'll have plenty of time left.
Here, Lotte.
When you're done making the braids, change into this.
Whoa!
Mom even bought such a pretty dress for it?
I'm too embarrassed to wear it myself.
Well, I can always go there myself
and play the piano to the best of my abilities.
Now, Editor, if Lotte is still home,
I'll invite her to go with us.
Sure, we'll wait for you.
Lotte's mom here!
This way, Lotte it out of options for running away!
Told you, she'll feign a sickness at the last moment.
Well, if she does, I'll make sure everyone knows:
her only real disease is her inability to play the piano!
Looks good, Luise?
Yeah! Pretty.
Like it was cut out for you!
Lotte, are you still here?
We came to pick you up.
No way! Mom returned home!
Lotte?
Did you leave already?
Lotte, quick, hide under the bed!
Luise, why should I be the one hiding?
Right!
I am Luise again, and you're Lotte now!
Huh? Not here?
Now that's odd.
Quick! Quick, Luise!
Lotte?
Uh... What are you doing?
Ah? There! My pen fell into under the bed.
Needed to pick it up.
But I could have sworn, in the hallway,
I heard you talking now.
Oh, that... I was just humming the tune
I'm to play at the mini-concert.
Really?
Also, this dress you bought for me
is just gorgeous!
It looks becoming on you too.
Thank you, mom.
Never mind it.
Now, Editor-in-Chief Bernau
is waiting for us in the taxi
Let's set out.
I need to finish just one more thing,
can you go ahead?
Okay, just make it quick.
Huh?
Did you catch a cold, Lotte?
I didn't. It's all right.
Fine.
Hurry up, then.
Okay!
Luise, when the mini-concert is over,
meet me at the science class, will you?
There, we'll change clothes again, right?
Yeah!
Well, see you there.
Jeez, that sure was close!
Now this is weird.
Lotte is going there with her mom like it's nothing!
They're gone.
We should go too.
Ah! Maybe her plan is to make a run for it from school?
Annie sure is a diehard believer.
Wrong. This is called a tenacious disbeliever.
Maria, Miria, what are you waiting for? Let's go!
Yeah! On our way!
Well, what do you know -
nobody noticed a thing!
Oh, but that's for later.
I need to get to school now!
While we're at it, your schedule for tomorrow:
at ten - first round of rehearsals.
Yes, this sounds wonderful!
As expected of a genius!
Hey, Chauffeur, stop the car around here.
Yeah, from here on, I'll walk.
But you're free to return on wheels.
However, Herr Palfy,
it's still quite the long way from the hotel!
A strange town and a strange wind
are exceptional ingredients for making a good music.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Yeah...
It's totally strange -
she doesn't seem to be running away!
Is she really going to play?
That's my sis Lotte! Amazing!
It's true what they say Lotte is good at this.
Hmpf! All she can do is play piano!
How can one be such a one-trick pony?
True. Playing the piano is the only thing she's good at.
I never had any idea Lotte was that talented.
She sounds like the first-class pianist already.
Oh my, you needn't exaggerate.
No, no, that's what I really think.
Still, you can't deny she's gotten remarkably better.
How did she manage it even without practicing?
I guess, she inherited her dad's aptitude in full.
Come to think of it, this piano
sounds very alike to how he used to play it.
Where had I heard this play before...
That's right!
It's just like Luise's play!
Still, could it be?
Luise is playing in a place like this...
All right.
I had no idea how good she was!
Alas, we'll have to exchange places again.
I'm returning to my mom, and Lotte stays with dad.
Right, I'll be waiting for you
in the science class, as planned.
Spectacular!
You'd never tell she is an elementary school student!
Wonderful!
Oh... Pardon me.
Eh? Dad?
Oh no!
Dad!
Luise! I knew it was you playing it all along!
That's right. Look, I can explain...
You don't need to explain something so good!
Your gift is astonishing, that's all that matters!
I know! A professional pianist career
is what you should aim for!
Yes! That's decided!
You shouldn't be deciding this for me...
Now, we should celebrate with a good feast.
Let's return to the hotel.
Eh? But...
Ah... Wait!
Ah! Lotte, what do I do?
Lotte, this performance was something.
Thank you, mom!
I see you're really excited, aren't you?
You can turn into such a child
in a matter of minute!
Of course I do!
Terribly sorry to interrupt a precious intimate moment
of parent and child, but still, may I add something?
Editor-in-Chief Bernau!
You really have a gift for that kind of thing.
The performance was fantastic.
Thank you very much.
My, my, you're not only graceful with piano,
but your whole bearing had become thoroughly lady-like!
You think so?
Lotte, Editor-in-Chief Bernau
offered to treat us to a delicious dinner.
Lotte's success today
ought to be properly celebrated.
Tonight, pick anything you like from the menu.
Whoa! Delightful!
Are you serious?
Most certainly.
Oh no, I'm supposed to be in the science class,
exchanging dresses with Luise right about now!
Okay, mom, please wait for me outside.
I just need to finish one more thing.
Sure, go ahead.
Lotte, you've outdone yourself today.
That was the best mini-concert we ever had.
Thank you very much, Frau Linnekogel.
Lotte, good job!
Thank you.
Why is Luise there with dad?
Lotte...
Luise...
In a twist of fate that was considered inconceivable,
things returned to normal:
Luise left with her dad,
and Lotte is going to live with her mom again.
However, it'll be premature to assume
things are staying this way for long.
As fate would have it, both the twins and their parents
all happened to be in Munich.
Now, what else does fate have in store for them?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode
Can you believe it, Luise?
I finally mustered enough courage to ask mom.
Eh? What?
Because Editor Bernau and mom are getting along so well,
I asked if they're considering a marriage.
And what did mom say to that?
"I've had my share of marriage."
Eh? Dad told me the exact same thing!
He had his share of marriage.
Eh? Really?
How come both gave the exact same answer?
Next time in I and Myself:
Quirk of Fate.
Episode 16
Quirk of Fate
Don't miss it!