After suddenly finding a friend in each other,
Luise and Lotte
changed they hairstyles to matching, too,
surprising everyone around them
with how indistinguishably alike the two girls can become.
While just casually exchanging stories,
an unthinkable revelation dawned upon them -
Luise and Lotte
are actually blood-related twins.
Episode 3
Oath by the Lake
Don't tell me, they are off
to somewhere else again, Luise and Lotte?
Since yesterday, those have been inseparable -
thick as thieves!
And whenever they glance at one another,
they grin like that - ear-to-ear!
Having a girl looking just like you around
is a mighty exhilarating thing, I imagine.
Last night, even after the lights went out,
I heard them gossiping to one another.
Think they might be scheming something again?
Those two are a prankish bunch.
They no longer even come out to play with us.
This must be a major conspiracy.
But they could at least tell me something!
It seems, we somehow ended up
surrendering Luise to Lotte.
Let's go!
Say, peculiar, isn't it?
Is that really so?
It is!
And that's what I've been telling him.
Dad sure seems like an interesting guy.
But still, all the people coming to listen to the opera
don't seem to share this view.
And so, as soon as he starts conducting the orchestra,
he becomes so gravely serious!
Wish I could see it, too!
But to me, he'll be sure to send a certain signal.
A signal?
When the music is over and the audience is applauding,
while bowing, he sends a quick glance my way
and combs up his hair here with his left hand.
And this is the signal?
And so, I also applaud him with all my heart.
Sounds exciting.
Hey, hey, is mom actually a lot of a crybaby?
She never lets herself cry while someone is looking.
But to me, she always says this,
"A woman shouldn't waste her tears on trifles.
It's unforgivable for a woman
to break into tears to extort others' sympathy."
So that's why you didn't cry back then,
even after receiving my kick on the shins.
I guess so.
I so want to meet her, my mom!
Me too! If only I could meet my dad!
By the way, I'm writing a letter home today.
I'm going to ask dad to send over a photo of himself!
True? Sublime! My heart is pounding.
Say, which one of us you think is older?
Well, it's hard to say.
But if I had to guess, I'd say it was you!
You really think so?
Turns out, I have both a mom and a sister!
I so want to shout it for everyone to know!
You shouldn't, we settled on it last night.
For the time being, we shouldn't tell anyone
we're actual twin sisters.
Alas, it is so.
We don't know the full picture ourselves.
How come dad and mom no longer live together?
First, of course, they got married.
Then they had us.
And then they must have quarreled and parted.
And they separated us just the same
as they separated mom's first name.
But why didn't they ever ask us about it?
Like, whether or not we two
wish to be separated, too.
They couldn't! By then, we were still little tots,
probably hadn't even learned to talk yet.
You think so?
Luise! What are you doing in a place like this?
What is it you're scheming this time?
No scheming involved to my knowledge. Right?
You only ever play with Lotte these days,
and brush us off as some gnat! It stings a bit.
I don't try to brush you off.
It's just that me and Lotte
have crucial matters to discuss.
Those could those be? Crucial matters?
That'd be a secret!
Sure, sure. Keep sticking to each other
like two cherries on a twig.
It's not like anyone here wants to play anyway!
Say, what do you think could be that secret?
I'll go ask myself!
No you won't! Stephie!
Hey, hey, what is that secret?
Can't say! It's something nobody
but me and Lotte would understand.
Oh, don't you tease me!
In exchange, you can count on my help
next time you two plan to prank everyone!
Come on, spill it.
Now you're getting pesky.
There are still more things we need to discuss
than you can shake a stick at, and no time is enough for that!
Quit getting in the way!
Luise...
Luise! You can't be shooing others away like that.
But come on...
I'm sorry, Stephie.
Please don't take too close to heart what Luise said.
But it's true that for some while
we won't be able to confide it in anyone else.
Deal?
I'm sorry, Stephie.
My, my. Now Luise even brought Stephie to tears.
Look for yourself, I'm not crying!
However, I no longer want to play
with someone like Luise!
But say, those two sure are being strange.
Ah, Frau Braids and Frau Curls are back again?
You are no longer the one.
Speaking of which,
I'm told you've taken a photo together.
Isn't that so?
Yes. We'll collect them the day after tomorrow.
And then, you'll send them home, right?
That'll sure be a bolt from the blue
to both your parents.
I mean, meeting a friend who is a spitting image of you
completely by chance - it's not something you do every day.
When your parents's response arrives,
please let me know it, too. See you!
That's right, the picture...
No way we can send it home!
Exactly! If they know we've met each other,
our play is blown!
Take care on your way back.
Thank you, Herr Eipeldauer.
You're welcome. Come again,
whenever you need a picture taken.
That's a fine picture, if I do say so.
This looks just like something
the illustrated magazines are looking for!
If I send this picture home,
I bet, dad jumps out of his skin, if not more.
I wonder if dad recognizes me.
And what would mom have to say about this?
Aren't you curious?
But we can't!
This picture must be kept for private eyes only.
But say, you really can't tell us apart here, can you?
Everyone, the post had arrived!
Here, a moment of silence, please.
I am going to read the names now.
And the first would be... Truda!
Next is... Stephie.
Monica, Luise.
It's from dad!
Look!
This is dad...
My dad!
It's our dad.
Here I go:
"To my dearest, only child."
My, what a liar!
He knows perfectly well he has twins.
"I think you must have completely forgotten
what your old father looks like.
Otherwise you wouldn't be so anxious for a photo
just before the end of your vacation.
At first, I thought I would send you
my usual photo of choice -
the one that pictures me as a baby,
sleeping in my birthday suit on a polar-bear skin.
But you wrote that it must be
an absolutely brand-new picture.
So I rushed off to the photographer's,
and explained to him just why I needed it in such a hurry.
I told him that unless he took my picture, my Luise
wouldn't recognize me when I went to the station to meet her.
The reason I'm not as handsome as usual there
is because we did it in a hurry."
It really shows!
"I'm sorry for the counselors there.
I hope you don't lead them such a dance as you do your father.
I send you a thousand kisses
and am longing to have you home again."
He sounds lovely! And funny, too!
And yet, in the picture he looks quite serious.
He keeps a straight face in front of others.
But when we're alone we always have lots of fun!
Say, you mind if I keep it?
Not at all!
After all, you'll let me keep mom's photo, too, won't you?
You can't find Stephie anywhere?
Have you searched everywhere?
Yeah, I checked every corner of the house and the garden.
No signs of her anywhere.
Hey, what are you up to?
What's the meaning of this?
You girls! Eavesdropping again, aren't you?
Me and Frau Muthesius
need to discuss a pressing matter!
Come on, out you go.
No, wait a minute. Had anyone among you girls
seen or talked to Stephie this afternoon?
Last time I checked, she was reading a letter
in the inner garden.
But soon after, she was no longer there.
And I saw her running towards the lake.
To the lake?!
Could it be...
Frau Muthesius!
Oh, don't you be so alarmed.
Our first course of action should be
searching the area together.
Yes, you're right.
Stephie!
Stephie, where are you?
Please answer if you hear us!
Stephie!
Stephie...
Where could she have run off to?
Truda!
Any luck?
Luise, it was your fault
that Stephie decided to go missing!
How is that my fault?
Explain yourself!
Remember how you upset Stephie today?
Me?
But I didn't do anything of the kind.
You told her to get lost, didn't you?
Stephie was extremely stung by that!
But I... never...
All of this is happening because of you.
Let's go, Truda.
Don't get hung up on it, Luise.
It wasn't because of what you said.
Let's hurry up to find her instead!
Stephie!
Stephie, where did you go?
Answer something, Stephie!
Stephie!
She's not here either.
And there...
Right! She might just be over there.
After me!
You alright?
On this hill, there's a big tree.
If you climb up there, a great view
on the lake and on the summer camp opens up.
Stephie!
Luise! Lotte!
What are you doing there?
Climb down, please!
Everyone is sick worried about you!
But I can no longer climb down!
Oh, what a strange thing to do.
Be careful, Luise!
Stephie!
Luise!
You even managed to climb all the way here!
While climbing, I was in a daze.
I wanted to just leave for somewhere else.
Here.
Thanks.
Stephie, did I hurt you that much?
What do you mean?
It wasn't you.
But then, what in the world...?
A letter arrived... from my mama.
My papa and mama are breaking up.
The hearings started already.
There, they're going to decide
with which one of them I'm going to stay.
I can't believe it!
So cruel!
They send you away on the vacations here
to do such a thing behind your back!
Mama is trying to find an ally in me.
And papa seems to have fallen in love
with another woman.
It's already decided, I don't even get any say in it.
But what's worse, I feel that I am currently
the most hapless girl in the universe.
And I'm also hungry.
Let's return, Stephie.
Stephie! Where have you been?
The counselors were scared to death!
They had already sent us to get a policeman!
Oh my!
Let's show you to the counselors already!
Did you really have to do all this?
Wait!
Our dad hasn't got
another woman in the house, has he?
There's nothing of the kind.
If that had been true,
I'd be the first person to know.
Still, could it be, that even if they're not married yet
there's someone else he is in love with?
Not to my knowledge.
And I daresay, I know nearly all of his friends.
But what about mom?
Does she have anyone?
Like a... A man friend?"
No!
Mom keeps telling me this all the time,
"I have my daughter Lotte, and I have my work,
and that's all I will ever ask of life."
My, but why, when, did dad and mom
break up in the first place?
I don't know...
I wonder if to split us, they went to court, too.
Just two babies who don't yet understand a thing,
why did they have to keep us apart,
like just some toy they couldn't share?
Not just that, they never told any of us
that we have both another parent and a sister!
But why?
If not for the fluke that brought us together here,
we'd be still going on with our lives,
without ever realizing we have a sibling this adorable!
Fine parents we've got, haven't we?
Just wait till we tell dad and mom a few things upfront!
That'll be sure to make them sit up!
We couldn't do such thing.
Why?
After all, we're still just children.
Lotte, are you awake?
Yes.
We need to talk, let's come out for a second.
Luise, where are you leading me to?
To the lake.
At this hour? I'm scared.
Don't you worry, the moon is bright.
Look, when I first met you here, completely by accident,
it seemed like a thing straight out of a fairy tail.
I believe it was due to the providence
wanting us two to meet.
I think so, too.
Are you suggesting we pretend nothing of this ever happened,
return to our homes, and lead the same lives we led before?
I don't think I'll be able to live on
without seeing you.
Neither do I.
So, I came up with a plan.
You won't be returning to Munich,
but you'll come to Vienna with me instead!
To Vienna?
You'll get to meet dad yourself!
I want to meet him, but...
We'll confront dad together.
And then we'll ask him for a permission
to see each other every now and then!
But what if dad gets mad
and forbids us to see each other ever again?
I don't think...
...he would do such a thing.
I still might see dad if I become you...
I will become you and go to Vienna.
And you'll become me to go to Munich!
Sublime!
Your idea is by a mile brighter than mine!
It's great, if we both switch places!
But... are you sure it'll work?
You've seen yourself how alike we are.
No way it doesn't work!
We can do it, Lotte!
I'll get to meet my mom!
And I'll meet my dad.
I'm so excited to get to know him!
And then... Then, if it would seem possible...
If possible?
If possible...
I know what you mean.
Luise, raise your hand.
Like this?
Me and mom do that all the time.
With this, the promise is sealed.
We swear an oath of guarding this secret.
Before us, a task of unprecedented magnitude.
Starting tomorrow, we'll put our minds
to developing the strategy.
Let's do our very best, Lotte!
Only after you, Luise!
What just started as but a vague idea,
unbeknownst to the two girls behind it,
is yet to evolve into a daring adventure
through the uncharted seas.
However, Luise and Lotte
know that this journey is not for the faint of heart.
They set their sights on an untrodden new continent.
What's left for us to just bring a prayer
that the seas stay calm on their way.
A miserable Romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
I'm Luise!
And I'm Lotte!
I'm supposed to be good at cooking?
Of course! Mom always returns late from her work.
Does that mean
cleaning and laundry, too?
Naturally! There's no housekeeping you can't do.
After all, mom calls me
her little housekeeper for a reason!
No way! I can't do all that.
For my whole life,
we had a servant Resi at our place.
This would be troublesome.
Next time in I and Myself:
Onset of the Operation. Don't miss it!
Episode 4
Onset of the Operation
Translated by Perevodildo | Timings by Sub-RoRo