Lotte and Luise thought
they might be seeing a dream.
Father and mother finally held
the wedding ceremony.
Starting now, as the family of four,
they can live happily together.
The long-awaited days
of limitless happiness had finally started.
Episode 29
Our First Family Trip
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Modern day Vienna was granted
the capital city status in the twelfth century.
It was around the time
when St. Stephen's Cathedral was completed.
And now, Luise, what was the year when Wenia
was renamed into modern day Vienna?
That was...
1030 AD!
Yes, correct!
Some tea.
Studying hard?
Well, we're having a social studies​ test next week.
Do your best, then.
This all is so tiresome.
And what fine weather!
I'd rather be playing outside.
Eh? A trip?
Destination is my uncle's villa.
Uncle's villa?
Right. Last time I've been there some years ago,
I left my important bag in his custody.
But now I suddenly remembered it,
and rather than going to pick it up alone...
Going as a family of four!
Exactly. A good occasion for our first family trip.
It's a wonderful place,
embraced by the nature itself.
Our first...
...Family trip!
Sublime!
Then, I'll also try to wrap up
that manuscript I'm working on until tomorrow.
Oh no! We depart today!
Right away, in fact.
Today? Right away?
As soon as you conceive something fun,
realize it immediately, before it becomes boring.
And so, look at this - the tickets!
Dad sure is quick tempered!
Well, he is our dad, after all!
But say, if we show up so suddenly,
are you sure we won't bother your uncle?
Don't you worry about that.
I had already telegraphed him.
Still, it's so inopportune.
I only have two days left until the manuscript deadline.
That's right, how should we prepare for the test?
Oh, it'll be fine!
For a bunch of bright Frauleins such as you,
even cramming it while on the train,
or upon arriving to the villa, would pose no complication.
Isn't that right, Lotte?
Well... I don't really know...
Not going..?
I also support prioritizing the fun over anything else!
Now come on, let's have a break, Lotte, mom!
All right, that settled.
Now, let's hurry, hurry!
You got ten minutes to pack.
We don't want to miss the train.
Okay!
Well, what do you say?
Shouldn't we start packing, too?
Yes!
I love this trip already!
Hey-hey, Luise.
It's dangerous to lean out so much.
Dad, look, look!
Breathtaking scenery!
What is it?
A scenery straight out of heavens!
Someone needs to take a short break.
Lotte, you also forget about studying for now!
Why can't I finish studying first,
to fully enjoy myself later?
You're too serious, Lotte.
It's you who is too carefree, Luise!
You just don't know how to enjoy yourself.
This excessively serious Lotte is a bore!
Oh! The grazing cows, Luise!
True! One is yawning!
Look at this giant mouth!
Very true.
Ah! Nice air, nice weather.
For now, yes.
But what if it starts to rain?
Why'd you say such a thing?
I'm trying my utmost to immerse in joy here!
Ah? But I was really wondering that.
You're weird, Lotte.
Not the usual you.
I'm the most usual!
Look! You sound mad, even just saying it.
What do you even care,
if I'm too serious and boring a girl anyways?
So you're still mad at such a trifle?
Ah, it's a trifle now?
See? I said you're too serious,
and now you're taking it too seriously!
So what it is you want from that serious girl?
Why don't you stop copying her homework, then?
I used to make do without it!
Not the end of the world.
Wow-wow, what's this all about, you two?
Well...
What are you doing?
The bus is leaving! Hurry up!
Come on, let's put this off until we're home.
Hurry up, hurry!
Ah! I forgot.
The manuscript is with you, honey?
You took it away earlier!
Did I really?
How odd...
Excuse me, we need to leave now,
are you riding?
We're sorry, you can leave without us.
Ah, but...
So? Found it?
No, not here either.
Ah... Left it in train, after all.
I'll go try looking for it.
Mom, the train left already.
Ah, my bad...
How do I get myself out of this now?
Ah, just remembered!
Right here, in your pocket.
There, see?
Whoa! Found it!
Mom, aren't you glad?
Oh, why did you have to do this...
I may have forgotten to tell you...
Ah! Oh no! The bus!
Gone already.
No big deal, not at all!
Can just wait for the next bus.
But that was the last bus of the day.
What's with everyone? Cheer up, you!
As long as we keep walking,
a car would pass by us at some point.
And then, we'd ask for a ride.
But...
We've been walking for an hour already.
And not a single one passed by us yet.
No more
walking for me...
Come on, just one final push, Luise.
If we stop for rest now,
the sun will set before we get there.
The sun would set?
It's still such a long way?
Well, I mean, it's possible...
I'm exhausted.
Also starving. And thirsty.
Oh my, now the rain, too!
What do we do?
Right...
Come on, everyone. Stick close by.
Why do we have to go through all of this?
I'm fed up!
If only we had taken the bus...
My, you don't suppose I'm to blame for that?
This rain had started now
because Lotte is so irritable about boring stuff.
You make it my fault now?
But you were the one who...
Hey, hey, people!
We're on our first family trip, remember?
Come on, with a glee! A glee!
Rain makes for perfect leisurely strolling.
Staying here would get us nowhere.
Come on, time for one final push.
Well, it's here. My uncle's villa.
Finally here!
I hope they got some warm milk for me to drink!
I'm showering first, okay?
Knowing my uncle,
I bet he prepared a gorgeous feast for us.
What's this?
Doesn't seem like anyone's home.
Returned to big city life until the next spring.
Why didn't you check with him aforehand, darling?
Ah... Well.
Dad's telegram is here, too.
What are we to do now, dad?
The night is almost here.
And we've nowhere else to go.
Ah, it seems, stopping here is our only option.
Here? How is that an option?
Honey, but what'll you do about the lock?
Please witness, as I conquer our way in.
Honey!
Are you okay?
Dad!
Yes, I'm all good.
My, that's so much like my husband.
One never knows what to expect from you.
Yeah... Either way, this gives us
some roof over our heads for tonight.
We're staying here?
Where I lay my hat is home.
Isn't that exciting, also at a night like that?
And this, to our first trip as a family of four!
Even the water drunk
in a place like this tastes special.
What's with everyone?
It's like you're attending a funeral.
Food tastes better if you eat it happily!
I honestly would have preferred
to stay home and study some more.
Come on, it can't be that you're all thinking
about what would have been if we didn't go on this trip?
I mean, why'd you think that, right?
That's just the way you always are.
Acting on the spur of the moment,
without any plan at all.
Learn a bit of self-reflection, please.
Excuse me, what?
Hear this, then!
You're the one always absorbed in work,
and as I take you out, you still...
You didn't think about children either,
even though they need to study.
Frau Serious in particular.
What's wrong with being serious?
Better that, than being too frivolous, like Luise.
Say, feigning an illness and skipping school
whenever you have an arithmetic test.
Excuse me?
Is that true, Luise?
No! That one time, I really-really had a bellyache!
I don't want your excuses!
Dad, and what about you?
What?
I saw it myself!
You went on a secret date with a young woman.
Is that so?
No, she misunderstood!
It was a business meeting!
Luise, I thought me and were always on the same side.
When facing a choice,
children always pick mother's side.
After all, it's the mother
who prepares their dinner daily.
Oh, it's called daily now?
Even if I do it myself at least three times a week?
That's right! Mom constantly brushes it off with "work"
and "more work," leaving all the laundry to me!
You should know those are not the same thing!
Instead, why don't we return
to the question of Luise skipping school?
But I'm telling you I didn't feign it!
Mom, now you believe it, too?
Well, did Lotte tell a lie, then?
Don't call me a teller of lies!
Enough!
Why is everyone putting on a vain act today?
Each one of you!
Look who's talking!
You were the one who started it.
It's the worst trip.
Fine, I heard you.
Not taking you out on a trip ever again.
No objections.
With that settled, I need to get my rest now.
So will I.
And I.
Suit yourself! The wicked need rest, too.
It's a disaster.
Worst ever.
My, what's becoming of our family so soon?
One is featherbrained, the other is headstrong.
Where did I take a wrong turn?
Still, why does it all have to come to this?
So much for our long-awaited
first ever family trip...
What?
What's this?
What's going on?
Something happened?
No... I don't have any idea...
Darling, the ceiling!
A fallen tree broke right through!
Oh my God!
Lotte and Luise are on the second floor!
Lotte! Luise!
Lotte, say something!
Dad! Lotte is... Lotte is in there!
Lotte! Lotte, are you safe?
Lotte! Answer something if you're all right! Lotte!
Step back, you two!
Lotte!
Lotte, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
The floor!
Floor is crumbling!
Lotte! Wake up!
Open your eyes!
Lotte? Lotte!
Lotte!
Lotte, are you okay? Are you hurt?
Yeah, I think I'm unharmed.
What?!
Wait! I'll try to reach you now! Stand still!
I'm coming too!
Never! What'll they do
if something happens to you as well?
But...
I said never, so it's never!
These children don't have anyone else
as important to them as you are.
Neither do I.
Darling...
Please be careful, darling!
Don't take any chances!
Come on, Lotte.
Move slowly and try to reach me.
I can't! I can't do that!
Lotte!
Lotte, now or never!
Jump with all your might!
I can't! I've never done anything like that!
You can do it, Lotte!
Please do it for me!
Do it with all seriousness,
like nobody else can do!
Actually... This seriousness of yours
is what I love the most about you!
Because if you wouldn't discipline me, I'd...
I'd remain a bungler for the rest of my life!
So please... Please do it!
Luise...
Dad...
Lotte.
You're alive...
You're alive and well!
Dad!
I'm so glad.
Yes...
Good morning, Luise.
Good morning, Lotte.
You seen mom and dad today?
I think they're up already. Let's go.
Good morning, mom, dad.
Dad, mom!
Hey, good morning.
Good morning.
Whoa! Goodness!
The house is in shambles.
Yeah... And uncle is probably
going to kill me when he finds out.
Dad, and what's that?
My famous bag.
The very one I left in my uncle's custody.
Still here!
Dad!
And mom!
This is my treasure from the past.
On this photo, they are barely a few days old!
One is acting up!
The other is smiling.
We were already this way!
At last, I could show it to you.
Is that why you arranged a trip?
The rumors were true,
you really are the world's best dad.
My, my! You sure sounded mighty different yesterday.
Did she really?
I don't remember!
Lotte and Luise now look with hope
into the distant future.
On the path of the Palfy family that had barely started,
some happy, some sad - myriads
of the most diverse happenings are waiting for them.
But whatever challenges they are bound to face,
by combining the powers of the four,
they can definitely overcome any obstacle.
After all, those four are one family now!
The End
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Thank you for sticking with it.
Yours truly, Perevodildo.