Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
Luise's heart was blooming more with each day
from having her loving mother always by her side.
As for Lotte, she started
taking piano lessons from her father.
The two that switched places had finally
come to realise the bright sides of their new lives.
Episode 11
Little Detective Agency
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
It's Sunday morning,
so dad is probably still asleep.
Let's try not to wake him while we clean up.
Whoa! A complete disarray!
Yes, in moderato!
"Luise, I know you'll be here in the morning again.
I've been working this whole night, and the only reason
I went to sleep was because I passed out.
I intend to get my sleep now, so until I'm a hundred years old,
please don't wake me up."
Hundred years old?
"Also, a letter for you,
supposed to be delivered on Rotenturmstraße,
apparently got mixed with correspondence
bound for this address."
Okay, Lotte! I'm going to the office now.
Good luck!
When will you be home?
Let's see. I don't think we'll have
the work up to our eyeballs today,
so I should be home by noon.
See you!
Ah, right, right.
A letter had arrived for you.
A letter?
Whom might it be from?
Lotte's letters are supposed to be in General Delivery.
It's from Stephie!
I have my dad and mom breaking up.
It seems, dad fell in love with another woman.
I hope she's not taking it too hard.
"Lotte, are you doing fine?
I'm writing to say my dad and mom
managed to reconcile."
Eh? They reconciled?
Mom had noticed, that dad
sneaks out of the house every night,
so she was steadfastly convinced
he is visiting his paramour.
But in reality, dad was just looking for a way to lose weight,
so he picked up karate classes again.
And he didn't tell to a single soul!
In the end, dad never managed
to lose even an ounce of weight through karate,
but during his row with mom,
he actually lost some due to uneasiness.
But as soon as they reconciled,
he started eating plentifully, just like before!
"Well, I guess losing some weight
will forever remain a pipe dream," he said!
I'm so happy for you, Stephie.
Oh, already done cleaning up in the atelier?
And I was about to do groceries,
so would look after the house?
Sure thing.
Yes, Palfy is listening.
Hello, I'm looking for my friend.
Is there anyone named Luise?
Ah? Luise here. It's me!
Lotte!
Can you talk now?
Yes. Nobody else is home.
But if you're calling like that...
Something happened?
Not at all!
I got a letter from Stephie.
And I got one, too!
I was so surprised! I bet, this very minute
all her friends from the summer camp feel the same!
Stephie's lucky, don't you think?
True.
If only our dad and mom
would also reconcile, one way or another...
Aren't you curious about why did our dad and mom
break up in the first place?
I'm thinking, it could be because of a misunderstanding,
just like in Stephie's case!
Both are constantly in a hurry,
they always jump to the wrong conclusions!
Do you... Do you suppose,
if it was really due to misunderstanding...
Ah!
Think they can reconcile, too?
That's right! They should be able to reconcile!
Hey, Lotte, how about we try to investigate
the cause of dad and mom's break-up?
Investigate it?
Listen to their own explanations!
No way!
As long as it would help to reconcile them,
I won't stop at anything!
Ah... So do I!
Ask him! The reason for break-up.
Ah! Mozart is amazing, after all.
How did he manage to give birth to a tune that enthralling
into a world that mundane?
Need to ask him now.
Why did he break up with mom.
Ah, Luise?
Thanks for your morning clean-up.
Dad, I need to ask you something.
What could it be?
Don't try to evade the question.
Put it frankly!
Oh my, oh my, how intimidating.
Would you look at that.
I mean... Please...
What is it, Luise?
Ah! It's no use. I can't ask.
I need to muster some courage.
Father...
I mean... That is... If you don't mind...
Why did Mozart only give birth to enthralling tunes
into this mundane world?
Is that what concerns you?
Ah... no. Actually, not! What I wanted...
Yeah, it's me!
All right, got it. Will be there now.
Luise, I have to go now
to conduct a final general rehearsal.
Tonight, I want you to show up as well.
Deal? Make sure to free up some time for that.
Ah... Dad, wait!
Before I forget! The reason Mozart
gave birth to such enthralling tunes -
that's rather simple,
he was a genius of about the same magnitude as your dad!
Will this suffice for an answer?
It's just impossible. For me at least.
Could she be the reason behind dad and mom's parting?
Oh, I see. So you've been fond
of that Palfy gent for some time?
Let me correct you there, father.
Mere "fondness" doesn't do it justice.
My fixation on him is out of this world.
Just as I thought, Frau Gerlach...
But then, what was Palfy's reaction to that?
You see, for the last ten years, he only had one woman in mind
while giving birth to his music.
Only one woman?
That must have been you!
Alas, it's been only half a year
since we got to know each other.
Is that so?
Who, then, might that woman be?
Hey-yo!
What are you up to, in a place like this?
Oh, sorry.
I was talking to the boy serving tea.
What a weird kid.
But let me tell you, this is highly ignoble of Palfy.
Being infatuated with another woman,
while having you around.
I am, most certainly,
several orders younger and prettier than her!
This is as clear as a day, Irene.
It appears, his ex-wife might also have a clue
of who this woman is.
Do you also suppose that woman
might have been what precipitated Palfy's divorce?
Who in the world is it?
If only I had any idea,
I would have given her a mouthful long ago!
Investigating the reason
behind your dad and mom's divorce?
Then, it's like Luise
had opened her little detective agency, right?
Little detective agency?
I'm nowhere near that talented.
And that woman Frau Gerlach mentioned...
How should I even start looking into it -
I don't have a single clue!
Alright, then we'll run this little detective agency together,
with joint efforts!
Me and Hans?
Oh, come on now, Resi!
Eavesdropping, too?
But I know exactly who that woman is!
Eh?
Last year, when cleaning up in Master's atelier,
I noticed a diary in a brown binding.
You peeked into dad's diary, didn't you?
Not in my life! I just glanced over it
and spotted some scribblings, accidentally.
It said "Pamina."
"Pamina?"
But I closed it immediately after,
so that's really all I've seen. I swear, it's the truth!
Or is it?
Maybe you glanced over anything else?
Well, if only a little.
"Oh, my passion springs eternal, Pamina.
In all my life, I only loved you."
There was a photo included, too!
But when I tried to look at it...
Like a bolt from the blue,
Master returned at that exact moment.
Seems like a pretty scrupulous "quick glance."
Unlikely!
Let's go, Luise.
Eh? Ah... Wait, Hans.
Hans, where are you going?
Hey, wait, Hans!
Where are you going?
We'll go there and look for the diary ourselves.
But we can't do that kind of thing!
The contents of dad's diary are private...
Then we'll just look at her photo.
Wait, Hans!
Do you want to find out, or not, Luise?
The reason behind your dad and mom's parting.
But I'm not ready to go as far
as peeking into his diary.
Then, let's strike a deal.
We'll only search three places for it.
If we don't find it still,
then have it your way.
I see.
Well, that's your choice.
Sorry. Even if I myself would have liked
to know Herr Palfy better out of my huge respect,
if the price for it is Luise's disappointment, I can't do that.
That's what I just realized.
Hans...
If you don't want it, we don't do it.
No need to gloom over that.
See you later, okay?
Wait, Hans.
If we search in only one place...
Might be over there!
I don't know...
If it was up to me...
A key.
And where's the lock?
That might be...
You know?
This casket, probably.
That's our one place!
Let's look inside.
But promise me that we'll back off after that.
I'm not sure it'll fit.
It it doesn't, so much for an investigation.
I'm opening it, ready?
It's open!
I changed my mind!
Gosh, dad is such a prankster!
It's like he always knew.
That's your investigation concluded.
This must be it.
What'll we do?
What should we do?
Ah, so it finally went off?
Yeah, I spent a good hour
choosing the most conspicuous spot for the scare box,
but Luise kept avoiding it,
as though on purpose.
I even thought I'd need to choose a new spot.
But dad, why did you return so soon?
Uh? It's for this. Forgot the main score
for tonight's big concert!
Ah! And that must be
Hans of the Winds, isn't that right?
Luise had told me some about you.
Honored to meet you.
Ah, speaking of which,
you're coming to listen to tonight's big concert
alongside Luise, don't you?
Unless... You've planned a date just for two?
No, not at all...
Thank you very much.
Fantastic.
That's one fantastic dad you got.
Somewhere in this opera hall,
Frau Pamina is listening, too.
This concert, too...
Are you conducting it for Frau Pamina, dad?
I guess, I should take a quick look.
But I'll return it tomorrow!
Luise, are you still awake?
Yes!
Come in.
Today, you seemed gloomier than ever.
I don't think I did.
Now I can't help worrying, if I was the one
who upset my Luise somehow, even without realizing it.
Oh, you shouldn't be...
Tonight's concert was excellent.
I couldn't help getting deeply moved by it.
That's a honey to my ears!
Only when a profound affection for someone
is overflowing me, the greatest music is born.
It was only thanks to that emotion
that I've been able to keep making music for ten years now.
I know. But I'm not feeling left out because of that.
Even if all the space in dad's heart
is currently occupied by Frau Pamina.
Pamina?
Is Frau Pamina a good person?
So that's what this all about, Luise?
You'd be mistaken to think that Pamina was the one
I cherished for those ten years.
No, it would also be wrong to say
I'm not one bit concerned about Pamina.
But still, it's nothing new,
as music fans are in love with her all over the world.
Yes. Pamina would remain a celebrity for all times.
After all, she's from Mozart's opera,
the heroine of The Magic Flute.
But... Then...
Who is the one that you cherish?
She has loose curly hair,
and bright eyes, like two blue jewels.
The only problem is that lately,
various trifles often mislead her into feeling lonely.
Luise, you'll always be the prime source of my music.
Tonight's concert was also my present of gratitude.
Are you still uneasy?
You're fantastic, dad!
Eventually, just for a second,
I couldn't help glancing into the brown diary.
Turns out, it was not a diary at all.
But instead, a complete libretto
of Mozart's Magic Flute opera.
"Oh, my love, Pamina..."
But also... Also one another thing.
I took the liberty to look at this precious photo,
squeezed between last pages.
In the end, I never managed
to get to the bottom of dad and mom's parting.
But there's at least one thing I now know for sure.
Dad still remembers
both of us.
A report like this was something
Lotte would be willing to write daily, till the end of times,
feeling fully surrounded by the love of her amazing father.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode preview
We switched places!
Luise, I'm begging you!
Try to dig out the truth behind dad and mom's parting.
Don't you worry,
I'll definitely make mom answer me.
Remember that Frau Luise here
doesn't tolerate those evading the question.
That's the spirit, Luise!
Spirit plays the decisive role in such matters.
Alright, root for me!
You won't give up, won't you?
Counting on you, Luise.
Next time in I and Myself:
The Secret Brought to Light.
Episode 12
The Secret Brought to Light
Look forward to it!