Pretending to be Luise, Lotte had rendered
her dad speechless at the sight of a special dish she made.
Accordingly, while pretending to be Lotte, Luise
had bungled her cooking spectacularly and with a bang.
The big adventure of the two little hearts is ongoing.
Episode 7
The Classes Start
Translation: Perevodildo    |    Timings: Sub-RoRo
Hurry up, Luise!
Whoa, me and Lotte are both in opera!
That's not what I brought you here for.
We're in trouble!
That's just our usual dad, not a thing is off about him.
Watch closely.
That woman...
You think she might be dad's mistress?
What do I do?
What do I do, Luise?
Luise? Luise. Luise...
Luise... Ah, Luise?
A dream?
This is certainly bothering me a great deal
Good morning, Peperl.
Thank you for your concern.
Let me make you a tasty breakfast in return.
What could be the meaning of this?
Luise suddenly cleaning my room like that.
There's more to this than meets the eye.
The one I knew prior to summer camp
is like a different person from the one that returned.
Before, if you peek into Luise's room...
It was a scene of bedlam.
Never mind cleaning,
even a banal tidying up seemed unthinkable.
And if you compare her to the current Luise...
Dad, mind your manners.
From today on, I will be making you
a breakfast every morning!
Now, you can come home for it,
even if you stayed overnight in atelier.
A mystery.
He's deep in thought.
Could it be because of that woman yesterday?
Ah, it must certainly be it!
He is looking so restless...
She has not once in her life been this quiet.
What might be occupying her thoughts?
Should I ask directly?
I made up my mind.
- Luise.
- Dad...
- What is it?
- Yes?
Well, dad, you go first.
Ah... No, I would like to hear you out first.
Good morning, Luise!
Truda stopped by to say hello.
Good morning, Truda.
School starts today.
Let's go together!
You don't mean to say you haven't eaten yet, do you?
Yeah. Already finished.
Wait, I'll be ready in a minute.
I'm off!
We're off, Luise's dad.
Take care, Frauleins.
Let's face it, you're hiding something, don't you?
Terribly sorry, Herr Master.
Last night, I was feeling mighty hungry, so before I knew it,
I helped myself to just one of your precious donuts.
Well, maybe two.
Donuts?
Those weren't yours?
Then I guess it shouldn't be your concern. Yes.
I'm just hopeless.
Still struggling to make a talk with dad.
And it the future, it'll only get worse, I imagine.
Luise?
Where are you going?
Did you forget the way to school?
This is the school Luise attends.
What's the matter?
You look like you're seeing this school for the first time.
It's just that we've been away for a while.
I can't wait to see my other friends again.
Let's go now.
We don't want to be late.
Ah, I'll be late again.
Late!
Lotte, mind your manners!
You don't eat while running.
But I'm also running late!
Suit yourself then.
But I'll go ahead, now.
Ah... Wait, wait! I'm coming with you!
Can you keep up with me?
Yeah!
I'm going this way now.
And I'm...
Lotte, ketchup!
Mom, your hair roller!
Later!
I'll be home by six tonight!
I'll be waiting!
And now, "after the poplar tree, turn right."
Huh? This doesn't seem to be the place.
I followed the notes exactly,
but the school is nowhere to be seen!
Found it, found it!
Right there!
Good morning!
Morning, everyone.
Hey, hey, did you hear?
Lotte had slapped Annie on her face yesterday!
No way! Our Lotte? Our Annie?
Ilse!
Good morning.
Is everything well?
Don't come near me.
Please. And don't try to talk to me.
Did I offend you somehow?
I thought I was just trying to defend you from Annie.
But I never asked you to slap Annie!
Now she's coming back for me later!
Why would she target you?
I was the one who fought Annie, and I did it myself.
That's... what Annie told me.
Annie!
Hey, Lotte Körner,
Frau Annie needs to have a word with you.
Frau Annie? A word?
What's this all about?
Frau Annie had taken a grave offense
in your behaviour yesterday.
To express her protest, she won't ever again
condescend to talking to Lotte personally.
Therefore, from now on, she will rely on our -
Maria and Miria's heralding services.
Frau Annie said, until you apologize to her,
she would never forgive you two!
One, two...
Is it clear?
What will you do, Lotte?
Annie is gravely injured this time!
She'll start harassing me even more!
Don't you worry about that.
I'll be there to protect you.
Now, let's go.
Is that clear? When the denominator
is smaller than the numerator,
you need to calculate how many times
the nominator is more than denominator.
Lotte Körner?
Are you not feeling quite well today?
Usually, I'd not expect you to fall out of line in the class.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then, would you please tell us the answer to this problem?
I don't know it.
Did you hear it?
Lotte said she doesn't know it!
How odd.
Have you not been listening to my explanation at all?
Pay attention!
Well, I will now be writing the right answers.
Everyone, check them against your own calculations.
She's doing it again!
She thinks I'll not stand up to my promise
just because we're in the class!
Now this is too much!
Teacher, it's Lotte!
Lotte, what's the meaning of this?
Shucks... She blew the whistle before I could strike.
Why is it unsuitable?
Don't you see how this article
is prejudiced towards one of the sides, Missis Körner?
Miss Körner!
This article is nothing but a product
of extensive research on the matter!
Excuse me...
What is it? We're busy now.
You can bring it later.
A call for Frau Körner...
So...
For me?
We'll finish this when I'm back.
Damn straight!
Yes, Körner listening.
Yes.
Eh? Lotte did? In the class?
Yes, I see.
I'll go there right away.
Editor, we'll have to settle our article disagreement
after I return from some other place.
Ah... Hey, wait a minute! Hey!
Are you kidding me?!
Which one of us is Editor-in-Chief here?
It seems, this school is somewhat lagging behind
my old school in Munich.
Oh, what do I ever do about the upcoming test?
It's so difficult, no way anyone is going to pass!
Ah, this is so bothersome.
Hey, Luise, can you understand that problem?
Eh?
Margarete, do you seriously expect Luise
to help you with that kind of thing?
Hey, what problem is it?
This one.
I see.
This is pretty easy.
And...
You bring them to the same denominator
and just sum up the upper part.
Great!
The same for the next one.
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Huh?
Tell me, do you also see Luise
explaining the recent material to everyone?
This can't be true.
So I thought.
Ah! Something bad happened!
Luise is at it again!
She hit someone and now they're crying.
Leave her alone!
Luise, you're at it again?
You're wrong!
Well...
I tripped and tore my skirt while falling!
But then, Luise...
Offered to mend it.
Oh?
My!
Yes?
Ah, teacher? The pleasure is mine.
Eh? It's about Luise again?
Yes.
Yes, I'll head there immediately.
Yes. Well then...
There we go again, I guess.
What was it this time?
She fought someone?
No.
Then, climbed the tree in the schoolyard?
Nothing of the kind.
Why, then...
Truth be told, I don't know how to put it...
She was helping the other girls to study.
Eh?
She even volunteered to water the flowerbed!
And then...
During the class, she has also been
more compliant and docile than ever.
In stark contrast with before,
as soon as we present the problem,
she raises her hand first in the class
to solve it spectacularly.
Lotte bullying Annie?
They say, she slapped her yesterday.
This can't be!
She is the most peaceful child.
Or so she has been until now...
In contrast, she's been constantly jiggling today.
Made no effort whatsoever of listening to the material.
What could have affected Lotte,
our exemplary student?
I wish someone would explain it to me...
Frau Mother, did you loose your grip
on supervising her behaviour?
I am terribly sorry.
Well, if you excuse me.
I'm sorry. Because of me,
they even called you out from work.
Never mind it. I'm certain that the person you hit
had seriously deserved it, somehow.
Mom...
Make way, make way!
Make way, you hear?
Can't you see I need to pass through here?
You daft dotard, don't you know who I am?
I beg your pardon.
In this town, I am quite the figure!
You find it appropriate to throw stuff
at a figure of such magnitude?
That's right! Don't you mess with my daddy!
Now pick my hat up!
Pick it up, you!
Not so fast!
How can you treat
someone older than you this way?
Oh? Oh-ho-ho.
Annie, isn't it that very girl?
The brat called Lotte that attacked you.
You've a good eye, daddy.
Here is the Lotte who had attacked me yesterday!
Yeah, I could tell.
She has a face of a ruffian!
I am Lotte's mother.
Your may be a figure of infinite girth,
but you're still equal to other humans.
You will yourself pick up the hat
that you dropped yourself.
She has a delicate face,
but she likes to play strong of heart​!
What are you doing?!
You're in the school, an institution for children.
I won't stand you lighting a cigar here.
Bring it outside, if want it so much.
Right, right.
I like a woman who doesn't fret at the sight of me.
Not everyone knows to speak so frankly.
Your intrepid kind is in decline these days.
Please spare me your patting.
Oh my, is he okay?
Frau Körner, what a fine example
you give to your daughter!
You deem it appropriate for one
to raise a hand at others?
A thousand pardons.
And you, Lotte?
We're sorry!
Show some repentance!
We repent.
One more to the bag of unsolved mysteries!
Are you that much concerned with her
suddenly acquiring a talent for learning?
This really is highly unusual.
I don't see how that is one bit unusual.
After all, even if your daughter's hidden talent
suddenly wakes up in her, it's the most natural thing.
Don't you understand?
Her father is Herr Palfy. The acclaimed genius!
Well, that's a good explanation.
I thought so, too!
That's relieving.
I'm glad you could solve this for me!
To you, Herr Palfy.
Thank you, Frau Gerlach.
Oh, no need to be that formal.
Feel free to call me Irene.
Peperl, could you imagine it?
It seems, that woman is none other than dad's mistress!
Consult with Luise?
No way! What if mom answers the phone?
Still...
Five pfennig coins: 5, 10, 15, 20, and one mark.
Also, 15 pfennigs in 3 notes.
With a compensation
for the broken chair and the picture...
Mom, compensation for hat, too.
Duly noted.
Ah, there goes two weeks' worth of salary...
But the numerator is a month's worth!
But at least it was fun!
I was relieved, seeing Annie's dad tumble down the stairs.
So did I.
Ah, this face Annie's dad made back then!
But still, I need you to understand, Lotte.
In the end, resorting to violence
doesn't solve anything.
From now on, keep your cool
when you feel like doing it again.
Got it.
Alright... Now, whatever happens, I'll be one step ahead
and would try to outwit Annie without violence.
You can count on my help with that!
Yes, Körner listening.
Hello?
Hey, hey, mom!
How do you like this idea...
Hello?
Huh? Hung up?
That's odd.
Hello? Hello?
Must be that they got a wrong number.
Lotte, it was you who just called, right?
Are you doing well and fine?
How was your own first day in school?
Lotte.
Lotte, what's the matter?
No, nothing. Yeah!
The school is the only good thing that happened today...
Well, it'll pass.
Luise, I won't let you down.
Now, where were we...
After hearing mom's voice even for just a second,
Lotte couldn't help getting struck with feelings of longing.
However, when the letter arrived, informing her of the commotion that Luise and mother caused in school today,
the one laughing her head off
would also be none other than Lotte.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
We two switched places!
Hey, Luise! What else could I do
to start getting along better with dad?
Let me think. I know!
Dad's birthday is approaching.
Dad's birthday?
That would be your best chance!
I see!
Luise, I just had a fantastic idea. How about we celebrate
dad's birthday simultaneously in Munich and in Vienna?
I love it! Good Idea, as they say it.
Next time in I and Myself:
Dad's Birthday.
Episode 8
Dad's Birthday
Don't miss it!