Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
An exemplary student, Lotte
surprised everyone by scoring 100 on a test.
In turn, the hoyden Luise
nearly started a brawl in the class.
The two may have switched places,
but they are still to get used to their new roles.
Episode 8
Dad's Birthday
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
And this...
Resi, I was checking housekeeping account book here...
Oh no! You can't be playing
with a housekeeping account book.
I checked the account for this month only,
but the calculations are already largely off.
Oh, is that so?
Even though I'm diligently updating it day after day...
Let's see...
For today's shopping,
you allocated 50 schilling for vegetables, right?
Liquid detergent - 20 schillings 40 groschens.
Meat - 5 schillings 30 groschens.
And then, even if we add Peperl's food expenses...
See? Doesn't add up.
About 10 shillings of change are missing.
Eh, well... I'm pretty sure
I didn't get any change back then...
Resi.
Ah... What are you doing?
I take it those candies
are what became of the change?
Terribly sorry, Young Fraulein...
On nearly every page,
Resi, your cooking expenses are overblown.
From now on, adding up figures
and keeping a housekeeping account book -
all the pecuniary matters I will supervise personally.
Eh? All of them?
Understood.
May I add, Young Fraulein
had never been that meticulous before.
Don't worry, Resi. Seeing how you depend on it,
I will allocate some budget on snacks for you. A plentiful.
Are you serious?
Thanks you very much!
A plentiful of gratitude from me!
Naturally, a plentiful for Peperl, too.
Rest assured.
Dad, you're back already?
Needed to collect some scores.
Then, I'll make you some tea now.
Ah, no need. I'm in a hurry.
I see.
Is he going out for a date with that woman again?
What's the matter?
Such a disheartened look.
While I'm here, Luise, is there anything
you wanted to tell me today?
Eh? No, I don't have anything to say.
Ah... I see. Some other time, then.
Dad!
Yes, Luise?
It's nothing.
Take care.
I will, then.
"Take care, but only after I kiss you."
I'll never be able to say that.
You see, I spend my whole life
living with mother, up until now.
I haven't a clue how would dad react
if I try to kiss him.
And it's been a week already since I've arrived!
Oh, Frau Irene.
Herr Palfy, fancy a ride?
I could give you a lift.
Yeah, thanks.
Is something bothering you?
Your whole being says "deep in thought."
It's something about my daughter Luise again.
The way she was before, she'd invariably
cuddle me and give me a kiss, whenever I'm going out.
But these days, nothing?
Yeah. She didn't do it even today, on my birthday.
Your birthday?
In all the previous years,
she'd be sure to come to atelier in the morning,
hands full of presents and bouquets.
And today..?
Nothing.
May I have somehow
fallen into Luise's disfavor?
Thanks for the food.
Aren't you lucky to be a grown-up?
Can even sleep until the noon.
Whoa, whoa! Can I not redeem myself
even by the fact I was working until late?
I have no sway even over my own sleep!
I'm happy enough to just know
you'd be home when I return from school.
The evening shift should be made a norm!
This may happen elsewhere,
but certainly not in our magazine!
Well, I'll have to leave soon.
Will you wash this for me?
I'll see you off.
Hey, mom.
You know what day it is today?
Too late for sports day,
too soon for Christmas matinee.
What day is it?
A birthday!
Whose?
Well... Uh...
Of a friend of mine!
Anyway, good luck with your work.
See you later, then.
Take care!
A friend?
Well, so be it.
Oh, it's hot.
Herr Postman!
Any General Delivery letters from Vienna?
There are, Lotte.
The second one in a row.
Thank you.
Who in the world might be sending those?
Can't tell!
Bye-bye! See you.
Watch where you run!
Luise, there is something
we totally need to discuss directly.
On the seventh, at two o'clock sharp,
I want you to call me.
This would be the time
when I and only I will be there to answer.
On the seventh...
Today... Today at two?
Shucks! Two o'clock is now!
It's almost time.
A call from Luise.
Fraulein, I need to mop the room,
so I'd like you to wait outside for a moment.
Resi, can't you mop somewhere else for now?
Everywhere else is mopped already.
But how about the bathroom?
There, too.
We're in trouble.
While Resi is in the room,
I can't talk to Luise on the phone.
Hey, but what if you take Peperl on a walk outside?
But that's something only you ever do.
Today, Peperl is beside himself
about going out with Resi!
Have a safe walk!
My, the phone!
I'll take care of this!
A nice walk!
Hello?
Lotte!
Luise.
Lotte... You're Lotte, aren't you?
Luise!
Great, great!
Great, I finally got to hear you!
It's still been a little over a week
but it feels like ages had passed already!
So, are you doing well?
Better than ever! Mom was just like Lotte described her:
very kind and with a great perfume.
Also a bit feather-headed, just like I am!
How was it on your end?
What's that supposed to mean?
Actually...
Eh? Dad has a mistress?
Yes. I was afraid you also don't know.
Is there really a woman other than mom that dad loves?
I don't know.
But...
It appears, he enjoys her company a good deal.
Even when he's there with you?
I have...
not been out with dad yet, because he is always busy.
He spends most of the time in atelier.
You mean to say, you spend all this time on your own?
This lousy dad gives more love to some broad
and to his work than to his Lotte?!
That's beyond outrageous!
Ouch.
You okay, Luise?
Lotte, you need to take a decisive action!
Like celebrating dad's birthday, for instance!
Dad's birthday?
Have you celebrated yet?
His birthday... is today?
Did I...
Forget to tell you aforehand?
Great! Great idea!
Up until now, I've only been celebrating mom's birthday.
But now I get to take part in dad's birthday, too!
Right, for the first time, you do.
Indeed! And I have a fantastic plan!
Fantastic plan?
We will both celebrate dad birthday,
in two different places!
Both in Munich and in Vienna.
In Munich and in Vienna?
Starting simultaneously, at six tonight.
Sounds incredibly fun!
I'm in, I'm in.
I know, right?
It's a promise! At six! Bye!
She sounded might ecstatic.
I hope it all goes fine.
Well, we'll see.
Dad's birthday...
Thanks for your purchase!
My, Luise, is there a carnival in the city?
Herr Strobl?
Good Lord, I can't even see your face.
Good day!
Ooh, that excitement does wonders to your little face.
Doctor's beard is also handsome today!
That's something only Luise could say!
Actually, I was on my way to the Opera House.
Want me to say something to your dad while I'm there?
Ah! That's just what I needed!
Then, could you give him the letter
from my left pocket?
This one?
It's an invitation.
An invitation, eh?
Oh! We've met in the...
OK. Now, let's do one final rehearsal
from the very first act.
I wanted to ask, Frau,
if you could pass this to Palfy after he's done.
You can count on me.
Alley-hop.
Now, how do you like this, Peperl?
Wish I could show it to Luise, too!
Ten years' worth of birthdays
that we spent apart...
are all getting repaired in a single evening!
Now, it's time for us to change.
Dad should be here soon!
Dad, congratulations on your birthday!
Lotte and dad are probably
having a party right about now.
I hope they're getting along well.
Herr Palfy!
Frau Irene?
You've been waiting all this time?
Even if it was still just a rehearsal,
this performance is spellbinding already!
Oh, no need, no need.
Do you have any plans
for the rest of the evening?
Let me think...
Uh...
Oh well, guess I'm free.
My, sublime!
I'm free as well.
Then, care to accompany me for a dinner?
Yes, with big pleasure.
Imperial Hotel
Something bothers you still?
Yeah, you see...
I just can get Luise out of my mind.
Lately, she's definitely hiding something from me.
I think, it started with her
going to the summer camp.
In some bizarre way,
I think, I may just know what you mean.
The girl's feelings in that age
are rather easy to read.
Eh?
She must be just feeling lonely.
Lonely?
My Luise?
Yes. After all, she's still a child
and she is having to grow up without a mother by her side.
But then...
Luise is yearning to have a mother, too?
Girls depend on their mom
more than on anyone else.
A mother...
Herr Palfy, maybe it's just me thinking out loud,
but suppose you remarry sometime about now,
wouldn't that provide for the most natural way
to give Luise a mother?
And I also think, I probably would provide
for a splendid mother myself.
For this week's front cover,
I'm considering one of those three portraits.
Unless someone here can think of a better one?
Ah! I can!
Who would it be?
I think, today is that man's...
That man?
Which man?
Do you mean to say dad gives more love to that woman
and to his work, than to his Lotte?
This can't be the truth.
This can't...
Be...
Remarry?
Like me...
and you?
Ah! So sorry!
My, this dress is ruined!
I beg a thousand pardons.
Luise?
Ah, this is something Herr Strobl entrusted me with
while you were busy rehearsing.
Dad, world's most spectacular birthday party
takes place tonight.
Be sure to witness it in atelier at six.
At six?
Ah! Good Heavens!
Apologies, I am urgently needed elsewhere!
Boy, give her whatever she wants.
Okay.
Herr Palfy!
Are you serious?
My, this is scandalous!
He values this little shrimp more than me?!
And just as I was starting to get somewhere!
I beg you to forgive him for the clamor.
Frau Gerlach, your purse!
Salute to Herr Palfy. Young Fraulein...
Dad...
Luise.
Dad!
Luise!
I knew it...
I knew it that you'd come!
I'm guilty for making you wait.
Love you!
I love you, dad!
Dad...
Can I kiss you?
You most certainly can!
The most precious kiss in the world, too.
And now, dad's turn.
Your bristle is spiky!
Lotte and Dad's party,
I hope it went well.
Lotte.
Your friend that had a birthday today,
who was it, after all?
It was Ilse's.
Well, goodnight now!
And good luck with your work!
So I thought. Lotte cannot possibly know
it's her father's birthday.
Luise, can I ask just one thing?
Don't you think it's about time
you finally let me know what happened
in the summer camp to cause such a change in you?
Eh? Oh, that...
I met someone.
Who might it be?
Some girl who has been growing up without a mom.
We argued first, but quickly became best friends.
And that's all?
That alone has been enough to turn you
into a diligent girl that loves cooking?
Yeah. That alone.
I see. This sheds light on the entire conundrum.
Through an encounter with another girl like her, Luise realised
how important it is to have a mother in the house.
It seems, she really yearns for mother, after all.
Thank goodness.
I nearly blew it.
Luise has been feeling lonely, huh?
So Irene was right all the way through,
I might just need to start looking for a new mother.
Ah, but who could have thought
that woman is actually so much into me.
I wonder how is he doing by now.
I bet, still as much a woman magnet as ever,
and still drooling when you spot a good one.
Something's wrong, dad?
Ah? Ah, no. Nothing at all.
Soothed by the long-awaited success
in getting along with dad,
Lotte's mind is engulfed completely in gentle dreams.
After all, tonight
for the first time in life, she is able
to embrace her dad's warmth with all her heart.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
We two have switched places!
Lotte, I'm seriously in trouble!
I'd never tell becoming Lotte would be that hard!
It's not easier for me, Luise!
It's cooking and cooking, day after day!
I'll never be able to cook as good as Lotte,
or get that good scores on a test!
No way! At least try!
I'm telling you, it's impossible!
Doesn't matter! If you want to be
with your dear dad again, you'll endure it!
Next time in I and Myself:
Mom's Home Cooking.
Episode 9
Mom's Home Cooking
Look forward to it!