Having ascertained the reason
behind dad and mom's divorce, Lotte and Luise
were relieved to know that apparently,
their parents parted on good terms.
And in that case,
it wouldn't be impossible for them to reconcile.
The heaviness in Lotte's chest had subsided.
Episode 13
Lotte's Quandary!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Okay, next pair.
Lotte is coming next, Frau Annie.
Horizontal bar is Lotte's archenemy! Which means...
She'll be the clumsiest girl in the class!
Rightly so, then Annie would only be the second.
And after her...
Shut up!
Next pair!
Look!
Way to go! Show us your prowess already!
What's the best technique in the class?
Wow!
My...
Lotte, you nailed it!
You must have practiced a lot for this.
Eh? You think so?
Yes!
Okay, next pair, then.
Annie!
It's your turn now. Don't keep us waiting.
Okay!
If dad and mom manage to reconcile somehow,
me and Luise would be able to live together again!
Like a family of four people.
Can you imagine how fun that'd be?
Luise!
Truda?
Sitting quietly, absorbed in thoughts, smiling lightly -
since when are you like that?
Oh, but I haven't been smiling!
Whatever, let me show you something!
What is it?
5!
6!
7!
8!
Impressive, Ingrid!
You revolved eight times!
This way, our class is certain to emerge victorious!
The tomorrow inter-class competition is predefined!
Not so fast, everyone!
Truda?
Don't you disregard our class so carelessly!
What do you mean?
We have Luise, who can do much more than that!
Ten, or twenty times - piece of cake!
Right?
Eh? What do you mean?
Horizontal bar!
Horizontal bar?
Now I'm in trouble.
I can't do the horizontal bar for toffee!
Ah! Right, in our class, there's also Luise!
The great maestro of horizontal bar, right?
Yeah...
Now, give them a little demonstration,
as a representative of our class.
Luise, do your best.
Go ahead, Luise.
With your usual flair!
Wait, okay?
I don't see the need
to compete with another class in that...
What's the matter, Luise?
Usually, you'd be the one proposing it
and leading in the vanguard.
Still...
Come on, hurry up!
She can't do it!
Just admit it and don't force yourself, Luise.
That's right!
Your know you can't win against Ingrid! Right?
I've been promoting you up to this point,
so don't make me blush, Luise!
You just gotta do more than eight,
whatever it takes!
But I don't feel quite in the mood today...
Oh, enough babbling!
What now?
Luise!
Let's start with a simple back hip circle.
Eh? What's a back hip circle?
Ah! I guess I just gotta do something at least.
Ouch!
Luise, are you okay?
Are you hurt somewhere?
Oh, you!
See you!
Good bye.
'Till tomorrow!
Hey, are you still mad at me?
I've never been "mad."
Just embarrassed.
I'm sorry.
I feel a bit off today.
Luise, you're strange!
What happened?
What do you mean?
Well, I can get behind your sudden talent for studying,
I can get behind being mindful about others...
But what happened today...
What in the world had happened to our old Luise?
I don't think...
You used to be quick on the uptake,
a tomboy and an arithmetic bungler,
but a gym class enthusiast,
Luise who always speaks whatever is on her mind!
An "exemplary student Luise" is a bore!
Oh goodness, I can't allow this.
Eat this! Don't you dare
calling me an exemplary student!
Even stranger now.
How do I handle this? Gym class today...
The class representative in horizontal bar...
If I don't do something about it,
I might as well scribble "Not Luise" on my forehead.
Say, Peperl.
Why was Luise so fond of the gym class?
What's taking Young Fraulein so long?
It's way past her usual time to wake up.
She'll be late for school!
Huh?
Fraulein, what in the world had happened?
You're as red as a tomato.
I don't feel so well.
Head is buzzing, too.
I don't want to eat.
Oh my?
But you don't seem to have any fever.
I really don't like the looks of it.
I'll go consult with Master at once.
Don't, Resi.
Eh? But what if something's wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong, I am all right.
We shouldn't give dad any reason for concern.
Then, I should at the very least
send for Doctor Strobl.
No need! I said it's fine, okay?
I don't want to see anyone.
Ah, is that so?
I think I know now, Fraulein.
How about you give yourself some rest?
Just for today.
Just staying in bed
and getting your well-deserved sleep, right?
Oh, I see! If I stay home,
I'll be spared the horizontal bar class.
It's been quite some while
since Fraulein played hooky last time.
Could she be fearing an arithmetic test again?
Ah? Luise is absent today?
Yeah, seems so.
Before, she was only ever absent
on arithmetic test days.
But there's no arithmetic test planned for today.
Did she really fall ill?
This is getting beyond weird now.
I should go check on Luise myself to be sure.
Truda?
Isn't that Truda?
Eh?
Christine!
Long time no see.
Looking good, girl!
Ah, this is my little brother Martin.
They always make me look after the children,
it's such a pain.
Good afternoon, Herr Martin.
Good afternoon, sis.
But say, we've barely left the summer camp,
yet it already feels such a distant memory!
Ah! Luise is doing well, too?
She does, just...
Right, right, Luise even met this girl Lotte then.
They were so similar, like twins!
I still remember how they got a similar hairdo
to confuse everyone completely!
Lotte... like a twin...
Back then, in order to ascertain
which one is the real Luise,
you pulled them both on their braids!
And then, the one that was Luise
gave you a hearty slap!
I haven't laughed that hard in my life!
Lotte... Luise... Could it be..?
What's on your mind, Truda?
Hey, Christine.
Will you hear me out?
What's the matter?
In an instant, you're the epitome of serious.
Luise is acting strange.
I even think, she might not really be our Luise.
Eh? What are you saying? It's impossible...
I'm convinced by now,
this Luise must actually be Lotte!
No way!
Lotte?
That alone wouldn't be enough
to say Luise is actually Lotte.
Why can't one become serious about math,
even if suddenly?
Or why can't one just make a mistake
on the horizontal bar?
But then, consider, also, that she played hooky today.
Before, she only did that
for when we had an arithmetic test.
But if you suppose it's Lotte, everything adds up perfectly!
Lotte couldn't even swim, remember?
Uh-huh. She was only ever playing in shallows.
And she was clumsy in dodgeball, too.
Lotte isn't good in any kind of sports.
Never mind the horizontal bar.
But hey, why do you suppose
they would switch places?
This... I don't know.
Alright, go there now
and invite Luise to hang out with us.
Eh? Right now?
Exactly so.
We'll ascertain it here and now.
You're right.
Wait here.
Better yet, bring her to the park by the canal!
Got it!
Come in!
Fraulein, Truda is here to check on you.
Truda?
Apparently, there is someone she wants you to meet.
Someone I need to meet?
But she knows I took a rest from school today...
Oh, that won't be a problem, Fraulein!
By this point, everyone around you knows
when you're playing hooky!
Eh? Everyone knows?
I mean, come on,
weren't you supposed to have arithmetic test today?
Eh? Ah... Right... Right you are!
Then, I just need a moment to change.
Tell her to wait, will you?
Sure, got you covered.
Oh my! Has Luise been this spoiled a girl
for her whole life?
Just like Christine said, we'll ascertain it on the spot.
Resi, could you come here for a second?
Luise's dad! Okay...
Good afternoon.
Ah, Truda? Good afternoon.
You mind if I ask you one thing about Luise?
About Luise?
What can I help you with, Master?
Ah... I left my address book here.
Have you seen it?
No, I don't think I saw it.
Hm... Pretty sure it was still here
last time I used it.
I can't do without it.
Could you try looking for it everywhere else?
Sure, will get to it right away.
Please do.
Excuse me,
don't you think that Luise had changed recently?
Luise?
Ah, that girl sure did change.
Oh, so you know?
She's like a completely different girl, isn't she?
Yeah. The change has been so profound,
it was hard to comprehend.
And I might just have an idea
as to what had caused it.
Now, that's strange... And here?
In the summer camp, during summer vacations
Luise had happened
to meet one particularly interesting girl.
That girl...
Truda, I'm ready!
Welcome home, dad.
Hey, Luise.
Have you seen my address book anywhere?
That would be right here.
Here. This one, right?
Ah, yes, it is. Thank you.
Well, dad, aren't you in a hurry now?
Have a safe trip!
Got it. I'm off now.
Oh, what a bummer.
I was so close to asking!
Whoa! That was a very close call.
I was so close to being discovered!
Wait though, what was it Truda was telling me about?
Something about Luise and the summer camp...
Ah, whatever.
Say, Truda, who that might be?
The person I'm to meet.
It's rather simple.
Look! There she is.
Ah! Christine's here!
Christine!
Luise!
Long time no see!
Truly! Doing fine?
Christine, you?
Doing finer than fine!
You can just ask my parents,
who get called to school two times a day!
Our house is near this place.
And there is my little brother Martin.
They always make me look after him.
Such a pain!
You have a brother...
And he is adorable!
By the way, Luise.
Yes?
I ran into Christine on the street earlier,
and then, before we knew it, we were talking about you.
What is it? Something wrong with my face?
Shucks, not much I could say by just looking.
Eh? What do you mean?
It's about Truda.
She thinks you ain't our real Luise.
She's somehow convinced
you're just Lotte Körner who switched places with her.
Oh my! Why'd you ever think I might be Lotte?
Say what you will,
but I don't believe I'm talking to Luise now.
But Truda, this is the real me!
Why, then, have you been acting so strange ever since
we returned from the camp and the school term started?
What are you saying? I'm not one bit strange!
Very strange!
However, if we suppose you're actually Lotte,
it's not strange at all!
That's... just a bunch of rubbish.
Because I am Luise!
Nah-ah. You're definitely Lotte!
There's a surefire way to tell Luise from Lotte.
Ouch!
Why did you do this?
Oh no, I was supposed to slap her.
Told you!
You're Lotte, aren't you?
Lotte.
Help me, sister!
Martin! Martin!
Hang on!
Ah! What's going on?
Help me, sister!
Luise!
Oh no! If this Luise is actually Lotte,
she can't swim!
Idiot! Why are you saying this now?!
But it's true...
Where is Martin?
Sister!
Look! She is drowning!
No way!
Martin... Need to save Martin!
Martin! I'm coming!
Hang on!
Martin! Martin!
Look!
She is swimming...
Martin!
You can do it, Luise!
Luise, do your best!
Please, Luise!
Just a little more, Luise!
Almost there!
Keep going!
Please!
Just a little more!
Did it!
She saved him...
She managed it! Our Luise!
Yeah!
I'm so glad!
Martin? Martin! Are you okay?
Martin!
Martin, are you hurt?
Can you recognize your sister?
Sister!
I'm so sorry. I had just one job,
and yet I somehow bungled even that!
Are you okay, Luise?
I jumped without even thinking...
Thank you, Luise.
You really saved him from the worst!
That's right. Tell me our Luise is not amazing!
But I'm not...
That was our telltale sign.
Now we know you're not Lotte.
You're Luise, hand on heart.
I'm sorry, Luise.
I doubted you.
No need, it's fine.
But really, without you,
we'd never have managed, Luise.
That was unexpected even to myself.
But, really, I'm just happy
I've been able to save Martin.
Then, little Martin who fell in the river...
was selflessly rescued by Luise!
Through saving Martin, I made all Truda's doubts vanish.
But then, there's one more news I need to share.
I learned to do the back hip circle!
I was convinced, the frontiers of gymnastics would forever
remain sealed to me, but turns out, if I try, I can do even this.
Nearly revealed by Truda, the precious secret,
binding the two together, is safe once again.
Somehow, at the last moment,
Lotte managed to preserve it, and even more.
However, will Luise be able to do her part?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode
We two switched places!
Lotte, you know Frau Leitner, don't you?
Yeah. It's my piano teacher.
About a year ago, she moved to Bonn.
But now, that teacher had returned! Which means...
She wants to renew the lessons?
It seems so.
What'll you do, Luise?
I'll manage. Just trust me with this, will you?
But you don't know a thing about playing piano!
Next time in I and Myself:
I Can't Play the Piano.
Episode 14
I Can't Play the Piano
Don't miss it!