Everything that had happened, now seems to be
but a test from the contriving minx, which is fate.
A few words left unsaid, a tiny misunderstanding unsolved
and the entire family ends up being torn apart once again.
The day Lotte was supposed to return to Munich,
the two pleaded with their father:
"There's only one thing that we want.
That is...
For us all to live together,
as a family of four."
And then...
I want to marry you, Luiselotte.
It's you.
It's you who I need.
I do. And our children do.
Episode 28
Best Birthday Ever
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
But you're already...
Yes. It's true that I had proposed a marriage
to Frau Irene Gerlach.
However, last night...
As the parting with Lotte was drawing near,
it dawned upon me for the first time.
If I marry Frau Irene,
I'll never forgive myself for it.
I had been inconceivably wrong.
So first thing in the morning,
I headed for her house.
I went there to revoke our engagement.
But then, suddenly, the tables have turned,
when she was actually the one
who initiated the cancellation of engagement.
She did that in response to me giving her
a cold shoulder the day before.
Unknowingly, I mistreated her.
Editor-in-Chief Bernau is a hearty guy, too.
If you marry him, there would hardly be
a single rainy day in your life.
And I know, he'd dote on Lotte as much as I do.
When returning to Vienna last time, I thought I'd send you
and Editor Bernau my heartfelt congratulations for wedding.
However, these girls opened my eyes to the truth:
it's no use trying to trick my own heart into feeling so.
It might be terribly late for that now, but still,
I'd like to tell you, with all due candor, just how I feel.
I still love you even to this day.
I want to marry you.
Mom! You should answer something to dad!
By being excessively vain in the distant past,
I myself brought this about -
to you, to Luise, and to Lotte,
I have delivered long years of suffering.
Well, that... Was the same on my side.
I must...
apologize to you for one more thing.
By saying that I'm about to marry Editor Bernau,
I lied once again.
Then...
Mom!
If only you would permit another chance for me,
I'd like to try living together once more,
as a family of four.
Luiselotte...
Dad!
Lotte, we did it! Did it!
Mommy! Love you!
Cheers, dad.
I'm so happy for us all!
Thank you, Lotte.
Cheers, mom!
This means we four are living together now!
Forever, forever, fore-ver!
Right. All the way until you two
walk down the aisle yourselves.
Now I really feel that I won't need
a birthday present ever again!
So do I! From now on,
I'll do fine without Christmas presents, too!
This year, next year, and every year!
They're a good match, don't you think?
Those dad and mom of ours!
Well...
Now, then, shouldn't we raise a toast to this?
You're welcome to my flat if you'd like that.
I owe you a feast, seven years' worth of them.
Let's go, Lotte.
These children are something else.
Yes, they took that from you.
Oh no, it's from you!
It's from you, admit it!
Been a long time!
Ah! Lotte!
What are you up to, skipping school?!
Annie! And with you, Maria and Miria.
Not even denying you're playing hooky?
Right, right! It's plain to see now!
We should whistle-blow it to the teacher, Annie!
Who are you whistle-blowing it to?
If you try to mess with Lotte,
I'll come to deal with you personally.
Lotte is two!
I'm Luise. Even if some mere days ago I was still Lotte.
Luise is my big sister.
And I'm...
My meeker, but no smaller sister.
Together, we switched places some while ago.
Lotte, Luise, show the way.
Ah! It's this guy!
He had been swinging the stick at the recent concert.
Pa... Par... Pap...
Palfy.
Our dad.
Dad?
Sorry, Annie. Since explaining the whole story
would take too long, let's do it some other time.
Well, some other time, Annie.
Did you understand anything, Frau Annie?
I bet she didn't.
Unfortunately, as we move there,
you'll have to change schools, too.
You're probably feeling sad
about parting with your friends.
I know I'll have to say goodbye to everyone.
To teacher Linnekogel, to Ilse Merck,
to Annie, Maria and Miria.
Even parting with Annie and her goons
is somehow saddening.
In addition, the people who taught you to cook...
Butcher Herr Huber.
And grocery store owner Frau Wagenthaler.
And the piano teacher Leitner, too.
Ah! How could I forget!
That's right...
Oh? What is it?
Editor-in-Chief Bernau.
We should definitely drop by
to say our goodbyes to Editor.
Good point.
However, Editor-in-Chief Bernau
had always been a good and faithful friend of mine.
And he'll remain one forever.
Mom, what about your job?
I'll find myself a new job in Vienna.
Staying home, doing whole lot of nothing
is not in my nature.
For housekeeping, we already have Resi.
Naturally, that doesn't mean we can't help her, too.
I'll be sure to!
Yes.
It means parting with this flat as well, Lotte.
Yes...
Thank you for all the memories we made here.
Good bye, Munich.
But also...
Vienna
Hello, Vienna!
Hello, our new life.
Can you explain in simple terms,
who is the newcomer?
This here is Lotte.
In short, she was the one who attended this place
under Luise's name since the end of summer vacations.
Oh, my...
I still don't know what to make of it.
Excuse me...
If I'm getting it right, you had two twins, one of which
was attending this school, and now the other one joins her?
Yes. Well, to put it simply, it's so.
Hm... Still, what a puzzle.
Oh, and how could they be so similar, too?
Indeed. At this rate, we'll have no choice,
but to stick name tags on them.
I'm starting, Truda!
Next is you, Margarete!
What's up, Truda?
Can you believe it?
Lotte is now also going to this school!
Moreover, our dad and mom
now live together again!
I'll have you know all the details
sometime later!
Hey-hey, Truda.
Why am I seeing two Luises?
Bye-bye!
Oh, I see! There really was more to it
than meets the eye!
I bet, people would start confusing them again.
Oh no! I must let Christine know!
And Stephie, too!
Hey, Truda! What's going on?
Will you ever explain?
I don't get it!
Amazing, Lotte!
Enthralling play!
Yes, impressive indeed.
It seems, I should be the one learning from Lotte now.
Here, Little Herrin Pianist.
Cake that's as refined as you.
Whoa! Sachertorte, isn't it?
The yummiest cake in the world!
Well, then.
About your birthday tomorrow...
Told you, don't bother with presents.
We've already received ours.
What better present one can get
than living together as a family of four?
So the matter is...
I'll need you two to lend me
a few hours of your time.
Eh? Our time?
You see, tomorrow, we're going to the registry office
to hold the official ceremony.
Marriage ceremony, right?
All that on our birthday?
Yes. We'll do it tomorrow,
whatever it takes.
After all, there wouldn't have been any remarriage
if not for Luise and Lotte's intense arbitration.
Every year, starting now, together with your birthday,
we'll also celebrate the second birthday of our feelings.
Agreed?
Most naturally!
Fantastic! This way, we'll make our birthday
the day of our parents' wedding as well!
As a matter of fact, Editor-in-Chief Bernau
also promised to come.
Ditto for Doctor Strobl
and Herr Gabele, the painter.
Sublime! This spells "great day" already!
Best birthday ever!
Oh, I so can't wait for tomorrow to come!
Dad, mom! Hurry, hurry!
Still too soon?
Good morning, Doctor Strobl.
Herr Gabele, good morning.
My, is that a beaming of happiness
I'm seeing on your faces?
Yes! Absolutely!
Hans! You managed to come, too?
I already know the whole story.
Congratulations, so you're...
I'm Lotte. This one is the true Luise.
Pleased to meet you, in this quality, too.
You guys sure are miracle-makers.
Not everyone can bring
his divorced parents to reconciliation!
Damn well said. From myself, though, I'd like to add:
I gave you an inch and you took a mile.
How do you suppose I should run Munich Graph
with our main scooper enticed by you?
But in exchange, we supplied you
with a first-class correspondent in Vienna!
Yeah. At least we didn't yield her to any rival company.
No way I let some odious bunch
get their hands on a staff so valuable.
Thank you! That's exactly what I love
the most about you, Editor-in-Chief Bernau!
But say, Herr Editor,
won't you miss her personally as well?
Yeah! I'm not too happy
about losing "a thorn in my side" either.
Maybe something else?
What are you getting at, Fraulein Shrewd?
Now, all aboard.
You can't go, Peperl!
Well, I guess there's no helping it.
Let him come along, too.
My heartfelt congratulations, Frau.
Thank you. Now, would you please
finish the party preparations?
Sure!
Come back safely.
Here, the bride's carriage.
Congratulations, Miss Körner.
Thank you, Editor-in-Chief.
Ah, right. This morning, someone entrusted me this.
Munich Graph cover!
Our photo?
Oh, why did this happen?
I was planning to surprise Lotte and everyone
on a better occasion.
Who'd betray me like that?
It was from some pretty woman.
She also asked me to pass to Herr Palfy and his wife
her best wishes for the wedding.
So it was her...
Herr Palfy, I don't consider myself a loser.
You'll be happier this way,
but so will I, and by several orders more.
Vienna First District Family Registry Office
So, then... Frau Luiselotte Körner
and Herr Ludwig Palfy...
Right, and now I would ask you
to sign this marriage certificate.
I wish we could see it one day,
mom wearing her real wedding dress.
Yes. But don't be too greedy in your wishes!
Attending their own parents' wedding ceremony -
not many children get that kind of luxury!
Well, that's true as well.
With this, the ceremony is concluded.
Have a happy marriage.
Lotte, Luise, starting today,
we're officially a family again!
Congratulations, dad.
Congratulations, mom
Dad.
Mom.
Your left hand, please.
Here is the magical ring.
It's unseen to the eye, but with magic,
this ring protects its wearer at all times.
The two rings are connected
with a thin thread, invisible as well.
Two persons wearing those can never take them off
and are bound to love each other until the end of times.
In times of abundance,
and in times of need...
When you're in good health,
and when bedridden...
Lotte, Luise...
Thank you.
They say, you repay magic with even more magic.
Oh, welcome.
Good morning, Herr Gabele!
What is it you said you wanted to show to us all?
This something is ought
to exhilarate you both, I reckon.
If anything, it was enough to compel me
to bid my farewells to this place, starting today.
Herr Gabele, you're moving out of here?
Well, what's the use of talking? Come on in.
What exactly is happening here?
How come dad's piano is in this room?
We heeded to Lotte's suggestion and acted on it.
I negotiated an exchange of rooms with Herr Gabele.
Really? So Herr Gabele
biding farewell to it just means...
Exactly that!
Dad, from now on,
you'll be working right next to us, right?
Yeah. It's about time I get rid of that old habit
of not showing up at home for weeks on end.
And my new atelier is a garden of light.
By your courtesy, I can now work to my heart's content.
So here is my late present to Lotte and Luise.
Lotte! Luise!
You're going to be late for school!
Honey, your notebook.
Oh... Thanks.
I guess there's no reeducating dad.
Ah! Mom! There's no second earring!
Eh? Gosh, I left it upstairs!
Oh no, I'll be late for the interview!
We're off!
Come back soon!
I'm off!
Take care, Frau!
Granted at last, Luise and Lotte's wish.
The whole family lives together again.
What started as a tenuous conspiracy -
the adventure of the two had arrived to a happy ending.
However, nobody can say for sure
if the true adventure is not just merely starting.
Why don't we sneak a wee peek
into the new everyday routine of the Palfy family?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next Episode Preview
Lotte, dad had proposed a trip
to his uncle's villa.
A wonderful place in the countryside,
surrounded by nature.
Wonderful! Our first family trip.
Dad said "It can't wait," didn't he?
That's right.
That's very dad-like, but I'm still a little worried.
What is it, Lotte? Why are you worried?
Final episode of I and Myself:
Our First Family Trip.
Episode 29
Our First Family Trip
Meet you there!