Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
Seebühl Village
Bühlsee Lake
It's so peaceful here.
No better place to spend your holiday than the countryside.
Let's change the point from our usual one today.
What's with those children?
Girls from Viennese elementary schools.
They are living in a summer camp.
Summer camp?
Girls from various school come together
to spend their vacation here.
There, that red-roofed building is where they live.
One way or another, they are making a lot of fuss.
Enough to make this point unfit for fishing.
Precisely. We'd be better off someplace away from them.
For an urbanite, you reasoning is quite sound.
Hey-hey, I'm not that stupid!
Episode 1
Meeting
Everyone, let's get out of the water
and have a little break!
Where is Luise?
We were swimming over there just a moment ago...
Luise Palfy! Hurry up to the shore!
Don't tell me...
Luise!
Yes?
Luise... Why did you do that?
You shouldn't be fooling around in the lake,
how many times did I tell you?
But I wasn't fooling around, Fraulein Ulrica.
Merely practicing to better hold my breath underwater.
Luise, I'm well aware of your fondness
for challenging others' authority.
Come on, get on the shore now.
Okay.
I'm bored.
It didn't change one bit this year either,
this Seebühl Village.
But it's so serene.
Maybe even too quiet!
It becomes outright eerie when night comes.
Monica is saying that because she misses her mom from Vienna greatly and spent last evening sobbing in her bed!
Lies! All lies! Don't believe it, people!
Monica is still so dependent.
I, in turn, am enjoying a break
from my annoying mom's attention!
Look, Christine, you're much prettier this way.
You think so? But it's a pain to weave.
I can do it for you.
Hey Luise, let's give you a braid, too!
No way!
Not making use of such great hair is a crime!
Stop it!
Okay, everyone, you can go swim again.
Let's go!
Wait!
Sure is snappish, our Luise.
She is actually very kind.
Having spent my whole life
in the same class, I know for sure -
she is bristling against others doing her hair,
because it's not in her habit, that's all.
Not in her habit?
She had to grow up without a mom.
Yet you'd never tell by the looks.
But her dad is a real big fish!
A famous composer,
and a head conductor of the Vienna Philharmonic.
Everyone in our school knows about that.
And if you try to ridicule her dad,
she's not letting it slide!
Might even slap you.
Come on, hurry up and change.
It's almost lunchtime.
Make sure no one's left behind!
Now, now, a minute of your attention please.
Frau Muthesius has something to tell to you.
I want you all to listen to me while you eat.
This afternoon, we expect more of our friends to arrive.
Twenty new girls from elementary schools of Munich.
Munich?
Twenty of them!
Within this summer camp,
you are all to become their temporary mentors.
Please introduce them to our way of life
with all due geniality.
We want you to start getting along soon, learn about their towns and schools and tell them about yours.
Let us all enjoy this summer vacation together.
I'm finished.
Girls from Munich.
I wonder if they are a lot different from us.
I would just be happy
if they are not ill-tempered.
Have nothing to fear, Stephie.
If anyone tries to mess with you, I'll show them their place.
More importantly, you think they'll bring along
anything interesting to play with?
That's right, maybe a big new ball?
Mine one started leaking air recently.
If you need a ball,
can't you borrow Brigitte's one?
That one is a dead end.
She shut it in a locker and hid the key.
Because it's a brand new item!
Can't lend it to someone as barbaric
as Luise or her friends.
Miser girl!
Let's hope they bring along some new game.
There should be at least one!
Let's make friends with them to start playing it soon!
There's the bus! Bus is coming!
Well, this is your stop, young Frauleins.
Careful! That seems like a lot of heavy luggage on you.
There, let me help you with this, heigh-ho.
Yes, and you too, there you go.
Yes, careful, like that.
Hey, hey, look there!
This girl is carrying a ball!
I hope someone brings a set for playing bagatelle!
Enjoy your holiday.
Thank you.
Good afternoon!
Good afternoon.
You come from Munich, right?
Yes. Mind showing us the way to the dorms?
Follow me!
Good afternoon!
Good afternoon.
One of the Frauleins got left behind?
Something's wrong, little one?
I stayed behind to see
that nobody forgets anything.
That is very thoughtful of you.
Now, your hand...
Oh my, what did you do to your hair?
Usually bristling against others doing your hair,
suddenly you are wearing pigtails?
Hey, next time you want them braided,
let me do it for you.
Wait!
Sorry.
Truda! Did girls from Munich arrive already?
Luise?
What is it? Something happened?
It's just...
Well, I'll be... What's this?
What... What's going on?
Luise, should apologize first, at least!
Unruly child.
Glad to see you're here.
All girls but one checked in...
Right. This one.
You're not Luise Palfy, are you?
Truda, Luise... Find Luise, will you?
This is urgent!
This is big, people!
Hear this, hear this!
You wouldn't believe what has happened!
I just saw Luise two!
What are you saying?
What does this mean?
I'm more or less content
with this proposed meal plan.
However, just on this one day...
Come in!
Frau Muthesius, twenty new girls
from Munich have all safely arrived.
Well, glad to know. Thank you.
What I meant to say is, on this one day,
we planned an outing for children.
There's something else...
What is it?
A peculiar thing concerning Luise Palfy.
What kind of trick she pulled this time?
No, it's not exactly something she did...
Please enter now, you both.
So what's this all about?
Had I been wearing spectacles,
I'd wipe them right about now!
The one with the pigtails -
arrived from Munich today, Lotte...
Lotte Körner, Frau.
Like two beans in a pod, you two.
Are you relatives, perchance?
It seems, one had never met another up until today.
What a puzzling turn of events...
How is it puzzling?
That's just the most natural thing.
One was brought up in Vienna,
the other was brought up in Munich.
That's not what I find puzzling.
Either way, let's not make too big a fuss over it.
A striking resemblance.
Two girls so alike are bound to make good friends!
I'm sure of it.
Never!
Well, not like anyone would force you to.
You two are free to work this out by yourselves.
Luise is at it again...
Just a moment, Lotte.
Let me write down your name, before I forgot.
"Lotte Körner," isn't that right?
When and where have you been born?
Also names of the parents?
My family is just mother and me.
I see. Then, let's start with the date of birth.
Luise. Hey, answer, Luise.
What's going on?
Don't know!
I can't understand a thing.
Still... Still, I don't like it one bit already!
Look, this one is Lotte.
Word is, she came from Munich.
A spitting image!
If you ask me which is which, I'd never tell.
Are you kidding me?
Getting constantly pointed at for the rest of my vacations,
because another girl has the same face!
Takes some nerve to act like that!
Today is not your lucky day.
What should I ever do about it?
Might slap her on the face.
Like you usually do.
Would rather bite off that little nose of her.
Nobody would say you two are alike then!
My long-awaited summer vacation turned into this.
What a bummer.
But it's not like you can blame her for that.
What do you mean, Stephie?
Just imagine it for a second:
somebody else comes, looking exactly like me...
No way I can imagine that!
Who else in the world would be such a dope
as to go around looking like you!
Just hear me out seriously!
Say, Luise, had you been in Lotte's shoes now,
that is, as Lotte, if you would have earned Luise's anger,
how would you feel?
I think...
Stephie! Say anything more convoluted
and we'll have our brains boil!
But...
If I had been in Lotte's shoes...
Oh, this is so unbearable!
You just killed everyone's mood, Stephie!
Why can't you think once before you speak?
But hey...
Alright, I know how to handle this.
Let's go, Truda.
Hurry!
Mom...
Are we really alike?
I'm Christine.
We need to talk something over.
I'm Truda.
In Vienna, I go to the same class as Luise.
You and Luise sure are alike.
It's becoming a nuisance.
A nuisance?
Like if I ever wanna talk to Luise,
but end up babbling with you.
Naturally, I can't be bothered to ascertain
who is who every single time.
But...
From now on, don't come near Luise!
We came here before you did,
so you should show some respect.
Wait a minute!
What's your deal?
I'm Nina. We don't go to the same school,
yet Lotte and I became friends while we were on the bus.
What is it you accuse Lotte of?
Should she even bear a striking semblance to some other girl,
how can Lotte be held responsible for that?
'Bout that...
Can't believe you can blow even such trifle
out of its proportion!
Let's go, Lotte.
What's with that demeanor?
All Munich girls have their noses in the air!
Lovely!
A better day comes tomorrow.
Supper time!
Right, from today on,
we share a meal with our new friends from Munich.
Make friends with them sooner,
to have loads of fun together!
Let's take a better look at Luise and Lotte
when they are sitting in one row.
You mean next to each other?
Won't they start quarreling?
Times like this always call for decisive measures.
I understand.
Truda, won't you be so kind
as to free up this seat for Lotte?
Eh? But...
Take that as my humble request.
Okay.
What'll Luise do about it?
Oughta be a sight to behold!
Someone's getting slapped.
There she comes!
No difference at all!
Aren't they sisters?
Lotte, your seat would be right here.
Such a sinister silence.
What's the matter, girls? Done eating already?
That's it! She's about to cry!
How come?
How come this timid thing
didn't break into tears?
Things go far from smooth.
Imagine, a person who is the spitting image of you
suddenly barges in, what'll you do?
Well... Probably, pinch myself to see if I'm awake.
Then, I'll try talking to this person.
But why would you ask something like that?
Isn't that obvious?
Such would be an adult's approach.
But those girls are just ten years old! Would take
them some time to become comfortable with each other.
Those two will figure it out. Definitely.
Tonight, we're also giving Lotte
a bed next to Luise's.
The sooner they grow closer - the better.
This over there is my bed!
But the counselor said I'm sleeping next to Luise.
You've delivered Luise enough trouble today
by hanging around her!
You again!
Why are you being so rude to her?
Why are you being so nosy?
Should keep your trap shut, Bavarian kid!
My, can't believe all the girls in Vienna are so boorish!
What did you say?
I was told Vienna is a fantastic place,
and a Capital of Arts.
But it seems, people inhabiting it
are still fresh out of cave!
What did you mean by that?
We won't let you badmouth Vienna like that!
I don't need your permission!
Asking for a beating?
Go ahead and try!
Stop it! I don't want you starting a brawl over me!
But why? Why are you so mad with me?
Counselor's here!
How'd you feel if you were in Lotte's shoes yourself?
Why did I let it get on my nerves so much?
I don't quite understand it myself.
If dad had been here now,
what would he have to say?
Luise, your spring and your candor
are two things I appreciate the most about you.
However, when you're about to speak your mind,
take a moment to consider the feelings of others, okay?
Mama...
Lotte, make sure to enjoy your vacations thoroughly.
I want you to make lots of friends.
You tend to be acting way too serious for your age.
It's not your fault, but mine.
Cooking, cleaning, washing -
I have to entrust everything to my little housekeeper!
Use this time for games,
like the most ordinary child!
See that you come back
with a lot of smile-wrinkles.
Mom, those wrinkles are not from smiling.
Lotte...
Luise!
Lotte, I still can't be sure if I have the guts for it,
but tomorrow, I'll try to talk things out with you.
With the warmth of their hearts,
the two girls started building the bond between them.
Like two magnets that first repel each other
when their identical poles meet, Luise and Lotte -
what is it that draws them together despite everything?
Where this gentle moonlight shows the way,
let's keep a close eye on those two.
To be continued
I am Luise.
And I am Lotte.
Hey, Lotte, do you usually let your mom brush your hair?
It's been this way since I was little. Always.
I see.
But these days, I do it myself.
There's no dad in our family,
so mom is constantly busy with work!
In our family, there's no mom. And our housekeeper Resi
just can't stand it when she has to brush my hair.
Next time - I and Myself: Thread of Fate.
Look forward to it!
Episode 2
Thread of Fate
Translated by Perevodildo | Timings by Sub-RoRo