"Dad, don't marry Frau Gerlach,"
Lotte was so sick worried about it,
she actually fell ill.
Upon discovering that, Luise and mother rushed to Vienna.
Finally, the time had come
for all the secrets to come to light.
Abrogating her pledge, Luise disclosed to father and mother
the fact of twins having switched places.
And thus, right there, on Lotte's bedside,
at long last, the family of four had been reunited.
Episode 25
Love Reborn!?
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Lotte.
She is asleep already.
Doctor Strobl had arrived.
Please.
Are we looking better?
Yes, the fever is nearly gone, it seems.
Splendid.
Told you, any extra check-up would be superfluous.
However, you shouldn't let your guard down.
It's best that tonight
you stay closely by her side, just in case.
Right, I was also hoping I could stay here overnight.
It's probably better this way.
They are still such a long way
from defeating awkwardness...
Tonight, I'm staying in my atelier.
This way, I won't get in the way
of you nursing the girl.
But...
So...
Well, I entrust Lotte to you.
Luise.
Somehow, I knew... you'd come.
Awake already?
Hey, Lotte, what in the world happened?
A terrible thing.
Dad is engaged with Frau Gerlach.
No way!
When I learned of this, somehow,
I was feeling worse and worse.
This is not happening!
Absolutely not happening!
But what can we do?
You shouldn't be worried no more, Lotte.
After all, I'm here in Vienna with you!
Luise.
Cheer up. And get back on your feet soon.
Dad will not marry a woman...
...Other than our mom!
Never!
So? You like it?
I love it!
Great!
I made sure to put in plenty of fresh cream.
After all, it's your favorite.
Just like I remember it -
your cooking is the best in the world!
Thank you.
But that doesn't mean
you can just push the carrot to the side.
You'd make me oh so happy if you eat it all!
But come on...
You even try to avoid it the same way I do!
A scene of gaiety.
Doctor Strobl!
Welcome!
You can see, I'm full of life again!
The recovery is marvelous indeed.
It's because mom had applied
some magical ointment!
Magical ointment?
In my long career, a good many lauded me
as a miracle physician, so I tried to live up to it,
but turns out, the world's first
miracle physician had been you!
Lotte, do you want a refill?
I could eat a bit more.
Then, give me a moment to bring you another serving.
I didn't know you're home.
Yeah... It seems, there's no longer
any need to worry... About Lotte.
Yes. She's out of woods now.
That's my daughter for you.
I mean...
That's her mother for you.
My, that's nothing!
Are you serious?
Really impressive, Irene!
The world's greatest musician, Herr Palfy...
...Is engaged to you!
It was actually last week, when he proposed.
While doing it, he stared at me so earnestly,
I could almost read it in his eyes:
"If you don't marry me, I'd rather go throw myself
into the lake and die right there..."
My, so romantic!
I really envy you.
In all of Vienna... No, in the whole world,
the jealousy of women is probably directed at me right now.
Frau Irene, we need to finish the preparations
for the wedding ceremony.
I told you before to not spare anything.
Make it the grandest wedding ceremony the money can buy.
Right, understood.
Irene!
Father? What in the world had happened?
Need a word. Now.
What might it be?
Excuse me for a minute, will you?
A word just came,
Herr Palfy's wife is spotted in Vienna!
No, to be precise, his ex-wife.
Perhaps, it's the mother
of the impeding little beast?
It seems, she's in Palfy's house right now.
What did you say?
Here you go, Doctor Strobl.
Right, thank you.
Here, for you as well.
Thank you.
Boo!
My, Luise! But what about the other Fraulein Twin?
Good heavens...
My, how should we even...
Quite confounding indeed.
Well, can you tell which one is Lotte now?
And which one is Luise?
Try to guess!
The one on the left is Luise, probably, I think...
No, if I try to distinct by the voice...
Ah, I don't know now!
Frau and Herr Master, please come to our rescue!
You're Luise, aren't you?
And here is Lotte.
On Luise's cheeks, there's always this sensation
of a place under the sun, my cute little tomboy.
You really are my mom!
I knew them after just one close look -
those glittering eyes,
always full of tears when you feel lonely.
Dad, love you!
Well, this is highly impressive!
Right you are!
I can now return to being Luise.
From today on, meet the old, boyish Luise!
I can also now return to being the usual Lotte.
And then, play piano to my heart's content!
Hey, let's listen to your piano together!
In dad's atelier!
Mom!
I want you to hear it, too!
And dad is coming with us!
I may...
As long as you don't mind.
Amazing!
Dad!
Mom, you hurry up, too!
Yes, Palfy listening.
Ah, it's you, Luise?
Good morning. This is Gerlach speaking.
Frau Gerlach?
Could you invite Herr Palfy to the phone?
I wanted to ask him
to meet with me sometime soon.
Meet with you?
That's very apropos!
Dad asked me to pass this to you:
"Wait for me in front of the Opera House."
In front of the Opera House?
If I may, a useful tip for you -
dad is every inch an artist, so he especially likes a woman
who surprises him by doing things out of ordinary.
Things out of ordinary?
For instance, like if you'd wait for him there,
frozen like a statue, under two umbrellas!
Under two umbrellas?
Right! Under two!
That's remarkably well thought out for a joke.
Well, if you think it's a joke,
just disregard it altogether.
See you!
Are you sure, Luise?
This is getting pretty far.
It's fine, fine! It'd be her own fault
for not smelling a joke here.
Why the wait, you two?
It's nothing.
Let's go, Lotte.
Under two umbrellas?
I wonder if this kind of vagary
would really be enough to impress Herr Palfy.
A fine performance,
worthy of today's special concert.
And it was so much like yours.
They both are gifted in so many different ways...
They're the exact copy of you.
Kind at heart, but can stand their ground.
I like this mood.
Let's go.
Then, we'll go play somewhere now!
You two enjoy yourselves!
Wait a minute!
We're off!
It's never easy with these girls...
How about we also take a stroll outside?
If possible, I would have liked to stay here for a bit.
I feel strangely sentimental here.
This room brings back the times
when we lived together.
The room of a thousand memories.
Seven years have passed,
and it's still the same.
Your place under the sun.
Great!
Great, indeed! Dad and mom...
I'm sure, they will...
They definitely will...
reconcile!
In just five days, it's fourteenth of October!
Our birthday!
Let's make it the best day ever!
She came with umbrellas...
For a joke, this is going too far.
I feel sorry for her.
Luise!
You were messing with me?! How dare...
We're sorry! Luise didn't do it out of bad intent.
Luise is now two...
What's the meaning of all this?
Luise and me are a pair of twins.
Twins?
How can this be...
I'm seeing a nightmare, am I?
Right now, we're happier than ever!
Both dad and mom
are closely by our side.
Do you still remember that time?
Yeah. I've not forgotten.
We used to sing a lot, in a duet.
To my piano accompaniment.
You were still a fameless composer,
blind to everything outside your dream.
And you were determined and unyielding, not thinking twice
before quarreling with me over my egoism.
I even thought to myself,
"How can one be so headstrong?
I'm flabbergasted..."
But then, also,
"Well, isn't it fascinating?"
Glad to see you've not changed a bit in that regard.
Even now, just as fascinating.
Can you really blame me for it, Herr "Busy-Busy"?
I felt lonely.
Eventually, you wouldn't even give me
as much as a look.
Music was your only love.
One day, I felt like playing a little trick on you.
I thought, "if I tell him I'm leaving,
would he probably look at me at least then?"
What are you saying?
You did that to provoke me?
Yes.
However, even then,
you didn't make any attempt to stop me.
But I... I thought you just
grew cold to me, that's why...
But I never...
But it was you who acted
like you no longer need me.
This is so complicated...
But it starts to clear up.
Could it be that we both fell victim
to a disastrous misunderstanding?
Are you...
Yes?
Orchestra tuning?
Can't it wait just a bit?
Understood!
I'm needed elsewhere right now.
I'll have my leave, too.
No, wait please.
I still need to tell you something...
Everything I couldn't say in the past years.
It's too late now, isn't it?
This work won't take more than two hours.
Please wait for me in the Cafe Schubert.
Make sure to be there, okay?
Cafe Schubert...
We two spent countless dates there.
We're home!
Welcome back, Frauleins.
I was talking to Frau Mistress on the phone just now.
Our mom called?
I think... She mentioned going to Cafe "Something,"
so she's going to be a little late.
Cafe "Something?"
Good, that settles it for today.
Herr Palfy.
We need to have a talk.
Frau Irene?
Just as father and mother seemed to be finally
on their way to open their hearts to one another,
a major obstacle was about
to be wedged between them.
However, Lotte and Luise
are still altogether oblivious to what is coming to them.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Luise, mom had disappeared!
Where did she go?
Last night, she didn't warn us.
This is strange!
Could it be that something bad
happened to her in Cafe Schubert?
That must be dad's fault!
Dad offended her somehow!
You think it's possible that mom
had returned to Munich already?
That's unacceptable! Totally unacceptable!
Next time, I and Myself:
Saying Goodbyes? No!
Episode 26
Don't miss it!