Lotte and Luise both joined
the Little Detective Agency,
determined to get to the bottom of the reasons
behind dad and mom's break-up in their investigation.
Lotte's investigation ultimately ended in a failure,
and now, let's check on Luise...
Episode 12
The Secret Brought to Light
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Not bad, Hans!
You have a talent!
Hans! Let it be known to Vienna,
its number one street performer is here!
Thank you!
Thank you, Europe's number one audience!
Thank you very much.
You play really well, Hans.
Thank you, Luise.
I liked it, too. Certainly, I'm going to send
my orchestra's scouts after you, in the future.
Don't mean to sound disrespectful, but I really intend
to be performing on the streets for the rest of my life.
After all, how can I let down
the town folk, my devoted fans?
We'll manage, accept it!
We believe in you, Hans!
Well, this is a pity.
It seems, our orchestra had just suffered a loss
of one more musical genius.
My! That must be Herr Palfy! Over there!
You mean the composer?
Thanks for this.
The resemblance is striking.
By the way, Luise, is our investigation
of your dad's affairs still ongoing?
I gave up on it.
It seems, on my end, it's a nonstarter.
But I'm sure, on Luise's end...
Nevermind. Ne-ver mind.
Right. You must have already
brought it to light by now.
As a fellow Little Detective.
I must get an answer out of her today.
How come dad and mom ended up divorcing?
Yeah. Maintaining the pressure
is essential in such matters.
Mom?
Not here. Not here either!
My, where else could it be?
I can't get anything done if I don't find it!
My report on business communications​!
Sorry I come at an unfortunate moment,
but I have an important matter to...
Ah! Found it. Here you are, here.
Hey...
Ah! Blimey!
Ah... Ruined.
Mom...
Can't you see, Lotte, I'm busy now.
Let's talk later.
Ah? It's that late already.
Oh, I can't get anything done in time!
Mom...
I need to ask you something.
Oh, two women candidates stepped forward...
Listen!
It's about raising your allowance again?
Actually not!
Ah... Well...
Give me a moment,
this article just gave me an idea.
Enough work already!
I really need to discuss this urgently!
Did you get in a fight with Annie again?
I know, okay?
We'll take our revenge later.
And it's not something that petty either!
I need an answer right now!
And for that, I need your full attention,
not diverted to eating and reading news...
For me, this is a matter of...
A minute of silence, please!
Ah! Hey, that's rude!
Look, you didn't eat your carrot again.
Go finish it, it's nutritious.
You leave some milk in your cup every time!
And yet, you make me drink mine while gagging me.
But of course!
In any discussion, grown-ups do the speaking,
kids do the listening.
It seems, the grown-ups are convinced, the rest of the world
is supposed to cater to their needs.
Lotte.
What's this kind of talk,
in return for my patient listening?
But mom, you're always...
Not a word more.
So? Any more complaints?
Listen, Lotte.
A grown-up is someone who has to constantly consider
both his own affairs and his child's ones.
The need to work hard for the success of those
is what warrants such conduct.
I don't think so.
Adults are those who prefer to turn a blind eye to it
over conceding the inconvenient truth before the children.
Nope. I never turn a blind eye
to anything you bring up.
Tell me then!
Sure, what is it?
It's about dad...
Why did you two break up?
There's no reason we should discuss this.
But you said you'll face anything!
Mom, wait!
Please understand that mom
has her own mom matters to tend to.
I'm doing this for you, too...
Not a thing of that is actually for me!
I hate you, mom!
A mom like that just can't be my mom.
Very well.
This mom is no longer qualified
to be Lotte's mom.
I'm living in the office, starting today.
You can ask Cleopatra, Queen Elizabeth, or whoever it is you prefer more...
to be your mom!
I...
Why was I so sharp...
What do I do?
This all spiraled out of control.
That's the kind of world we're living in.
Most of the grown-ups are pretty uptight
when it comes to the reasons for their divorce.
It's not at all surprising that you quarreled.
You're pretty well-informed on marriages, aren't you?
Not at all.
It's just that when the others only ever bully you,
you start pondering on intricacies of life merely to kill time.
I don't envy you.
I know! I should introduce you
to a "Benevolent Person."
"Benevolent person?"
One Elderly Herr, and a source of my wisdom.
He is a friend of a friend of mine.
And he also runs an advice column in a periodical.
His pen name is Friedrich.
Whenever Annie is harassing me again,
I address his column for an advice.
I'm sure he'll find a remedy for Lotte's plight, too!
What are those lousy manuscripts?!
I can't make heads or tails of any of this!
Rewrite all from scratch!
We can't let your rebel views get in the way!
Missis... No, Miss Körner!
Oh, my bad, Editor-in-Chief.
I'll rewrite it at once. Will be done by tonight.
Counting on you.
Mom!
Hungry, aren't you?
House No. 123.
It's here.
Yeah, it's open. Come in.
Huh?
Is this...
Where Herr Editor lives?
Can't you tell it's not a janitor's shack?
Come in now.
But then, Herr Friedrich is...
In our line of arbeiten,
we use pen names sometimes.
But what's more surprising here is you -
visiting me as a customer.
Please. I need your help with my plight.
I've nobody else to ask.
Well, I finally know.
You sure came here
with a quite the quandary on your hands.
I hope you don't mind me having a bit of wine.
Why do grown-ups
always drink stuff that's so bitter?
Hmm. That's a good one.
As you grow up, the reality makes you acquire a certain taste
for the things that are rather bitter, don't you think?
A taste for bitterness?
Like dreams that you have to leave behind,
or like a mutual feeling, that you're forced to forgo,
despite your best effort.
Even a sip of this bitterness
helps you forget it a little sooner.
Perhaps, that's the kind of memories
your mother has about your father.
I had... asked her something I shouldn't have asked.
And now, mom is never going to forgive me for this!
She threw at me, "Go find yourself a new mom, then!"
What should I do?
New moms are always mean to their new children!
The one in Hänsel and Gretel sure was!
You don't have to worry!
There's not a soul in this world
who wouldn't love our little Fraulein Lotte!
It won't work! Because I myself
won't be able to love any mom other than my own!
Actually, this must be your mother
who came to hand in the manuscript.
Eh? This is bad.
She doesn't want to see me now. What do I do?
Not home, then?
No... No!
Editor!
Here, the manuscript.
Yeah, thanks.
See you tomorrow.
Ah... Wait!
I may... need your advice on one more matter.
So what was it you needed help with?
I wanted to ask about Lotte.
You see, up until now,
I have never talked to her about her father.
I thought this would spare
her little heart some undue worry.
And yet... I still hurt her this morning.
So now I'm starting to question this decision.
It's just as she said.
I guess, I really am a whimsical grown-up.
Mom...
My... Were you already receiving someone before me?
Eh? Ah... No, not really.
So sorry! Such matters should not be your concern.
It's best that I have my leave now.
Ah... Miss Körner.
But...
Ouch...
You okay, Lotte?
Lotte?
Ah... Well, well... Ah... You two...
Our Lotte sure is adorable!
And... Miss Körner is always in her best shape, too...
Care to join me for some wine?
A taste for bitterness, huh?
What now? Giving up already?
I never give up!
Aren't you cold?
I'm sorry, Lotte.
Up until this day, I was avoiding
talking to you about your father.
Can I ask now?
You won't be mad?
Sure. I'm not mad anymore.
I now know that even my bitter memories
can be turned to joy if I share them with you.
Your father is a gifted musician.
However, by the time we two married
he wasn't yet enjoying even a fraction of his current fame.
And yet, day after day, in front of the piano,
he was composing, as if in a daze.
Therefore, I was also offering a prayer daily
for your dad's passion and talent to be rewarded.
Then, one day, this wish came true, didn't it?
I guess so.
However,
when the fame found your father,
it became even worse: day after day, after day,
he worked away in the atelier. "I'm busy, busy, busy!"
Eventually, he stopped coming home altogether.
That was when I decided
the time has come to have my leave.
Right. Soon after, people from all around the globe
became profoundly awed by your father's talent.
Well, so be it.
Sometimes, the best way to make another happy
is to rid them of your presence.
This is also a form of love.
Between you and dad, who is to blame?
Neither is to blame here.
We were both merely trying
to get the best out of our lives.
It's a bit hard to comprehend,
but aren't you sad about it?
Not in the slightest!
I'm confident -
tomorrow will always be better than today.
There would also be sad days, sure,
but with enough hard work, you can make them good, too!
And I think it's the same for your dad.
For dad, too?
Right, he'll keep making great music
with unrelenting passion.
You father is primarily a composer,
known to the world as a virtuous gentleman,
but also as a conceited featherbrain.
Right, right, an easygoing fellow!
Huh? What does that mean?
Well, he totally should be like that.
I mean, hey, he's my dad, after all!
Yes, that'd make sense.
Ah! It's cold! Let's hurry. Let's hurry home!
Oh my, Lotte?
Mom, hurry up!
I'm glad you understand, Lotte.
You're not overly concerned
about who exactly your father is.
Mom,
thank you. Now I know for sure.
At last, the reason for dad and mom's break-up
was brought to light in all the details.
Both dad and mom
both turned out to be the most amazing grown-ups.
"The way things stand now,
one day, they very much might reconcile,"
so thought Luise in that moment of happiness.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
We two have switched places!
Luise, this is bad!
We're having a gym class tomorrow.
But because I'm not actually Luise,
I can't do neither the horizontal bar, nor athletics!
Lotte, try to make it through, somehow.
All hope's lost now! Moreover, Truda is starting
to question whether or not I may be Lotte.
But still, we must do our utmost to protect our secret.
Do your best, Lotte!
I'm sorry, I don't think I'll be able to protect it.
Next time in I and Myself:
Lotte's Quandary!
Episode 13
Look forward to it!