Father and mother were already
a hair's breadth away from reconciling...
But then, suddenly, the very next moment,
mother returns to Munich.
And the reason was because Frau Gerlach had informed her
of receiving a proposal from the father of her children.
"Oh, just as things were finally
starting to look up... Why?" -
Luise and Lotte indignantly
demand an answer from their father.
Episode 27
Two People, One Wish
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Even after you parted,
mom was still attending your concerts for some time.
She knew your music comes from your heart,
so listening to it, she could feel and share your sorrow!
And thus, it was just as painful to her.
So that's how it was?
I'd never think...
Dad, answer honestly!
Do you detest mom?
No.
Without a doubt, I love her.
I believe, she is a breathtaking woman.
Mom also once told me
my dad is a breathtaking man!
Maybe just a little bigheaded, featherbrained, too,
and with a naive soul!
Still an unknown composer,
torturing the piano daily, to the point of exhaustion.
And mom would also offer a prayer daily
for that passion to bear fruit!
Those were the happy times for me...
Your mother was also my most devoted listener,
able to grasp my music thoroughly.
Not just "was!"
She still is!
Last time I saw someone badmouthing your music,
mom threw a giant tantrum!
She says, your music
is a cornucopia of the most genuine kindness!
And that she hadn't met anyone
who'd understand as much as she does!
I saw it with my own eyes,
during our time together -
mom still very much loves you,
even to this day!
I see. So Herr Palfy is getting married?
Yes. You can imagine, what a reputation it would give him
to have his ex-wife hanging around at such a time.
Therefore, I returned home.
You don't plan on going to Vienna any time soon?
Yes. I've gotten quite used to living in Munich.
Quarreling with our headstrong Editor is my true calling.
But what about Lotte? What about Luise?
What will become of those two?
I think they should go back
to where they belong.
Lotte stays with me,
and Luise with him.
You want to separate them again?
Just as the sisters had finally found each other?
Even after swapping places and everything
they've been through, you'd still do that to them?
I take great pity on those girls,
so it pains me just as much.
I repent this one divorce
more than anything else in my life.
However, it's too late now
to try and change anything.
I'm sorry. You really didn't have to hear all that...
I appreciate your concern.
But I'm all right now. Thank you.
Well, let's return, then.
When you get home, make sure to call Vienna.
You shouldn't let Lotte worry so much for you.
Dad, call Munich now!
Call and ask mom to come at once!
The four of us should live together,
that would be the only fitting way!
I can well understand
how you two feel about this.
However, this matter is for grown-ups to decide.
In real life, things are never as simple as that.
But...
I wish to be left alone
for some while, too.
Please.
Lotte!
Luise, spying is wrong!
Yes? Palfy listening.
Hello? It's me.
Ah, you see... The point is...
I was just about to try dialing you myself.
What in the world had happened?
You went home so abruptly.
It's mom!
I'm sorry. I remembered
about a certain work that was due today.
I was in such a hurry,
couldn't even drop by to bid my goodbyes.
And... How are girls?
They look restless.
Oh...
On an unrelated note,
I was told you're engaged now.
Congratulations.
Frau Gerlach's beauty is truly striking.
You met her?
Yes...
Oh, I see...
That was how she found out.
Peperl!
Ah, actually, speaking of Frau Gerlach... Well...
You see...
I'm also... considering a remarriage.
Eh? Remarriage?
With Editor-in-Chief Bernau, right?
Yes.
And that's why I made up my mind
on staying in Munich for the rest of my life.
I see. Congratulations to you, then.
For Lotte?
But... That's so out of the blue!
Maybe she could, for just a little longer...
I understand.
Your point is indisputable.
Good night.
Dad!
What was it... What was it mom wanted to say? Dad!
I'm sorry, Lotte...
I'm sorry, Luise...
You're kidding, right?
For Lotte to return to Munich so soon?
Could mom ever say something like that?!
"Everyone should return
to their usual lives as soon as possible.
Send her home tomorrow."
Tomorrow?!
But... But..!
I protest! You can't just scatter
me and Lotte, like some pebbles!
This disobedience is unbefitting of you.
Think of your mother's feelings!
Hear this.
This doesn't override the fact you two are sisters.
From now on, whenever you feel like
seeing each other, you'll have that freedom.
How can you...
How can you be so callous?!
Luise.
Lotte!
Lotte.
What?
It went completely south.
Our cherished plan.
Oath by the lake, in the Seebühl Village
is not getting fulfilled.
But really, isn't there
anything we can still do?
I know...
I know, I'll never be able to get along
with a person such as Frau Gerlach!
Never!
Gerlach Mansion
Now, that's highly unusual.
My Irene is in the parlor until so late...
Palfy's record, isn't it?
I realized that I've not been
listening thoughtfully to it up until now.
All I could see was his imposing figure,
on a fuzzy background.
Well, isn't that the most ordinary
for someone truly in love?
But his music is quite the phenomenon indeed.
Irene, you now have every right to hold your head high.
You're about to make this renowned genius yours.
Well, an artist's soul is inscrutable.
Perhaps, you'll be understanding enough
to shed light on it in your memoirs one day.
Understanding?
Nothing surpasses in importance
being understanding and caring towards your partner.
So far, I've been in love
with only one half of Herr Palfy?
I won't be able to make him happy.
With Editor-in-Chief Bernau?
He definitely sounds like someone
able to make her happy.
Come in.
What's the matter?
Can't get any sleep?
Dad, thank you.
It was only a short spell,
but I enjoyed every second of it.
Dad really is my dad.
Oh, what a delight to know!
From now on, I'll be practicing the piano
with full devotion.
So that next time we meet,
it won't leave you unimpressed!
See that you both treasure Luise, will you?
Then, Luise will write me many happy letters about it.
If I can read those,
it would be as though dad...
As though dad is by my side, too.
So I'll feel soothed...
Therefore, promise me
you won't send Luise away!
It goes without saying!
I'm never sending my Luise away.
No matter how many years have passed,
I will never forget my Lotte.
Knowing that you'll listen to it,
I'll be composing the most ravishing music ever.
I'm delighted.
Ah, Lotte...
Why do I have to let you go?
Okay, it's very late now. Good night.
Good night to you, too.
How can a father be that foolish...
Inflicting such unthinkable suffering
on his own children...
I made an unpardonable mistake.
Need to talk to Irene immediately.
Ah... Frau Irene,
you see, I must confer to you
on a certain delicate matter.
I would like to have a word with you as well.
I can't tolerate it, if my husband-to-be
is so indifferent to me, he doesn't even look my way.
You, however, have nothing but music in your eyes.
If things keep going in the current direction,
I'm turning into a recluse as soon as we marry.
This is unthinkable!
I absolutely can't stand being neglected.
To tell you the truth,
I can't stand children either.
Once we're married, I was considering your daughter's
enrollment into a boarding school.
I had already informed Luise as well.
Or wait, was it the other one of the twins?
Frau Irene, about that...
I understand. You'll never be able to bring yourself
to do something like that.
I've been carried away by my fantasies
to even come up with such an idea.
But then we come to a dead end.
I was willing to marry you,
but not your music.
Let us therefore pretend
this promise was never made.
Now, if you excuse me.
Frau Irene...
Irene, what is it you're saying to Herr Palfy?
Don't be disheartened, Herr Palfy.
Somewhere out there, there's a place,
where you, your music, and your child
would be altogether welcomed,
and sincerely loved
by someone better.
Irene...
A thousand pardons, Herr Palfy.
I have a somewhat willful daughter.
No, it was me who failed everyone.
Me alone.
So that's how it happened?
You two switched places?
But well, it sure is getting lonely here,
once Lotte is gone.
Still, my allegiance is unwavering - you'll find an ally in me,
no matter how many years pass.
Thank you, Herr Gabele.
Got it? You never give up on hoping.
After whole seven years,
you met with each other completely by chance.
This is what they call fate.
Fate?
Right. A chance that God bestowed upon you.
Whatever obstacles you meet on your path,
the key is to keep going.
And for that, the God will be sure to reward you.
Vienna Western Station
This past month feels like a dream already.
Everything that happened...
I'll be sure to remember it for the rest of my life.
All right, your bags are loaded.
Lotte, you should wrap this up and board soon.
Lotte, I don't want to let you go!
Luise... Such a pity we can't be together
even on our birthday.
Birthday?
Ah, right... Fourteenth of October.
Only three days left.
Somehow, it slipped my mind completely...
I'm sorry, Lotte.
I'll go get you a present after this.
Something you'd like?
Nothing, already...
No need to be shy. Say it out loud.
I'll grant anything you want.
Really anything?
Yes, anything at all!
I should compensate Lotte for seven years of waiting.
Wrong! Luise has been waiting for this
for seven years as well!
That's right!
I've been wanting it for seven years, too!
Just what...
are you talking about?
I want to have a dad!
And I want to have a mom!
We want dad and mom
to start living together!
We want us four
to live all together!
You're asking for such a thing...
However, it's not something I can grant.
For your mother, it's too late...
It can work, if you ask mom yourself!
We wouldn't need another birthday present ever again!
I would do without any presents for the rest of my life!
Not even for Christmas!
Please, daddy! This is our last chance...
Please...
Please, I beg you...
Munich Central Station
Lotte!
I'm home.
Welcome back. Was the road tiring?
Let me carry this for you.
So, shall we head home?
Tonight, we're having your favorite,
sole meuniere.
Luise?
How did that happen?
You didn't have to come to Munich as well.
Does your father know?
Hey.
Well... I see you made sure
she makes it here safely. Thank you.
I want to marry you, Luiselotte.
It's you.
It's you who I need.
Both me and my children.
Oh, this one moment...
How much had Luise and Lotte dreamt of it before!
Their father proposed a remarriage to their mother.
Now, what would be the mother's answer?
Two tiny hearts are now beating so violently,
you'd think they're trying to jump out.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Dad had finally made a proposal to mom!
"I love you, and I want to marry you."
Had he really only realized it now?
But now, we're all living together!
And we're the happiest family ever!
They say, "Lotte, you're just like your dad!"
And mom's face is all wrinkled from crying!
But overall, we've never been happier!
Next time, I and Myself:
Best Birthday Ever.
Episode 28
Best Birthday Ever
Don't miss it!