Lotte realized that her father and Herr Gabele
could exchange their ateliers,
so she presented this idea to her father.
However, after hearing her out,
father flatly rejected this idea.
Not just that,
he announced his intention
of marrying Frau Irene Gerlach.
As if struck by lightning, Lotte had experienced
a shock strong enough to render her paralyzed.
Episode 22
Lotte's in Danger!?
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Munich
Luise...
What do I do now, Luise?
What's wrong?
Someone spoke just now!
But I didn't say a thing.
That's odd, I could swear...
That must be Editor.
Probably needs an urgent manuscript.
Hello? Hello.
Oh?
That was odd, they just hang up.
It was a call from Lotte. Must be.
Did something happen on her end?
The thing is... I've been...
Feeling a need for a bit of a change in our lives.
And...
Once more, I...
So the point is, I've decided to remarry.
And it's with Frau Irene Gerlach.
You can't!
What should I do now?!
What to do...
Ah... Fraulein, where are you going?
It's quick.
I'm visiting someone on Cobenzl Boulevard.
Ah, is that so? Take care, then.
And be sure to come home soon!
Cobenzl Boulevard?
Wait, I'm pretty sure Young Fraulein
doesn't have friends living in that area.
Hans?
What's cooking, Luise?
Something happened?
You could tell?
Now that you ask...
You really do look mighty troubled.
Lotte...
Herr Palfy gets married?
Nobody but me supposed to know it yet,
but it seems,
he really does.
Cheers, then!
I'm not one bit cheerful about this.
Why so?
That's...
Because my mom
still loves dad, even to this day.
Your mom?
I see...
If I were Luise, I would have probably wished
for him to return to your own mom instead.
Yeah.
But what matters the most -
how does Herr Palfy himself feel about this?
Well, he...
The prognosis is grim, isn't it?
Still, I want to stop him, at any cost!
Don't you think it's futile?
I mean, Herr Palfy probably divorced your mom
because his love for her was gone.
They say, you sometimes need a break
even from the people you love.
Even if we suppose it's so...
For the moment, he certainly loves
another woman, doesn't he?
Sorry to break it for you,
but I see no way out.
Dad, before, you told me
you don't want to get married again.
Herr Palfy is a heartthrob, right?
He has the fame, and he has the "handsome."
Luise, could you be possibly heading
to where this dad's lover lives?
Hans, why are you asking like that?
So you really do, huh?
Luise, I've no way of telling
if doing so will bring you good or harm.
But whatever happens,
I'm always on your side.
Thank you, Hans.
Luise, want me to accompany you?
It's fine.
This ordeal is mine and mine only.
I'll deal with it myself!
I see.
Good bye, Hans.
Give it your best, Luise.
Come in.
Frau, you have a visitor.
Who is that?
Fraulein Luise Palfy.
Luise?
A little girl?
Yes.
So she's here?
What is it she wants here?
All right. Show her in.
Okay.
Ah, in the meantime, make her a cup of cocoa.
And prepare cookies, too.
Will do in a minute.
Having ascertained
that Herr Palfy's love for me is genuine,
she decided not to prolong the feud
and came here to bury the hatchet, I imagine.
Very well, then. I will reciprocate
your commendable humility with leniency,
Luise.
I honestly can't stand the thunderstorms.
How about you?
I can't stand it.
Pleased to know we have so much in common!
Now, please help yourself to cocoa.
You love it, don't you?
Yes.
It's thanks to Herr Palfy telling me oh so much about you,
that I now know you like the back of my hand.
It's only natural, since we're to live as a family
for the rest of our lives!
Actually, it's in my habit to dote on children.
So I'm sure, you and me will make the best of fr...
It won't happen.
I...
The reason I came here...
Pray, don't marry my dad!
Coming, coming!
Hello! It's Resi, right?
Yes, dear, that's me.
To whom do I own the please?
Well...
This is a classmate asking.
Is Luise home?
You're Fraulein's friend?
Okay... She went out some while ago.
Haven't returned yet, dear.
Is that so?
Tell me, did something happen to Luise lately?
Like, she's gotten into trouble?
Fraulein got into trouble?!
My, what should I do?
A traffic accident or something like that?
Calm down!
I'm just asking if she did!
Oh, is that all?
Weird, where could I have heard this voice before?
Gotta go now, have a good day.
It doesn't seem like she knows anything...
This can't be...
It has to be a hoax... A joke!
Did I hear it quite right?
Don't marry my father, please.
I'm not the one to be joking
about matters so crucial.
And why exactly shouldn't I?
That's...
Because I protest it.
I can't let you marry my father!
Give me the reason.
The reason is my protest!
Luise, no protest of yours has any sway
over such matters.
This marriage was Herr Palfy's idea...
It was your father,
who had proposed to me of his own accord.
Do you believe, it's in a child's power to override it?
Because you've no power to change it yourself,
you came here to ask me to do it?
Herr Palfy's love for me is attested by his own words.
In fact, I am the one in position
to enforce my will upon you.
Once our marriage is concluded,
you'd be sent to a boarding school, so better start packing.
That's such a pity.
I was really hoping we'd start getting along.
Farewell.
It can't be...
Leave us alone, the way we are now...
Please!
What should I do?
If nothing changes,
dad will end up marrying Frau Gerlach!
What can you recommend, Luise?
We have decided to convince dad and mom
to make up and live together again.
But...
All is lost now...
Well what do you know - we had but to ask
and they sent us all these leftovers.
Yes, but still...
Finding a good cover for Munich Graph among those
is anything but easy.
Well, who knows is they don't
send over anything good one of this days.
Right. Let's wait and hope.
Now, then.
Ah, Miss Körner...
Yes? Anything else?
No, nothing... Good job.
Excuse me, then. See you tomorrow.
Turns out, Herr Palfy had been her husband all along.
However... They broke up a long time ago, didn't they?
Right. That doesn't mean I should desert her as well.
Seebühl Village
Eipeldauer's Photo Studio
Munich Graph cover contest?
Ah! I know...
Let's see, pretty sure I stuck it among those...
No, wait, where else... Did I lose it?
Well, here you finally are!
That's the one.
You really don't see two twins
that much alike every day.
That's right! I should send this one
to Munich Graph and see what comes out of it.
Fraulein!
My, you're burning!
Ah! What should I do with you?
Strobl listening.
What? Luise is?
All right! I'll be there in no time!
Don't forget to call Palfy, too!
What? Concert tonight?
Nonsense! He must be made aware!
...For his refreshment,
even the few tears
you deny him.
Where's that barbarian,
Just wait for me, Luise.
Where's that barbarian?
As soon as this piece is over,
I'll hightail home!
Who even for our Lord
denies few tears?
39,8 degrees.
That much?!
Could it be that Fraulein has measles again?
This has nothing to do with measles.
But then... Ah... It's not pneumonia, is it?
Not this either.
Not this, but what?
Whatever it is,
we should first bring down the fever.
You can't...
You said something, Fraulein?
Can't do this...
Please...
What... should I do?
We'll now...
Do something!
Taxi!
I had just barely managed to put her to sleep.
Put to sleep? Was it really necessary, doctor?
Doctor,
what wrong with Luise?
The more I look at this, the more it seems
like she is experiencing a severe mental shock.
However, it's no run-of-the-mill case.
Mental?
Shock?
Even separated, the twins are connected with a link
that sometimes allows them to share one another's pain.
Luise's perturbation of the last few days
was entirely justified.
To make matters even worse,
the photo of the girls,
taken during their summer camp trip
is now on its way
to the Munich Graph Publishing House.
The fate of the two
is currently hanging in the balance.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Lotte, I got something I have to apologize for.
It's the same for me, Luise.
The secret that we two pledged to guard
was delivered to mom on a silver plate!
And on my side, despite my best effort,
I couldn't do a thing to somehow stop dad from marrying.
Who do we do now, Lotte?
All is lost now, Luise!
Next time, I and Myself:
Sorry, Mom!
Episode 23
Don't miss it!