In the quiet countryside, next to a lake,
there's a summer camp.
Luise, who came here for her summer vacations
suddenly meets another girl, Lotte,
looking exactly like her.
Denial was her first reaction.
Between the two girls, who had never exchanged
a word before, a bizarre sentiment suddenly arises.
The two are probably yet to realize -
it was the most fateful meeting of their lives.
Episode 2
Thread of Fate
Good morning, Luise.
Today it's certainly going to be fun, too.
No way she gives in.
Not to some Munich snob girl.
Come on, Luise.
Let's go play over there.
Everyone, I got a ball!
Brigitte let me borrow it.
That miser girl did? Can't believe my ears!
Hey, maybe we do dodgeball?
Nina, we'll be needing this court to play dodgeball now,
you go use some other place for chatting.
Let's have our leave, girls.
They are still just as uncommunicative to each other.
It seems, Luise and Lotte
are not starting to get along any time soon.
This morning, we never saw one
kicking another's leg, didn't we?
And yet, they are so strikingly similar,
it's as though they are astrological twins.
Astrological twins?
When people look absolutely alike,
without being even distantly related,
most likely, they just happened to be born
in the same fraction of the same second.
This reminds me of some older story I've read...
There was a tailor in London
who looked exactly like Edward VII, the King of England.
You couldn't tell them apart.
And they had actually been born in the same second?
Yes.
And then...
At the King's behest, the tailor had to shave off his beard
to differ from the King.
But still, what do we do about those girls?
We can't make one shave off her beard.
They will be just fine.
While in their souls,
the sentiment of rebuke still predominates,
the sentiment of attraction
is soon to displace it.
Luise, let's do it!
What's going on?
You're not being your usual self.
Where's that energy you always have in you?
True! The always tireless Luise
is just indifferent instead.
Think I'll pass today.
Wait a minute, Luise.
You're being weird since yesterday, Luise
Is it because of this Lotte?
Don't let her get under your skin!
Instead, just hurry up and bite off her nose already!
Will you stop saying such rubbish, Christine?
But I thought she is going to reap
the full extent of your anger!
I can't go around biting off everybody's noses
just cause they anger me one way or another.
That's right.
It wouldn't be reasonable.
What's that talk?
I was just trying to put myself in your shoes.
You've never been in my shoes!
Besides, Lotte never earned my anger in the first place!
Fiddles, you were glowing with anger!
And while we were dining,
you kicked that girl in the shin!
That's right, she nearly broke into tears then.
Someone like Stephie would have cried right away.
But Lotte is too boring for that.
Enough I said!
If you don't shut up at once,
you'll be the ones getting a kick on the shins next!
What's the matter with her?
It's not the usual Luise we know.
I really wonder what's gotten into you, Luise.
Lotte...
It's pretty.
Want one?
Would you be willing to put it on my head?
Lovely! It looks great on you.
Thank you.
But aren't you still mad at me?
You were the only one mad at people!
Because it came as a surprise.
You appearing so suddenly...
I was a little started myself.
Did you leg hurt bad?
A bit, yes. Nobody ever kicked me like that before.
I yielded to my habit.
Slapping people here and there...
You're such a tomboy.
Sorry.
I forgot already.
Still, don't you think it's really peculiar?
What's peculiar?
Well, you know...
Let's go.
Say, you have any siblings?
I have none.
So do I!
Come on!
I know! Luise, would you mind
sitting here for a moment?
Ouch!
Bear with it.
You always yell like that
when your mom combs your hair, too?
But I don't really have a mom.
That's why...
Ouch!
People say, that's why
I'm being so noncompliant sometimes.
That explains a lot.
It feels like they've never been brushed before.
Maybe you're just too used to your mom
always combing your hair for you?
It's true that she's been doing it
since I was small.
But these days, I do it myself.
Mom is being too busy with her work.
And dad... Well I don't have one.
We are such a polar opposites.
In my family, it's dad who is constantly busy.
He is a musician.
Sometimes, he composes,
sometimes he conducts operas.
Also living with us -
our housekeeper Resi.
She's nice and all, but combing a child's hair
is not something she's fond of.
Doesn't your dad ever take a slipper to you?
Are you serious?
My dad dotes on me too much, saying this all the time:
"You are my most precious treasure!"
Even when I do something deserving scolding,
he just looks me straight in the eyes,
and asks me this, ever so seriously:
"Are you asking for a spanking?"
My! So he spoiled you beyond belief.
Not at all! It's just that my dad
is always preoccupied with other stuff he has to tend to.
But can't he free up
even just one hand to do it?
I don't recognize our Luise.
She's not here either.
Where else could she be?
Forget about her.
She can't make up her mind herself!
Let's go now.
Like two beans in a pod!
I couldn't tell one from another myself!
Say, Lotte, you have another apron like that?
There's a spare one in the bag.
Sublime! You mind if I borrow it?
No, don't mind at all.
Alright, deal.
This smells like tons of fun!
I can't wait!
Where could those two be?
Wherever they are,
I bet they are fighting to death.
Maybe we'll see a full-blown slap this time!
It'll be such a waste if she does it
while we're not watching!
Christine, she's here.
Hey, you! This there is Luise's seat!
Asking for another kick, are you?
What in the world is going on?
Which one is the real Lotte?
Luise, how do we ever tell which one is you?
She is from Munich!
I wonder if there's ever a third one
looking exactly like this!
Oh, you gotta be kidding me!
You were like cat and dog just yesterday!
How did it come to this?
What's all this commotion about?
What exactly is going on here? Pray, try to explain, Lotte.
Oh no, is Lotte the one over there?
Ah, why is this happening?
I'm going mad.
My, my! Your resemblance is so remarkable,
it is now bordering a mischief?
You're such a troublesome bunch.
But still, won't you tell us just to be sure,
which one is Luise Palfy and which one is Lotte Körner?
That would be a secret.
What are you saying?
This transgress an innocuous joke, you two.
Oh, aren't we in trouble now?
How should we ever tell you apart?
Girls, can anyone here distinguish them?
Truda can! Truda, if there's anyone
who could, it must be you.
You spend your whole life in the same class as Luise.
Eh, you think so?
I don't see a difference. At all.
Got it! There's a surefire way
to tell apart at least one of them.
Ouch!
This here is Luise!
This girl sure knows what she's doing!
My, how most unexpected!
That can be considered sorted out.
Now, now, everyone.
Return to your seats.
We can postpone the discussion to after the lunch.
Hey, you plan to dress up like this every day now?
No way! Those braids are too burdensome to wear.
Minding your conduct,
like a proper braided girl would, is above me!
Some things in Luise never change, after all.
My! Not a hint of consideration for others' feelings!
You swore your eternal enmity just yesterday,
and now you bring her along like we don't mean business!
My bad, my bad.
I hope we can become friends now, Truda.
I hope so too, Lotte. At least, I shouldn't be afraid of you
slapping me any given moment.
Say, Christine, how about us two
also bury the hatchet and move on?
Sure thing, you make friends where you find them.
You'll tell me all about how Vienna is like, won't you?
Only as long as you reveal to me every secret of Munich!
A photographer?
Yes, we have one.
But why would you need him?
We wish to fix our "doubleness" by a camera.
We'll send the pictures back home.
Just letters would never suffice.
The fact the two can be so alike -
you wouldn't believe it until you see a picture!
I see. You want your relatives to see it, too?
Very well.
You two can go down to the village.
Thank you.
Make sure to take a great picture.
Remember, you should be back by dinner.
Okay!
Seebühl Village
Get ready now, young ladies.
We're starting.
Now, Twin Frauleins, please straighten up your backs.
The photo is done,
good job, everyone.
Thank you, Herr Eipeldauer.
When will the picture be ready?
Give me just three days.
I'll format it into a postcard.
Then, we'll come pick it up later.
I'll make sure you'll love this print!
After all, two young Frauleins on it
are as similar as twins!
He said "twins!"
Really, it's not every day
that you get to see two girls so alike.
Actually, I'll send a few glossy prints
to some of the big illustrated magazines.
They're often interested in things like that.
Ah, that's better.
I can finally feel like I am myself again.
Hey, those pictures sure are expensive,
I was startled by that tag.
Don't you worry about it.
Dad sent me here with a hefty allowance.
Lotte, aren't you thirsty?
Let's get something to drink here.
But...
Don't be shy. I'll take care of you.
Just a small detour, we'll be fine.
Say, has your dad been dead for long?
No clue.
I don't remember.
Mom also never mentions my dad.
And the last time I was pressing her to tell me,
it was just too distressing for her.
So I no longer try to find out.
But I shouldn't think that he is really dead.
I've never been to his grave.
I also don't have a single memory of my mom.
We used to have a photo of her, though.
On the piano in my dad's office.
All I can remember is that she was pretty.
When I was small,
I was looking at her all the time.
Then, some years ago,
I asked dad directly,
"Where is my mom now?"
Dad never gave me an answer.
Next day, the photo was gone.
I'm sure he locked it up somewhere.
We're both so unfortunate.
One doesn't have a dad
and the other doesn't have a mom.
It seems, along with appearances,
we suffer a common fate as well.
Probably, age, too.
You're ten, aren't you?
Yeah. Will turn eleven on the fourteenth of October.
Fourteenth of October?
Yes, this is my birthday.
Mine, too!
And your birthplace is...
Linz on the Danube.
Mine, too.
My mom's name is Luiselotte Körner!
Luiselotte?
Luise...
Lotte...
A photo...
I have mom's photo in my locker!
Show it to me!
Hey, hey! Is it epidemic among kids these days?
Drinking the juice and leaving without paying...
I'm sorry!
Ah... Hey! Your change!
Now what another mischief
are those young monkeys up to now?
We're in trouble, Frau Muthesius!
Those girls are actually not astrological twins.
Please take a look at this register.
Luise and Lotte
were really born on the same day!
It simply cannot be a coincidence.
Yes, that's what I had concluded, too, Fraulein Ulrica.
Then, you knew this already?
After writing down Lotte's birthday,
I immediately compared it to Luise's in the register.
Then, what do we do about this?
It seems, those two are yet to notice it.
They said they'll take a picture together
and send it home.
If that helps to unravel the knot,
all's well and good.
However, as mere bystanders, you and me
should limit our long-term interference in their fates.
Right, Fraulein Ulrica?
Mom...
My mom...
Our
mom.
Which means
we really are sisters, aren't we?
Luise and Lotte had finally discovered
the thread of fate that binds them together.
However, that thread is long
and is still lavishly knotty along the way.
How would the two
proceed with unraveling this thread further on?
Perhaps, in a way distinctive to them only?
A miserable Romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
I am Luise.
And I am Lotte.
Say, Lotte, did you know
that Stephie's parents are getting a divorce?
Yes. They have already started the hearings
to decide, which parent she is staying with.
It's cruel, don't you think?
While sending Stephie away for summer vacations,
doing such a thing behind her back!
Poor Stephie!
I wonder if we would ever be able to understand
the feelings overflowing her now!
Next time in I and Myself:
Oath by the Lake. Don't miss it!
Episode 3
Oath by the Lake
Translated by Perevodildo | Timings by Sub-RoRo