Lotte and Luise swapped places.
Lotte had become Luise,
and is heading to Vienna to meet her father.
Luise had become Lotte
and is rushing to Munich for a meeting with mother.
Two little twin sisters
embarked on a grand adventure.
Episode 5
Long Day for the Twins
Translation: Perevodildo    |    Timings: Sub-RoRo
"Dad's atelier is in a one-room apartment
along Kärntner Ring."
Kärntner Ring...
"Dad may be a huge egotist.
When music he composed himself is playing,
he gets completely absorbed."
However, while in the composing daze,
he is always grumpy and irritable.
And God save you,
if you try to talk to him at such a time.
Conversely, if the composing is going smoothly, he breaks into the room in the dead of night to pepper me with kisses.
But then, he also reeks of alcohol a bit.
That would be our dad, one word - an oddball!
Will I really be able to get along with dad?
Especially, if he reeks of alcohol?
Christine, you can't have this!
But come on! Even on the train,
you only think of studying!
You're not being the usual Luise!
Eh? I'm not the usual Luise?
Mischievous and insubordinate tomboy!
The teachers' bane Luise Palfy.
What's that talk?
I'm the most usual myself.
See? See?
Ouch!
Even more strange!
Maybe you need a break?
Monica, sorry, sorry.
I'm so awkward in this role!
Everyone finding out is a question of time!
Probably, with dad in the vanguard!
I've had enough already.
I want to run away!
Luise, how have you been doing?
Munich Central Station
So that's what Munich is like!
I'm finally here!
When mom shows up, before saying anything,
I'll kiss her hard! Definitely!
I wonder how it feels
to be kissing your mother?
Luise, you'll know it's mom
by her totally irresistible smell.
But first, you'll notice her yellow dress.
That'll be a surefire feature.
Let's see. Yellow, yellow...
Mother!
Nina!
My, you look so fresh!
Did you like it in the summer camp?
You bet!
Oh, it's just Nina's mom? She's pretty.
But it goes without saying,
my own mom would be times as pretty!
Vienna Western Station
Yes! We're here! Vienna!
Been a while.
Look, Luise!
Your dad is already here.
Right there!
Handsome whenever I get to see him,
Luise's dad.
No less from a famous Viennese composer!
You're lucky. Wish I had a dad like that, too.
This is him... my dad.
The gentleman down the platform,
I think, is Herr Ludwig Palfy himself!
Indeed! Ladies, shall we go pay our respects?
My! If it isn't Herr Palfy.
I am infinitely honored to meet you!
No need...
I have listened to your every opera!
Master, your genius is unquestionable!
Ah... Yeah. Thank you.
But I'm meeting my daughter from this train.
Ah! Luise, this way!
Just as I thought.
He is not some scary bogeyman.
Excuse me, could you?
I need to get to him, please...
Excuse me! Please let me through!
Please let me through!
Ladies! Silence, please!
Hey, Luise! Welcome back.
I mean... all that humbug at a place like this
might deliver someone a nuisance.
I humbly ask you
to show some decency and etiquette.
Eh?
Decency? Etiquette?
Did I hear that right?
I'm so sorry I'm late, my dear!
Mama!
You must be sick of waiting.
Come on, let's head home.
Did you like it in the summer camp?
I loved every minute of it!
That's what I wanted to hear!
I thought, I'd be already
lavishing mom with kisses by now.
But mom still...
Munich Graph Magazine
Oh, how many more times
do I have to tell you, Editor Bernau?
This week's top article is the grand success
of a women rights activist! Nothing else is even close!
I got it, got it. But for the top article, you should be choosing
something more eye-catching, Missis Körner.
Miss Körner!
It's the first time I'm meeting a woman
as headstrong as you!
Which one of us is headstrong here?
Women rights have been the talk of the town
in the recent years!
All I do is ensuring our magazine
keeps up with the trend!
Ah, but because of all this,
I am now indecently late!
I was supposed to pick my daughter up
back from vacations.
Oh, my poor Lotte.
Wait, the matter is not solved yet!
No way I make her wait any more than that!
Are you running away
because you can't handle the job?
Running away?
Don't say nonsense.
We'll settle it when I'm back in two hours.
Until then, don't you decide on it without me,
Herr Headstrong Editor-in-chief!
Are you kidding me?
Any other chief would have fired her long ago!
This magnificent man... my dad.
I want to make a talk.
But what do I say?
What is it, Luise?
Something's off with my face today?
Nothing at all.
It's just that we've not seen each other in a while
so I've been missing my dear dad and his face.
Glad to know my daughter
didn't grow to detest my face in that time.
Enough a reason for me to be a happy dad.
And yet, it's as though something's off.
This relatively short time has been enough
to cause a barely perceptible change in you.
But I haven't changed one bit!
I'm the same as always.
No. For starters, you're been sitting tight
throughout the whole drive.
No hint of usual jumping around,
frolicking, excitement.
Must be that I'm just a little tired after the train.
Add to that what you said before,
about decency and etiquette.
Before, hearing such a thing
would have led me to think you're out of your mind.
I know! You're playing a good child now
to ask me for a big favor in the future.
Either that, or some other conspiracy...
Why would I need to conspire against you?
Thing is, summer camp girls knew some manners,
so it rubbed off on me.
At summer camp, sure... But... manners?
Lotte!
Mom!
Uh... Ouch.
You okay?
Ah, my Lotte! Sorry I made you wait.
You're finally back!
What's the matter?
While on the way,
I made up my mind to kiss you before you do!
Very well.
Mom!
Good perfume.
My, was just one month away really enough to make
my resolute little housekeeper so suddenly sentimental?
Now, shall we get something good to eat
before returning home?
Can I have an omelette?
Huh? Did you say omelette?
Sure, no problem.
We'll take what you want.
Great!
Mom, love you!
Imperial Hotel
Huh? What's the matter, Luise?
It's your very first omelette today,
but you barely touched it!
It's because... You see...
Thing is...
Very odd! Even when bedridden
with a fever of 39 degrees,
even when weeping
over a boyfriend breaking up with you,
you would invariably empty
at least five plates of omelette.
Actually, my tastes may have shifted a bit
while in summer camp.
Oh? Tastes shifted in summer camp?
Ah! I can't stand omelette.
No way I would ever make a convincing Luise.
Oh my, Luise, back already?
Did you enjoy your summer vacation?
Who is this man?
Still, I bet you'll never choose it
over being with your dad in Vienna.
I know! Always talking with his hand on his beard.
Herr Strobl, isn't it? The doctor.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet me?
But I was somehow sure
you and me are ancient friends!
Right... But we've not seen each other in a long time.
So it's as though we meet for the first time.
Sublime! Such a great change
in just little more than a month.
A girl is well-behaved, refined and tender!
Exactly! A different person!
This immature susceptibility, a plasticity of soul,
with excitements of youth!
Ah, the emotion is strong!
It's overwhelming!
He's at it again.
At it... again?
Childish subtlety as opposed to maturity...
This is it! It's this melody!
The name would be "Vivacity of Childhood."
No! "The Fickleness of Children."
Right. Before I forget,
gotta write it down in a score.
Ah! But your meal...
Ah... Herr Strobl, look after Luise, will you?
Sure, you can leave this to me.
Boy, serve the girl a dessert.
Ah... Okay.
My, my. You may have changed somewhat,
but there's nothing that can affect your dad.
Well, we've arrived, Luise.
It's here.
This is our home at Rotenturmstraße!
My father's house!
You haven't been here for over a month.
Must have been missing it?
Now, come on it.
Those comic books are quite amusing!
Who could that be?
Master is not supposed to be coming home today.
Hey, Resi, it's us!
Fraulein Luise is back!
Right! It's the day when young Fraulein returns!
Hello.
Welcome back.
Herr Strobl, come inside for some tea, too. Please.
No, no, you will now have to excuse me.
See you later, Luise.
Farewell, Herr Strobl.
Ah, Peperl! I'm back!
My, usually, he'd be jubilant beyond belief by now.
How could you forget your master completely
after not seeing her for just a month, you dense dog?
No big deal. I'll make friends with him again in no time.
Don't mind what she said, Peperl.
You're the shrewd one here.
Want me to serve a lunch soon?
No, I've had my lunch already.
I'd like to rest a bit for now.
And here it's the living room. Pretty!
Huh?
My, how did this happen?
Just as I've finally finished cleaning up,
Peperl decides to give me more work!
Lotte, be wary of her.
Resi is a big fat liar.
Her words and her actions seldom meet.
But she also said,
Resi is not a completely disagreeable person.
Either way, I should
keep my ears to the ground with her.
That was a good restaurant.
I didn't expect my Lotte to order an omelette...
Moreover, you ate five of them!
Didn't see that coming.
Well, Lotte is home, for the first time in a month.
This is it.
This is my and mom's home.
Why wouldn't it be, you quirky child?
Just saying I'm happy.
It's been a while.
Hey, you mind if I recheck everything?
Wanna make sure all the rooms are
where they were before the vacations.
Sure, why would I mind.
Need a guide to show you the way?
If that wouldn't bother you too much.
I like those manners.
Right. Here, as you may remember, we have a kitchen.
Behind there - toilet and bathroom,
and the bath itself, too.
Towels are all stored here,
feel free to help yourself to them.
This place we both use for recreation -
a living room, if you will.
And a messy one at that!
I may have neglected it a bit, because of work.
Finally, here is the room for Lotte and me.
I left your half exactly the way it was
before the summer camp.
I am in Lotte's room.
And also, when I start living here
with mom, my room, too!
Right, and this here is mom's side.
Not the biggest room around,
but enough for two.
I hope you find it comfortable.
I absolutely like it!
And it's pretty!
Thank you. When Lotte is beaming like that,
I myself can't help but to rejoice, too.
I've been away for so long, I nearly forgot it.
It's as though I've never been here before!
Now I'm quite certain
you're nothing like my usual Lotte.
Normally, I'd think you're an adult in a girl's body.
But today's Lotte is a normal lively child again!
Was it that fun in the summer camp?
We did this, we did that...
I wasn't sure how you'd react
to being sent alone to the summer camp.
But now all my worries are behind.
Also, just being here with my mother
is even more fun.
It's the same for me, Lotte.
I'll make sure we never part again.
Oh no, I completely forgot!
What is it?
I have to meet the Headstrong Editor!
Headstrong Editor?
Editor-in-Chief of Munich Graph.
I need to return to the office now.
I'm so sorry.
I promise to return as soon as I can.
Later, this evening, we'll play cards.
Cards? You promise?
I'll be waiting, awake!
Okay, later then.
Hooray! Playing cards with mom.
How odd. It's past nine already.
But she hasn't returned still.
Apparently, not keeping their promises
is inherent to all the grown-ups, not just dad.
Could it be because that Headstrong Editor-in-Chief
is not letting mom go?
Lotte said he is a hearty old chap.
But so far, he just sounds mean.
You could use some coffee.
Ah? Thank you.
Today, your sweet daughter
finally made it home, didn't she?
From this point,
I could finish the manuscript for you.
Don't you wanna get home sooner?
No.
Not after going through all the trouble of persuading you
to make women rights activist's success our top article.
I must now bring it to the completion myself.
My, my. There's no helping your obstinacy.
But I'm quite certain, with this,
I'm earning your daughter's animosity.
Well, do your best then.
I expect a fine article.
Sure.
I'm sorry, Lotte.
But I've no time to slack off. Fight, fight!
At this rate, by the time mom's back,
I'll fall asleep already.
Well, it's fine, too.
We're yet to have plenty of evenings together.
I know! I'll use that time to write to Lotte.
She seems a little feather-headed so far,
but mom is still the best!
95 out of 100!
I wonder what is Lotte doing now.
Has she been able to find her way around dad?
In the end, I couldn't bring myself to eat any omelette.
But it seems, nobody paid any attention to it.
Tonight, dad stays in his atelier
on Kärntner Ring to work.
My impression of dad is 95 out of 100.
He may have his head in the clouds sometimes,
sometimes straight up childish.
But he's still cool and handsome.
And so, so caring!
Today, I didn't really have a chance to talk to him.
But tomorrow, I made up my mind
to talk plenty to him.
On my part, tomorrow
I'm starting my foray into cooking.
But I'm sick worried
about whether or not I can do it.
Mom, will it be good enough for you?
My cooking.
In the cities, strange to them,
a stranger before - now is dad, or mom.
A day full of magic had finally come to an end.
But the excitements of tonight that the two experienced
would hardly be forgotten any time soon.
A miserable Romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next Episode Preview
We swapped places!
Luise, cooking is not that hard!
Cooking does not scare me!
It can't be harder than fighting.
And I have prepared for dad
a beef macaroni soup this morning!
To which they said, I haven't heard
the word "cooking" not once in the ten years!
What did you expect?
Alright, I'm trying my luck with beef, too!
Mom will sure be surprised!
Next time in I and Myself:
Solid Cook, Horrid Cook.
Episode 6
Solid Cook, Horrid Cook
Don't miss it!