Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
To arrange a meeting for their parents,
the two gave them both invitations to a restaurant.
And thus, finally, having met in Munich face to face,
dad and mom managed to talk peacefully.
However, contrary to Lotte's reckoning, even after that,
their parents preferred to leave things as they currently are.
Once again, Luise had become Lotte.
And Lotte had also become Luise.
Separately, they return to their alternative lives
in Vienna and Munich.
Episode 19
We Can't Understand Dad!?
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
What do you know -
our trip to Munich feels like a dream already.
After such a long time,
I was delighted to see Luise and mom again.
We moved mountains
to make dad and mom talk to each other again.
And yet, unlike the movies,
they turned it into the least romantic thing ever.
Why are you playing innocent?
After getting this far, why?
You tell me why,
after bringing me out to a place like this!
No! I didn't...
Save your breath.
This man's vaunting about his love
is what you wanted me to hear!
Vaunting about love?
I know exactly why you invited me here - to injure my pride,
to humiliate me in the most aggravating manner.
I've had enough!
Maybe we should come up with some new plan
for drawing them together?
Still, Luise, it's just the way you wrote it in your letter.
Even if she doesn't let it show through,
mom still loves dad.
I'm sure of it.
And still...
Dad, how do you feel about her?
Not that, not that!
For whatever reason,
I can't get in the right mood.
At least one of us
is entering the happiest years of his life.
Useless!
Take your mind off this.
It's all in a distant past now.
We became strangers as soon as we broke up.
She can do whatever with her life. Not my concern anymore.
That said...
It's as though she became even prettier.
Radiating confidence, livelier than ever.
You two are so alike.
You and Luise.
Oh, him... I wonder if he is leading a happy life.
Even if he is still just as willful,
just as egocentric.
And Luise...
What kind of upbringing is he giving to Luise?
Is he treasuring her more than anything else?
Could it be that I shouldn't have
entrusted him with Luise when we broke up?
Luise...
Mom, the bath is vacant.
Okay!
Very well.
Ah! I sure am tired today.
Mom...
was crying?
I'm sure, it was about dad...
Still, though...
You stand fast on your points, just like in old times.
No, even more than before.
And yet, it was our first meeting in years.
You could have shown at least a bit of amiability.
Ah, no good, no good.
This kind of obsession
is a shortcut to becoming neurasthenic.
An artist must have a free and unbound mind,
with no shackle, no chain able to ground me.
As my soul is soaring freely through the skies...
Oh, it's so much like dad!
You'll catch a cold this way!
Dad!
I guess the time has not come yet.
Ah! And everything's in a jumble again!
Mom's photo!
Why is it like that?
Don't tell me dad...
feels this way towards mom?
No!
Yes?
Herr Palfy? This is Irene.
Ah, Frau Irene!
Oh my, were you still asleep?
I'm so sorry.
Have you finished this latest work of yours?
Yeah... more or less...
Does it mean, then, we can pick you up soon?
About that...
What for, exactly?
My, you managed to forget already?
The other day, I invited you on a party, held today.
Ah, it's that day already?
Make sure to bring Luise along.
Then, I'll meet you outside your house
at Rotenturmstraße.
Right! Well, then.
Ah, this is bad.
It slipped my mind completely.
Now then, what time is it?
What's that, Luise?
You're already here?
Yes. Good morning, dad.
Ah, you'll say your mornings later,
we need to go to Frau Irene's party now.
Come on, hurry up to preen yourself.
Eh? Me too?
Naturally. Now, start moving,
lest we'll be late.
Luise!
Come on, we're in a hurry!
Resi, make it real quick.
They'll come to pick us up any minute.
Fine!
Goodness, whenever our Master is at home,
he wants everything and at once.
Going to Frau Gerlach's house...
Why should I do it?
What's the matter, Luise?
We're going out on a party.
But looking at you,
one would think you're going on a funeral.
Well, it seems, my head starts to hurt a little.
Your head? Hurts bad?
For how long? Huh? Temperature...
I don't think there's anything else wrong with me.
But maybe... I just stay to watch after the house?
Yes!
As arranged, I'm here to pick you up.
Right, sorry for the trouble...
Now, shall we go, Luise?
Ah... About that, unfortunately Luise cannot...
Oh...
My, your necktie!
Ah... Thanks.
Really, sorry for the trouble...
Oh no, if dad goes there alone, it's even worse.
Sorry I kept you waiting.
Ah, Luise, better already?
Huh? Your head?
I'm fine now.
Shall we go?
Take care!
Today, you'll have the pleasure
of meeting some of my special guests.
Oh? But you still don't mind Luise coming,
to such a top-tier party?
Without a doubt! After all, Luise is my dear friend,
and I hope we'll become even closer friends after that, right?
I'm not becoming friends with her.
I plan to use this occasion
to finally introduce you, Herr Palfy, to my father.
Ah... I was also hoping for a chance
to finally get acquainted to your respectable family.
What? What's this all about?
Of course, for Luise as well,
it's a good chance to get used to our company for the future.
"For the future?"
Just what...
What can she possibly mean by that?!
You are a long-awaited guest here, Herr Palfy.
You always look after my daughter Irene,
which I can't help but to appreciate.
Ah, no need... You're welcome.
Father, Young Fraulein over here is Luise.
Luise Palfy, Herr.
You've been so kind as to invite me.
Thank you very much.
My, my, a little lady, aren't you?
Pleased to meet you, Luise.
The pleasure is mine.
This old man looks friendly.
No wonder he's the owner of the Imperial Hotel.
My, isn't that Madame?
You finally managed to come?
Thanks a lot for inviting me.
I know you've been terribly busy lately.
That woman...
Where could I have seen her?
Allow me to introduce. This is my friend,
a famous Parisian designer, Madame Sharman.
So she's a famous fashion designer!
Madame, this here is composer and conductor,
Herr Ludwig Palfy.
My, that Palfy?
May I add that I am highly delighted to meet you?
Pleased to meet you, Madame.
It's your sublime music that sparks
this inspiration inside me, whenever I need it.
Well, I'm honored, Madame.
Herr Palfy,
I am Meyer, pleased to meet you. One can't help
appreciating the distinctive stance that your music has.
It's awe-inspiring!
Herr Meyer is a professional architect.
I also had been waiting
for a chance to get introduced to you.
Herr Palfy, before you - Herr Fischer, the writer.
I was really moved by your opera the other day.
It was unforgettable.
Ah, I am honored...
Now, why don't you join us in the lounge?
Sure.
Everyone here is unbelievably famous...
And dad is admired more than anyone!
Suddenly, it feels as if dad somehow got transported
to another, completely separate world.
Dad now have a personal dad's world all to himself.
The world incomprehensible to us children.
The grownups' world.
So sorry, Luise, I had neglected my dear guest!
Now, come join us, too.
There are plenty of delicious cakes there.
Come on, don't be shy.
Help yourself to anything you like, Luise.
Luise, anything caught your eye yet?
There are still a good many things
I need to learn about you, the sooner - the better.
Why so?
Irene, Herr Palfy is a truly amazing gentleman!
Why, you! Rumors reach me too, you know.
Are you two engaged already?
Oh my, have some patience!
We need a little more time.
Engagement?
Now, help yourself.
Don't want any.
Luise?
Dad...
Something's going on in your world.
Something I have no idea about.
Well, isn't Luise an adorable child?
But still, she is not making it any easier for me.
She follows Herr Palfy's each step!
Not every wife can be that clingy.
She is feeling lonely in absence of a mother.
I'll be all right when she starts seeing one in you.
But father, Herr Palfy himself
also clings to his daughter whenever he can!
Between me and that girl -
which one, do you think, is more important?
My, your rival is but a child.
In some ten years, she'll get married off.
I can't wait for that long!
I want a clear victory, here and now!
It's only attainable
if I make Herr Palfy mine altogether!
Dad, for how long do you plan to stay here?
I want to go home already.
Luise is probably having a dinner with mom...
If only you knew, how much I'm earning
to be able to talk to you now...
My, this evening air is so refreshing!
Herr Palfy, won't you keep me company?
Sure.
Look, Herr Palfy...
Yes?
Do you intend to keep teaching Luise piano yourself?
Yes, naturally.
This girl's gift is unquestionable. And it's similar to mine.
So I must do my utmost to cultivate it.
My, but I was sure a composer
of quite your magnitude
would find a better use for his talent,
than tutoring piano to a little girl!
Don't you believe it's a waste
of your precious time?
A waste? No, don't joke like that!
Let it be known,
this girl is what my own music originates from!
Lately, I just think "Luise" and the melody
starts flowing by itself, like from a spring!
Is that so?
In that case, I guess I'll never be able
to become a source for your art, after all.
Ah... No, I never said that.
When I'm with you, I feel something...
Like what?
Well, it's...
Maybe they call it "sweetened?"
All in all, a jolly good time.
My, I'm so happy!
I was feeling the exact same way!
Irene!
It's unfair to have him all to yourself.
My bad...
Herr Palfy, let's finish this talk inside.
Now, let's hurry.
Dad... Is really in love with Frau Gerlach?
Does this mean he is no longer
one bit concerned about mom?
I can't understand!
I can't understand dad's feelings!
But think of it - writing music just for children is nonsense.
There's no benefit in the art that caters to kids.
No, I don't seek benefit from it, Herr Fischer.
The ultimate art is universally appealing
both to grown-ups and to kids alike.
And still...
Dad.
If you excuse me for a moment.
What is it, Luise?
Feeling sleepy already?
Yes, can we go home now?
I might need just a tad bit
of explaining left to do.
Luise, you find our society tiring?
I could drive her home, if you'd like me to.
Ah... You'd really help me out by that.
Luise, you return without me and go to sleep.
But...
Your dad's companions still need him
to figure out all those complex matters.
Let's go, Luise.
Dad...
Thank you very much.
Suddenly, this feels like a strange house.
It's the first time I feel this way
ever since I came to Vienna.
I feel lonely,
as if in this whole city,
there's not a soul besides me.
What's the matter, Fraulein?
I bet you've been through something terrible.
I could tell by the Imp of Sorrow
sitting on your shoulder.
Imp of Sorrow?
Yeah, with this guy around,
you won't be able to get any night's sleep.
But fine, this old Herr
will look after it for you.
And... got you!
There, caught the guy.
Right, he is not your problem now.
Make sure to get a good sleep.
You'll be young and cheerful again in the morning.
Fraulein Luise!
Well, good night, Young Fraulein.
Good night! Thank you, Old Herr.
What just happened, Fraulein?
Did he want something from you?
Resi, do you know who he is?
Some painter, lives next door to us.
Has a reputation of an outcast and an oddball to boot.
I think, his name was something like Gabele.
Fraulein Luise, I suggest you avoid
even an eye contact with someone like that!
Herr Gabele?
He's right, I ought to get cheerful again!
Having seen the dad's world, hidden from her up until now,
Lotte had spent this whole day utterly downhearted.
But thanks to the encounter with Herr Gabele,
her heart had become a little lighter already.
However, what other trials
may be awaiting her in the coming day?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Luise! I had found myself a new friend.
It's a painter called Herr Gabele.
Glad to know! Dad cannot even work from home,
so Lotte might feel sad, being left alone.
That's exactly why, while talking to Herr Gabele in his flat,
I came up with this new great idea!
Eh? What is it?
Just pray for my success, will you?
I'll make them swap! Will think of something.
Next time in I and Myself:
New Ally, Herr Gabele.
Episode 20
New Ally, Herr Gabele
Wait for it!