Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
The only thing on Lotte's mind ever since she returned
from Munich is "Dad and Frau Gerlach - what's going on?"
Usually so liable to despondency, Lotte did not expect
Herr Gabele, living next door, to reignite her determination.
While conferring with the kind Herr Gabele about a matter
so painful to her, Lotte couldn't help breaking into tears.
However, through crying heartily,
she managed to bring her feelings in order,
allowing Lotte to come up with a new,
even more ingenious plan.
Episode 21
Dad, Don't Get Married!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Would you like me to leave them here, Herr Palfy?
Fine by me.
Oh my... Could I be possibly
distracting you too much, from your job?
Ah, no! You're... Oh, wow!
Those flowers are majestic.
My... Then, I guess, I must start
bringing you flowers every morning.
No, it's...
The one thing more striking than flowers here,
is you, Frau Irene.
Thank you. Don't you want
to take a few minutes break?
Yeah... I guess.
Dad!
Hey, Luise.
Ah, good morning to you, Luise.
Good morning.
I have...
Right! If you have a visitor,
I'll go prepare some tea!
My, she sure keeps you under her thumb.
It's as if she was your wife.
I'm amazed myself at how briskly
she picked up this thoughtfulness.
It seems, the summer camp this year
exerted the most beneficial influence on her.
That's a good observation,
kids her age make rapid steps towards independence.
But a constant overprotection, like that of yours,
may seriously hamper the process.
My overprotection?
But I'm just doing what a father should...
If a father exerts an excessive influence on his child,
the latter ends up developing a father complex.
Meaning that even in the future
she won't be able to stand on her own feet.
Do you really think so?
Here. Sorry I kept you waiting.
Thank you.
Ah, while we're at it, Luise,
are you here for a purpose?
Yes...
Oh? Then please don't pay me no mind. Go ahead.
Dad, do you know the painter who lives next door to us?
Ah? Herr Gabele, right? I know the man.
Well he is my friend, too!
And, well... Today I'm going to his place
to let him sketch me.
Very glad to hear that.
About that... You see...
It's getting a bit difficult for him.
The room where Herr Gabele lives
has tiny windows that don't let through enough light.
But really, he would have liked a more spacious room
with lots of light coming from above!
For example, it could be...
Something like this room, exactly!
Then, I guess he ought to find
a more accommodating atelier.
That's... What I thought, too...
However, the vacant ateliers
are not thick on the ground, he says...
What exactly is this girl's play?
So I thought this,
to do the composing, you don't really need a room like this,
with a lot of light coming from above, do you?
Oh, I guess that sounds about right...
So well... I put two and two together
and thought this -
if dad and Herr Gabele
exchange rooms,
wouldn't it be better?
In that case, Herr Gabele would have
an atelier with all the light he needs!
He'd be making good paintings!
And dad would also be working right next to us!
You'd even be able
to come home for dinner every time!
Every day, I would be making your favorite...
Then, even when you are working, I'll be able to hear
your piano, so I... won't feel so... lonely...
Now, I hope you both excuse me.
Herr Palfy, I shan't distract you any longer.
Ah... But... Frau Irene!
What's the matter, Frau Irene?
I thought we're dining together tonight.
Oh, really? But won't you be too preoccupied
with moving to a new place now?
No...
You don't take her words seriously, do you?
If this keeps up,
rumors will start spreading like wildfire.
You should consider taking a slipper
to your daughter, sometimes.
Don't hesitate to take a firm stand -
that's what all the fathers do.
Okay. I understand.
That girl will learn not to meddle in grownups' affairs.
I'll be sure to tell her off a bit.
Yes. If you wish the best for Luise,
that's exactly what you ought to do.
Well then, it's enough for today.
Dad seems irritated...
Still more work to do?
Are you... coming home to supper?
Luise, I want you to listen closely.
I don't like it when other people
deliver me any unnecessary worry.
Even if it's my daughter Luise.
What's good for me and what's not -
I can very much figure it out for myself.
Is that clear?
Yes, dad...
It's better this way.
She looked distressed,
but this all is for Luise's own good.
What a brazen girl!
Despite being just a brat, she tries to manipulate
and monopolize Herr Palfy, by keeping him on a short leash!
You're not having it your way.
I won't hesitate to accept your challenge, Luise.
Fraulein, are you not feeling well enough?
You haven't even touched your meal.
I'm all right, Resi.
Maybe just a little extra tired.
I'll go to bed early today.
If you say so.
Well, sweet dreams then.
I thought it was a brilliant idea.
Luise...
Dad refused to even consider it.
This is disheartening beyond possible.
Do you have any business here?
Excuse me... My dad...
Irene, we got a visitor?
No, darling.
Just some Fraulein whom I don't know.
But I am Luise! Luise, madam!
That girl is not Luise.
Dad? But I...
Well...
I really am...
Don't lie, you know you aren't Luise.
Dad...
Dad!
Peperl!
Here you are, Lotte.
It came! Finally came!
Thank you, Herr.
It's the joy that those letters give you,
that makes my work worth doing!
A painter that lives next door?
Luise, I came up with an idea which is oh so bright!
Please pray that my plan works, will you?
I'll make sure they swap, whatever it takes!
Quite an undertaking!
Lotte sure is giving it her best.
On my part, I'm not let her down either! Alright!
Lotte!
Mom?
It's dangerous to read while walking!
So who is it you're not letting down?
That's...
I got a letter from a friend I met at the summer camp.
In it, she wishes me the best of luck
in improving my grades.
So I said, I'm not...
Well, best of luck, then!
Speaking of which,
I was mighty lucky to meet you here.
My work for today is done and dusted with.
What do you say if we go eat somewhere?
Sounds great!
Whoa, heavenly!
The work was a breeze,
the dinner was a feast.
I'm so happy!
Are you...
Truly happy, mom?
Lotte is with me! Together, we lead a carefree life -
that alone is enough for me to be happy!
Say, mom, suppose your could "re-bear" me,
would you prefer me to get born as a boy instead?
Or would you rather still have a girl?
If I could "re-bear" you?
Let's me think...
I wouldn't mind having a boy either.
But I guess, a girl is still preferable.
A child such as Lotte,
I would gladly "re-bear."
Then, should you meet my dad again,
would you remarry him, too?
Eh? What's this about?
Well, you'd need my dad and my mom
to "re-bear" me, wouldn't you?
Oh, I see. That makes sense.
If... it would avail the present day me to "re-bear" you...
Remarrying doesn't sound bad at all.
"Present day you?"
By the time I married your dad,
I was still just a girl, barely out of the nest.
But as of now...
...Now you know how to make it work?
Well, nobody knows for sure...
All that is supposing
your dad hadn't changed either.
Ah, whatever. This had already happened,
and there's no overwriting it!
Now, let's return!
In real life, you can't just erase events
with a piece of rubber!
But mom, you don't necessarily have to erase it.
You can just turn the page to a clean one
and start writing anew.
Mom!
What, need my hand now?
So, shall we go?
What's the matter, Luise?
It's unbecoming of a girl
to look so pensive for a week straight.
Did someone in school
say a nasty thing about you?
Nothing of the kind so far.
Let's call it here for today.
By the way, Luise.
To drive out that rainy mood,
how about we go out on a stroll for a tasty cake?
Thank you, Herr Gabele.
Herr Gabele, the cakes here are a terrible rip-off!
What's the better time for squandering than this?
Now, come in.
Dad?
Been quite some time
since you last visited me, Frau Irene.
Did I forget to shave somewhere?
No.
Just trying to remember your face,
while I still have the chance.
What exactly do you mean to say?
Soon, I'm leaving for America.
With a good chance, I might never return.
To America?
That's so out of the blue...
I'm going there to marry someone.
Someone my father knows really well.
Marry?
But then...
Congratulations.
"Congratulations," you say?
My, how cruel!
Frau Irene...
Is that all you got to say?
Even knowing perfectly well
about my feelings towards you?
This is what father told me,
"Herr Palfy is a man of arts,
therefore he is too fickle and noncommittal.
I'm sorry, my dear,
but this marriage is not coming true."
Just like that.
But still, Frau Irene...
So harsh...
Our time together was short,
but I enjoyed every minute of it.
Even becoming a mother for little Luise
no longer seemed such a distant dream, and still...
I'll remember you as the best thing
that happened to me, forever...
In your memories, I'll probably remain an egoist,
to whom the music was more important than anything.
However, please remember,
that you were equally as important to me.
But you never really came
to feel any true need in me, didn't you?
I need you!
We both do - both me and Luise.
Frau Irene,
I want you to be my wife.
Oh my...
I'm struggling to even believe my ears right now...
I want to marry you.
My!
I'm so happy!
Oh my... What am I doing...
I hope you excuse me
fixing my makeup for a minute.
Said it out loud, at last.
Seized it at last.
A complete success!
The final victory is mine, Luise.
Ah, welcome home, Master.
Hello, Resi. Doing groceries?
Yes, I'll be out just for a moment... I'll be... back...
What is it, dad?
This something you wanted to tell.
You see, Luise...
When me and your mom were, well...
Since we split ways,
I've been completely alone all this time.
For seven years.
Well, naturally, you've also been here with me...
Well, thing is...
I think...
In short, I'm introducing some changes into our lives.
Dad?
And...
Once again, I...
Or well... I've decided to get married.
And it's with Frau Irene Gerlach!
You can't...
You can't do this... You can't!
You can't!..
You can't get married!
I beg you, dad...
Don't get married!
I beg you!
I beg...
Well, don't you think
you'll be happier, having a mother?
I'm quite certain, Frau Gerlach
would make a wonderful mother for you.
It's nothing! You'll love it yourself,
as soon as our new life starts!
I know you, and therefore, I have faith in you.
But I have to run.
I have to go now.
I need to be at the Opera House
for a dress rehearsal.
Later, then.
Above anything else,
this house requires a proper mother.
You realize that, don't you, Luise?
Dad?!
Dad! Dad!
Alas, the time had come
for the worst nightmare to come true.
Father made up his mind
on marrying Frau Irene Gerlach.
Upon hearing of this, Lotte felt
her whole body becoming as cold as ice.
It even took her some time to be able to move again.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
What should I do now, Luise?
Something happened, Lotte?
I'm sure, something disastrous must have stricken Lotte!
Will I be able to prevent this?
Please make sure you stop Frau Gerlach
and dad from marrying!
I cannot allow this!
Just wait till I tell him personally!
Next time in I and Myself:
Lotte's in Danger!?
Episode 22
Don't miss it!