Lotte, who came to Munich, found herself in her
former place, after switching places with Luise once again.
But then, what you can't call anything else
but a quirk of fate, came into play -
somehow, the entire family of four
happened to have come together for Palfy's concert.
But what will become of it now?
Episode 17
Munich in an Uproar!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Section A, seat three.
Ah! Here it is.
Lotte..!
Luise?
Seats one and two of the A section...
I think it's more to the front, dad.
Oh, right.
No way! Annie and her dad!
Oh, Annie, it's here, here.
Right, let's sit...
Annie, that dress looks perfect on you.
Everyone's eyes are on you tonight!
But hey, father, those concerts are the most boring stuff!
Annie, you should know,
there are not many people in Munich as rich as we are.
Our duty is to spend money on refined pastimes,
a "richnesse oblige," so to say!
What's going on, Luise?
We're between the hammer and the anvil!
And nowhere else to run!
Eh? What is it, Lotte?
Nothing serious.
Oh?
Oh? Well, well.
Munich's first intrepid lady.
Something like Frau Körner, isn't it?
Cute little hamster!
I see you're also excited for the concert!
Hey, bringing animals to the theater is...
What's your problem?
She is quiet kid, alright?
Damn right!
As a figure in this town, I swear by my name of Habersetzer
that every member of my family is an epitome of propriety!
My, some people are quick to fly off the handle!
You know him?
Munich's first prudish family.
The girl next to Lotte is with them, too?
I can't take a good look...
My, what's the matter, Lotte?
Well, maybe I went to sleep
with an open window yesterday.
Look! Mom, they're starting!
Lotte, hide your face.
Dad's going to greet me now.
Don't tell me I've caught a fever.
It was as though I saw two Luises.
Herr Palfy seems to be slightly out of condition today.
He doesn't usually do this.
Something is definitely off.
Is my mind playing tricks on me?
What's wrong with him today?
He is not being his usual self.
His music sounds unsteady.
Lotte, we're in trouble if dad gets a good look at you.
Let's run away.
But how?
You tell mom your head hurts,
then escape to your right.
At the same time, I'll escape to the left.
But...
We've no other choice!
Mom, I'll have to go home now.
My, what's wrong?
Just a little headache.
Ouch!
Watch where you're going!
Eh? You...
AH! It hurts!
There's a mouse!
Help, I can't stand them!
What's going on there?
Enough! Enough! Stop playing!
The concert is disrupted!
Well, mom, I guess there's no point staying anyway.
Lotte, get some sleep when you're back.
Whoa! Made it out!
And I thought there was no saving us.
All thanks to Annie's hamster.
Gonna thank her later!
Still, this all turned into such an uproar.
I'm sure, dad is also mad now...
My music is made into a hullabaloo!
Not once in my life, I've been ridiculed like that!
You're right, everything that happened is our fault only.
Because of just one hamster,
the entire concert is disrupted.
It's the first such debacle
in the history of our opera house, either.
Enough already!
Don't try my patience and leave me alone!
Herr Palfy.
What is it?
Well...
Multiple local news magazines
are requesting a press conference.
Press conference?!
Why do I have to explain it even to my manager?!
I'm not seeing a single soul more today!
My tuxedo!
Who had this bright idea of leaving it here?!
Herr...
did just five minutes ago...
Ah! That I know myself!
Anyway, just arrange a car to the hotel now!
How did it go?
A dead end.
Press conference has been cancelled. Needless to say,
he didn't give a single personal interview either.
They say, Palfy is retiring to hotel now.
We've exhausted our options.
Exhausted? Don't say nonsense!
We've plenty of options to interview him
in the hotel! We need to hurry!
I wash my hands of it.
Going that far is not something I'm prepared to do.
Be it for the Berlin concert last time,
be it for today's one.
More than ever, the fans are eager
to hear some explanation from him.
Getting it out of him -
is the part and parcel of our work.
But I can't imagine a worst time for an interview
than that after such an uproar.
Now, if you excuse me.
Wait.
For someone who usually stops at nothing, your willingness
to accept defeat in the matters pertaining Palfy is suspicious.
Is there a reason for that special treatment?
None that I know of.
No reason for special treatment.
Very well.
I'll get you an interview from Palfy.
That's what I wanted to hear!
This article could only qualify as a professional one
if you, as someone educated in classical music, write it.
You're a life-saver.
Now, let's not waste any time.
Mom is going...
To meet dad...
Interview?
Refusing an interview even now
is against the rules.
We have applied for it
through official channels three days ago.
Even if I try to talk him into it now,
Herr Palfy is still profoundly shocked
by the events of this evening.
He'd probably say "I couldn't care less for interviews..."
That would still be due to his personal issues -
unacceptable in business.
Right... Well, I guess, I could ask him just once.
Interview?
A lady journalist from Munich Graph.
She asserts that canceling an interview is against the rules,
and she just won't back off.
Hadn't she seen how my art got ruined barbarically?
I'm not seeing anyone,
whoever they call themselves.
Whoever they call themselves?
Yes! Be it even Napoleon himself.
Be it even Cleopatra asking me out on a date.
What about Marilyn Monroe?
A flat "No!"
To me, the journalists' ilk is the worst scum ever,
doubly so for female journalists.
Huh? That in particular? How come?
Well, some years ago,
I made a mistake of marrying an aspiring reporter.
Not even five minutes could pass
without us two quarreling.
In other words, when first four minutes of marriage ran out,
my happy family life was over.
From the fifth minute on,
the life had been but a chain of quarrels.
Well, at least for now, I've no idea where she is
or what she's up to.
But my point stands, the marriage is...
What were we talking about, again?
About a lady journalist,
demanding an interview.
Just go there and tell them what I think.
What did you say? He had only been happy
for the first four minutes of marriage?!
It appears, the nagging of his journalist wife
did a number on him.
If you want to blame him,
please blame that woman.
Very well.
Please tell him that he is a selfish musician,
not sticking to his promises.
From here on, he doesn't deserve
so much as a footnote in our magazine.
It's all just as she said.
If you excuse us...
We're in trouble!
It's all happening because we
turned the concert into a hullabaloo!
Wait a minute, Miss Körner.
Editor-in-Chief, do you deem me a wonder-worker,
demanding me to do anything more than that?
I think you've done an excellent job.
Rather, I was the one at fault,
asking you to do the impossible.
Therefore, would you let me
treat you to dinner as an apology?
Yes, I would gladly follow you elsewhere.
If I stay here any longer,
I would soon require something to vent my anger on.
My, my. You can be pretty intimidating, did you know?
If they go, mom would come home late again...
Then, let's return first
and use this time to formulate the future strategy.
Yes, take my word for it,
when I say your spirit of journalism was on its peak today.
That's why I should apologize
for trying to abuse it.
You sure need some nerve to say it like that.
Are you still mad with me?
What Palfy said back then is unforgivable.
Ah, you mean Palfy?
It seems, the men are all like that.
Blame his unhappiness on the marriage,
thus covering up his own shortcomings.
Editor...
What is it?
You think so do, don't you?
I'd never do something like that.
Honestly.
Dad and mom only keep
distancing each other further on.
What'll we do now?
Imagine, if dad and mom remarry,
but to their own new lovers...
To their own new lovers?
Like whom?
Well, if you think of it, mom could...
I think...
I'm convinced you live in a misconception.
I do? In a misconception?
The view the marriage is the source of unhappiness
is not necessarily shared by all men.
Then, Editor, have you ever
considered a marriage yourself?
Most naturally.
I had no idea.
Who could she be?
Oh my...
About that...
I must have taken a bit too much...
For instance, Miss Körner,
that could be you.
Don't you ever think about entering a marriage?
Right, I must check on Lotte's headache...
So, Miss Körner?
You see, Editor, I'm worried about Lotte now.
Most certainly!
I didn't forget about Lotte.
Moreover, I think that little Lotte
should be our mutual concern.
You're so caring, Editor.
No, it's nothing.
I'm only doing what's natural.
Then, I consider my part concluded here.
My, won't you even come in to say hello to Lotte?
Yeah...
Then, only for a bit.
Well, Lotte, we'll talk tomorrow again
to sort out the rest.
Okay. I'll be waiting for a call.
See you, Lotte.
Take care.
Come on, be my guest, Editor.
I really think there's no need
to walk you home any further.
No way!
Returning so soon? Lotte is probably still awake.
She'll be happy to see you.
She is back at a moment like this!
Whatever, I'll hide in the bedroom for now!
I guess you're right.
Then, I only show my face in.
I'm home!
You're back sooner than I thought, mom.
Lotte, is your headache gone already?
Yeah! Completely.
Hello, Lotte.
Good evening, Herr Editor.
I'll make you some tea now.
Please wait in the living room.
Well, this way.
Luise, I'll distract them in the living room for now.
Use that time to slip away!
Got it.
Lotte, I don't think I'll be staying for long.
Eh? But...
She has every right to feel exhausted.
Please make sure she gets a good rest.
Now's my chance!
See you, Lotte.
Luise!
All is lost!
We're goners now.
This is bad!
I must have overdrunk myself!
I suddenly see two Lottes instead of one!
It's best that I get home soon.
Don't just stand here!
Good night, Lotte.
Good night, Herr Editor.
Look...
Adorable Lotte!
Ah, my little angel!
Drunk?
She sounds mighty lively.
What's going on there?
Mom talks to herself sometimes.
It's all right.
But say, Lotte, you mom sure is a caring person.
Her mind is with you at any given time.
She is Germany's number one caring mom.
But in being headstrong,
she might just be number one in the world!
That's just what I thought!
She's nothing like the fragile women
that you see everywhere around you.
Her radiance of living by her own rules is unmistakable.
Herr Editor...
Good night, Lotte.
To you and to your always beautiful mom.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. It seems, she was too drunk
to tell me apart from the usual Lotte.
Lotte...
Editor Bernau is a caring and good man...
Mom! Don't you mean
you consider marrying Herr Editor?!
Don't, Luise!
The commotion they caused at the concert, had once again
only served to fan the flames of Lotte and Luise's worrying.
With a new major problem
arising before them all of a sudden,
will the two ever be able to overcome
both it and their own doubts?
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode
Lotte, let's go for it. Make or break!
We'll come up with a plan
to make dad and mom meet when they least expect!
Let's try talking, at least...
Talking is not an option!
Somehow, we must make them get along again!
I can't tell what'll come out of this,
but the plan certainly looks worth trying, Luise!
It must be our last chance, right?
Let's do our best!
Next time in I and Myself:
Dad and Mom Meet Again.
Episode 18
Dad and Mom Meet Again
Look forward to it!