Dad's birthday -
Lotte and dad celebrated it
with a sumptuous party for just the two of them.
Even if dad nearly failed to show up.
Thankfully, the girl knew that patience always pays off.
For the first time, Lotte could muster the courage
to ask dad's permission to kiss him.
Even if she did it as Luise.
Episode 9
Mom's Home Cooking
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
There, there, what'll you do about it?
Still wanna defy me?
Please stop, it hurts!
Annie!
Today, you're not getting away
with harassing Ilse again!
Oh, really?
If I'm not getting away, try to stop me!
You alright, Ilse?
Get back here, Annie!
Get back I said, Annie!
Get back my bottoms!
Are you okay?
Got you! Told you, not getting away.
Eh! I was never even trying!
This will teach you not to bully Ilse ever again!
Wait a minute, Lotte.
Lotte.
Didn't you promise me
not to resort to violence again?
But mom, even together, me and you never managed
to figure out a way to stop her without slapping her.
Oh, we didn't? My bad, my bad.
We'll definitely try again sometime.
Huh? Smells like smoke!
Oh no!
Ah! Only the charcoals are left.
It was Annie's fault, too.
I was cooking, when I saw her
bullying Ilsa in the window.
Well, this sometimes happens, too.
How about we eat in a restaurant today?
Eh? For real?
You can count on me.
I've been rewarded heftily
for the recent manuscripts.
We can afford some splurging.
Splendid!
I should consider burning our meal more often!
You crafty thing!
Say, mom, did you reserve
both the table and the food?
What did you order?
I'd rather keep that a surprise.
But I have no doubt you'll be pleased with it.
Let's just say it's your one very favorite dish.
Whoah! What could it be?
A Burgundian sole fillet,
garnished with champignons.
Your favorite, Lotte.
No way...
I can't stand eating any fish!
It's always so full of bones!
It's what you told me back in the day,
"It's so delicious, I could eat
ten plates of it at once!"
Uh-huh. That's how it was.
Come on, it's getting cold.
Yeah.
Of all things, Lotte ended up
being head over heels for fish.
That's something I'd rather know beforehand.
In that case, maybe I would have
averted it somehow.
Was very tasty!
Want a refill?
Thanks, I'm full already.
My, why did you make such a mess of it?
Eh?
Whoa! Mom's fish bones look perfectly intact!
You used to keep it intact, too.
Even better than I do.
I did?
What?
This change in you is beyond explainable.
This, and how you suddenly
acquired a taste for omelette. And also...
Before, whenever I would propose going to a restaurant,
you'd say, "No, it's too expensive," and stop me.
I figured, if it's mom's idea, it should be good,
so I must comply with it, without objections.
Very well. Well, if that's the case,
I can but to encourage it.
Whoa! This woman is pretty.
She looks familiar.
Isn't she a famous model?
I see her a lot in fashion magazines!
I noticed a colleague here.
Mind if I come pay my respects?
Sure, no problem.
Hey.
Good evening.
Fraulein Lotte, it's been a long time.
Good evening!
Whew, this is dangerous.
Seems like he knows me. Who is that?
That Frau in Helen, you know her?
Yes, name rings a bell.
I'm considering using her photo
for our next gravure.
We came here to fix the details.
Gravure?
I know!
You're Editor-in-Chief Bernau!
Yeah, that's me.
Did you just now remembered it, Lotte?
I know it's been half a year,
but am I really that forgettable a guy?
Absolutely not!
I remember you very well.
You're a devoted bachelor, right?
Proudly so.
And then, you're also a thorn in mom's side.
Eh?
My, Lotte! Mind your tongue.
That's honestly a revelation.
It seems, you have changed a good deal
since our last meeting, I can swear.
Changed?
Mom, and even people from outside our family
are all saying Lotte had changed.
If I keep giving them that kind of impression,
I'll be in trouble.
Worst case scenario - everyone finds out.
Alright...
You what?
Want me to teach you to cook meat?
Uh-huh. If only you have some free time for it.
Even if I have the time for it...
Herr, you know how to cook, don't you?
What are you saying?
Wasn't I the one who taught you
most of the recipes you know to-date?
Ah, this... This is correct.
No further questions, then. It's decided.
I don't mind it, but most of the meat dishes I know
you should already know how to cook yourself.
Unfortunately, as of late, a great many things had happened,
and my cooking expertise may had been blunted.
All right, I heard you.
I'll take you in as a disciple.
Later, then!
Is everything I taught you before
no longer good enough for you?
Actually, I just forgot a lot of it!
You forgot?! Oh, come on! Next, you'll tell me
you're not actually Lotte!
But I have truly forgotten!
Will you do it for me, please?
Well, so be it. How can you say no,
when Lotte is asking so earnestly?
Thank you!
What was it you called me out for?
Annie.
Watch out, she's about to attack!
Not before you defeat us first!
Today, I'm not here to fight.
I apologize for what I did before.
When the steak looks brown enough,
promptly flip it over.
Now, you try yourself.
Hot!
Hey, hey, you okay, Lotte?
More or less.
Okay, now it's time to peel the onions.
First you cut out the middle.
Then do this.
Come on, try it yourself.
It's easy if you don't rush yourself.
Haste makes waste.
Like this...
Ouch!
Are you all right?
Seems like nothing serious.
But it's the fifth time today!
If you keep this up,
you'll be left with no fingers soon!
Oh, it can't be that bad, Frau.
Don't worry about me.
Let's continue.
Well, if you say so, sure.
A small blister is still there,
but it doesn't hurt anymore. It'll be fine.
And this one could use one more bandage.
Alright! Tonight, I'm not making any blunders,
while cooking a delicious meal!
Mhm! Today's vegetables soup melts in my mouth!
And the meat is also just the right degree of tenderness.
That's what I thought!
How can it not be perfect,
after all those hardships?
Huh? What happened to that finger?
This?
Just squeezed it a bit with the door.
My, how most unusual to see Lotte getting hurt.
Take care, will you?
Sure!
Bring to the common denominator...
Still not in the bed, Lotte?
You should stop now, it's time to sleep.
Okay!
The real Lotte, by now,
is probably fast asleep already.
But here, a certain Fraulein Luise has to work more and more,
in order to make a convincing Lotte.
Every day, cooking is my main concern.
But even if I pretend being Lotte, her level of cooking
and her perfect scores on the test are still out of my reach.
Oh no! You'll get us discovered!
That's why, sometimes, I can't help wondering
what would it have been like, if I just stayed Luise.
But because I'm going through this with my dear mom,
I can bear a bit of hardships for the sake of staying here.
That's a good question. If I had still been living as Lotte,
where would I have been by now?
Hey, Luise!
It looked like she was too engrossed in some letter.
Whom could it be from?
Dealing with kids her age is often a demanding task.
No wonder you can't manage it, being the only parent.
No, no.
What you said may be true,
but not for our family, that's for certain.
Well...
What had happened?!
Ah, sorry for startling you.
A kitten just jumped out in front of us.
Collier - 65 points.
You could try just a little better.
Scudelli - 80 points.
Wow!
The test was a little more difficult than usual this time,
but you did well.
Lotte - 92 points!
A great job, however you look at it!
I'm not Lotte, but a completely different person,
and yet, I managed it!
Annie - 3 points.
The honest score would be 0, but you wrote your name
in your most neat handwriting ever, so 3 points it is.
Silence!
Annie, this problem is getting worse
with every semester passing.
Please ask your father
to come to school tomorrow, will you?
Will you do it?
Okay.
Why does she only asks Annie's dad to come?
Obviously, because she doesn't have a mom!
Ah? Oh, right, right...
Good afternoon.
Ah, welcome, Frau Körner!
Having a day off?
I work in the evening today.
Can I have half a pound of ham?
Sure. By the way, is Fraulein Lotte's burn healing up nicely?
Burn?
The burn that is on her foot.
Eh? My Lotte's foot?
Oh my, she didn't tell?
Oh well, that was to be expected.
She didn't want to give you an extra worry,
so she kept it to herself.
That's the kind of kid our Lotte is.
Ah, Frau Körner!
Ah? Good afternoon, Frau Wagenthaler.
Something distressing on your mind?
No, nothing at all.
By the way, has Lotte's finger cut
healed up already?
Her finger cut... You know about it, too?
How can I not know it?
While I was teaching her to cook,
she cut it like five times in a row, with a kitchen knife!
With a kitchen knife?
Just squeezed it with a door, a bit.
Good afternoon, Frau Körner.
Ah, glad to see you're back.
Had a lot of work assigned to you lately, hadn't you?
Eh?
Ah, well I can't help noticing
you work until late every night.
The other night, your lights weren't out until the sunrise.
Until sunrise?
Well, remember the night when it was raining?
Night when it was raining?
Because it was raining,
I couldn't get any sleep,
so I looked out of the window
and saw your living room still lit.
Erm, pretty sure it was
well past three on the clock.
Lotte...
It's about Lotte again?
She goes to such extremes just to hide it from you?
It must be because I keep telling her,
"You are my little housekeeper, my most precious little Lotte."
So her determination stems
from her unwillingness to disappoint you?
It all started when she returned from a summer camp.
Since then, Lotte has been the least Lotte-like.
So I was sort of glad
when she started to return to norm.
In other words, because you treasured her so much before,
she now treasures you back just as much?
I'm thinking, in this age
kids undergo some major changes, so...
Hm. This must be it.
What must?
It's not unusual that a growing child with only one parent
becomes emotionally fickle as a result of those changes.
Editor-in-Chief, our world knows countless examples
of single parents rearing their children without any problem!
No, I just wanted to say... You can't argue the fact
that the child's growth tends to be more stable in full families.
Neither can you debate the fact
many single parents rear their kids without any issue.
You'll have to excuse me for today.
Wait a minute, I...
I swear. Why does it come to this,
every single time with Körner?
Mom, I can do this myself!
It's fine. Whenever you're doing something now,
I want a part in that too, however small.
I can cook myself sometimes, you know.
What's gotten into you, mom?
Just have a rest, will you?
But you've also got a work to do...
I went home without taking any extra work today.
And if they got anything to say about that,
I'll go find another work.
Wow! Cool!
After all, ever since you've been so small, day after day
I was counting on you to cook dinner for us both.
Now it's finally my turn.
I see. She did this every day for mom,
ever since she was little.
And I, ever since I was little,
has been counting on Resi to cook for me...
Just like Lotte has been cooking for mom.
Lotte, you still remember it?
What?
When you were about three years old,
you were trying to help me with everything.
I did?
Yeah! If nothing else is left to do,
you were helping me place the bowls on the table.
Or helped me to pour the soup!
Even while you were still a baby,
helping others was your prime passion.
I had no idea.
Because I am not Lotte!
And I will never be Lotte.
Wow, looks yummy!
Thanks for the meal!
Whoa! Delicious!
Great to know!
Um! I think, I went a bit overboard with salt.
Not at all!
Delicious, however you look at it!
Really?
Really!
Yes! Mom's home cooking today, compared to everything
I had ever tried before, is like heaven and earth!
Thank you.
By the way, are you making
any good progress with school?
Yes.
The test results returned today.
I got 92 points.
Dandy! Keep that up.
But say, mom...
What is it?
Did you know that Annie doesn't have a mother?
Yeah, I think I heard about it.
This is sad.
Annie would never have a chance
to try her mother's cooking.
Homework done and dusted.
Now, time to go to bed.
Mom?
Huh? Where could she be going at such hour?
That's all? She wanted to ride a swing seat?
Crying...
But why?
Luise...
I'm sorry. You'll also never be able
to try mom's cooking.
Mom...
You didn't...
forget about me!
Luise...
You're... well and happy, aren't you?
Yes, mom.
I'm doing well.
Well and happy!
I also got to try mom's cooking.
And I'll be having it afterwards, too!
You shouldn't worry about this!
Luise... Luise!
Mom, Luise is right here!
Mom!
Luise was barely managing to control her urge to emerge
from her hideout and give her mom the most loving hug ever.
Unable to drop the mask and come clean,
Luise could almost feel her little heart breaking apart.
"However, come what may,
I shall keep my solemn promise to Lotte" -
were Luise's thoughts at this time of doubt.
...another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
We have switched places!
Luise, I just met a very talented street artist!
I'm jealous.
Lotte, what kind of boy is he?
He performs under the name of Hans of the Winds,
playing accordion.
But he can play piano, too!
Eh? You mean to say...
Exactly! Say what you want,
but I want to learn piano, too!
Lotte, you can't!
Dad would be able to tell it's not you immediately!
Next time in I and Myself:
Birth of a Genius Pianist.
Episode 10
Birth of a Genius Pianist
Don't miss it!