Lotte met with Frau Gerlach personally
to make a plea: "Please don't marry my dad."
However, even the possibility of that had been ruled out.
Deeply shocked, Lotte had fallen ill with a terrible fever.
In the meantime, the photographer
from the Seebühl Village, Herr Eipeldauer
decided to send the photo of Lotte and Luise
to Editor-in-Chief Bernau from the Munich Graph magazine
as a candidate for the cover photo.
Episode 23
Sorry, Mom!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Seebühl Village
Eipeldauer's Photo Studio
"To Munich Graph Publishing House."
If there's ever a photo good enough, it's this one.
Egern Station
Doctor Strobl had mentioned
a severe mental shock as the possible reason...
Luise, what in the world had happened?
Just... what?
Good morning.
Herr Master, have you been up this whole time?
She seems to have settled down a bit.
The fever won't subside.
Call Doctor Strobl again, Resi.
Okay.
Why is there not a word from Lotte?
There's also this uneasiness in my chest.
Lotte, something happened?
Anyone home, Lotte?
Yes?
What's with that blank look?
Is something troubling you right now?
Not a single itsy-bitsy thing!
Come on, come on.
Not need to rush like that.
Are you okay?
Mom, you coming early today?
I have one interview planned for today.
After that, will probably have to finish the manuscript.
All in all, it spells "Late" to me.
Got it. Good luck with your work.
It's green.
Well, I'm off!
Take care!
This would help to bring the fever down, right?
Only God knows.
What do you mean?
With medicine, I can make the fever
subside for an hour or two.
But I've no sway whatsoever
over her mental state.
If you're saying the reason lies in mental plane...
Anything particular comes to your mind?
A complete blankness...
Until now, Luise had been going to school quite cheerful.
Day after day, she was a paragon of joy.
Something that could have shocked her...
And yet, at present,
she is traumatized and in an agonizing fever.
This is a serious condition. Can't you really think
of any event that could have caused it?
Consider all the possibilities.
There was definitely something...
And here I was, thinking
I know my Luise through and through.
Resi, what about you?
Yes?
I mean, while I was away,
wasn't there anything strange happening to her?
Anything helps, any tiniest detail.
Can't recall anything in connection to this. I'm sorry.
I see.
What, then...
Just what could be tormenting Luise?
Well...
Yes?
I'm not sure if it has anything to do with this...
Anything helps. Speak out.
Yesterday morning,
when the fever didn't strike her yet,
she told me she is going to Cobenzl Boulevard.
Cobenzl Boulevard?
Is that all that happened?
Well, as I said,
I don't know if it has anything to do with this...
Cobenzl Boulevard?
That's where Frau Irene Gerlach's residence is!
But still, why?
Come in.
I beg your pardon.
Frau, a call from Herr Palfy for you.
Really? Redirect the call here, will you?
Certainly.
Hello? Herr Palfy?
Irene listening.
I'm told you had an extremely
successful concert last night.
Yes... Luise appeared on my doorstep out of nowhere.
Ah... So Luise really did? She went there to see you?
But pray, what did she want?
This is something I hoped we'd discuss in person,
should a good occasion arise.
For now, pray tell, what did Luise want?
Sure. She came here to tell me,
"You can't marry Herr Palfy."
I asked her for the reason,
but she just kept insisting, "You can't."
She was like a broken record!
Pardon my straightforwardness,
but don't you find the very idea appalling?
Therefore, I cut it short
and returned in the most unequivocal terms:
"Calling off my marriage with Herr Palfy
is absolutely out of question."
The matters of our marriage are not for children to decide.
Besides, it's settled already.
Hello? Hello?
Huh? Hung up?
What? She went there to tell her "Don't marry?"
My! I had no idea you've gotten
that far with the madam already!
This pinpoints the cause underlying the fever
with quite the certainty.
Luise...
I never realized the extent of your brooding over it.
I thought I'm doing it for your own good,
thought you need a mother of sorts...
Still, why are you that much opposed to it?
I was sure you and Frau Irene
are on your way to becoming friends.
Munich Central Post Office
The arithmetic class sure was tough today.
Lotte!
My personal view on it is this:
I don't think it was just this one time alone, rather...
Let's just say, whenever I create,
I don't set a particular theme for that in my mind.
What I'm saying may lead you to conclude
there's no uniformity in my works -
at one moment I'm obsessed with one peculiarity,
at the next - blown away with something else.
But unless you have multiple personalities,
enforcing a theme upon yourself will lead you nowhere.
As for uniformity, it will come by itself, in due course.
It's strange.
The letters from Lotte just stopped coming.
Was she somehow rendered unable to send them?
As always, good job.
Glad to hear.
The time is ripe to propose more formally.
All right, that's it!
No reason to delay it - tonight!
What's going on?
You're speaking out loud.
Yeah...
Welcome back, Miss Körner.
Here, the mail had arrived.
Thank you.
It went well?
The interview was a breeze.
Manuscript will be ready today.
Good, counting on you.
Miss Körner...
Yes?
Well...
What is it?
I mean...
There's something I want to say to Lotte and you.
To Lotte and me?
My, that sounds like a pleasant talk.
Naturally. I hope, you like it...
Very well. We'll be waiting for you today.
Sounds good. But I've some more work to sort out,
so I'm probably only coming late in the evening.
Okay, I don't mind.
Ah? Seebühl Village?
That letter... Does it say "Eipeldauer" as a sender?
This one?
He submitted a photo for a cover candidate.
What about it?
Pretty sure, the summer camp Lotte has been to
was also located in that Seebühl Village.
Something interesting?
Two Lottes in here.
A photomontage, albeit a masterfully crafted one.
Well, if I hadn't known our Lotte,
I'd probably think those are some genuine twins.
Why didn't Lotte tell me about this photo...
No...
Why didn't she ever tell me
she got to meet Luise there?
I bet, that photographer
never even considered the possibility,
that the mother of his model
might be working right here, in Munich Graph.
That girl...
Could it be that she is not even Lotte?
Well, Lotte is pretty cute on that photo, right?
Editor...
Would you mind if I borrow this for a moment?
Ah, no problem.
Doesn't seem to be of much use to us.
It's yours.
Ah... See you tonight, then.
Whatever we do, Young Fraulein
is not getting one bit better...
Dad...
You can't...
Don't get married...
Please, Frau Gerlach! Leave us two alone...
Luise...
I'm home.
Welcome back, mom.
I didn't even notice!
I'll get your dinner ready in no time,
just need to put the plates away.
You said you'll be late today,
so I wasn't expecting you now.
I needed to tend to one urgent matter.
Urgent matter? What's this about?
It's about you,
Luise.
About me?
What is it? Do te—
Broke... another one.
Luise!
Luise...
Mom...
Mom.
Mommy!
Luise!
Mommy...
Mommy! Mommy!
Luise, it's you!
It's really you, Luise...
Mommy!
Having found herself in a tight mother's clasp, Luise realizes
that the astonishment in her heart turns to glee.
No longer as Lotte, but as Luise.
At the same time, Lotte
keeps crying through her dream, tormented by the fever.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode preview
Lotte, I can finally tell mom a million different things!
How we first met in the summer camp,
how we switched places!
And of course, about how dad is doing!
Luise, I'm so sorry!
I would have to apologize to mom.
Lotte, something happened?
Dad will... Dad will end up marrying another woman!
Next time, I and Myself:
Hang on, Lotte!
Episode 24
Look forward to it!