...is mighty strange with her.
She had always been a gymnastics enthusiast.
A sneaking suspicion arises in Truda:
"Might she be actually Lotte?"
By chance, when she failed to talk her way through,
she dispelled the doubts by saving a kid that fell into the river.
But at the same time,
Luise was besieged by another major crisis.
Episode 14
I Can't Play the Piano
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
Okay. Come on, Annie, one more time.
Keep it up!
Frau Annie, almost there!
Even this clutz Lotte
was able to do it! To the end!
Okay, so be it.
Annie, you need to practice more.
Who asked you to shout all that out loud?!
Apologies.
I'm very sorry,
but I really wasn't laughing at you.
But then, who were you laughing at, huh?
Ouch-ouch-ouch!
No, you won't do that!
How many more times do I have to say it?
Lotte!
Your ineptitude on the horizontal bar
can't be mitigated through blaming others!
Let's go, Ilse.
Gosh, she is annoying!
Nobody gets on my nerves like that!
It's highly indecent of her to put on airs
just because she managed it herself once!
Alright! There has to be something
Lotte is a complete bungler at!
We'll put our spines into finding it!
Okay, now the next page.
Oh, this tune is something everyone should know.
Schumann's Träumerei.
And for that, let's see,
who should we ask to start...
Lotte Körner.
Yes?
Play it for us, will you?
Excuse me, but how do I do that?
Why, with piano, obviously!
The one you have such a talent for.
Eh? No, I'd rather...
Whoa! At long last, we'll hear Lotte's
piano play again! I can't wait!
I can't wait!
Come on, let's hear it!
What's wrong with you two?
My bad.
Oh no... I'm supposed to know how to play it.
They think I'm Lotte now,
the prominent pianist!
Excuse me, but at the moment,
I'm unable to play piano.
My... But what could be the reason?
You see...
I hurt my hand!
Impossible! Lotte was doing horizontal bar just an hour ago!
So, well...
I was doing it for so long,
all my fingers went numb.
This won't do for a piano...
My, is that so? If it starts hurting too much,
go see the school doctor, will you?
Okay!
Oh well, I'll play it myself, then.
Right, eyes to the sheet music.
That's odd! She didn't hurt no hand!
Instead, she nearly hurt Annie
when pulled away her hand so brutally!
You think she malingers?
I'll go there and expose her!
Wait! We can still leverage it.
Annie! Silence, please.
Avoided it for now, somehow. Oh my, oh my.
Odd!
She used to be beside herself when playing the piano.
And this excuse, too... The oddest of all!
Don't you lose sight of her!
If there's any field Lotte is lacking in,
we'll have it on our radar.
Ah? No way!
I forgot to buy the butter.
Lotte!
Lotte Körner, are you not?
Why, it's been ages!
Have you been well?
Yes...
Oh my, who could that be?
I'm glad I ran into you! I am now once again
living in Munich, can you imagine?
I'm glad to see you again, too!
Tell me, you still practice regularly, don't you?
Eh? Yes, I try to keep up with it.
Practice what?
That is just dandy! This means
we could renew our lessons right away!
What do I do?
I've no clue what she's talking about.
Lotte never told me anything about it!
What's the matter, Lotte?
You look disconcerted.
No, it's nothing.
But could you tell me...
Lessons... what about them?
Oh, that's right.
We'll just pick up where we left off.
Can start tomorrow already.
Is that fine by you?
Yes. Just...
Maybe I'll figure something out on the spot.
Go for all or nothing!
Yes! Perfectly fine.
Splendid! Then, come to my place by three.
Okay!
Ah! Excuse me, but your place is...
It's the same where I stayed before.
Lotte, I will be oh, so happy
to be able to teach you again!
Returning to Munich was a splendidly good idea!
I can't wait to see your transformation
into a marvelous pianist!
A pianist?
Well, I'll be waiting for you tomorrow.
Oh Lord!
Wait, please!
What is it?
Well, you see,
I was actually considering quitting piano.
My!
Lotte, who gave you that most ridiculous idea?!
One way or another, I quit piano!
Goodbye!
Ah... Lotte!
I do know that woman! That was Frau Leitner!
She's giving piano lessons.
There was a time I visited her, too.
Frau Annie learned piano?!
Eh? You can play, too?
It was in the old days and only because dad asked me to!
I got bored of it right away.
Lotte also said she is quitting piano just now.
So suddenly... Odd, isn't it?
This and what she said during the music class.
Lotte keeps feeding others the excuses
for not playing the piano!
Alright, we'll get to the bottom of this!
Hm... In the end, I'm thinking this one!
No. Certainly, this one.
Oh no, it's too flashy!
It's your sense of style that is too out of date!
Miss Körner, a phone call for you.
I redirected it your way.
Thank you
Yes. Körner listening.
My, Frau Leitner!
Ah, maybe this one, after all?
Wait, though!
My... Lotte said that?
Very well. I'll try to talk her out of it at once.
Thanks for letting me know.
Alright, it's settled.
Miss Körner, we're using your photo.
Miss Körner...
She was always madly fond of piano...
But now, this?
Could she have acquired a distaste for it
after learning about her dad's occupation?
Miss Körner, we're making this photo
the front cover. Agreed?
Anything you like.
Ah, you'll have to excuse me for an hour or so.
Still, I'd rather expect one to pick up the piano
upon discovering her dad is a musician.
Quitting it instead is counter-intuitive.
All right...
Lotte!
Ah? What's the matter, mom?
You're back so soon today.
I'll go there again in a minute.
Say, Lotte, you've met
with Frau Leitner today, didn't you?
Ah... Yes. What about it?
She called me in the office.
Did you really decline her lesson?
How come?
Before, you've been making such progress with it.
And now, Frau Leitner is back, at last.
Don't you want to pick it back up?
This is so unnerving.
How should I explain it away?
Say, Lotte, you're not fretting
over minor bumps along the way, are you?
Should you pick up the piano again,
I'll also do my best to support that endeavor.
If you need a piano to practice efficiently,
I'll find a way to do that too.
Eh... No need, it's fine.
I'm not worried about that.
Lotte,
I'll tell you this.
You've been born with an innate talent for music.
It's one of the things your mother takes pride in,
along with a great joy.
There's nothing more important
than leveraging that talent!
Please. Start taking lessons again.
Tomorrow, come to Frau Leitner's place.
I'll let her know via a phone.
Okay.
Very well.
Now, I'm off.
I'll be home early today.
You'll sort out the dinner, won't you,
my little housekeeper?
That's a disaster. What do I do?
My! Luise, everything's fine?
Right now?
I'm home alone.
It's all alright.
Ah! Thank Goodness.
I was trying to guess when would Resi go out.
Hey, Lotte. Need you to tell me something. Thing is...
Yeah.
Oh, I got it!
That must have been Frau Leitner!
Frau Leitner?
She is a hearty and cordial lady,
who used to teach me piano back in the day.
But about a year ago, her work
made her leave for someplace far away.
I wasn't counting on her return, so I never told you.
I'm sorry.
But now, she's back again? Glad to know!
Hey, Luise, don't you mean to say
Frau Leitner told you to come take another lesson from her?
Bull's eye! Yes. That's exactly what she did.
Eh?! What now?
She finds out you've suddenly unlearned to play piano -
this doesn't bode well at all!
Don't worry, I'll employ all my talents to make it work.
Ugh! Good gracious.
It seems, Resi just returned.
Till later! Do your best.
Eventually I managed to find my way around horizontal bar.
But now Luise and piano..?
I hope she makes it through.
"I will,"
or so I'd like to say.
But still, I'm a complete piano layman.
Even in arithmetic, if you just study for dear life,
you can get something done.
Okay, next - shape the minced meat...
I was wrong by not taking it seriously
while I had the chance.
That's not how you do it, Luise.
How many more times do I have to say it?
That's better, once again now.
Luise!
Do you mean to say you haven't inherited
even a fraction of your dad's talent, Luise?
Must be the meddling of your mom's lousy genes!
How dare you?!
I'll never want to play piano myself!
My!
That lady was the worst of all!
Still, it seems to be true that dad's talent
was wholly inherited by Lotte.
Well, so be it.
Perhaps, I have inherited some of mom's talents, instead.
Alright, don't give up,
Luise.
There!
What a mess.
Now then, I guess I've no choice.
Somehow, she's even weirder than before!
Where do you think she's going?
This seems to be the place.
Okay, here goes nothing.
So she was going to Frau Leitner's place, after all.
She's going to take piano lessons again?
And yesterday, she said she won't!
Totally strange!
Been ages, right?
I'm certain that piano is delighted, too.
Lotte will finally be playing it again.
Now, won't you get straight to playing?
I can't wait to hear how much better
you've grown in the last year.
But first...
Can I ask for a favor?
What is it?
You see, I haven't actually been practicing with piano.
My! But why?
I can't tell you the reason as of yet.
I'd like to explain, but my lips are sealed.
However, in the shortest term,
I was planning to renew the practicing.
Until then, I'd like to ask you to wait.
Good gracious, you must have
a lot going on for you now.
Yes.
Therefore, I would have to ask you to tell mom
I am attending the lessons like I'm supposed to.
No need to give her extra worries now.
Since Lotte is asking for this,
I should think this is all for the greater good.
Okay, very well.
I'll follow your instructions to the letter.
Thank you very much!
But in exchange, as soon as you're able to tell me the reason,
you'll give me the whole story, start-to-end!
Oh... I'm dying to know,
so please don't take too long!
Okay!
I don't hear a thing. No piano playing.
What is she doing there?
Ah! She's back! Lotte's coming!
Did it! Talked my way through, somehow!
Yahoo!
What just happened?
I don't have a single clue what had happened,
but it seems, Lotte can no longer play piano.
Just forgot it or something, I bet.
Just like Miria forgot how to do arithmetic!
She forgot how to play piano, that's it!
But hey, when you learn piano,
isn't it written to that part of your brain
that cannot be rewritten,
no matter what happens to you?
I've also heard of this another thing,
like when you fall from a cliff,
then wake up not even remembering who you are!
Now that must be it!
Lotte had suffered an amnesty!
It's called amnesia, Annie.
What does it matter?
Either way, there's the fact Lotte
completely forgot how to play the piano!
Now, that spells fun!
And in that manner,
I had also safely talked my way through the crisis.
Say, aren't we two the lucky bunch?
However, I shall be henceforth praying
that I'm not asked to play piano during the music classes.
And you should pray, too!
My, this Luise!
That said, the day we two finally return to our usual places
is certainly becoming quite the wild ride for everyone else.
Luise!
Hey! Luise!
Ah! What great news I have!
We're going for an unforeseen trip.
With Luise in tow!
A trip?
When?
Today, dear!
Come on, start packing now.
Resi! Resi!
So suddenly... At least tell me where to!
Give me just a moment!
Hurry up! We're late for the train!
I need to tell Luise as soon as possible!
Please reach her in time.
Okay, everyone, quiet now!
Our trip to cinema, scheduled for tomorrow,
is getting postponed!
What? Unfair!
But to not leave you without a treat,
we're holding a records-listening party, instead.
Nobody cares about the records!
Bo-o-oring!
Teacher!
What is it, Annie?
Why settle on records, when we can listen
to some live performances, instead?
We've got some people here really adroit with piano,
why don't we cooperate with them to hold a mini-concert?
My, that also sounds very good.
But who do we ask to do it?
No doubt about it,
that must be Lotte Körner!
Aw shuuucks!
I can't do that!
This is all... so sudden.
Come on, Maria supports it, too!
So does Miria!
I support!
I know Lotte won't let us down!
The class representative,
show them what you're made of!
We got her! This paves the way
for Lotte's grand embarrassment!
No way...
You don't joke with such things!
Please, Lotte.
Answer the phone.
This is important!
As soon as she talked her way out of one crisis,
Luise is watching helplessly
at an even bigger crisis
unfolding before her eyes.
She tries to get some help with it,
but Lotte is out of reach.
Once again, Luise's heart sinks in desperation.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
Next episode
The day of the mini-concert is finally here!
It must be that Annie and others
have gotten a lead that I might not be the real Lotte!
Luise, don't you have one of your usual "good ideas?"
Not a single one!
You're in murky waters, then!
If only Lotte could come here somehow,
it all would be set straight again!
Oh, why? Why is this happening to me?
Next time in I and Myself: Lotte, Help!
Episode 15
Lotte, Help!
Help, somebody!