...In the meantime, Lotte visited Frau Gerlach,
to make a plea with her, "Don't marry my dad," and such.
But that suggestion was ruled out.
Therefore, struck with the shock,
Lotte fell suddenly ill, feverish and delirious.
Episode 24
Hang on, Lotte!
Translation: Perevodildo | Timings: Sub-RoRo
So you've been Luise this whole time...
I'm really sorry. We two must be
some of the most unruly children ever.
We deceived mom and dad,
as if that was some game!
It's all right now.
It was a very trying journey for you two, wasn't it?
Both me and your dad
owe you two a great debt of gratitude.
Thanks to you, your dad got to meet Lotte,
and the same for me - I finally met my Luise.
Aren't you angry?
How can I be angry?
You both grew up into such bright ladies.
Still, there was but one time when you slipped up.
This photo?
It was supposed to be
at the bottom of the lake, in shreds.
If the original negative is there,
the photographer can make as many reprints as he needs.
But Lotte, what's up with you now?
Before, I used to collect your letters
from the post office daily. But lately - nothing.
Letters?
I've been to there today, yesterday,
the day before yesterday, too!
But each time, there's no General Delivery for me.
I'm sure... I'm sure, something happened to her.
There's this uneasiness in my chest, too!
Say, mom, can we call Vienna?
Can we talk to dad?
That's right. Now that I had found out,
I guess we ought to let your father know, too.
I'm also concerned about Lotte.
Miss Körner, as a father for Lotte, I believe...
No... I mean, I want to eat breakfast...
Not good enough either...
Well, whichever I choose,
I just need to propose boldly and openly.
It's impossible.
Luise, please do me this favor.
Wait. I guess I should call him, after all.
Who could that be at such hour?
Editor-in-Chief Bernau?
Hey, Lotte, good evening.
I promised to your mom earlier,
that I'd come visit you two tonight.
Is that so? You promised her?
I mean... Sure.
Come in, anyway.
Herr Master, you got a phone call.
Phone call?
Tell them I can't.
I did just that. But they say it's urgent
and demand that you answer.
It's someone called Körner, if I got it right...
Körner?
Was it Körner? The one who called?
I think that's just what she said...
Hello? Palfy listening.
Well...
Hey...
Sorry I'm calling so suddenly...
The thing is, I'm worried about my child.
Could she possibly be sick or something?
Yeah, that's exactly the case.
But... How did you possibly...
My... She really is?
Hey, please hear me out calmly.
The actual Luise is here with me,
she confided to me everything that happened.
Wait a minute there! What do you mean?
My Luise is now...
No, the one in your house is Lotte.
The two have switched places.
Switched places?
Yes. When it was the time for them
to return home from the summer camp,
Luise pretended to be Lotte and returned to me,
and Lotte took Luise's place by your side.
Yes, just like that.
But these days, Lotte went out of touch with her.
And so, she was wondering,
"Is Lotte ill or something?"
What's going on?
At this rate, I'm falling ill myself!
Please be lenient to these children!
Considering what these girls had been through,
you can't judge them.
How is Lotte looking?
Ah, that...
In bed, struck by a terrible fever.
And well...
The cause seems to be psychological.
I see...
But say... Is there anything I can do to help?
Most certainly, you can! That...
No...
Sheesh... What's with those two at a moment like this?
Dad! Dad, you hear me? This me - Luise!
Can you imagine,
how much we two are worried about Lotte?
Hey! Would it help,
if us two come to Vienna now?
Luise...
That sounds like a jolly good idea.
You should come. The sooner the better.
Thank you!
Ah, hello?
Yes. If you come here now, she might just...
Lotte will definitely get better.
In her delirium, she is constantly calling out to you.
"Mom,"
that is.
If possible, please come at once.
Okay, I understand.
I'll make every effort to get there sooner.
Now, then.
Great! Mom, let's rush to the airport!
Oh no!
We won't find any plane at this hour!
An the last train to Vienna is gone already!
Editor? Have you been here for long?
Quite some while already.
I overheard everything that happened here.
I didn't mean to, of course...
Ah, no, it's fine...
I'm so sorry! Your promise from earlier
had slipped my mind completely!
Come one, hurry up.
We're going on an overnight drive to Vienna.
Lotte...
Turns out, you are my another daughter.
That timid little Lotte...
And yet,
you managed such a switch...
Resi! Resi!
Yes, yes, anything I can do for you?
Something with Fraulein?
No, tomorrow, my wife comes here.
Counting on you to prepare the meal and such.
Eh? You mean, your bride?
The wife that I broke up with!
Luise is coming with her.
Fraulein Luise had finally gotten better?
Ah? No... Well anyway, just take care of things.
Don't tell me that the fatigue from looking after her
had driven Master delirious as well?
What do I do now?
Still, he said the reason is psychological...
What in the world could it be?
There's one thing I know of
that may or may not have something to do with this.
What is this thing?
That... I mean...
It seems, for the last few months,
dad has been seeing a woman named Irene Gerlach.
I have a suspicion,
this might just be the case.
I see...
Right there, Editor Bernau!
Editor-in-Chief, I really don't know
if I'll ever be able to repay this...
Don't you worry about me.
Rather, hurry up to check on Lotte, Miss Körner.
Mom, hurry, hurry!
Luise! Going outside with a fever like that...
I swear, she is intractable.
Peperl! Long time no see.
Fraulein Luise, is it all right for you to get out of bad?
It can't be any other way than all right for me.
The one with the fever is Lotte.
Nice to meet you, I'm Körner
My! You're the wife Master told me about...
I'm Resi, to meet you, yes.
Excuse me, how is it looking for Lotte?
If you mean the girl struck by a fever,
that had been Fraulein Luise. And as you can see...
Told you you're wrong!
The one with the fever is Lotte.
After me, mom!
Not so fast, Luise!
Doctor Strobl! It's been a while.
Don't give me that "a while!"
It's way too soon for you to get up!
But I'm not even the one who fell ill!
Stop! You can't just disregard the doctor!
Luise, stop at once!
Lotte.
Lotte, are you okay?
Dad...
We...
It's okay. You don't have to say it.
How does it feel to be back, Luise?
Dad!
What's the meaning of this?
I see two Luises!
There were actually two girls,
two twin sisters.
But in unexpected turn of events,
they switched places.
Switched places, then?
Still, such a thing...
Lotte, mom is here.
Lotte!
Lotte...
Lotte?
Lotte, mom is here.
Mom...
Mom?
Yes, your mom is here.
I am here with you, Lotte.
Lotte, it's me, Luise. You recognize me?
Luise...
But... why?
It's fine now, Lotte.
Don't have to worry about that.
Instead, get better soon.
Mom...
Right, don't worry now.
Apparently, even a check-up wouldn't be necessary.
From now on, she'll recover by herself,
provided the appetite is there.
Right, here you go, then.
Eh...
I'm the one that is Luise.
Right, Fraulein Luise.
But then, the one sleeping
on the second floor would be...
There!
Thank you for your hard work!
Here, Lotte. Say "Aah."
Delicious...
Really?
Then, you should eat it all
and recover in the shortest time!
Here.
It appears, we can trust Luise
to take care of Lotte now.
Why don't we go downstairs now
to catch a breath, at last?
Editor-in-Chief...
It's been some years...
Seven of them.
Seven years, then...
It sounds like a long time,
yet they also passed in a blink of an eye, somehow.
That's a good point.
Ah, and that man...
Well, this chap, Editor-in-Chief Bernau...
Is he...
No, I mean... Did he make a proposal already?
To you.
A proposal? To me? Why should he?
There's no need to disavow anything now.
Right, back then...
In Munich, albeit I didn't know who he is yet,
I met him.
When I saw him at Don Giovanni's,
it was apparent,
he was there to propose to a woman.
And the one he was supposed to meet there
was none other than you.
Editor-in-Chief...
to me?
Ubiquitous to grown-ups, but unknown to children,
the complicated ways of heart are often hard to grasp.
Lotte and Luise, just happy at being reunited again,
relish this moment of tranquility.
Certainly, both are going to see
the most delightful dreams tonight.
Forever and ever, let us offer a prayer
that the happiness of the two is never disturbed.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams -
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, my duty is to protect it!
Next episode preview
Today, I finally return to being Luise!
Luise, who is boyish!
I also return to being Lotte.
Great!
Great indeed!
Dad and mom...
Maybe they can...
They definitely can...
Reconcile!
How can they not, when they have
such amicable mood between them?
Next time in I and Myself:
Love Reborn!?
Episode 25
Look forward to it!