Glistening like crystals,
Morning fog starts to form
I and Myself:
The Two Lottes
What gentle breeze is bringing us
Somebody out there playing Vivaldi
Reflection I'm seeing in the mirror
Is like a glance straight into a maze
Mysterious image - a time's mirage
There is one more, another me
The one that keeps on living in the depths of my heart
Just like a childish fruitless dream
"You are no longer alone" -
I hear a whisper
Lotte had to become Luise
in order to meet her father for the first time.
Luise had to become Lotte,
to kiss her mother for the first time.
The fact the two switched places
has been so far successfully kept secret.
Episode 6
Solid Cook, Horrid Cook
Translation: Perevodildo   |   Timings: Sub-RoRo
Vienna
Mom, wake up!
You'll be late for work, mom.
Oh no! I'm not in Munich!
I now live with dad.
So refreshing!
Feels good.
All right, let's make the best of this day.
Kärntner Ring Atelier
What is it?
Dad, I know you've been working till wee hours.
But right now, I'm making you a breakfast,
so, would you rather scrambled eggs, or boiled?
I hate boiled eggs...
Then, scrambled it is.
Come home soon, lest it goes cold.
Oh, this Luise, so early in the morning.
Excuse me?!
Luise is making breakfast?
No way!
Morning, Resi.
Young Fraulein...
Resi, could you take the juice out of the fridge?
And put that bread in the basket.
How is that...
Morning, Peperl.
I actually made a proper breakfast for you, too.
Ah, it must be that the end of times is already near.
Fraulein Luise is cooking!
Luise!
Did you cut your fingers somewhere? Any burns?
How many times did you drop the pot?
Does it hurt anywhere?
No, nothing of the kind.
Nothing?
Here, Peperl.
It's going cold. Hurry up.
You don't like it?
It's great!
Ah! Glad to know. It's the first time I'm cooking at home,
so I was morbidly nervous.
Dad, you don't eat while standing.
Mind your manners.
Manners, cooking...
I never had any idea you know words like that.
Herr Master, this must be a divine miracle!
Really? What's so miraculous in that?
Just a little something I picked up in summer camp.
This, too, because of summer camp?
Well I'll be, this summer camp
sounds like an excellent place!
Great!
Ah... This is bad!
Oh my, I was counting on Lotte to wake me up as usual,
but something went wrong...
Lotte. Lotte, what's the matter?
Are you not feeling quite well?
Let me sleep, I don't care!
Okay, okay. I can see now you are quite fine and well.
Ah! But nothing's fine about this!
You'll be late for school.
School only starts tomorrow.
Let me be, Resi.
I didn't think about that...
Huh? Resi?
Oh no! I am in Munich now.
Good morning, mom.
Good morning. Who is that Resi?
Well, this is... The girl that used to wake me up
every morning in summer camp.
So I mistook you for her.
Oh, that's relieving. You almost had me scared
that you're feverish or something.
Ah, but that's for later!
I'm late now!
This was a close call.
I must be more careful!
Lotte, mom has to go out now.
Hope I'm not too late.
Mom, should I cook you something today?
Please do. I'll try my best to finish the work sooner, too.
See you!
My first attempt at cooking.
Gotta give it my best.
And mom's favorite dish is...
Beef soup with macaroni.
Buy the beef at Huber's Butchery,
corner of Prince Eugene Straße.
Prince Eugene Straße...
This here is Prince Eugene Straße.
Butchery on the corner...
Good morning!
Hey. Welcome back, Lotte.
Back from vacations?
Yeah. Tomorrow, I go to school again.
But today, I need to make mom a dinner.
A beef soup with macaroni.
I see. As usual, then.
Just a moment.
Excuse me, half-pound of filet with marbling,
"Half-pound of filet with marbling..."
also a kidney and some marrowbones...
I got you covered, Lotte.
You're the best, Herr!
Sorry for the wait, Lotte.
Thank you, Herr.
Neither mom nor the old Herr have had a single clue
that I'm actually Luise. All according to plan!
And the next stop is,
Frau Wagenthaler's grocery store -
there, buy vegetables and macaroni.
Lotte, stop for a moment.
Do you do your homework even in the street now?
Don't you know vacation isn't over yet?
Who could this girl be?
Don't you know people look strange at you for that?
Good morning!
Need to change the subject, let's see...
Wanna come with me?
I'm going to get some vegetables.
Hey, what's the meaning...
Come, come.
Lotte!
Why did you have to bring me along for some shopping?
I would like some carrots, potato,
and some broccoli, please.
My, that's a rare sight!
Annie and Lotte together!
This is pointless.
I'm leaving!
She said, "Annie."
That's who you are.
Let's see...
Annie Habersetzer.
We go to the same class,
but this girl is a huge thorn in my side!
Because of her, some girls in the class,
especially the smallest one - Ilse Merck - are crying daily!
But nobody dares to fight her off,
because she'll come back for you later.
How interesting.
Leave me alone, Annie!
Ilse Merck, didn't you just try to run away
as soon as you noticed me?
I never did!
Ah, speak of the devil.
Eh? Do you mean to declare
you just disregarded me on purpose?
I won't let you harass Ilse, Annie.
Help me, Lotte!
Oh, really? Our perpetually voiceless Herrin Lotte
is suddenly feeling valiant?
Harassing the weak -
how come you yourself don't find it shameful?
What the dickens?
You think you can lecture me?
Who'd do such a thing?
Lotte!
No way! Lotte slapped Annie!
Next time you try to bully Ilse,
remember that I coming for you!
Let's go, Ilse.
Lotte, you'll regret this!
Oh, Young Fraulein, please don't do this to us!
You're leaving me completely out of work!
It's fine. I always wanted to try it.
We're not dreaming, are we, Herr Master?
No, whatever is happening, it's real.
Come to think of it,
where did you get that apron?
Apron...
It's... Well...
A friend from the summer camp gifted me one.
Pretty, isn't it?
It's the first time I'm seeing you wearing an apron,
but it looks becoming already.
Except mom bought it for me as a present.
Ah, I will, unfortunately, have to leave you for now.
I have a meeting at Opera House.
But in the evening,
you join Herr Strobl to come see the opera.
Ah? I can't wait!
Then, see you in the evening.
Take care!
Let's do it, Peperl. While dad is away in the Opera House,
we'll pay a secret visit to his world of inspiration!
Here is St. Stephen's Cathedral.
"You turn left after passing by the Opera House
and find yourself on Kärntner Ring."
This is the place!
Astounding!
How do you even manage to clutter a place this much?
Luise.
Peperl, I have a confession for your ears only.
I'm actually not Luise.
Luise is my twin sister,
and I am Lotte, the other one!
But make sure you don't spill it.
And in exchange, I'll be keeping you
on a tasty breakfast diet, from now on!
Thank you.
So, let's seal our friendship with an oath.
Well then Peperl,
we've got some cleaning to do.
You'll help me, won't you?
Luise, this is your dress.
First time I'm wearing something this elegant.
Young Fraulein! Herr Strobl had arrived to pick you up!
My, that's a sight to behold.
Nobody in the world would say
you don't look like the most proper lady, Luise.
It's been some time since I wore this.
It's a little embarrassing.
Oh no, it looks strikingly becoming on you, Young Fraulein.
I wonder if dad notices this dress,
if I wave my hand to him.
Have no doubt in that.
In all those years, the one thing that remained unaltered
is your dad noticing you, wherever you may be.
With that said, will you allow me
to escort you to the destination, Young Fraulein?
Yes. I kindly hope you do, Herr Strobl.
I swear, this girl is a polar opposite
of our usual Luise!
Have a safe trip.
But really, her being that docile is uncanny, even.
And she left me with a whole lot of nothing to do!
Well, let's hope it's not forever.
Let's see. The cook book is...
Here you are.
If I follow this, I've naught to fear.
And so, beef soup with macaroni...
Ah, there it is.
"First, you boil some water
and cook the meat until it's soft.
In the meantime, you boil macaroni
with a spoonful of salt."
That's all? Piece of cake!
First, we make soup by boiling the meat.
Hot!
"In the meantime - macaroni.
Add a spoonful of salt."
But how do I know which spoon they used?
Well, let's just say, "moderate amount."
"In the pot with the meat,
grate a nutmeg with a grater."
But where might the grater be?
Must be there.
Oh no!
Hot!
What was it... "To make sure the meat is soft enough,
try piercing it with a fork."
No! I haven't found the grater yet.
Ah! And what are all those vegetables for?
This is bad, the vegetables belong in the soup.
I must wash them and put in the soup,
first and foremost.
Ah! Nutmeg was also there!
Ah... Now it's all wet.
But either way, into the meat pot you go.
But wait! I was supposed to grate it first!
Aw, whatever.
Won't make any difference in the stomach.
The water is overflowing!
So many plates are in pieces.
To top it off, I'm soaking wet.
I'm so out of luck.
Ah! This Onion is so evil!
Why am I crying that hard?
What's going on?
"When the meat is soft enough, remove it from the pot.
And take out the bones with a colander."
Oh God!
Ah... Half of the soup is now on the floor!
Can't be helped.
Will have to refill it with water.
It seems, I made it through, somehow.
Let's get a little taste.
What's that?!
Mom would refuse flatly to eat something like that!
It seems, I won't ever be able
to make a convincing Lotte.
Lotte!
I gotta hurry if I'm to do it before mom returns!
We made a rule against it,
but it's my last resort measure!
I just need a little guidance on seasoning.
Yes?
Hello?
Ah? Is that you, Fraulein Luise?
No, I'm not.
But is Fraulein Luise currently out?
Oh, our Fraulein won't be home until the night, Ma'am.
Very well. Thank you!
Gosh... Just where could Lotte have gone off to?
And at such a crucial time, too!
Hot!
Magnificent, dad!
The best in Vienna...
No! The best in the whole world artist!
I'm so out out patience for when he looks over here!
And for his secret signal, too!
A gorgeous Frau, isn't she?
Dad!
My, my, it seems, she is also a friend of your father.
Want some?
No thank you.
What shall I do without Eurydice?
Where shall I go...
Lotte's dinner, which dish might it be,
after such a long break?
I can't wait to find out.
I'm back, Lotte.
Huh? Nobody's waiting?
Lotte?
My!
Lotte, are you here?
Lotte, will you tell me what happened?
I'm sorry mom.
You return home to such a disarray.
Even the apron you bought me last year is soiled...
It's okay, Lotte.
There's nothing simpler
than washing a dirty piece of cloth.
Aren't you mad at me?
I destroyed the meat and the plates...
I was more worried that you may be mad at me.
I had overburdened you
with all the housework there is.
But the way I bungled mom's favorite
beef soup with macaroni is beyond salvation...
To bungle something so spectacularly
takes a true artist, Lotte.
Mom!
"Together with mom, eventually,
we made our whole flat shine again.
After that, starting from scratch
we prepared another beef soup with macaroni.
The soup that I cooked together with mom
has been the tastiest ever.
I even regretted I can't let Lotte taste it, too. I really did.
Mom has been the most understanding,
as though we've known each other for eternity.
I pray that Lotte, too
stays on the best possible terms with dad.
From Munich."
I'll be sure to see some good dreams tonight.
The opera has been gorgeous.
I was so anxious to not miss a single second of it,
I even came an hour too soon.
Oh, that's flattering.
I was wondering if you would allow me
to take a look at your atelier.
Eh? Sure. Just be prepared it's a little messy.
Truly sorry for the mess, but please come in.
Which part of it do you consider a mess?
You're right, it's actually a pretty tidy place.
Among those who have the keys...
Luise cleaned it!
That woman...
I wonder if she and dad are close friends.
Luise, it seems, I'm about to lose
another night's sleep to worries.
Munich and Vienna -
it appears, both those worlds
have been shaken to the core by this day.
And yet, with the fall of night,
Lotte and Luise - just two little girls,
gently tuck away the happiness in their hearts,
merely breathing out a sigh of relief.
A miserable romance
A tear-jerking nuance
If you turn another page of your memories,
Here she is - heroine of the past
I raise my eyes to your face -
Suddenly, I'm in full bloom
A sunflower amidst the blizzard -
that would be me, my dear
Always on the verge of freezing,
My feelings are out of control -
Too stiff to even say "Do you still love me?"
My lips just keep wavering in this wind!
A pitiful Romance
Something that only happens in dreams:
Trying hard to forget, I fell even more in love
with heroine of the past
Miracle that I came across now is hugging me tight
This is the story of my life, I'll do my best to protect it!
In the next episode
We two have swapped places!
Lotte, I made a big fuss
in a school I've never attended before.
No way! Did you give away our secret?
Not that big! But still, I've had enough
of Annie bullying the weak, so I introduced her to my palm.
Oh God, Luise, why can't you ever control your urges?
I know I should.
But the teacher had already summoned mom!
Next time in I and Myself:
The Classes Start.
Episode 7
The Classes Start
Don't miss it!