Yes! Yes!
Masahiko-kun, yes, like that!
Aunt Hitomi, I'm about to cum!
Me too...
Here it comes!
You've become really good
at this, Masahiko.
That's all thanks to you, Aunt Hitomi.
Oh, don't say that!
Auntie, I think it's about time
we stopped doing this.
Really? Then you won't mind me
telling all your friends your secret?
What do you mean?
This here.
P-Please don't joke like that!
When I was little, I looked a lot like a girl,
so my mother would dress me in girls’ clothes
and take countless pictures of me—
that was her hobby.
It's an embarrassing stain on my life.
And this is my aunt, blackmailing me with it.
If you don't want your friends to find out,
you'd better obey me.
All and everything I say.
Now, lick it.
Okay.
Yes! More! More!
Mizuhara
I'm Kisugi Masahiko,
second year of high school.
Mizuhara
Six months ago, I came to stay
with the Mizuhara family.
Mizuhara
My father had to move to France for a while,
and my mother went with him.
Mizuhara
But to be able to go to college in Japan,
I've been left in this family's care.
My uncle died six years ago
from exhaustion after my aunt worked him to the bone every night.
I'll be living with you from today on.
Nice to meet you all!
Nice to meet you.
This is my Aunt Hitomi.
By the way, she's a writer at the moment.
This is her oldest daughter, Nozomi.
Her strong-willed second daughter, Taki.
And Rika, her third daughter—
four people total.
And when I joined them,
my new hard-on life has begun.
Surrounded by four beauties,
my heavenly life began.
Well, just watch to see how it ends!
Freeloader's
Paradise
Auntie, you're going out?
Just going to hand in my manuscript.
Then I'm going to play pachinko.
See you later!
After that invigorating yesterday,
I'm full of ideas!
I—I see.
Take care!
The food here is great.
And when you throw all the sex
into the equation, it's like heaven, man!
I'm home!
Masahiko!
The batteries in this are dead.
Can you buy some new ones?
You should go buy them yourself.
What? I don't wanna...
Masahiko has to study.
Some other time, okay?
Darn!
I need to let in more fresh air.
It still smells of last night.
Nozomi-san... Gorgeous!
Tantalizing!
I'd love to do it with Nozomi once.
But if auntie finds out, she'll kill me.
Nozomi-san, do you need help?
Oh no, it's fine.
When I'm done, I'll make you coffee.
Just wait in the living room.
Really?
Here you go.
Thanks!
This is the first time we've been left all alone.
I want you to do with me
what you did with my mother.
You were doing it until morning yesterday.
I heard your voices.
You've been very busy,
yet you're already this hard again.
Nozomi-san, if you keep doing that,
I won't be able to hold back.
Nozomi-san...
My thing's biting into Nozomi down there!
I can't hold back anymore!
Nozomi is already so wet.
Hurry up!
Not yet!
Nozomi, please put it in your mouth.
I-It's big...
Will it fit?
That's good!
She's as good as her mother!
Masahiko-kun, hurry up!
You're already dripping wet down here.
Oh geez...
Well, I'm going in.
You're tearing me apart, I'm breaking!
Yes... Yes!
N-Nozomi is so nice and tight.
So deep!
I can't take it anymore! I'm cumming!
Me too!
Nozomi-san, drink it!
S-Sorry! I did it without thinking...
Don't worry, I don't mind if it's you.
Do you always do it like this with my mother?
O-Of course not...
But it was so amazingly intense.
I can't believe you used to be
so girly in the past.
P-Please don't say it like that...
Let's do it again, okay?
S-Sure!
Whoa, so you're home already, Taki?!
Yes, I am.
Were you perhaps peeking at us?
No, why would I?
That's fine, then.
I actually saw everything!
I'm sorry.
I already have someone I love.
Huh? What did you say?
That's why I can't go out with you anymore.
See you.
"See you"?
"See you" when?! I'm not that dumb!
And when I come home, I see...
I won't be able to calm down like this.
Okay...
Maybe Masahiko would be able to help me.
D-Don't scare me like that!
That said...
He really does look like a girl.
But when I saw them in the afternoon,
he looked quite masculine.
And Nozomi looked so satisfied afterwards.
It kind of feels like I'm taking over after her.
Well, even then, I'll start with a kiss for now.
If you're awake, you could've said s—
I don't believe it!
He's reacting to it,
even though he's asleep.
And I'm getting wet down there.
I want your help more than ever now.
W-Wow! It's at least twice the size of my ex.
Mom is one thing,
but it's incredible how it fit in Nozomi.
Will it fit?
I'm a little scared.
It's unbelieveable how big it is!
I'm so excited.
Coming!
Wh-What?
Taki-chan, what are you doing?!
Wh-What am I doing?
Surely you don't have to ask to know.
T-Taki, can I really?
Yes. Masahiko-kun, make love to me!
Yes! Masahiko, you do it so well!
Shush. Not so loud.
But it feels so good...
Hey, Masahiko-kun, hurry and put it in.
Taki-chan, you're so sensitive!
Look, you're dripping wet already.
That's not true...
Any woman would be like that.
I drank too much juice.
Masahiko is still awake?
Wh-What are they doing?
They're naked.
Playing wrestlers?
Do you want me to go in?
Yes, put it in.
Ah! He's putting such a thick stick in her butt,
that's gotta be a foul!
It's so hot... I'm melting!
It looks like Taki is in pain...
Masahiko-chan, that's a foul!
You put a thick stick in her butt!
That's a referee stop!
She has no idea about sex, of course.
She thinks we were wrestling.
Y-Yes, that was a foul.
Because I was playing the bad guy.
You know, I'm actually a big wrestling fan.
I was wondering whether I could go pro,
so I asked Masahiko to test me.
Yes, that's it!
But he did put a stick in your butt, didn't he?
No, look—there's nothing wrong with it!
But it's wet.
Did you pee in the bed?
I-It's just sweat.
But why aren't you wearing
any panties or leotards?
Because we don't have any.
Rika, it's late, so go to bed.
Okay.
We talked our way out of it this time,
but from now on, we'd better lock the door.
Taki-chan, should we continue?
No, she killed the mood.
Let's finish it another time.
But I really want to continue.
Next time, promise?
I'm not a liar.
That's a deal, then.
I've done it Nozomi,
and now with Taki as well!
This is becoming more like heaven!
Until later!
Yeah.
It's already half past eleven.
Auntie should be coming at any moment.
I need to pick a time for Taki.
Here she comes.
Good thing she didn't see Taki.
Did I make you wait?
Oh, how nice. You're already waiting for me, naked. Are you looking that forward to it?
Y-Yes, I knew you'd be coming soon.
Well, then, let's enjoy it fully today.
O-Okay...
I'm going now!
Masahiko-kun, wait for me!
Taki-chan, you're early today.
I have a club meeting.
Let's go together.
Okay.
Right, I need to arrange a time with Taki.
I'm going this way.
Okay. See you tonight, then.
Don't be late.
Okay.
Tonight I'm going to have lots of fun with Taki!
And after that, with Auntie?
I'd prefer it the other way around, though.
To summarize, if X moves towards A,
and A comes next to B, it looks like...
Oh?
HIGH SCHOOL
Science
Kisugi. Kisugi!
HIGH SCHOOL
Science
It's only the first period,
and you're already asleep?!
I-I'm sorry...
Kisugi, wanna hit on some girls after school?
Girls? I'd rather not.
What's wrong with you?
Are you already seeing someone these days?
Or are you working part-time after school?
Is that why you're always so tired?
And always sleeping during class?
Something like that.
You’ve got a pretty girly face,
you’d be a hit working as a host at night.
Yeah, from trendy girls to middle-aged women.
Too bad, seems it'll be only the two of us.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Hello.
So... you're here to do it?
No can do. Mom's here today.
She came with you twice
last night, didn't she?
Y-Yes.
Who do you prefer more,
my mother or me?
W-Well, that's... um...
It's okay.
I'll come again when mother has left.
Sure.
Like mother, like daughter—
she’s just as into it.
Mom, here's the mail!
I'll leave it for you.
It's probably fan mail.
Bye!
Let's see.
"Greetings, Sensei."
"I'm a 16-year-old female high school student."
"Your stories are filled with youth,
and they always make my heart race."
Oh, really?
I only write down my feelings as they are,
and they make all those young girls excited?
I'm hungry.
Huh? Where's Auntie and Taki?
Taki is taking a bath,
and mother is still writing.
I see.
We can start eating without them.
Now, let's begin.
Thanks for the food!
No...
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh? I—I just choked on my food, that's all.
No, not there!
What if I come?
Ah, guess I'll dine first, after all.
Oh, hello, Auntie.
We started without you.
Sure thing.
What's wrong?
You look so flustered.
No! I-It's nothing...
I hope we won't be disturbed today.
Ah, when I think about how large it was,
I get so excited.
That idiot Masahiko!
Why did he do that just then?
Now I'm too turned on to stop!
Masahiko will have to pay for this.
Ugh! This is why
mechanical pencils are useless!
But I hate typing on the computer as well.
I'm just not in the mood to write today.
It's a little early, but...
Time for a little break.
Mom!
Huh?
N-Nozomi?!
Are you going to Masahiko's again?
I'm not going to let you upstage me!
Upstage? You?
And you're also going dressed like that? Gross.
What are you talking about?
I still have confidence in my figure.
Look, you..
You're bothering Masahiko, you know.
It's time to leave him alone.
O-Of course not...
He enjoys it too, I know it!
Did he ever say that himself?
Then go ask him yourself.
Don't mind if I do, Mother.
Hurry! I want you!
Okay...
Like this!
Masahiko-kun!
Th-That's Auntie.
I'm coming in.
Wh-What is this?
M-Masahiko-kun... and Taki?
Nozomi-san...
You did it with her too?
I wanted to, but I never got around to it.
N-Nozomi is crying.
Is it because of me?
I'm sorry...
That's not fair! Not fair!
Leaving me out and doing it on your own!
The two of them are having all the fun to themselves! That's so mean! Right, Mother?
Y-Yes, of course.
Oh geez, what am I saying...
But no matter! You're just doing it with everyone, indiscriminately, isn't that right?!
N-Not exactly indiscriminately...
I seduced him!
My boyfriend left me,
so I wanted him to comfort me.
Taki-chan...
You were sleeping with him too!
I saw it myself!
No way! You said you hadn't seen anything back then!
What did you expect me to say?!
"Yeah, I've seen it"?
Look, you...
Enough of that!
This is all my fault.
Let's stop arguing.
This is going nowhere.
Then what do you suggest we do?
Well, look. We've become disunited as a family over this, so what we should do is reunite.
Aunt Hitomi?
What I mean is this...
M-Mom!
What do you mean?
We're going to do it all together!
Oh, you're just as sensitive as I am.
All together...
This way, I can do it with Taki and Nozomi
all I want without hiding it from Auntie!
Come on, you join us too, Nozomi.
Doing it together with everyone...
That could only be Auntie's idea.
You think so?
I just want all of us to get along.
Exactly! Oh, I can't wait any longer!
You can't cum yet.
Me too!
A-At this rate, I'm gonna...
Taki, you go first.
Okay.
Now I'll finally do it properly with Taki.
Ooh! Here we go!
He's really big!
Yes!
Oh, so good!
Masahiko-kun, stick your tongue in deeper!
Taki, hurry up! I want my turn too!
Wait, I'm almost there.
I—I'm cumming!
Masahiko-kun, hurry up!
Right, right, I'm here!
Here it goes!
Great!
Yes!
I can't wait until you put it in me too!
Don't take so long with Nozomi!
I—I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
No way, you can't leave me hanging like that!
Come on, big boy, get stiff again!
A-Auntie, let's continue tomorrow...
No way.
Right, I also want another turn.
He's young, so it's already stiff again!
Incredible! Mom, hurry up!
Well then, don't mind if I do...
Yes, so good!
Ah, yes!
Yes, so good...
I-If you keep moving like that, I'll come!
No way! It's way too soon!
A-Auntie, if you keep going so wild...
Ah, yes... So good!
You're taking too long, Mom!
We want our turn too!
Just a little bit more!
You're already doing it every night!
And so, this heavenly life where I'd spend
every night with all three of them has been going on for a whole month already...
I wonder how much longer I can last...
I'm afraid to go home.
My body's completely worn out—
this is Hell, not Heaven.
Huh?! You're leaving?
B-But why?!
W-Well, that's...
Kisugi, if this continues,
you'll have to repeat a year.
Huh?! Repeat a year...
Are you studying for the exams at all?
And you're sleeping during the class
nearly every day now!
I don't have time to study, and I'm always feeling anemic and light-headed.
If this keeps up, I might fail the college entrance exam
and disappoint my parents,
who have such high hopes of me.
Then, I know what we'll do—
divide up the week!
Say, Mon-Wed-Fri.
For example, Monday will be my day,
and Wednesday is for Nozomi.
Right, that way, it won't be so hard
on your body, and you'll be able to study.
Taki, what do you think?
I'm fine with it.
Masahiko-kun, how about you?
Y-Yes. Sounds fine by me.
Because life without any sex at all
would be awful.
Okay, then it's settled!
Let's divide the days right away.
We can do it with a lottery!
To tell you the truth,
I wouldn't ever wanna leave them.
Masahiko-kun, hurry up!
Early morning club again?
Yes.
It was decided that my day
would be Sunday.
That means that on Sunday you do everything I say, Mr. Freeloader.
Does this means every Sunday
I'll be going on a date with you?
Wrong. That means you'll serve me.
N-No way...
Kidding!
Will my freeloader life in paradise
last long or turn into Hell again?
Original translation
Editing
Translation check
Typesetting
QC
Erobeat
Collectr
Perevodildo
Collectr, Perevodildo
Muzussawa