Someone, help!
Heike forces are shooting fire at us!
Run!
You cowards!
Advance! Let no one
from the Genji clan escape!
Father! Where are you?!
Father...
Father!
Orphan Fansubs presents
Genji
Part 1, First Volume
Orphan Fansubs presents
Genji
Boo...
What're you doing, Katsumi?
Mouth etiquette.
I'm going on a date with Sakura today.
It's always, "Sakura, Sakura"!
You're so young,
but you're obsessed with her!
Oh, drop it already! You're being crude!
Still, Sakura's the only thing
on your mind lately.
My bad, Kotaro-chan.
I know you feel a bit neglected.
You're no fun!
It can't be helped!
After all, he even got on his knees
to ask her out.
Katsumi could really use more pride.
I got pride! Plenty of it.
But who says I have to toe
the same line as my siblings?
Kiyomori?
Are you Kiyomori no Taira?
Long time no see, Yori.
Or wait, do you go by Genji now?
You alone?
Yeah.
Mind taking the blade away from my face?
At least when we're alone,
we can drop the enmity.
Kiyomori no Taira!
We're here to claim your life!
Who the hell are you?!
Are you from the Heike Clan?!
Watch out!
Katsumi!
Genji!
Tsk. Missed my mark.
Genji! Hang on!
It's poisoned.
Bastard!
What did you do to Genji?!
He didn't do a thing.
Calm down, Yoshitsune.
But...
I cut the crossbowman down.
Wait, Kiyomori.
Sheathe your weapon too, Benkei.
Kiyomori and I were just exchanging greetings as childhood friends.
Today, I want you to listen closely.
We'll meet again.
And when that happens,
call me by my first name.
Like you used to...
"Yoritomo."
Sakura!
Where are you?!
H-Huh?
What just happened to me?
"What happened?"
You tell us what just happened!
You suddenly collapsed for no reason!
I did?!
Ah, shucks!
I don't have time to slack off here.
I'm late for my date!
Date?! With whom?
When did you...
Who are you taking out?!
Didn't I just tell you?
Sakura, of course!
Sakura?
Don't make things up, Katsumi!
What's going on?
Why did everyone suddenly
forget about Sakura?
Say, Katsumi...
If a day comes when I'm gone,
will you come looking for me?
What are you talking about?
Come on, answer!
Of course. Even to the ends of the Earth.
Sakura-sama, as per your command,
I have made arrangements so that only that boy retains any memories of you.
I see. Thank you.
Are you quite sure this is what you want?
After all, you'll lose all of your own memories as a consequence.
I don't mind that.
Sakura-sama...
Losing all my memories is nowhere near as frightening as losing his love!
Sakura!
Katsumi...
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Katsumi?
Katsumi!
Sakura! I found you! Sakura!
Katsumi! What are you doing here?!
I promised you, didn't I?
I'd come looking for you!
Katsumi!
Sakura, where are you going?!
Sakura, come back!
Sakura!
I love you!
Katsumi!
Sakura!
A lie... It's a lie!
A lie.
Ebata Katsumi.
Do you wish to follow?
Where Sakura-sama is going.
Are you serious?
Yes. If we set out now,
we can catch up with them.
We'll have no trouble following,
as long as the ship's wake is visible.
Would you ride in my boat?
Ah! Hang on, a talking peacock?!
Did it just dawn on you now,
you scatterbrained kid?
Haruna Castle
Kiyomori-sama.
A sleeping beauty?
Hey... What is this place?
Presently, we're in the unfortunate land
that Japan has become under Heike rule.
There are two clans, Genji and Heike,
both descended from noble court blood.
Minamoto no Yoritomo commands the Genji forces, and Kiyomori no Taira opposes him.
The two clans have been waging
a bloody civil war for a long time.
So this is the Genpei War, huh?
Well, that doesn't concern me.
What's that?
This doesn't look good.
Someone's holding a funeral.
A funeral?
All the flags are lined up.
And they reserve this spot only for high-ranking funerals.
A renowned samurai must have died.
And what's that white flag?
What? A white flag?
Benkei...
You haven't eaten for two full days.
If you don't eat anything,
you'll get sick, Shanao.
Come on, eat up now.
Genji... My older brother died.
I couldn't care less for eating now.
Don't even think of following him.
If you die, I will also...
follow the two of you.
However...
Will there ever be a shogun quite as influential or beloved as Genji was?
It hurts me to think that Seiwa Genji's army has lost its only support, now of all times.
Say, this guy Minamoto
no Yoritomo died or what?
You jerk!
Seems I hit a sore spot.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to ask if you'd seen my friend around. Well, later!
Wait!
Genji!
It's you, Genji!
What the...
Sh-Shanao! He's not.
He's not Genji!
Let me go, Benkei!
How... How is he not?! Look at him!
Is this...
Wh-What's going on?
Genji?!
Say...
Are you just gonna stand there
and watch me all night?
You sound nothing like Genji.
Sorry to disappoint you!
Maybe I'm not Genji, after all?
Of course not.
He was a much more wonderful person.
Tch! What a pity I'm nowhere
near that wonderful!
Truly so.
I'm sorry.
Spare me your apologies.
Just leave me alone.
Your sorrow is contagious.
I have more than enough
on my plate as it is.
I mean, I appreciate you
letting me stay tonight.
But I don't have time
to grieve for him with you!
I have to go look for Sakura
tomorrow as well.
Say, Katsumi.
If a day comes when I'm gone,
will you come looking for me?
I've come to look for you, Sakura.
This is the one and only promise to Sakura
that I can't afford to break!
I'll follow you to the ends
of the Earth, even to Hell.
I came looking for you, Sakura!
As long as I have her,
I don't need anything else.
Gosh, you're obstinate!
I was dead serious about that!
What are you...
I should have done this
while Genji was alive.
Genji this, Genji that!
Shut up, will ya?!
I'm Ebata Katsumi, you hear?!
I'm not here to replace Genji for you!
A replacement is exactly what you are.
It's your own fault!
For having a face exactly like his!
You idiot!
Oh, no. He's stronger than me.
And besides, this feels kinda good...
What should I do?
Usually I'm not into guys!
Stop it, you!
Aren't you his younger brother?
Would you have done this
to your actual brother?
That was why I hadn't done anything.
And that's why I can do it with you.
You look like Genji,
but you're not him.
You were into your own brother?
That's right.
I was in love with him.
I was madly in love with Genji.
But now, he's gone forever.
I loved him more than anyone,
more than my own life.
This is just unbearable.
Even more than your own life?
Of course.
Then, I don't mind you
trying to kiss me once more.
I get it now.
More than heaven, more than the stars...
he was that important to him.
With him gone, nothing in this world matters anymore.
You're an idiot, you know?
You should've just done it with him.
He'd have understood right away.
You could've conveyed more about what Genji meant to you
with one kiss than a thousand words.
You idiot. I'm a stranger,
but even I understand.
You had a very strong
connection with him.
It's all right. Come on. I'll let you do it.
I'm like him, aren't I?
We're suffering from a similar fate.
That sounds nothing like Genji.
Well, I'm not Genji!
Ah, you're burning the corpse?
Makes sense, or it'll rot in the summer.
What do you mean by that?
May his soul rest in peace.
You bastard! Mind your own business!
Calm down, Shanao.
Katsumi-dono, I take it you share both his appearance and his armor size?
Let's order one just like Genji's.
In pure white!
Why? I won't wear no armor.
But you have nowhere
else to go, do you?
Doesn't matter! Piss off, you creep!
You'd need something better
to recruit me for your cause!
That's regrettable.
I thought we could strike a deal.
It'd be a fair deal: 50-50.
We'd both get something we wanted.
Mind your own business!
When I want something,
I try to get it with my own hands.
Hey, you can't do anything
by yourself here.
Don't you all need to mind your own goddamn business?!
True.
It's none of our business.
Please feel free to depart
to the four winds... all by yourself.
Feel free to travel this unknown country, this state of Japan, all by yourself.
The overly optimistic
invariably come to disaster.
Disaster?! Disaster, you say?!
How is this not the worst possible disaster already?! Sakura's gone!
How is that being overly optimistic?!
I just want Sakura back!
Nothing more than that!
Nothing else... Nothing else matters to me!
Just for that one wish to come true!
Hey!
Don't follow me!
He sure is a hot-tempered brat.
What is it, Benkei?
I like that guy.
He's going so far for a woman.
Barely 16, and he's managed to find his true love already.
Anyone would act that way in his shoes.
Roses covered the bed every time
we made love in this room
I believed I had your every word,
your every movement, to myself
Two riders are too much
for our poor Yoriko!
Oh, it'll be fine.
So why do you avert your eyes?
Speaking of that, where's your Sara?
She's about to give birth to a foal.
Just so you won't see me?
I entrusted her to Masako's care
and sent her back home to Yokohama.
Even more than your lips,
even more than your warmth,
You should have gone with her.
I couldn't. I'd be too worried
if you were left all alone.
I coveted feeling you so close to me most of all
We'll look for Katsumi together.
I'm blindfolded, I'm lost,
all alone this night, like a child
To me, he's just as important an asset.
Well, whatever.
I wander in circles,
clutching a dream that will not end
Perhaps this is my continuous love
Hey, sport, wanna buy an apple?
Huh? Hang on a minute...
Is this enough?
A hundred yen?!
Uh, sorry. Not enough, actually?
But it's all I have.
N-No, a hundred yen will do!
I don't think so.
With a hundred yen, one could buy
all those apples and get change too!
Sa... Saga-sama!
What are you doing,
tricking kids like that?
I'm sorry!
You need to be more careful
with your money.
I see. Money has different value here.
I'll remember that.
Thanks.
I'm Ebata Katsumi.
And you are?
I'm Sagano Kuya.
Nice to meet you, Katsumi-dono.
Oh, you should feel free
to call me Katsumi.
And the apple...
Want some?
Sure, thanks.
But let me say, you look exhausted, young man.
Yeah, that's true. I'm a bit worn out.
I'm looking for someone here.
Then we're in the same situation.
Let's join forces. We'll search together.
Really? Thanks!
So what's her name?
Sakura. Hasegawa Sakura.
She's my girlfriend.
A real beauty, with long hair.
Kinda like yours.
And are you looking for
your sweetheart too, Kuya?
I've never met them, so I don't know what they look like.
That's weird... You know the name?
That's a secret.
No way! When someone tells you his secret,
you return the trust, so tell me!
All right all right, but only the name.
It's Yoritomo.
Genji!
Kuya, what are you doing?!
That right there is Genji!
She's mistaken, Kuya!
We're different people.
There's no doubt! I saw him with my own eyes during the Battle of Fujigawa!
This is Genji?
Kiyomori-sama's...
Hold it!
Shanao Yoshitsune!
Musashibo Benkei!
Katsumi?
Hang on a minute, you people!
You're not planning to kill Kuya, are you?
Nitwit. Are you still half-asleep?
This guy deserves
to have his head displayed
on the prison gate pole, if not worse!
No way! That's not happening!
You bastard! What did you put in Katsumi's head already?!
He didn't do anything!
If I said no, it's no!
I won't allow any killing,
no matter who tries it!
Quit defending his ass!
Don't you know Sagano Kuya
is the vice-shogun of the Heike Clan?!
He probably killed tens of thousands of the Genji army!
He's not getting away!
I saw you on the battlefield once.
You're the devil himself!
Stop it already, Yoshitsune!
I see.
He's Minamoto no Shanao.
A man like fire itself.
If I am the devil...
then you're a demon.
Save your eloquence!
You'll pay for showing up
here so heedlessly.
I'm about to introduce your body
to the lineage of the Kanto Genji!
Oh, really?
Putting a decisive end to you right now will save me a lot of trouble later.
Don't mind if I seize that chance!
Freeze!
I will shoot.
We're in neutral territory.
You know that combat is prohibited within the city of Tokyo.
Kiyomori-sama.
Damn you, Kiyomori!
Kiyomori-sama!
What are you doing here?
We followed you.
Sakura!
Genji?
It's you, Sakura!
Wait, Katsumi!
Genji! What's going on?
Sakura, why won't you say anything?!
It's me! Katsumi!
Sakura!
Sakura, what's wrong?!
I came to look for you!
Sakura, where are you going?
Sakura, what happened?! Sakura!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Who are you?!
It's me, Sakura!
Sakura!
Let me go, Yoshitsune!
Let me go this instant,
or I'll hate you forever!
Let me go, damn it!
What should we do, Benkei?!
Don't even think about letting him go.
We'll settle this later, Shanao!
You're not getting out alive next time.
Right back at you! I'll kill you good!
Both you and Kiyomori.
Don't you forget it!
Sakura. Sakura!
I don't understand!
Who are you?!
Sakura!
I don't understand!
Sakura.
Sakura! Sakura!
Sakura!
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I can't remember anything!
Sakura!
It's me, Sakura!
Hojo Mansion
Still, Benkei-dono doesn't believe that
the strategy has any chance of succeeding.
Genji was no ordinary man, after all.
He pulled the strings.
No mere double can replace him.
It's a difficult issue.
He was very charismatic.
Very much so. It's indeed a problem.
But Katsumi's no pushover either.
We agree about that.
But even worse, if word gets out that Genji is dead,
it'll hurt the morale of our allies.
The Heike wouldn't hesitate to launch an attack.
Then what do we do about our three crucial issues?
No one but Genji can ride
Unicorn, his favorite horse.
Also, the armorer will know
if anyone else dons Genji's armor.
You can be sure of that.
Further, Genji-dono's left eye was biomechanical.
An artificial network of organic matter.
Well, I can assure everyone that
I'll handle Katsumi for the time being.
Kenreimonin-sama,
I have answered your call.
Sagano Kuya is here.
Oh, if it isn't Sagano.
I commend your work on
the last special assignment.
Well, come closer now.
I am comfortable speaking from here.
Would you mind telling me
what mission Kiyomori gave you?
I inspected the enemy's movements.
You state it so simply,
but was it really nothing special?
Well, no matter. I summoned you here for another reason. I need a favor from you.
It's for Tsunemori.
Tsunemori-sama?
Right.
He is not related to Kiyomori by blood, only to me.
He has no one else to care for him.
You should be well aware that I am Kiyomori-sama's vassal.
I cannot move a single finger
without Kiyomori-sama's explicit order.
Kuya.
If... If Kiyomori were to die,
would you then fulfill my request
and become Tsunemori's vassal?
My, you're such a handful.
You look impulsive, but you're smart.
Ha ha! Sorry about that!
If you run off by yourself again,
I'll have to punish you.
I'll sit here. Okay?
Seems to me you're already sitting.
My apologies.
Good morning, Zakuro-dono.
We apologize for any inconvenience caused.
I'll see you later, then.
What do you want this time?
Well, I just remembered one thing.
We have some fine horses
here in Yokohama.
There's even a unicorn.
It used to be Genji's horse.
A unicorn?
Yes.
If you're not too scared,
I thought I might show them to you.
What's there to be scared of?
It's just a horse or two.
I see.
Idiot! Liar!
It's a damn lot more than a horse or two!
Take your time, Katsumi-dono.
Damn that Benkei!
A strange man just intruded.
The horses are getting uneasy!
What's worse, they even let this big one roam freely.
This is the only horse here with a horn.
Oh, I see, so this must be the unicorn.
The unicorn I saw at the circus
looked more like a goat.
But this one is amazing!
It's just like the real thing!
I really was scared of a horse?
They're going to do it in a large battle.
Where did you learn about that?
Truly, no confidential information is safe in this castle.
I'm against it.
Naturally, it will cause many deaths.
You should be speaking to the Genji.
You should be ashamed to put the blame on them so quickly!
This is wrong!
Maybe it is.
You sure are short-tempered
since we returned from Tokyo.
Well... for that, you should blame yourself.
You try my patience.
Are you putting the blame on me?
I suppose.
But I'm itching to do something already.
It sickens me just to sit here,
dawdling around like nothing happened.
If you've lost your memory,
what can you do?
You're doing okay for an amnesiac.
That's not what I meant.
I don't care about my memory.
But I feel like I've forgotten
something way more important.
Something more important than memory?
Memory stores an individual's history.
It defines the values of your life.
Yet you say something's more important?
I don't know.
But I have reasons to think there is.
I feel I can keep on living,
even without my memory,
but not without what I forgot.
Women are such romantics.
No, we're realists.
This heartache is very real.
Sakura!
That's all.
Are you, like, a real unicorn?
I wonder how they bred such a thing.
Are you an idiot?
Have you not heard
of unicorns from fables?
You can't breed my species.
It talked!
You can hear my voice too?
Just who are you?
Your face is like Genji's. Your eyes too.
Your hair, your voice.
And finally, your ability to hear me.
However, Genji should be dead by now!
I'm Ebata Katsumi.
Ebata Katsumi?
How curious.
You resemble Genji completely,
and yet you're not him.
May I touch you?
You feel nice.
She's about to give birth.
It came out!
It's so tiny!
No.
It's useless.
What's useless?
Benkei?
Poor fetal positioning in the womb.
The hind legs are underdeveloped.
It won't be able to stand
on those hind legs.
No way! Anything is possible, if you try!
Hey, you! Stand up!
What will happen to it now?
Well, it's...
We don't have a choice, Sara.
You can't bring a horse
that can't run to a battlefield.
No! What are you implying by that?
You're not... going to kill it, are you?
Masako!
Benkei! You can't do that!
It tried to stand up, didn't it?
Don't be so cruel!
That's enough, Masako.
It won't live long with those legs,
no matter what.
Horses that can't stand, can't live.
But...
Stop it. It's Sara's foal. Who do you think suffers the most here?
Now then...
Something wrong?
No. I've known him for a long time,
but it's the first time this has happened.
Should I follow him? Or would it be better to leave him alone?
Go to him. He's about to cry.
You're right.
We gotta do something.
As a fellow horse, what's your opinion?
Would you, mere humans,
ever be able to understand?
Living creatures are straightforward.
We die when it's time to die.
We live while it's time to live.
It's as simple as that.
True, I don't really understand.
But simply put, this foal needs to stand up, right?
Isn't there anything we can do?
Nobody said that.
If nothing else, we'll stand by its side.
You can do it!
Just a little more!
How's the foal?
Look, I think he's feeling better already.
You can do it!
Come on.
Don't give up!
You can do it!
Wow. It's delicious!
Come on. No more indulging in mama's pampering.
Time to work hard again.
I smell blood.
It has been a long time, brother.
Yeah... I think the last time was at the Battle of Fujigawa?
Is it my turn again?
Yes.
So a major battle is coming?
I wish you'd send me
on a killing spree more often.
Then, let us begin the conference.
First, I'd like to hear the explanation
from the framer of this strategy.
Yes, sir. We have elected to name this operation "Kamakura."
A Thousand-Year City offensive.
We will crush the enemy's base
in an all-out attack.
We've been through this. Without thorough preparation, it's suicide!
Kamakura is Genji's headquarters.
Their army is weakened, true,
but not their reserves in the center!
Where did this come from, Kai?
Anyone could tell you it's madness.
Moreover, it's no secret that Kamakura is a natural fortress,
with mountains on three sides and the sea on the fourth!
A siege would be bloody.
I am well aware of that.
But we now have a perfect opportunity.
Genji's own intelligence says that
Minamoto no Yoritomo has died of poison.
Sakura...
Masako-chan!
Katsumi!
Quickly, get Benkei!
Bring everyone here!
I'm so happy. I'm so happy for you, little one!
There, there! Look, everyone!
He's standing!
Anything is possible if you try.
Don't die, little one!
Translation
Moho Kareshi, glenn
Translation Check, Research
Perevodildo
Timing
glenn, ninjacloud
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
QC
Nemesis
Uchuu
On a pale blue night, you keep on shining
Encoding
anonymous
In time, you'll be the only one there, so far away
Encoding
anonymous
I want you to look at me
with those eyes, like the stars
I want to feel you close, by my side
These hardships, flowing so gloomily
in your tears, mean everything to me now
Any time, any place you choose
That smile of yours will never grow old to me
If the future should engulf me wholly
Rather than feign kindness
that would hurt us afterward
I'll stick to believing in the present,
where you cannot hide
Under the star of meeting