Shonen Drama Series
They Were Eleven!
We'll now begin the final test.
You ten have made it through several rounds,
chosen from forty thousand applicants.
Each of you represents the brightest minds
your governments have to offer.
But the Galactic University
seeks more than intellect.
It seeks individuals of superior ability
in every respect.
That spacecraft is where
your final test will take place.
You'll find out what to do once you get there.
Squad... turn around!
Now go!
Stop!
Now you depart!
People don't say it anymore, but...
good luck!
The discovery of warp technology and anti-gravity revolutionized human space travel,
and in just two hundred years,
Earth had colonized fifty-one planet.
But many of those colonies
sought independence,
declaring wars of independence
on the Earth Federation one after another.
Humans continued to wage war between themselves, now in space,
until one day, contact with an alien race
forced humanity to unite.
Four centuries later, Earth—
now known as Terra—
joined the Interstellar Alliance,
alongside the great powers Lota, Segul, and Sava, and several smaller alien worlds.
Humans and aliens learned to coexist.
And today marks yet another
Galactic University entrance examination.
Hey!
The dean said there'd be ten of us, right?
What about it?
Look, there's one extra.
There're eleven of us!
You're right.
There're eleven.
Eleven of us, indeed!
They Were Eleven!
I don't know anything. I had nothing to do with this! Don't ask me!
Stop crying!
Hey, whoever snuck aboard, speak up!
Who are you?
Who's the stowaway?
The explosion succeeded.
The ship should begin drifting on its own now.
Dean, please give instructions to the ten examinees.
We've got a problem!
What is it?
Someone's stowed away aboard the exam ship.
What? Are you sure?
Yes, look at this.
It's a message he left behind.
A message?
Dean, it seems the intruder
intends to die with the examinees.
Who is he?
We don't know.
Only that he hates those aiming to enter
the Galactic University and become future leaders.
Dean, it's dangerous.
We should call them back immediately.
No.
The test will continue.
It's an unexpected accident, but perhaps this will serve the true purpose of our test even better.
Listen carefully.
What we seek are individuals
who can maintain sound judgment
and initiative to respond to any situation.
The final test will proceed as planned.
Hey, what's going on?
The lights!
Where?
Move!
There!
Careful!
The explosions started!
120 charges inside the ship!
We're safe.
Who are you?
The ship was set to explode automatically
once the airlock sealed.
One blast every three minutes.
So that's the test,
whether we can stop it or not.
“When you get there,
you'll understand,” huh?
Attention, Galactic University applicants.
You ten are to remain aboard and man this vessel
for fifty-three days as its crew.
Not ten, eleven!
This test is meant to appraise your teamwork
in a simulated drifting ship.
Dean, there's one extra!
Dean, can you hear us?
If even one person drops out, all ten will fail.
He still believes there are ten.
Dean!
If an emergency occurs, press the scramble button.
Otherwise, all communication is cut off.
Oh, crap...
We're done for.
You'll only be rescued if you either give up and press that button, or survive the fifty-three days.
Good luck.
Can't hear us, huh? Damn idiot!
Hey, so what do we do now?
Let's assume the University believes we're ten.
It's already an emergency situation.
So what do we do about the extra one?
Press the emergency button
and fail the whole group, right?
Knock it off with the jokes!
Show yourself, coward!
Whoever's the eleventh, speak up!
No point fighting.
How about we start by inspecting the ship?
We'll be living here
for fifty-three days, after all.
Hey, this door won't open.
Weird, no handle either.
Step on the yellow line by your feet.
You sure know your way around, huh?
Tada, take a look at that.
What do you think it is?
Electric ivy.
Electric ivy?
Like those used for wiring?
I'll turn on the light.
It sure has been allowed to run wild here.
Don't worry, Frol.
It's an antibiotic plant.
Not like it's gonna eat you.
Who said I'm scared?
I j-just got startled, that's all!
Listen up, everyone.
We'll have to survive fifty-three days,
isolated aboard this ship.
And one of us, this eleventh person,
is a total unknown.
So here's my proposal:
From now on, no one acts alone.
You giving the orders now?
Spoken like a true king.
Everyone moves in pairs now.
Room assignments, too—two to a room.
That leaves one person out, doesn't it?
You'll get your own room.
What?
I probably don't need to explain why.
You moron!
You think I'm a girl or something?
I hate women!
Women are trash!
You morons!
Frol...
It's been so long, I've forgotten
what face to make when something's funny.
Somebody, please tell me.
It's been so long, I've forgotten
why does a full stomach make people kind?
Somebody, please tell me.
It's been so long, I've forgotten...
Enough! Cut it out!
Let it be.
I found this old instrument in the living quarters.
Makes a pretty nice sound, doesn't it?
I said stop!
Come on, relax. Have a drink.
Helps you forget all the bad stuff for a while.
I said stop!
Who is it?
Who's the eleventh?
Please... tell us.
Um...
You know, I was thinking...
Maybe we should press the scramble button
and have them come rescue us?
Idiot!
If we do that, we'll all fail.
Still...
I don't think I can hold out much longer.
Let's press it!
What's gonna happen now?
What'll become of Terra after this, huh?
Anyone here know engineering?
I want to fix the computer.
Any progress, Ganga?
There's a maintenance manual.
If we can get the computer running again,
we might be able to contact our home planets.
and maybe even find out
who the eleventh person really is.
Tada, press that button there.
Okay.
Ganga!
Tada's acting suspicious.
He knows way too much about this ship.
I saw it myself.
Ganga told him to push the button,
and Tada must've pressed a different one.
Yeah. The only one who'd be in trouble
if the computer's fixed is the eleventh person.
How's Ganga?
Surgery successful.
Tada's a hell of a surgeon.
Good work, Tada.
But that doesn't mean you're off the hook.
What's that supposed to mean?
You've been on this ship before, haven't you?
What?
Then how come you know so much about it?
You're wrong! I've never...
A vote!
Anyone who thinks
he's the imposter, raise your hand.
What are you talking about?
Tada was working hard to save Ganga!
I'm against this.
Let's vote.
Who here thinks Tada's a sussy baka?
I protest!
Who thinks Tada's not suspicious?
Five to four.
By majority vote, Tada will be confined.
I protest!
Ganga, you can't get up yet!
I'm against it!
King, it's a five to five.
It's a tie.
Ganga, thank you.
What are you saying?
You're the one who saved me.
But you gave us a shock,
your blood...
Frol...
Yeah, it's fine.
You were gonna say it's green, right?
That's right.
I'm a Tredolaga-designed biomech,
a sort of cyborg created
through Chlorella cultivation.
A cyborg?
My race doesn't live long.
Our planet's plagued by food diseases,
no one lives past thirty.
So to survive, we developed a way to convert our bodies to living cells.
I'm the test subject.
Then it's really great you made it.
Yeah. I owe Tada my life.
But maintaining my cells costs a fortune.
That's why I want to get
into Galactic University
to find a way for my species
to make enough money,
and give every Tredolagian
a chance to live a long life.
I see.
What about you, Tada?
Why do you want in?
Me?
Same reason—for my planet.
Tada...
The reason is...
my species' population's small.
We're constantly pressured and suppressed
by larger neighboring worlds.
Some even call us a dying race,
like the Sibelius planet.
We needed to advance
our medical science for survival.
I want to join the Galactic University
to study how strong and weak species
can coexist in peace.
Everyone's got their own dream, huh.
From every corner of the galaxy,
each of us brought our own dreams and hopes.
Ten people, all about the same age...
No, eleven.
Yeah.
But I do wonder
what the eleventh one dreams of.
The eleventh one...
Maybe that person doesn't have
any dreams or future at all.
Frol, what's your dream?
Me? I just want to know
whether I'll become a man or a woman.
What?
Forget it. Nothing.
Hey!
Frol's a dual-sex species.
Until second maturity,
they're neither male nor female.
On Frol's planet, Vene,
men rule while women work.
And only those who become leaders
are recognized as men.
As the youngest child, Frol, was promised manhood
and leadership if admitted to Galactic University.
Tada?
Frol, you really are a girl, aren't you?
A woman!
You bastard...
So you figured it out?
What do you want?
What are you doing?
You—a woman! Why, you...
Damn you!
What the hell...
You broad!
Get off me, you nutjob!
Hey! What happened here?
Everyone, listen!
If I pass the University test,
I'm allowed to become a man.
And if I become a man,
I can become the greatest of them all!
So I have to pass this test, no matter what!
Please understand!
Calm down, Frol.
Shut up!
Don't treat me like a girl!
I'm a man! I'll be a man!
Um, this might sound weird, but...
What is it, Chaco?
Don't you hear something strange?
It's moving!
Hey, we're drifting off course!
It's that earlier explosion
that messed up the engines and orbit.
Damn, why's it getting so hot all of a sudden?
Frol, stop!
Idiot, I told you I'm a man!
Wait, this isn't the time for that!
According to my calculations,
this ship's headed straight for the sun!
What?! What do we do?!
At this rate, the temperature'll rise
three to five degrees a day.
Soon this place'll turn into a sauna,
then an inferno, and finally, we'll crash into the sun.
Is that true, Chaco?
Do we hit the scramble button now?
No jokes!
I refuse to fail!
Then what, Frol, you'd rather get cooked alive?
Come quick!
Th-The Electric Ivy totally went wild!
So much of it!
But why?
What's this?
Hey, everybody... what's happening?
It's the heat—the rising temperature
revived the plant.
Soon this'll be a jungle.
That's not the point!
If the temperature keeps rising,
they'll keep growing,
and then...
then...
What's wrong, Tada?
Electric ivy...
Crystals forming...
Dell's Red Spot Disease!
Dell's Red Spot Disease?
A disease?!
A viral outbreak...
and then...
Tada!
You know something, don't you?
Spit it out!
You're the eleventh one, aren't you?!
Tada!
Hey, hang in there!
You brought him?
Yes.
Okay, put him down here!
Hey, lay him on his side—
Tada hit his head!
Shut up! Leave that suspicious guy alone!
Tada, are you really the eleventh one? Tada!
I'm scared! Help me, I'm scared!
Don't play dumb!
Tada, keep your head up!
You're the one, aren't you?
The infiltrator—the eleventh man!
No, I'm not...
No... that doesn't matter now!
Hurry and hit the scramble button,
or we'll all die!
Tada, what are you saying?
I'm scared! Help me, I'm scared!
Tada!
Frol, let go!
There's no reason to pity someone like him!
No! I care about him...
Even if he's the eleventh man, I still...
Frol...
Would you rather become a woman or die?
Tada...
Listen to me!
When I saw that electric ivy,
it finally came back to me.
Everyone,
I was on this ship once before,
when I was a child.
So it's true after all.
Why were you hiding it, Tada?
No, I'd just forgotten.
That's right. Who remembers things from when they were a baby?
Then why did you suddenly remember now?
It's that electric ivy.
Yeah. That same ivy
was revived once already,
when I was a child, and just like now,
a virus spread from the crystal core.
The high fever, red spots across the body,
ringing in the ears, partial paralysis...
But there was no vaccine!
Preventive vaccines were too scarse.
So...
my people...
hundreds...
no,
thousands...
died from the Dell's Red Spot Disease!
The crystals,
red spots,
that sound...
Muscles stiffening...
N-No vaccine!
Grow, grow, grow!
Keep growing!
Spread the virus far and wide!
Kill them all!
I'm going to die anyway!
They took me from my home planet,
want to send me to the colonies,
where they'll work me to death!
Grow! Grow! Grow! Grow! Grow! Grow!
Amazon, what are you doing here?
Ganga?
Your wounds healed up already?
What were you just saying?
Sounded like you were laughing
a moment ago.
Amazon...
Who are you really?
I won't forgive you!
What are you doing?!
Wait, Amazon!
Wait! Stop!
Somebody! Come quick!
Ganga!
Frol, call everyone!
Hold on! I'll help you!
Tada, what are you doing?
Look, explosives have been planted
all over this ship!
One's already gone off,
there are 119 more left.
So what?
If we gather all of them on the roof
of the living quarters and detonate them,
the blast might shift the rocket's orbit!
Are you insane?
That could blow up the entire ship!
If we don't pull away from the sun,
the overheating will only get worse!
Why not just press
the scramble button and call for rescue?
We can't do that!
That'd be dishonorable!
Dishonorable?
Is getting into the Galactic University
and becoming a leader really so honorable?
It's not about honor!
It's about our dreams and our future!
I'd risk my life for that, no question!
Those who have dreams...
who have a future, they're the lucky ones.
What was that?
King, what do you think of my idea?
All right, let's try it.
It's all or nothing—
gather all the explosives in the ship!
If it works, our orbit will change.
Hey, hold that one down!
Got it!
Frol!
Tada!
Fools...
Dreams, future...
are they really as precious
as you make them out to be?
But still, if we lose two more people,
wouldn't that mean we all fail?
If all ten of us don't make it back...
Tada...
Frol...
You know, I'd be fine if we just kept calling each other's names till we die, like this.
Tada...
Tada, what's wrong?
Won't you call my name anymore?
I don't want to do this to a woman...
Forgive me.
Frol, you made it.
Tada...
Tada!
Tada, you moron!
Goodbye...
Everyone, take care.
Now that I'm gone, that makes ten again.
Get into the Galactic University safely.
My dream...
My future...
I finally understand...
why my planet's population is so small.
Ganga!
Tada, thank God!
Thank you, King.
You're the one who gave Ganga
the long safety line, right?
If even one person is missing,
everyone fails, remember?
All right, let's hit the detonation switch.
Ready?
We did it!
It worked!
We're moving away from the sun!
We did it!
Forty-two... forty-three...
forty-four... forty-five...
What are you doing, Toto?
I've been keeping track since we got here.
look, it's been forty-five days already!
Just eight more to reach
the required fifty-three.
Dinner's ready!
Eat up, everyone!
Finally!
Something's wrong!
Frol's condition is worsening!
Frol!
It's nothing...
Medicine...
Hang in there!
Frol! You're burning up!
I said I'm fine...
High fever, red spots, the ringing...
Dell's Red Spot Disease?
No... it's just a cold...
Look, the red spots are showing!
Don't touch me!
Frol, are you...
I'm sorry.
Back when I was caught in the vines,
Frol came to save me.
So that's it, Ganga...
You didn't get infected
because you're a cyborg.
I caught the Dell's Red Spot Disease?
You've got to be kidding!
Frol!
What do we do?
There's no vaccine!
But if we just leave Frol like this, she'll...
Tada!
Eyeing scramble button, aren't you?
Like I'd let you do that!
Let go! We can't just abandon Frol!
Only eight days left,
she'll last about that long.
Don't be stupid! We can only save her
if we ask for help as soon as we can!
Cretin! I won't let you to the button!
What's wrong, everyone?
What's the matter?
Why aren't you stopping them?
Isn't that right?
You don't even know if you're siding with Tada or with Dolph, do you?
Serves you right!
You all want to be leaders, right?
You don't care what happens to individual lives,
as long as you can stand out in people's eyes!
How admirable.
Splendid leaders, the lot of you.
And you, Amazon...
I'm from a slave planet.
Cygnus, on the frontier.
That's a planet where telepaths
think of you as less than animals.
And you used those telepaths
to make us work for you, didn't you?
Then, you're the eleventh one.
So what will you do?
Is Frol's life more important?
Or is honor worth more than life itself?
Well, leaders?
Everyone...
You're fine with me pressing the button, right?
Then I'll do it.
Don't regret it later.
In eight days, you'll all be demoted.
If you press it now,
our 45 days of hardship will go to waste.
Shut up!
Wait!
Stop, at least for my sake.
For me alone.
Frol!
And if I'm doomed to die anyway,
then I want to die as a man!
Frol!
There's nothing wrong
with becoming a woman.
When this all ends,
come with me to my planet.
Marry me.
Tada!
I'll push the scramble button.
King...
Shit...
Wait, Amazon.
Thank you.
It's thanks to you.
For the first time, I realized there's something more important than honor or anything else.
It's the heart to believe in others.
Perhaps we've all learned something even the Galactic University can't teach.
Rescue ship from the Galactic University is here!
Congratulations!
You've all passed!
You endured the full 45 days!
Until last year, all applicants
pressed the scramble button within 20 days.
Moreover, you did it while dealing
with the unexpected eleventh member!
Congratulations!
We did it!
Where are you headed, Amazon Carnais?
To the Space Prison.
You do not wish to enter
the Galactic University?
You held out for 45 days too, didn't you?
Amazon Carnais,
when you graduate safely,
I expect you to devote yourself
to the advancement of your planet.
Congratulations, Amazon!
Good for you, Amazon.
Shake on it, Amazon!
Congrats, Amazon!
We did it!
By the way, Frol, now that you've passed,
you'll really become a man after all.
That's great, Frol.
You'll be able to become a man.
Tada...
But if you...
If you'd rather me become a woman...
I...
I'd be fine with that too.
Frol...
Tada!
The long test has ended.
But before these boys, lies a future
that stretches on—endlessly wide and long.
They Were Eleven!
The End
Raw acquisition, editing
Encoding
Paul Geromini
Anonymous
Translation
Quality check
Perevodildo
sotoo
Marty McFlies