Emperor Meiji and the Great Russo-Japanese War
Translation                 Perevodildo
Editing               Paul Geromini
darkcart
In the 37th year of Meiji (1904),
Japan faced an unprecedented national crisis
in the face of Imperial Russia's Far Eastern policy.
Russian aggression in Manchuria exerted increasing pressure on Japan, and the anger of the entire nation reached its peak.
After the Sino-Japanese War, the Liaodong Peninsula at the southern end of Manchuria became Japanese territory,
yet our possession of the peninsula was declared a threat to world peace and we were forced to return it to Qing China
by Russia, who led the so-called Triple Intervention.
Now, Russia forcibly leased
the Liaodong Peninsula from China,
constructed a new city, Dalny, and is building fortifications at Port Arthur, all for what, exactly?
Yeah!
Furthermore, seven doctors—Imperial University professors Tomizu, Terao, Onozuka, Kanai, Nakamura, Takahashi, and Tomii—
condemned Russia for violating international law and petitioned the government to take a stance against Russia.
On top of that, Russia used
the Boxer Uprising of 1900 as an excuse
and refused to withdraw the troops it had dispatched.
Instead they have steadily built up in Manchuria, strengthening its military position,
and now appears intent
on extending its power into Korea.
Shall it be ruin, or war?
Will Japan simply allow itself
to become prey to Russia's Far Eastern policy,
or will the people unite as one
and face this national crisis?
The answer depends entirely upon the resolve of you,
the citizens of this nation.
Foreign Minister Komura has met more than a dozen times with
Minister Rosen of Russia,
and now the truth of the matter is clear.
Russia's attitude shows not the slightest trace of sincerity!
If we permit Russia's tyranny to continue unchecked,
it is as clear as day that Japan will eventually
fall victim to its Far Eastern ambitions!
Stand firm against this national crisis!
Crush Russia's arrogance!
Yeah!
Defend our two thousand years of history!
If we do not fight now, Japan will perish!
Yeah!
Every man, take up arms!
January 12
Imperial Conference
As the situation with Russia
has become so critical,
we have no choice
but to take measures of self-defense.
Russia's army and navy are three times
the strength of Japan's current forces,
but our military has taken every precaution
and stands ready to mobilize at any time.
At this Imperial Conference today,
we wish to arrive at a final decision.
As Acting Prime Minister Yamamoto has just stated,
our nation has forty million people,
while Russia has four hundred million.
Their army prides itself on great strength
and is by no means an opponent to be taken lightly,
but our people have already steeled themselves
to face this national crisis.
We now humbly await Your Majesty's final judgment.
At this point, there seems to be no choice
but to seize the initiative and take action in self-defense.
If we continue to hesitate and merely declare the facts,
we will only allow Russia to further strengthen its war preparations
and aid it in achieving its ambitions.
As for our finances, even judging
from the experience of the Sino-Japanese War,
adjusting them as circumstances develop
will not be difficult.
How do the nations of the world
view the issue between Japan and Russia?
Aside from those countries
with special interests in Russia,
almost all resent Russia's aggression
and sympathize with Japan's predicament.
However, since Russia is the strongest land power in the world,
most believe Japan has no hope of standing against it.
Nevertheless, the United States and our ally Great Britain—
as the Finance Minister will soon explain—
have shown our country extremely active goodwill.
The war chest is estimated
at approximately 450 million yen.
Of this amount, foreign expenditures will total 150 million yen.
Of that sum, 50 million yen
will be paid using gold held by the Bank of Japan,
and we are confident the remaining 100 million
can be borrowed in Britain and America.
How far into the war does that estimate extend?
After consultation with the Army General Staff and the Naval Command,
we roughly estimate one year.
And if the war continues for two or three years?
We'll dispatch Bank of Japan
Vice Governor Takahashi Korekiyo
to the United States and Britain
to devote all efforts to securing foreign loans.
As Chairman Ito has already stated, if the entire nation
stakes both life and property and rises to the challenge,
I am convinced we can overcome this national crisis.
How are Yamamoto's and Katsura's illnesses?
Yes, the Prime Minister forced himself
to attend the gathering despite his illness,
but he had to withdraw as the pain became too much.
Is there truly no room left for negotiations with Russia?
Things remain as they were after Foreign Minister Komura and Minister Rosen's fourteenth meeting.
They proposed recognizing the region
north of Pyongyang as a neutral zone, did they not?
That proposal was effectively
a blade turned against Japan.
We notified them that it absolutely must be withdrawn,
but we have received no reply.
If we accept this humiliation without an answer,
the people will surely lose their trust in the government.
It would be wise to consider once more,
carefully, whether a path to a breakthrough remains.
Your Majesty's will is that we once again
seek resolution with Russia?
This decision will be the final one.
Consider well
how it will be received by the people,
and do everything possible to avoid war.
W-We humbly obey Your Majesty's will.
In that case, shall today's conference be adjourned here?
You have all done well.
Your Majesty!
Please wait a moment.
The elder statesmen have already decided upon war.
Your Majesty, please wait!
The meeting has been adjourned.
Get back to your seat!
Minister Yamamoto,
your actions violate an imperial command.
Is this Prime Minister Katsura's doing?
What? I won't tolerate any talk
of me disobeying the Emperor's will!
Dragging Prime Minister Katsura
into this is most improper.
Listen well.
The council of elder statesmen called for war this morning—you even said so!
Yet when I attempted to report that decision,
you blocked me in that chamber.
I can only conclude that your action
distorted His Majesty's will!
Please wait.
I myself never expected the words
His Majesty spoke today.
Did you truly hear what His Majesty
said at that moment?
Since this conference is the final and highest council,
one mistake could drag the nation into the suffering of war
and even threaten the very existence of Japan!
Though it be presumptuous, daresay
I understand His Majesty's feelings.
If there remains any possibility of avoiding war, His Majesty’s will was that we should open a path to a peaceful resolution.
In those few brief words,
I am convinced that is what he meant!
Inoue-san, in truth, I too was deeply moved
by His Majesty’s words today.
It seemed clear that war pains His Majesty
more than if his own body were cut.
I failed to grasp the depth of His Majesty’s feelings.
That was my failing.
I must offer my apology to His Majesty.
Though all the seas
in every direction are thought to be born of one kin,
why then do the winds and waves
rise and rage against one another?
Yet Russia failed to reply, ignoring Japan's proposal for compromise,
and instead crossed the Korean border with massive forces.
At Port Arthur, at the tip of the Liaodong Peninsula,
they had nearly completed an impregnable fortress.
The commander of that fortress
was one of Russia's foremost generals, Stessel.
JANUARY 12-22
JANUARY 23-31
FEBRUARY 1-10
Even by February 3rd, no reply had come from Russia.
Prime Minister Katsura, never have our people
thoroughly examined the Russian question and earnestly debated whether war is right or wrong.
By now every argument has been exhausted, and opposition to war
has all but disappeared—you must be aware of that!
The government, for its part, has already made concessions to Russia to the fullest extent,
yet still no answer has come from Russia.
It is clear that Russia's aim is to crush Japan.
Even while Japan's independence itself is in danger,
do you still intend to avoid war?
To avoid war as far as possible
is the deep wish of His Majesty.
His Majesty's intention?
Yes.
I believe His Majesty cannot bear to see tens of thousands of precious lives once again sacrificed on the wild plains of Manchuria.
The hour for the meeting has come. Excuse me.
Sir!
I am about to attend the national assembly,
but I would like to hear the military's position regarding Russia.
The question of whether we should go to war
is not something the military should debate.
Where's Yamamoto?
He's convening with Dr. Tomita
and others at the Cabinet.
National Assembly Hall
Youth Hall Auditorium
Dr. Tomita will report on the results of his meetings
with Prime Minister Katsura and the other ministers.
At this time of unprecedented national crisis,
it appears the government too is prepared for grave decisions.
However, as for His Majesty, if war breaks out,
your brothers will all become tragic sacrifices,
and it is said His Majesty is deeply troubled by this thought,
as well as by the suffering that war
will bring upon the lives of the people at home.
At that moment, Naval Minister Yamamoto
was preparing to attend an important meeting.
To transport the army's large forces to the continent,
we must divide the enemy's Far Eastern fleet
between Vladivostok and Port Arthur.
Moreover, their new fortress at Port Arthur is an excellent naval base overlooking the landing points of our transports.
Therefore, blockading Port Arthur is an absolute necessity.
We will scuttle some ships at the entrance to the harbor,
and if this blockade can be carried out completely,
the enemy will be trapped inside Port Arthur like rats in a sack,
losing its function as a base, leaving Vladivostok
as the enemy's only base in the Far East.
But is it really possible to sink several ships like that?
Even sinking a single vessel caused great confusion during the attempt to block Santiago Harbor in the Spanish-American War.
With the training our navy conducts every day,
it should not be impossible.
If the worst should come,
we will take off these coats, take off our shoes,
turn everything we have into shells
and rifles, and send them to the front!
And if even that is not enough,
we will stand behind the lines ourselves!
We must fight Russia's Far Eastern policy
with absolute determination!
No matter if the enemy outnumbers us many times over,
if we do not drive them back, Japan will become their slave forever.
The movements of each fleet
will proceed roughly as described.
And at tomorrow's Imperial Conference,
I believe all matters will be finally decided.
Your Excellency, any further patience
and restraint will only benefit Russia.
I beg you to firmly advocate the opening of war.
Have you forgotten a soldier's duty?
Do not interfere in politics.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
An emergency cabinet meeting has been called.
What has happened?
The fleets from Vladivostok and Port Arthur both left at five this morning in battle formation,
and their destination is unknown.
On February 4th, the Imperial Conference
that would decide the fate of the nation was convened.
Every possible issue between Japan and Russia
has been thoroughly examined,
and we now humbly await Your Majesty's decision.
Is there truly no way to avoid war?
At this stage, there is none.
We carefully considered Your Majesty's feelings
from at the previous Imperial Conference.
The people, down to the very last man, are crying that they will throw everything they have into the fight.
What is the opinion of the Diet?
Both houses have resolved in favor of war.
If the worst should happen,
we could not face our imperial ancestors
nor the forty million people of this nation.
Your Majesty.
The elder statesmen and the cabinet,
and the Diet representing the people as well,
have all concluded that war is unavoidable.
I approve the severing of diplomatic relations.
Japan-Russia diplomatic relations SEVERED!
Extra! Extra!
Extra! Extra! Extra!
D-Diplomatic relations!
Diplomatic relations severed!
To smite injustice in Heaven’s name,
Our soldiers—peerless in loyal courage—
Amid the people’s cheering cries
Now march forth from the land of their fathers and mothers
Sworn that if we do not win,
Alive we shall not return—
How valiant is the heart that swears it!
Some lie hidden in the grass,
Others plunge into the water;
Braving death a thousand times,
The scouts return from watching the foe
On their shoulders rests the safety of the whole army—
How heavy is that charge!
Where no road runs, they carve a road,
Thus, the elite units of the army, under the escort of the navy,
carried out their landing operations.
They smash the enemy’s railways;
While bullets fall like driving rain
Then marched north across the snowy wilderness,
into southern Manchuria.
They bathe in fire and build the bridges
That let our army cross—
What could compare with the merits of those engineers?
To smite injustice in Heaven’s name,
Our soldiers—peerless in loyal courage—
Amid the people’s cheering cries
now march forth from the land of their fathers and mothers
Sworn that if we do not win, alive we shall not return—
How valiant is the heart that swears it!
February 24—Port Arthur Harbor Blockade
Yes, two o'clock.
Commander!
You're already awake, sir?
The blockade squad should be
reaching Port Arthur about now.
Does Commander Hirose's report have a liason?
Yes, sir.
Full speed.
Full speed!
Enemy sighted.
Approaching the designated position. Full speed!
Fire! Full speed ahead!
Roger! Full speed ahead!
Drop anchor!
Prepare the charges!
Our first attempt to blockade Port Arthur's Harbor was confused by the enemy's sharp maneuvers,
and we were unable to achieve the expected results.
Previously, ships could pass the harbor in thirty minutes,
but after the blockade, it now takes two hours.
In wartime, a difference of an hour and a half
means enormous losses for the enemy.
Therefore we will dispatch a second blockade squad,
and I wished to discuss the selection of its members.
Chief of Staff. When you speak of selecting men
for the second attempt, do you mean to replace us?
No. Miraculously, you, the pride of the Navy, returned alive.
For now, you will return to your ship Asahi and rest.
This time I will select from among two thousand volunteers.
Lieutenant Colonels Yamada, Oe, and Inoue
will take part as well.
What are you saying, Chief of Staff?
If this measure is out of concern for my life,
I must protest.
Why are Lieutenant Colonel Arima
and Commander Hirose not to be assigned this noble duty?
Commander, Hirose didn't expect to return alive from the first blockade mission.
During the first blockade,
a transport ships rushed forward,
that, among other accidents, will serve as valuable lessons
for the second blockade.
Lieutenant Colonel Arima and Major Hirose posess such experience.
Before you came, I requested this,
but permission was not granted.
Commander.
Please assign us to the mission.
Major Hirose.
Of two thousand volunteers, if you commanded the second blockade unit too, what of the men?
Will the seventy sailors be the ones who served the first mission?
Do you not understand Admiral Togo's intentions?
Silence!
What do you mean, silence?
I'll have you arrested!
What?!
Wait, wait, wait.
You two are so close
you fight like brothers.
Chief of Staff, even so, I am the commanding officer.
I agree that the men should be newly selected,
but I object to replacing the commander.
Very well.
Lieutenant Colonel Arima and Major Hirose.
For the sake of the nation,
I ask you to carry out this mission once again.
Commanders Arima and Hirose,
I am counting on you.
We swear we will succeed.
Second blockade unit—banzai!
Banzai!
Shikido, are preparations complete?
We're entering the harbor.
Five hundred to the designated position.
Let's hope no torpedoes come before then.
Two hundred to go.
Prepare the charges!
Damn it, we've been hit by a torpedo!
All hands abandon ship!
Shikido! Shikido!
Shikido!
Is Shikido here?
Where is Shikido?
Commander, it's dangerous! Please evacuate!
Hurry, get to the lifeboat!
Shikido!
The blockade was a success!
You're a fine soldier!
Shikido!
Everyone, quickly get to the lifeboats!
Commander! It's dangerous!
Hurry, get on the boat!
Ah... Commander!
Thus, in the two attempts to blockade Port Arthur Harbor,
results exceeding all expectations were achieved.
Just like last time, the courageous and calm leadership of Naval Major Hirose Takeo,
and his deep concern for his men was truly the essence
of a warrior's spirit, a shining example for all commanders.
Of the major's remains, only fragments of flesh
and a sea chart stained with blood were recovered.
Send a messenger
at once to Hirose's family.
Yes, sir. Your gracious words
will surely raise the morale of the entire navy.
The greatness of the Yamato spirit of our land of Shikishima reveals itself in times of trial
Time passes quickly.
It's already been nearly two months
since Lieutenant Colonel Hirose fell in battle.
Commander.
What is it, Akiyama?
You look pale.
Yoshino and Kasuga have collided.
What? Collided?
Yes, sir.
According to Commander Dewa's report,
at 1:40 a.m. on May 15 the Third Squadron encountered heavy fog while engaged in the blockade of Port Arthur,
causing the Kasuga to strike the Yoshino's port side.
The Yoshino took on heavy water and sank.
This is truly a terrible matter.
Investigate the details and report
to Imperial Headquarters at once.
Commander, in our report to Imperial Headquarters,
we must submit a request to resign.
You think resigning from your post
will free you from responsibility?
Sir.
This is wartime.
Until disciplinary action is decided, I cannot resign.
Commander, a grave matter has occurred.
Is this about Yoshino and Kasuga colliding?
No, sir.
Hatsuse and Yashima have struck enemy mines and sunk.
Battleship Hatsuse has been lost?!
Yes, sir.
Hey! Are you certain there's no mistake?!
At this time we have lost four vessels—
battleships and cruisers—and it pains me deeply to report it.
It is war.
One might even say all the naval battles
until now have been fortunate for us.
You must not lose heart over such matters.
Yes, sir.
More importantly, what of the men?
Were they rescued?
Read the report.
Yes, sir.
All hands prepare to abandon ship!
Prepare to abandon ship!
The captain and executive officer
ordered the men to the boats first.
Captain Saeki, Executive Officer Hirose,
and Navigator Takeda
remained behind after sending the men to the boats,
and calmly offered their apologies to His Majesty,
shouting “Long live the Emperor! Long live the Empire!”
before sharing the fate of their ship.
When the rescue teams rushed to the scene,
the sailors thrown into the sea, without regard for their own danger,
first pleaded for their officers to be saved,
while the officers ordered them to save the men instead.
Thus the true spirit of Bushido...
before our very eyes...
blossomed beautifully!
It is most regrettable
that several ships were lost at once
and that so many of His Majesty's
loyal officers and men were sacrificed.
I am filled with deep shame.
Therefore I humbly request that I be relieved of my post.
I share the same feelings as the Chief of the Naval Staff.
Has Togo made the same request?
I do not believe he has!
Ito and Yamamoto may resign
and thus escape all responsibility,
but the Emperor has no such option.
Yes, sir.
Meanwhile, the army had already secured order in Korea
and opened a vast battlefront across the plains of southern Manchuria with an army of one hundred thousand.
1st Army
2nd Army
4th Army
General Kuroki's First Army,
Oku's Second Army, and Nozu's Fourth Army
pressed forward like a splitting bamboo toward Liaoyang,
the site of the enemy's headquarters.
Meanwhile, General Nogi,
commander of the Third Army,
visited the headquarters of Marshal Oyama, commander-in-chief of the Manchurian Army, alongside Chief of Staff Kodama,
United Manchurian Army Headquarters
to discuss operations against Port Arthur.
Attention!
Port Arthur is defended by thirty thousand Russian troops and six hundred guns,
with sixty heavily fortified artillery batteries confirmed.
Its scale is almost without equal in the world.
As for the timing of the general assault, unless the navy first restrains the Vladivostok fleet and the Port Arthur fleet to some extent,
our army's casualties will be extremely heavy.
The Eastern Railway from Mukden to Dalian has already been destroyed, so the enemy's supply line has been cut in half.
Sir.
General Stessel boasts that Port Arthur,
even without further supplies,
could hold out for two years against the Japanese army.
But during the Sino-Japanese War,
didn’t Port Arthur fall in two days?
The outer defensive positions of Port Arthur—
Mount Takushan and Xiaokushan—
should, I believe, be captured by August 10.
If we can capture them by then,
it will be a great success.
Could Port Arthur, riding this momentum,
also be taken by October?
However, Port Arthur is on an entirely different scale
from Nanshan or Flanders.
Speaking of Nanshan,
I heard the commander's son was killed there.
Reports say he distinguished himself.
To have found a place to die in battle—
Katsusuke met an honorable end.
The commander has not yet visited
the place where his son fell.
Staff Officer Iguchi, take him there at once.
No, that won't be necessary.
We will pass Nanshan on the way back.
Mountains and rivers, grasses and trees
I shall shape into song
Ten miles of wind carry the stench of the new battlefield
The warhorse advances in silence, no man speaking
Outside the walls of Kinzhou, I stand in the slanting evening sun
Nogi
Katsusuke's
grave
Extra! Extra! Read the news!
Extra! Extra!
With our victory at the Battle of the Yellow Sea,
it has been decided to begin the general assault on Port Arthur.
I hear that there are many noncombatants
inside the fortress at Port Arthur.
Yes.
It is said there are a considerable number
of women and children as well.
Inform them so that noncombatants
may be spared from the flames of war.
We humbly obey Your Majesty's will.
3rd Army Combined Headquarters
Staff Officer Yamaoka.
Yes, sir.
Convey His Majesty's wishes, and issue
repeated proclamations urging the evacuation of women,
children, and other noncombatants
from the Port Arthur fortress.
Yes, sir.
On August 16, Staff Officer Yamaoka
delivered a message along the entire Port Arthur front calling on the Russian army to surrender
and urging the evacuation of noncombatants,
but Stessel refused, and the Third Army resolved to proceed.
August 19
The first
general assault
on Port Arthur
Forward!
Halt!
Captain!
G-Go on, hurry forward!
Move out!
3rd Army Combined Headquarters
Your Excellency, the enemy's resistance is far stronger than expected.
This will not be easy.
Chief of Staff.
The enemy is using new weapons.
Those machine guns we had heard about?
Yes.
Because of them, our casualties are mounting terribly.
Launch night attacks, push cautiously,
and secure the present position.
Yes, sir.
Fire! Go!
Forward!
Move!
Your Excellency, the battle will be prolonged.
Perhaps you should take some rest.
A report has come in.
What is it?
The right wing of the First Horie assault force has been wiped out.
Wiped out?
Yes, sir.
Hey! Hang in there!
Yes...
Stay with us!
Bring it up quickly!
The Russians are using new weapons, like machine guns and electrified barbed wire,
so our army's attacks are meeting extreme difficulty.
The fact that these new weapons are being used for the first time
shows just how important the enemy considers this fortress.
A frontal assault seems entirely impossible.
At present we cannot even retrieve the wounded.
This is the greatest fortress in the world,
built with all the enemy's strength.
The operational plan must be revised from the ground up.
Revised from the ground up?
There is a vast difference between the weapons
our army uses and those of the Russians!
However...
Imperial Headquarters has given strict orders that,
by any means necessary,
Port Arthur must be taken
before the Baltic Fleet reaches the Sea of Japan.
Stay with us!
Don't die! Don't you die!
Hey, hold on!
After four days of fierce fighting,
the general assault ended in failure,
and our army suffered more than fifteen thousand casualties.
LIST OF WAR CASUALTIES
Whenever His Majesty's official duties allow him time,
he examines the casualty lists and asks many questions.
All of the fallen, even down to the ordinary soldiers?
Yes.
At times His Majesty remarks that in this battle many named Kato died, or in another battle many named Yamada,
and from this we can sense the depth of his concern.
Heat like this could harm His Majesty's health.
Yet he wears his winter uniform.
What? That's his winter uniform?
He has not permitted it to be changed.
While attending to affairs of state,
he wishes always to be as one with the soldiers.
Thanks you very much for waiting.
In this intense heat, seeing Your Majesty
continuing your labors fills us with awe.
This summer seems especially hot.
However, Your Majesty, today I bring news
that may make you forget the heat.
What is it?
Thanks to the intense efforts
of Takahashi Korekiyo in America,
following the success of the first
foreign loan of ten million pounds,
the second loan of twelve million pounds
has also been approved by Britain and America.
Is that so? That is excellent news.
Takahashi must have worked very hard indeed.
Yes.
We have also received word that the outlook
for further foreign loans is very promising.
Let the people know that Britain, America,
and the other nations have come to understand Japan's position.
Yes, sir.
Also, Your Majesty, about your poem, "Though all the seas in every direction are thought to be born of one kin,
why do the winds and waves
rise and rage against one another?"
When Takahashi showed its English translation to President Roosevelt of the United States,
the president was deeply moved
by the greatness and compassion of Your Majesty's heart.
Your Majesty.
Since the war began, Your Majesty has not rested a single day,
nor have you once visited
the imperial villas or summer residences.
In this intense heat, might it not be wise
to spend a short time at a cooler retreat?
Ito.
Yes, sir.
Do the soldiers at the front enjoy a summer retreat?
The warriors, how do they endure the heat, even longing for water, in such a place?
Don't drink it! Stop!
Don't drink that muddy water!
Hold yourself together.
Once Liaoyang falls, there will be water.
Come on, just a little longer!
Get it together!
Don't waste the lives of the infantry on the front line!
Our Tachibana Battalion will launch the general assault
on Liaoyang tomorrow at four in the morning.
The target of our regiment's attack, Shoushanpu Fort,
is expected to see the fiercest fighting next to Port Arthur!
I expect every single soldier
to charge into Shoushanpu Fort's trenches!
That is all.
At dawn on August 31,
the attack on Liaoyang was opened by the elite troops of the Third Division under Lieutenant General Oshima.
A report!
The assault on Shoushanpu Fort is extremely fierce.
The 34th Shizuoka Regiment has advanced within five hundred meters
and is now engaged in hand-to-hand combat.
Forward!
Charge!
Captain, sir!
All of you... follow Major Tachibana!
Yes, sir!
Is the nearby position secured?
Yes, the position is secured.
Good!
Captain, sir!
Don't worry about me. Just get out of here!
Okay!
Take command and lead them out!
Battalion commander, sir!
Please hand over command!
What are you saying?
Second Lieutenant Nakayoshi,
lead the unit across the line!
Yes, sir!
Battalion commander!
Please hold on!
Battalion commander, stay with us!
Corporal, what's the situation?
It has fallen.
Shoushanpu Fort has fallen!
So it's fallen...
Our regimental colors?
Second Lieutenant Nagayama has them!
Please use this and evacuate!
East... head east!
Battalion commander, sir!
Today is August 31st, isn't it?
Yes, sir!
The birthday of His Imperial Highness
the Crown Prince, whom we serve.
B-Banzai!
Battalion commander!
The day before yesterday, on His Imperial Highness
the Crown Prince's birthday, Shoushanpu Fort fell.
It seems the fall of Liaoyang is now close at hand.
I wish to commend the regiment that distinguished itself
in the capture of Shoushanpu Fort.
It was the 34th Shizuoka Regiment.
In that battle, Regimental Commander Colonel Sekiya,
Battalion Commander Major Tachibana, and nearly all the officers were killed, and the regiment was annihilated.
Tachibana?
That Major Tachibana who once served under Togo?
To remember his name
through all these years—remarkable.
Tachibana himself surely died fulfilled.
When Tachibana's right hand was shot by the enemy
and he switched his sword to his left,
he was struck again in the left hand by a bullet,
yet he fought on like a demon incarnate,
shouting that since today was the Crown Prince's birthday,
there must be no retreat,
until he was hit in the chest by another bullet.
Holding aloft the case of the regimental colors,
he offered congratulations for the Crown Prince's birthday,
and while calling out “Long live His Majesty,”
he met an honorable death in battle—that is the report.
Make sure Admiral Togo is informed of this in full.
The Russian Navy's greatest force, the Baltic Fleet, set out
to reclaim command of the seas in the Far East in a single stroke.
On October 19th it departed its home port
of Libau and headed for the Orient.
Even though the Baltic Fleet has now sailed,
not a single key fortress at Port Arthur has fallen.
It's been two months since the general assault began,
what in the world is our army doing?
Admiral Togo has gone to see
General Nogi about that very matter.
Best not to raise too much of a commotion.
The Baltic Fleet is expected to appear
near Japanese waters no later than late January.
If Hill 203 can be taken before then, the enemy ships inside Port Arthur harbor can be completely destroyed.
Even Chief of Staff Shimamura believes so,
so it is hardly surprising
that the government and the people are asking
what is being done after sacrificing twenty thousand men.
However, if Port Arthur does not fall by December,
the navy will have to lift the blockade of the harbor
in order to meet the Baltic Fleet,
as we simply do not have enough ships!
That would be a problem. If that happens, the dozen or so
enemy ships pinned deep inside Port Arthur harbor
would begin appearing in Japanese coastal waters and on the high seas, threatening our supply lines!
If it does not fall by December, then the navy will have to take that extremely risky gamble!
All the effort up to now would be wasted!
Wait.
No matter what sacrifices must be made,
even if we build mountains of the dead,
Port Arthur must fall within December
to secure the safety of the nation.
As for the people's resentment,
I alone, Nogi, will bear it.
Your Excellency.
It is the harsh fate of war, so many precious lives
must be sacrificed to break the enemy's defenses.
Still, a commander's heart must surely find that unbearable.
IMPREGNABLE
Yet no matter how we press or attack, the enemy will not budge,
and now the eyes of the entire world are fixed upon Port Arthur.
When I think of the sons, fathers, and brothers
who have died such heroic deaths at Port Arthur,
I realize how merciless war truly is.
But if we do not overcome it,
even greater tragedy will come to Japan.
When the Vladivostok squadron once escaped,
there was the disgraceful incident of the public
storming the homes of Admirals Kamimura and Uriu!
Now that the Baltic Fleet
is at last heading toward the East,
if voices among the people begin asking
what the army attacking Port Arthur is doing,
then that would mean we have fallen
into the enemy's plan to disturb our rear!
Therefore, I propose that today's public meeting
on the Port Arthur attack become a rally to encourage the Third Army,
so that the people, united as one,
may of their own will support the home front!
My son died in the fighting at Port Arthur!
But I hear that General Nogi's eldest son
has also been killed in action.
There is nothing more to say!
We, the bereaved families, insist that Port Arthur be taken!
Colonel Sugimoto has brought up a matter
regarding your son, Second Lieutenant Nogi.
Has Yasusuke done something wrong?
It was suggested that he step down from leading
a front-line platoon and be assigned to headquarters.
Since your eldest son, Lieutenant Katsusuke,
has already fallen.
That won't be necessary.
But Your Excellency!
Do not pull Yasusuke back from the front.
To do so would be unfair
to the many officers and men who have already died.
According to today's foreign dispatch,
the Baltic Fleet has passed the coasts of Spain and Portugal.
If the Baltic Fleet reaches Japanese waters before Port Arthur falls, it will be a grave situation.
The war situation would likely
turn completely against us.
Port Arthur must be taken as soon as possible.
However, Port Arthur is truly impregnable.
Admiral Togo met with Commander Nogi the other day,
but they have yet to reach a conclusion.
Does the army have no prospect
of taking Port Arthur within December?
Considering all the circumstances,
I fear even by the end of January it may prove impossible.
Before this desperate struggle,
perhaps General Nogi's command should be replaced?
Hm?
We in the navy want Port Arthur to fall as soon as possible,
even if it means replacing the commander.
If the general assaults up to now have been failures,
then replacing the commander may be unavoidable!
But that would be tantamount
to forcing General Nogi to commit suicide.
Sir, we cannot let sentiment guide us.
What was that?
The voices saying General Nogi
is unfit are growing very strong.
Even some within the army are saying the same.
This is a disgrace at a most critical time!
Sir, we earnestly beg for your decisive judgment!
Sir, since this matter is so grave,
perhaps you should report it directly to His Majesty.
Orderly, bring another meal.
Yes, sir.
No, never mind.
Father, I have one with me.
Oh? Is that so?
Yes.
His Majesty is at his meal just now,
but he says it does not matter.
Hm, but when he's done eating...
No, when His Majesty says it does not matter,
that means you can see him at once.
Father, do you always eat the same food as the soldiers?
Yes.
That lets me remain here at home like this.
What is it?
Since I do not know when I may see you again,
I would like to have a photograph taken with you today.
Your regiment is to move around the flank
of Hill 203, is it not?
Yes.
This was my brother's keepsake
after he fell in battle. I leave it in your care.
I see.
Your resolve is admirable.
I will tell your mother about it.
Father.
It must weigh on your heart
to have sent tens of thousands of men to their deaths...
Yasusuke!
Yes?
I myself wish to go to the front,
to die in battle alongside the officers and men.
We humbly ask for Your Majesty's judgment in this matter.
Nogi must not be replaced!
There is no one but Nogi who can take Port Arthur.
If you replace Nogi now,
the one who will rejoice most
is the enemy commander, Stessel.
Nogi will surely take Port Arthur before long!
Your Majesty's will shall be engraved upon my heart.
My shallow thinking is inexcusable.
It is enough that you understand.
I desire full cooperation between the army and navy.
Your Excellency, how did it go?
By His Majesty's will,
the dismissal of Commander Nogi has been withdrawn.
Once again I was humbled by His Majesty's greatness
and by the keen eye with which he judges men.
Aide-de-Camp.
Yes?
Anything special about today?
Nothing unusual, sir.
But when we happened to see His Majesty's meal...
Yes, he eats that every other day without fail.
That naval ration?
No matter how we beg him to stop, he will not permit it.
Transmit His Majesty's message to the Third Army.
However, in the present circumstances
the situation of the army and navy alike
does not permit delay in the capture of Port Arthur.
At this moment,
hearing that the Third Army
has been granted permission for a general assault,
I rejoice greatly and earnestly hope for its success.
On this third day of November, we have unexpectedly received this most gracious message,
and with this inspiration our officers and men shall unite as one
to carry out the general assault on Port Arthur
and thus answer His Majesty's will.
Facing toward the distant Imperial Palace,
we celebrate this auspicious day
and offer three cheers for His Majesty's long life.
Long live the Emperor!
Banzai!
I can hear the voices of the people.
Okazawa, I can hear the voices of the people.
Fly the Imperial banner.
Yes, sir.
Hill 203, a corner of the Port Arthur fortress, has already seen countless of our soldiers fall in bitter defeat.
The success or failure of this third general assault
will determine the fate of the nation.
Therefore, with the spirit of giving your life
for the country, carry out the attack.
We all swear to fulfill our duty.
Let us give three farewell cheers to our homeland.
The assault unit will, at 6:00 a.m.,
attempt to seize the flat ground at the flank of Hill 203.
The Nogi platoon, according to orders,
will crawl forward to the assault position by 5:00 a.m.
No firing is permitted until arrival.
Dawn has broken.
Nogi, you have not rested?
Has there been any report from the front?
Forward!
Advance in order!
Get them!
Hey, hang on!
Platoon leader!
Leave me and go!
Hang in there!
Platoon leader!
Advance!
Everyone... hold the line!
Go!
Banzai!
What's the matter?
Still no contact?
Yes! At 8:00 a.m., the Fujimoto Regiment
succeeded in capturing Hill 203.
They captured it?
But no supporting units followed,
so the details are still unclear.
Even reaching Hill 203 is a success.
Before long, we will surely have taken it.
Lieutenant, according to the report of a soldier
thrown down from the summit...
Brigade Commander Nakamura and many others
are confirmed to have died heroic deaths in battle!
Is that all the report says?
It also says Your Excellency's son met a glorious end.
Nogi...
Well done.
At least now I can offer some apology
to the bereaved families.
He died well.
Your Excellency,
Hill 203 will surely fall within the month.
I say this as a final tribute to your son.
Though steep stands Hill 203,
who says it cannot be climbed?
A man's glory
lies in overcoming hardship
Iron and blood cover the hill, its very shape transformed
All people look up to it together, Hill 203
Have you been to the Imperial Headquarters yet?
Ah, I have just come from there.
His Majesty went to Imperial Headquarters
about thirty minutes ago, didn't he?
Where has he gone now?
He is not even in his sitting room.
Do your best.
Yes, sir!
Big brother, it’s cold over there, so take care.
I’ll be fine.
Just take care of your health, okay?
You don’t have to worry about things at home.
Son, say goodbye to your father.
That's impossible, he doesn't know me yet.
Even if you say that...
Brother, eat plenty.
All right.
It's good!
You men are going out as well?
Yes, we deploy the day after tomorrow!
Have you said your farewells to your family?
Yes, I have.
How many are there in your family?
Only my mother.
What happened to your father?
He died ten years ago.
Have you said goodbye?
My mother is waiting at the camp gate.
Go to her at once, don't make her worry.
Yes, I won't worry her!
Go on, open it.
Yes, thank you.
Hurry along.
Yes, sir!
Then you take care too.
Watch your health!
Be careful.
You understand?
Take care!
Your Majesty.
Goodbye!
Stay well!
Take care.
Brother, please take care of yourself!
All of them
have gone out
to the army
The old father alone
tends the mountain fields
Okazawa.
Yes, sir.
We have to win this war,
by any means necessary!
Or the people won't forgive us!
Flesh burst like shattered bullets,
and bones turned to swords.
Now this Hill 203, watched by the entire world,
was about to be soaked in blood once more.
Raise the flag!
Raise the national flag!
Your Excellency, Hill 203 has just fallen.
It has?
Yes!
Good... now I can face them.
Banzai!
Extra! Extra! Port Arthur has fallen! Extra!
Hey! Port Arthur has fallen! Extra!
As we greet the New Year,
we respectfully celebrate the surrender of Port Arthur.
Your Majesty, who continued to place your trust in Nogi,
I feel the deepest shame before you.
I hear that Nogi has lost both of his sons.
Though setting aside personal feelings is the way of a soldier,
one can scarcely imagine the sorrow
in Commander Nogi's heart.
Even as enemies, the Russian soldiers
defending Port Arthur fought magnificently.
Just as Your Majesty has said,
war must be guided by justice,
only then is it a glorious sight.
Under the mistaken policies of their country,
the soldiers under General Stessel
fought most bravely until now.
At the surrender of Port Arthur,
see that Nogi is instructed to treat them
in a way that preserves a soldier's honor.
With Port Arthur surrendered, the enemy general Stessel meets with General Nogi
Where is the place of their meeting? At Shuishiying
In the yard stands a single jujube tree, its trunk scarred by many bullets
Among the shattered remains of humble houses, the two generals now meet face to face
This time, through the united support of the nation,
even Port Arthur, said to be impregnable, has at last fallen.
Our army now advances with irresistible force toward Mukden, the enemy's greatest stronghold,
and its fall also seems near at hand.
On behalf of the army, I wish to express our gratitude
for the devoted support of the people.
Thus Japan with 250,000 men and Russia with 370,000,
a combined total of 620,000 troops,
met in the greatest battle in history across a fifty-kilometer front,
fought upon the wild plains of Manchuria.
Run!
Part of General Nogi's army has pushed into the western outskirts of Mukden and is fighting street by street!
Understood.
Banzai!
At last, on March 10th of Meiji 38 (1905),
our army entered Mukden.
Meanwhile the Combined Fleet continued relentless training
day and night in preparation to destroy the Baltic Fleet,
and the practice target island was battered
until even its shape was altered.
In battle it will not be an island.
The target moves! We must improve our accuracy!
Yes, sir.
Tell them.
Yes, sir!
Admiral, a telegram from the Chief of the Naval General Staff.
Continue firing practice!
Range 8,200!
Range 8,200.
Most likely this concerns
our operations against the Baltic Fleet.
First, regarding the Baltic Fleet,
much of the information being reported is incorrect,
so unless great care is taken,
sound judgment may become impossible.
This is different from other matters—
His Majesty has ordered it.
I respectfully believe
that His Majesty must be deeply concerned.
Admiral, this is a critical moment.
Please return by the 21st.
Enemy fleet sighted off Taiwan.
Yesterday morning, off Izu Oshima, a merchant steamer
of a certain nation was ordered to halt by a Russian destroyer.
At dawn on May 17th, something resembling a Russian torpedo boat
passed a point five nautical miles off the Boso coast in Kyushu.
The Second Baltic Fleet joined the Third Fleet
at Cam Ranh Bay in French Indochina,
and since leaving on May 15th,
its whereabouts have been unknown.
Reports published after that are likely false rumors, mere speculation, or perhaps spy activity meant to confuse the operations of our fleet.
The question is whether they'll pass through Tsugaru or Tsushima,
and where the Combined Fleet should await them.
In order to respond quickly to the enemy
passing through Tsugaru or Tsushima,
it seems best to station the main fleet off the Noto Peninsula.
This is the opinion agreed upon
by the majority of the Imperial Headquarters staff.
And the opposing opinion?
That the Baltic Fleet will surely pass through Tsushima,
and therefore we should wait at Tsushima.
Admiral Togo has just arrived.
It has been some time.
Yes, sir.
Togo, are the Combined Fleet's
training and preparations complete?
We are continuing our exercises
so that there will be no oversight.
Commander, do you still believe they will come through Tsushima, or do you expect Tsugaru or Soya?
With more than 120 ships,
we are searching day and night for the enemy fleet.
Togo, do you believe we have a chance of victory?
I pledge that I shall bring you good news.
I rely on you.
Hey, was it wise to give such a definite answer?
The responsibility is enormous.
You must have great confidence.
Even if we were to report the detailed plan before His Majesty,
it would only trouble his mind unnecessarily.
But...
No. All sixty-four thousand men of the navy
are now burning with the resolve to give their lives in service.
They are determined to destroy the Baltic Fleet.
Not a single man expects to return alive.
If we come back alive, Japan will perish.
That is the conviction of every officer and sailor.
A final strategy conference was held
aboard the flagship Mikasa in Chinhae Bay.
If such a great fleet is heading for Tsushima,
it should already have been sighted by one of our patrol vessels.
Therefore the enemy fleet may well be planning to break through the Tsugaru Strait in the north in one stroke.
However, since we know the enemy has transports waiting at Shanghai, it seems likely they will soon come toward Tsushima.
But it is also certain that two of the enemy's light cruisers appeared south of Kyushu and then headed toward the Soya region.
Since we cannot determine the enemy's course, the safest plan
would be to gather our main fleet off the Noto Peninsula
and place patrol forces south of Korea and toward Tsugaru and Soya,
then rush there as soon as the enemy fleet is sighted.
Waiting at the Noto Peninsula would certainly allow us
to meet the enemy, but the decisive battle would be brief,
and after a single artillery engagement,
there is a real danger the enemy might escape to Vladivostok.
Therefore I cannot agree with that plan.
I believe we should wait here.
If we possess the Yamato spirit,
the enemy has the Slavic spirit.
They will neither flee nor hide,
but surely come to the Tsushima Strait ready for battle.
Therefore I believe it best to wait here as we are.
Especially since the Tsugaru and Soya Straits
are extremely difficult for a great fleet to pass through.
I cannot accept that opinion!
Rather than adopt a one-sided strategy, even with its faults, waiting at the Noto Peninsula seems the only course.
I was delayed by rough seas.
Good work coming.
Admiral Shimamura,
opinion is divided about the waiting position.
Please state your view.
Why, it's quite clear, isn't it?
If the enemy fleet has even one admiral who understands naval warfare,
they come through the Tsushima Strait.
Even the Russian fleet knows it cannot enter Vladivostok
without fighting a decisive battle.
Therefore the only course left to them is to force their way through the Tsushima Strait, the shortest route to Vladivostok.
Besides, the Tsushima Strait is nine times wider
than Tsugaru and four and a half times wider than Soya.
If fortune favors them, they might slip through without being discovered by the Japanese fleet—
and that would only be possible through Tsushima.
I believe we will surely meet them here in decisive battle.
Perhaps we should ask Admiral Togo for the final decision.
Admiral, please.
The entire fleet will remain here and wait.
May 23
Should we request an imperial order
to wait at the Noto Peninsula?
Please wait one more day before asking his majesty.
May 24
Any messages from the fleet?
None.
If the enemy gains control of the sea,
hundreds of thousands of our army in Manchuria will be isolated.
Shall we request an imperial order?
His Majesty has entrusted the matter to Admiral Togo.
This is the moment when Japan will either rise or fall.
Chief of the Naval Staff,
as we saw in the case of Commander Nogi,
His Majesty's judgment of men is truly keen.
We should entrust it to Togo.
May 25
Okazawa.
Yes, sir.
Has the Naval Ministry sent any word?
Not yet, sir. What shall we do
if it comes in the middle of the night?
It does not matter, inform me at once.
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty, I am certain good news will come.
May 26
May 27
On May 27, the auxiliary cruiser
Shinano Maru was patrolling near Jeju Island.
Fifteen degrees to port!
Appears to be ship lights!
Fifteen degrees to port?
Yes, sir.
What time?
2:45.
It appears to be a Russian hospital ship.
Any other vessels in sight?
I can see signal lights!
Oh! That is definitely a signal light.
The enemy fleet must be nearby.
Captain, I can see them!
It is the enemy fleet.
What time is it now?
4:45.
I'm going to report the sighting!
Good!
Attention!
All hands assemble on deck!
Signal from Shinano Maru: enemy fleet sighted.
Report says they are heading toward the Tsushima Strait!
All squadrons, sortie immediately.
All squadrons, put to sea at once.
I hope that all of you, working together in unity,
will bring this glorious battle to a successful end.
Prepare to sail!
Move out!
6:31 a.m., signal sent from the flagship Mikasa.
At 5:45 a.m. on May 27th, the cruiser Shinano Maru
reported sighting the enemy fleet at position 456.
The Combined Fleet has immediately sortied to destroy it.
Today the weather is fine, but the seas are high.
All ships ready for battle!
Good!
Admiral, the enemy fleet is in sight.
Enemy fleet sighted!
At 1:40 p.m., the Combined Fleet finally caught sight
of the entire Baltic Fleet, thirty-eight ships strong,
with the flagship Suvorov at its head.
Leading this great fleet to battle against ours
was Vice Admiral Rozhestvensky.
Captain, the Z flag has been raised.
Good, signal it to the ship!
The empire's fate depends on the result of this battle,
let every man do his utmost duty!
Admiral, the Z flag has been raised on the Mikasa.
Range twelve thousand!
Twelve thousand!
The enemy is close.
Twelve thousand.
Twelve thousand!
Eleven thousand!
Shells ready.
Ready, safety off!
Range ten thousand.
Range ten thousand!
Light the boilers.
Light the boilers!
Captain, how is the position?
As planned.
Range eight thousand five hundred!
Chief of Staff, if we continue like this, we will
pass them head-on and exchange only a short artillery duel.
Admiral, I advise parallel courses.
I recommend turning left 180 degrees.
Execute the turn.
Chief of Staff, a turn?
Left turn!
Hard to port!
Hard to port.
Lead ship to port!
Lead ship to port.
Range eight thousand.
Forward lead!
Forward lead.
Men, to the forward guns!
Forward lead!
Togo is out of his mind!
Crush the Japanese fleet!
But of course! Let's crush them!
To the aft guns!
Man the aft!
Mikasa is maneuvering to avoid being hit!
A successive turn?
Not bad—making a great turn right before the enemy!
That’s the only way to do it.
We knew the risk from the start.
All guns ready for action!
Range seven thousand!
Range six thousand six hundred!
Target set!
Range 6,600!
Range 6,600.
Sir, they're firing heavily now.
Commander, has the order to fire been given yet?!
No, wait, wait!
Range 8,000.
Range 8,000!
Still no order to attack?
The Mikasa's in danger.
Range 6,000.
Commence bombardment.
Begin firing!
Target: Suvorov! Fire!
Commence bombardment!
Sir, the Mikasa's taken two or three hits!
Is the commander-in-chief all right?
With nerves like his,
the shells themselves might run away!
The enemy flagship is on fire!
Once our formation's complete,
we'll finish them off!
Sir, please move inside the conning tower.
I'll command from right here.
Sir, direct hit on the Suvorov!
The enemy ship's burning! Keep firing!
Concentrated fire!
Good, fire!
We're not dead yet! Keep firing!
Hey! Are you all right?
I'm fine, sir!
Take over for him! Move!
Sir! Direct hit! Massive fires!
Good.
Shoot!
Reload it!
Hurry up!
We need to beat them quickly!
Return fire! Hurry!
Evacuate the section! Hurry, hurry!
Hey, did you see that?
The shells you fired hit their mark!
Did you see it?
Good!
Banzai! Banzai!
The Suvorov appears to be dead in the water.
We're hit on starboard!
Get the fire brigade here!
The fire on board is localized!
What's the position?
As planned!
Sir, a Russian ship is sinking!
Load it!
Signal transmitted from the flagship Mikasa,
7:00 p.m., May 27.
The Combined Fleet engaged the enemy fleet near Okinoshima,
and by 6:00 p.m. today has sunk at least four enemy battleships,
inflicting heavy damage on many others.
Our own losses are negligible. Furthermore, the destroyer squadrons and torpedo units
will launch night attacks
on the remaining enemy ships after sunset.
Surrounded on every side by the seas, our Shikishima, our Akitsushima
To guard against enemies beyond our shores, batteries on land, warships at sea
Even if our bodies sink beneath the waves, loyal men will never retreat
With hearts of ironclad resolve, how could such defenders ever be broken?
Sir, as the enemy flagship and the other warships sunk,
it's said their officers and men sang their national anthem and went down with their ships.
Magnificent.
Thus the battle unfolded over the 27th and 28th.
Of roughly 38 enemy vessels, 20 were sunk,
5 captured, and 8 destroyed,
and the Combined Fleet annihilated the Baltic Fleet.
Meanwhile our own losses
were no more than three torpedo boats.
In this great war, the enemy's strength
was not too different from our own.
Their officers and men also fought
with all their might for their homeland.
Yet the reason our Combined Fleet was able to secure victory
lies solely in the august virtue of His Majesty the Emperor,
and the officers and men, whether living or fallen in battle,
upon witnessing this result are overcome with emotion,
as though they have no words to express it.
Let the people of the nation hear this joyful news at once,
and convey words of appreciation to the Combined Fleet.
The Combined Fleet intercepted
the enemy in the Korea Strait,
and after days of fierce fighting, finally annihilated them,
achieving an unprecedented glory.
I rejoice that through the loyal bravery of our men,
we have answered the spirits of our imperial ancestors.
Through the united determination of the entire nation,
centered upon Emperor Meiji,
this great war ended in a miraculous victory,
and Japan, once merely an island nation,
suddenly stood among the great powers of the world.
Now we must unite the pride and strength of the Japanese people and contribute to the future development of peace in the world.
Banzai!
Since ancient times, in wars such as these, countless lives have been lost
The End