Hello.
The work you are about to see
is a true story about my entry
into the so-called yakuza world.
I was 14.
It's already been 35 years since then.
But still...
Still, I remember going down the back streets
and seeing all these burnt-out ruins from the air raids.
Well, today I drive a Mercedes and wear a 300,000-yen suit. In comparison,
that yakuza kid's position...
was vastly different, financially.
But even in our rather pitiable economic state, our blood was hot.
And I still believe I'll carry that feeling
of having a close bond with my friends and mentors throughout my life.
Please...
enjoy this little...
autobiography.
Thank you for your continued support for Shibuya Honky Tonk.
Tales from Abe George's Stormy Youth
Shibuya Honky Tonk
"First Fight Back Home" Chapter
Translation & Timing
...Perevodildo
Editing
...Paul Geromini
Typesetting
..Collectr
QC
.Uchuu
.Collectr
Encoding
.anonymous
ONISAKAE
BUILDING
Presented by
.Orphan Fansubs
It's been two years, huh?
Still, no place like Japan!
The actions of the Namiki Group
have caught my attention lately.
They've been up to something sleazy
ever since that recent mess
with the Toyo Films screenings.
After all, Shibuya was originally
Namiki's turf, and we took it by force.
That's why they're constantly looking
for an opportunity to make a comeback.
Don't take your eyes off them.
Yes, sir!
Wow, they've even renovated the main office!
I'm sure the Chief and Boss Kingo are doing well too.
Stop!
Are you some expendable assassin sent by Namiki?!
H-Hold up! I came to see the boss...
I'm Tanaka Kingo's underling.
It's true!
You ain't fooling anyone!
I'm not trying to!
I can read it on your face, motherfucker!
What's all that noise?
What are you making a fuss about?
S-Sir, there's this suspicious guy.
What?
Oh! Nao!
Boss, I'm back.
Hey, so you're here?
When did you return,
you weasel? Huh?
Look how big he's grown
in the time he's been away!
You little bastard!
I'm truly pleased to see that you're still full of energy, boss.
Takekuma, this is my underling Naoya,
just returned from England.
Huh... He's been abroad?
I alone in the Todo Group have
an underling with connections abroad.
Nao, these blockheads are Otake and Kumada, your new brothers in arms.
Hey! Nice to meet you!
Y-Yeah, i-it's mutual!
Chief, it's Nao! Nao's here!
Oh, so you're back, Nao?
It's been two years.
Yes. I'm back, Chief.
Hey, you've really grown sturdy, Nao.
How was London?
It was wonderful, sir.
I see.
I guess that makes you the first
yakuza to go abroad.
The yakuza of the future will have
to study foreign countries more intensely
in order to do business with foreign yakuza on an equal basis.
What have you been
studying there, Nao?
Right... W-Well, lots of stuff...
Nao, you've not shamed the name of our family in that London prison, have you?
Boss, I've been working really hard.
I've gotten better at chess and poker and had plenty of practice with London girls.
Wh-What do you mean?
Nao, what do London girls taste like?
Much like their food: pretty bland.
In the end, our own food and women are the best!
I-I see.
You're talking just like a grown-up now, Nao.
Nao! You're talking to the group head.
Don't get cocky, you idiot.
Right.
Oh, by the way!
Sir, this is Churchill's favorite brand of cigars.
Oh, Churchill's?
You look mighty dignified with it, sir!
Far more than Churchill!
Really?
It's the real thing.
And for Boss Kingo, a brand dating back to Shakespeare's era.
Scotch only drunk
by the British royal family.
Th-That awesome Scotch is for me?
N-Nao, you're such a wonderful fella...
You flatter me.
Actually, I got both the cigars and
the Scotch cheap at London Airport.
Chief, Nao brought this for me!
Yeah.
Let's have a toast to celebrate Nao's return.
Take, bring the glasses.
Roger!
We raise these to celebrate Naoya's safe return and the start of his new life!
Cheers!
Thank you very much!
As expected of the British royal family's exclusive Scotch, it has a very rich flavor.
No doubt about it, this is the real thing!
The taste flows so nicely!
No! You're not getting any!
Naoya brought it all the way from London for me!
It's a valuable Scotch that only
the British royal family can drink.
I'll drink it sparingly for the rest of my life.
That's ridiculous!
That's right.
Show him that thing.
Okay.
Nao, take this. Your return gift.
What is it?
Unwrap it to see.
Oh! Is this the real thing?
'Course it is!
From today on, you're also a proud member of the Todo Group.
You're supposed to carry iron with you, at least.
Yes, sir! This thing is so heavy!
Take good care of it.
It's the 1911 model, used by the Feds.
A quality item, produced by Remington.
Yes, sir. I won't let it go to waste.
Imbecile! Think what you're pointing at!
It's loaded, you dimwit!
Something's brewing
in Shibuya these days.
You take care too, Nao.
Yes, sir!
Listen, Nao, you can't be so carefree anymore!
That thoughtlessness worries me!
We're counting on you to do some good with that luck of yours.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
Wh-What's wrong?
Well, you see, it slipped through.
Come on, Yoko!
Pick up the phone!
I already went to greet my bosses today,
so I was really looking forward to a love affair with you.
But she isn't there either, which means...
I guess we can't do it tonight.
Behave, Abe Jr.
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
Wow, p-perfect texture!
Japan-made for life!
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
HOTEL
AKAGAI
BLOOD CLAM
Did it...
You're amazing.
Do you know how many times I came?
How many?
I've lost count.
Well then...
Oh? You're leaving already?
Actually, since it's your first time tonight, it's only 800 yen for you.
What's this?
A Leica M3, a state-of-the-art device.
What does that mean?
You don't have any money?!
Are you kidding me?!
Think I'll fall for this camera?
It's a Leica, you hear? A Leica M3.
I'll even add this as a bonus.
"Leica" my ass!
We ain't gonna stand
for you making fun of us.
Wow, you're really good
at this whole tough guy act!
I ain't kidding, you hear?
Don't you look down on me!
Would you look at that! My body's so much more relaxed now, thanks to you!
You know, if you take that camera
to a pawnshop, it'll fetch 5,000 yen.
I can't accept something so expensive.
For me, 800 yen is enough.
You see,
I only have two things worth money with me, the camera and this—
AOYAGI
INN
B-Boss, let me see it too.
No, not yet!
In the end, a night without Yoko is a night wasted.
The fuck you're sidling for?
Walk behind us, you dumbass!
Oh, you're right.
It's all the way in!
Ah, I feel much lighter.
Damn it all, where did Yoko go?
Here you are, Nao. Finally.
Your boss was looking for you.
It seems he has a gift for you.
Huh? That stingy boss... has a gift?
Tanaka Family
Good evening!
Oh, Nao-chan!
Ma'am, I've returned today.
Welcome back. Oh my, you've grown so big. Come on up.
Kingo was waiting for you,
but he just went out on group business.
Ma'am, thank you again for looking after me.
No problem.
Wow, you've really grown into
a full-fledged man since I last saw you.
Come on, let's celebrate with a feast.
Ooh! Looks delicious!
Kingo was really impressed by that Shakespearean Scotch you brought him.
Look.
That's why he decided
to treat you to a dinner.
You don't see Kingo splurging on sea bream very often!
Come on, eat now.
Yes, thanks for the meal.
I'll go warm up the soup.
Why'd I ever think the Boss could change?
Nothing stimulates
the appetite like alcohol.
Huh? Crap!
Boss has only been drinking tiny sips,
and I've drunk this much in one go!
But I could always add some of this.
So, do you still like Japanese food?
Yeah, like... It's really good.
Your home cooking is second to none!
Oh my, you've gotten better at flattery as well.
But you must also go home
and let your mom know you're okay.
Yes, I'll go home tomorrow.
I just remembered. Kingo wanted to give you something.
Wow, it's a bike!
Does it run?
Don't be silly.
Kingo took this bike when one of
the family's clients couldn't pay.
Of course it runs.
Nice!
Looking good!
Yes, you're through to the Tanaka family.
Yes, Nao-chan is here.
Nao-chan, it's for you.
Coming! Who is it?
A girl.
Naoya is listening.
Nao-chan, welcome back.
Oh! Yoko! I've been looking for you!
We passed each other. I came to pick you up at the Yokohama port.
I see, so that's what happened?
Where are you now?
Yoko! I missed you!
Me too, Nao-chan.
What do you think? Have I changed?
You're a lot sexier now.
Ah, actually, I brought you a souvenir:
the same perfume that Marilyn Monroe uses, Chanel No. 5.
Here.
D-Does she know I actually bought it cheap on the outskirts of London?
This is too amazing for me to have.
Thank you, Nao-chan.
I'll put it on right away.
Wow, this sexy aroma...
I-I can't stand it, Yoko!
You're still the same as before.
Huh? You mean to say
I'm not developing at all?
Silly, you know that's not what I meant.
I wonder if our boss thinks the same.
Though I'm an official member now,
I'm still just a high-schooler, he said.
But he did promise to make me the Todo Group's legal advisor in the future.
Well, despite his unique approach,
I don't think he has an eye for people.
That can't be true.
I'm sure he's interested in keeping you.
He saw the potential in you.
Maybe you're right.
Boss Kingo says I talk too much,
so I don't fit the image of a yakuza.
Nao-chan...
I saw a hurt woman right in front of me
But I couldn't even bring myself to hug her
What would she think of a man
Such as me now?
Ah! Nao-chan!
Yoko...
"More, more, love me more tenderly"
"Love me tenderly," she says
Ah! Nao-chan, you're amazing!
Y-You too, Yoko...
You surprised me. I guess you've had a lot of practice in London.
You learn a lot of things by the time you turn 17.
Nao-chan, you don't want to listen to me at all.
Huh? Is something wrong, Yoko?
No, it's nothing.
Sign: Waitress Wanted
Nao, we've got work to do.
Come to the office.
Odawara is taking command.
This is your chance to prove yourself.
Ugh, I'm late...
It sure is cold tonight.
TRUTH
Oh, here he is.
I've arrived to assist you, Boss Odawara.
Good. Take, where's Gyuji?
Should be here soon.
Sup! Sorry I'm late.
What's the matter?
You guys know each other?
Yeah, sort of...
Good. That'll save us some trouble when we go out there together.
Where to, Boss Odawara?
A reclaimed island in Tokyo Bay.
Daimon Group opened a gambling den for the fishermen.
Because of that reclaimed plot, all the Chiba craftsmen are broke these days!
Sounds fun! So we're holding up a gambling den?
These hillbilly yakuza from Chiba are a shame to all of us!
I'm Abe Naoya.
Gyu-chan, let's be friends!
Yeah, I had no idea you were from our Todo Group.
Is there really a gambling den in a place like this?
Yeah, there is.
Whoa!
I've seen it with my own eyes.
Let's try the respectful approach, people.
Hey, ya got any more seats left?
Pardon the intrusion!
Oh, it really is here!
Who might you be?
The games held tonight are exclusive to our local patrons.
We just wanna play.
We're Shibuya's Todo Group.
Are you sure we can let them in?
Just hearing "Shibuya's Todo Group" makes them quake in their boots.
What's wrong, guys? Is this due
to the reputation of our major group?
All right, would someone else like to bet?
Couldja lend me some cash?
Me too.
Listen, you Shibuya bastards.
First you show up uninvited, now this!
Yeah, you see, I came in a hurry, so I forgot to bring my wallet.
We can do it the hard way.
Make a call to Shibuya and have them bring over our entire treasury.
Please enjoy your stay.
Much obliged!
Now, any more bets, anyone?
Bet, 5 key, bet, 3 ta.
The result is 23 shi.
The house wins it all.
Oh man, I'm out of luck today.
Damn right. Mr. Croupier,
I'm gonna need another loan.
Me too!
Ugh... Dammit. I lost again.
I was just so close this time!
Hey, wontcha lend me just a bit more?
Yeah, I just need a few pennies.
All right, it's almost time...
If we bail you out again,
I'm not sure you'll be able to pay it off.
Tsk. They've been asking
for loans this whole time,
only to stash the money in their breast pockets.
Hey! Didja just say something?
Listen up!
If ya ain't lending me any,
then it's a bust!
I'll have to pay with my body,
you hear?!
How much for these legs?
They're massive! If one isn't enough,
we can always go for a set of two!
Say it! 10,000, 100,000, whatever.
Actually, what if I threw in my balls too?
So? Whadja say?
Please be reasonable.
You heard that, Gyuji?
It seems your body was valued
at a much lower price.
Like hell!
If it's still not enough, I'll throw in my liver, heart, and brain too!
Just cut 'em out carefully,
or else... You got that?
Dear Shibuya customer, we don't want any material evidence left behind.
What was that? Didja call me tough?
Well, for our Shibuya guests,
what if we offer you this, and you stop bothering our other customers for today?
30,000?! Are you out
of your fucking mind?
Even a university professor makes more these days!
20,000 yen a month in Waseda,
22,000 at Keio!
Tell me, Gyuji, is that a fair price for your body?
Don't be stupid!
It's 30,000 just to carry this body
here from Shibuya!
Fine. If you wanna fuck us over
with 30,000, pay with your own body!
I'll cut it into small pieces and scatter it
on the street for stray dogs to eat!
Dear Shibuya customers!
We're not amused by your blatantly provocative escapades!
What the fuck!
Did you call it an escapade?
How dare you put a price tag
on a man's body, you coward?!
That's not an appropriate cut for the house!
Idiot!
What the fuck, you assholes!
Got a problem with us?
Open up!
'Preciate it!
Naoya, watch out!
Nicely done, Naoya!
You drove them away for good.
Who cares if it's Todo?!
Those shitheads think they can mess
with the Daimon's business in Chiba!
They're here!
Reinforcements from Daimon!
Oh, that's was to be expected.
Is the enemy fifteen or thirty?
Closer to 50!
What?!
They're not that scary!
Let's do it, Boss!
Let's show 'em Shibuya's guts!
It's is my first battle, after all!
All right... You got your irons with you, people?
It'll be fine.
Naoya's got his toy with him.
Huh? Did you guys come here empty-handed?
No way!
Oh? This is bad!
They got us surrounded!
Shit, this is becoming a bother.
I love trouble.
Gyu-chan, have you completely lost touch with reality?
You think so?
Take, where's the Jeep?
I parked it in the back.
Good. Nao, how many bullets do you have?
I shot once, so there are four more inside.
Ten more in the spare clip.
All right, we'll have to break right through them.
Yahoo! Leave the rugby to me, Boss!
It's not a game!
Don't you guys understand?
Yahoo!
So long, Chiba's hillbilly yakuza!
Don't let them get away!
Kill them!
Oh really? Did you forget we're major yakuza from Shibuya?
You don't even have guns, you second-rate yakuza!
Do it, do it, lucky boy
Nao! Don't be reckless with bullets.
Our life depends on those!
Tsk. Stingy as ever.
Do it, do it, lucky boy
Shit... Our Jeep could get away if we were driving on dirt.
No wonder, with the power-to-weight ratio being clearly on their side.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Well, we can't just drop you off here, can we?
Y-You cretin, want them to kill me?!
Boss, this is bad. We're out of gas!
Wh-What?
Oh, come on!
Do it, do it, lucky boy
Oh no!
Shit...
Goddammit! It's a dead end!
We got them cornered.
Run like the dirty rats you are!
Remember, the Todo Group can suck my dick!
We'll slice you up and feed you to the sea turtles in Tokyo Bay!
Boss, we can't find them anywhere.
Tsk. You can't be serious.
Is Todo a group of skulkers?!
Motherfucker! Don't you look down on Shibuya's Todo Group!
I'll fucking kill you all!
On the roof!
They're on the roof!
Come if you dare! I'll make you eat all the roof tiles before you can get me!
Nao!
Yes?
Try to blast that fire extinguisher!
Can you do it?
I'll try!
C-Cretin! Not that kind of blast!
Did it! Maybe I should enlist in our Olympic team, huh?
Right, Boss?
Shut up! This is a critical moment, Nao!
Chiba's hillbillies are going to start climbing.
There are dozens of them!
Your bullets are not nearly enough!
Why did I allow myself to be blinded by a mere couple hundred dollars!
They said that as an apprentice yakuza, I'd already be
lazing in a warm futon with a hot girl by now.
I'm so unlucky!
Don't lose heart! You call yourself a member of Shibuya's Todo Group, huh?!
Hey! Stop right there! Right there!
Huh? I thought it's the prefectural police, but it's just a guy from a police box.
Hey, aren't you a police box officer?
What are you doing here all by yourself?
Didn't it ever occur to you that staying out of it would've been smarter?
E-Enforcing public order and the safety of the people are also among my duties...
I'll arrest you for violating public order!
Come and try to do it!
I'm Hamako from Chiba!
Shit... Nao, try to scare him away.
Got it!
Bastards.
Oh?
Shucks, I hit a drum of gasoline.
Well, whatever.
Oh! The prefectural police
are finally here.
You're late, "civil servants"!
Nao, bury that iron in the ground when the cops get here.
Huh? Why?
Illegal possession of a firearm can land you six months to a year behind bars.
Right, but this is a talisman the Group Head gave me.
Besides, it's the Remington 1911 model.
It's worth more than money!
Are you really an idiot?
Let go!
Resisting an officer?!
That's a nice view!
Don't be stupid!
We need to hide!
You won't enjoy being behind bars
with the Chiba hillbillies, you cretin!
Boss!
Quiet!
You think Shibuya's Todo Group elite
would get jailed over such a petty gig?
Remember, now's the time for you all to man up!
Right...
Wh-What are you doing?!
We're sorry. All this sudden tension and pursuit, Boss...
Cut the bullshit!
Don't you look down on me!
The local residents reported hearing several gunshots!
So?
Sir, we're not to blame for that.
It was Shibuya's Todo Group who fired those.
They also took away all the money our patrons have donated.
This is robbery all the way through, sir.
Don't try to fool me!
You broke the law first by opening
a gambling den here, you blockheads!
You had such a simple job, you idiots.
Yet you let some Shibuya outsiders come and fuck it all up!
Try to think some more about
the people of your prefecture!
Don't forget the pride of Sakura Sogoro, you dunce.
N-Nao-chan, lend me
the gun for a moment.
I can't stand leaving it unfinished like that.
I'll break through the floor now
and try to run away in the confusion.
Don't be stupid, Gyuji!
If they mistake it for an attempt
on the officer's life, they'll shoot you!
But I'm already at my limit!
Gyu-chan, it stinks!
I'm telling ya,
Naoya is my friend for life!
Gyu-chan, I'm glad to hear that.
I'm sure we'll do a lot of good for the Todo Group together.
'Course we will, Nao.
Look at this. Our age starts now!
My 1911, when did you...
Gyu-chan, it seems we'll get along really well.
Yeah. I like you, Nao.
Yeah.
You're the best, Nao!
Tsk. You fools. The Todo Group is clearly barreling toward its own destruction.
Cheers to the Todo Group!
Ouch...
Don't be sad
You were devastated
by today's happenings in the city
But brooding over it won't accomplish anything
You'll take it back tenfold tomorrow,
so don't be sad
If you can forgive, if only you can forgive
So that I can give you a special smile tomorrow
When we pass each other on the street
And then you realize I didn't intend to betray you
This town runs
At the drive-in, I heard the stories of the mailmen
I will continue to run today
For my loved ones whom I cannot replace
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad
Don't be sad
Don't let you down