Hey, hello.
Coming to Shibuya always brings back memories.
Nowadays, the city of Shibuya has become shiny and modern,
compared to when
I was playing there.
I look at the people walking around.
They all look so classy and cool.
The honest working people and the thugs alike.
It looks like a foreign country now,
compared to back then.
I think... the whole city has changed a lot.
The times have changed.
Perhaps calling it a symbol of human progress would be arrogant.
Well, that's how it was.
And I...
They were about to gang-rape my Yoko, and to save her,
I stabbed one of the Tensei's thugs.
I got apprehended by the police.
But I was still a minor,
and it was clearly those guys' fault.
And well, at the time, my old man hadn't completely given up on me yet.
I ran away to England.
And although I would've also liked to ascribe that to my luck,
our boss hated the whole affair too,
so he didn't demand any bodily punishments.
Thanks to that, we, the henchmen,
got to keep our fingers.
Right, I was really lucky it ended up the way it did.
And that's how I became a writer
and started making a living from it.
I feel that I'm indebted to many different people for that.
If you think about it,
my luck came from the kindness of those who extended their blessings to me.
It shows that putting on a macho act alone doesn't make you strong.
You're not a true man
unless you're kind too.
But if you're kind and nothing else,
people will look down on you.
I'm going after various literary awards now...
like I'm in a constant race against Frederick Forsyth.
Well, in short...
Dare to dream big.
P.S. We need to make women's skirts shorter.
Let's settle on this.
Please enjoy the show, everyone.
"More, more, love me more tenderly"
Tales from Abe George's Stormy Youth
Shibuya Honky Tonk
"Love me tenderly,"
Tales from Abe George's Stormy Youth
Shibuya Honky Tonk
she says
Tales from Abe George's Stormy Youth
Shibuya Honky Tonk
Translation & Timing
...x...Perevodildo
I wish I could go see you
But you're already too far away
On the receiving end
Editing
...x...Paul Geromini
Of my last phone call
The sound of coins dropping
Typesetting
...x...Collectr
And the bell announcing the train's departure
I felt that if I chased after you
QC
...x...Uchuu
I would become even sadder
I'm in the busy hall
QC
...x...Collectr
But you're no longer here
That love song I wrote for you
Encoding
...x...anonymous
I can sing it to you now
Presented by
...x...Orphan Fansubs
I remember the sound of coins falling
And the noise of the hustle and bustle
I thought I could sing softly for you
In the spotlight
I saw a hurt woman right in front of me
But I couldn't even bring myself to hug her
What would she think of a man
Such as me now?
"More, more, love me more tenderly"
"Love me tenderly," she says
"Digression: Studying in the UK" Chapter
How are you, Boss?
I'm studying hard every day.
I really leave no stone unturned.
I found a part-time job, so I spent
my first paycheck on a gift for you.
The rest is written in English.
That guy Naoya really is learning new stuff.
Boss, we gotta make Naoya an official member next time he's in Japan.
Right... I'll think it over.
Bye.
That's sure to make Naoya ecstatic when he gets back.
Oh, Yoko!
Naoya is studying in London?
Don't make me laugh!
No... We can't!
Someone might come here...
Don't worry. They'll never notice us.
B-But...
We'll be in trouble if I get pregnant!
Relax! Just because it's possible
doesn't mean it'll happen every time!
What?
Check this out. The Yamato Spirit stands strong!
Yamato Spirit, it's big!
Wait till you find out how hard it is!
Don't worry, Susan.
If it starts to twitch, take it out.
Okay, okay.
No! It hurts, Nao!
Stop!
Naoya!
Shh. Why are there
so many people here?
Shoot! There was another class
scheduled for this room!
We need to run, Naoya.
It's too late now, and besides.
Look, I-I can't take it out...
Now then, boys and girls.
Turn to page 111.
How have you been since I left, Boss?
Even in faraway London,
I've never forgotten about you.
If you meet Yoko,
please tell her that
I'm living in strict discipline,
devoting my days to sports and studying.
As a proud member of the Todo Group,
I try to teach the Japanese mindset and traditional culture
to my peers in London, but they aren't making it any easier for me.
Hey!
Naoya, we weren't done yesterday. Let's play a game of See-Low.
You guys never learn!
One more try, Naoya!
All right! Here goes nothing!
Tongari!
Whoa! You lose!
Right, come to daddy!
Come on, keep the game going!
That's it! I win double my bet!
Wow! That combination means my bet is tripled!
Yes! Is something wrong?
Are you out of your betting money already?
The people of the victorious nations
are being humiliated by the defeated!
It almost feels like they're presenting me with offerings, as if it's an ancient king's
coronation ceremony.
What is it?
Lights out is long past.
What are you doing, Naoya Abe?
Ugh, dammit!
Naoya Abe, ever since you arrived at our school,
the dormitory's public morals have been in disarray.
This is beyond deplorable.
And it's not just the boys' dormitory.
Rumor says you've been seen inside the girls' dormitory as well.
Goddammit, someone snitched on me?
Our school is a traditional college.
If you keep violating
the school's rules,
we'll have to respond
with appropriate measures.
Are you listening, Naoya?
Tsk. "Measures"?
You really think that'll scare me?
I'm from Shibuya's Todo Group!
What's going on?
Putting up with it for half a year was quite an achievement for someone like me.
Feeling homesick, Naoya?
'C-Course not!
Go back to your room, then.
You'll catch a cold if you stay here for much longer.
Susan!
N-No! Not here!
No, Naoya!
It'll be fine. Just let me do it.
Damn it all.
What are you doing, Naoya?
This is the teachers' dormitory.
Shh.
Didn't you notice that security at the girls' dormitory is very tight these days?
Y-Yes. Now that you mention it, tonight...
Except it won't be just tonight.
It'll be like that as long as I'm here.
This is the best place.
No one would even suspect that we're doing it here.
Doing it? What?
No, Naoya!
Hurry up! They'll see you
if you keep hesitating.
Who's there?
Meow...
What, just a cat?
Naoya!
Doing it here... Are you serious?
Why are you even asking?
You're obviously aroused,
and your whole body is asking for it!
These babies are also perky and galvanized!
Galvanized? What?
You're a pretty lecherous girl yourself.
Lecherous? What, Naoya?
Don't worry about it.
Better show me what you foreign girls are like down there!
Wow! You're blonde down here too, just as I thought!
But the shape seems to be the same.
Wow, it glows yellow! So pretty!
No...
I-I like it too...
That's strange. Noises in
the shower room at this hour.
Unbelievable... Did someone forget to turn off the tap again?
Excuse me!
Naoya Abe?
As of today, consider yourself expelled from this school!
Pack your bags this instant, and get out of my sight!
Ah, I came.
Feels refreshing.
This is London unvarnished.
But I also thought that getting sent back to Japan
after just six months was kind of lame.
And my guarantor, the chief of the London branch
of a daily newspaper, felt the same way.
Answer me honestly, kid.
Do you really like girls that much?
Yes. I love them.
Don't you, department chief?
I do too, of course.
That's a relief to hear!
Thing is, you're clearly
taking it too far.
This is a country of gentlemen.
Yes, sir! I apologize for all
the problems I've caused you.
No wonder your old man is so worried about you.
You're a fine, honest young man, Naoya-kun.
But just because you're a minor,
you shouldn't think
that you can do whatever you want in the world.
Th-That was never really my intention.
Good. If you really understand that,
I'll give you a job.
R-Really? H-Here in London?
Yeah. Your father entrusted you to me,
so I can't let you go back
after six months just because of some trouble at college.
However, that job won't involve any girls.
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
Our photographer asked for an assistant.
It's a demanding job, so hard
that you won't even have time
to eat every day, let alone mess around with girls.
Thanks for having me!
I'll run all over London until my legs give out!
H-Hurry up, Nao-chan.
Hey!
Can't get through here.
Nao-chan, get down on all fours.
Okay!
I can't see the parade.
With his height, Nao-chan can do it on his own.
That's true.
He's getting the hang of it.
What?
Hillary's British team was the first to reach the summit of Everest?
Great! It's the big scoop we needed!
Hey, Nao-chan, hang on!
Unsurprising.
He's been on such a busy schedule lately
that he's barely been back to his place.
I'll be fine...
In four months, all of London will attend
Queen Elizabeth's coronation.
No, the whole world will be watching England and Great Britain closely.
Especially after Hillary's team made headlines by conquering Everest.
Department chief, by then,
we should make Nao-chan a full-fledged photographer, not an assistant.
He speaks good English and is tall.
He can take photos
from behind the crowd.
And he's shrewd too!
Yeah... I mean, we are extremely short-handed here,
but if we do that,
Naoya-kun might ruin his health.
Thank you!
I can develop the film at my apartment,
so please let me do it.
Hey, you were listening, Nao-chan?
Of course!
All right! On the day of the ceremony,
we'll let you try your hand at it.
Nice!
Come in!
N-Nao-chan!
Aoki-san, is that you...
Hey, what's the matter?
Stay strong!
I'm fine. I just spent all night developing the film.
Hey, it's evening already!
You're so passionate about it,
you even turned your wardrobe into a developing room.
And I still can't catch up.
I know you think you're tough as nails,
but sleep deprivation is very dangerous.
Oh, right, I've got just what you need.
Use it to wipe away fatigue and boost your strength.
Scotch?
That's right.
Only resort to it when your schedule gets too tight.
Also, you're still a minor,
so let's keep it a secret from the chief.
So, can you feel it sweeping away your sleepiness?
Oh, and I have one more present for you.
Wow, isn't that the Leica M3?
Oh, by the way, you're going to a military base to shoot the air show tomorrow.
So I was wondering
if I could ask for a favor...
Not just the air show, I want you to take
as many photos as you can of what the inside of the base is like.
I smell a scoop.
Scoop?
Leica's new model is the real deal.
It even has a built-in flash!
It's done!
Oh, finally.
This stuff's the best!
Ah, there it is!
Well done, Nao-chan.
This is probably their newest cutting-edge model.
Is this supposed to be a scoop?
Yes, more than a scoop. We now have pictures
of that complex's equipment and new machines.
We can sell it!
Keeping it secret from the chief?
Of course.
Why don't you think of it
as a part-time job?
So you sent me there to spy?
Well, when you're taking all these photos, you just look to them
like another one of those plane maniac kids.
This much?
It's just an advance. If you succeed, the actual pay is three times that.
Just as I thought, sneaking into this place
won't be as easy as the air show.
But I'm Naoya of Shibuya's Todo Group, aren't I?
To become a true yakuza,
I have to pull off stunts like this.
I don't have the time to play with you!
The girl just wouldn't let me get out of bed!
What'll I do with you?
I actually prepared it for the guard dogs!
Ugh, not again!
That's all I have!
C'mere.
Crap!
I think he said Hangar 6...
I wish Boss Kingo could see me now!
Rats!
No model number, no name, no nothing.
After I made it this far, might as well take a peek inside the cockpit!
Wow!
Howdy there!
Are you a jet fighter?
Whew! So shiny!
"Engine ignition!"
Isn't it nice?
Oh! What's going on?
This ain't looking good!
Hey!
Hey, stop, you stupid thing!
Goddammit! I said stop!
What? Emergency in block six?
Block all the gates.
Don't let anyone get away!
Shit!
Hey!
This way, Nao-chan! Hurry up!
Hurry!
M-My jacket got snagged!
Nao-chan!
N-Nao-chan!
Let's split for now.
Take care of the camera, Nao-chan.
Aoki-san, but I...
Ah, they're still after me!
They got me!
Firecrackers?
Hey!
You, the black guy!
I'll be your opponent!
Chinese?
Cretin! I'm Japanese!
Kamikaze! Got it?
Fuck you!
Bastard!
Oh no!
Jesus!
Never underestimate
the Japanese yakuza!
Boss Kingo taught me this secret technique himself! How'd you like that?!
Don't worry! I'll kick him out!
I owe a lot of money to this person!
I can't go home!
Oh?
I bet he lent money to your worthless parents to force you into prostitution!
Take it, you thief!
And keep the change.
Hold it! Give her a receipt.
Now get lost, you scum!
Oh! H-Hey, wait a minute.
30, 40, 50...
Perhaps I should stay
with that babe tonight?
Yes!
Oh yes...
Yes... Oh yes!
Keep going, keep going...
Yes...
I can't hold back...
Ah, yes!
Ah... No, I'm at my limit.
I've been abstaining for so long.
Now I've used it up all at once.
Forgive me, Department Chief.
Ugh... Everything looks so yellow...
S-Stop! What do you want?!
Well fucking done!
Stripping me naked and ransacking my room without permission.
How do you intend to make up for that?
Nao-chan? It's me, Aoki.
You made it out?
Yes.
But they summoned me to the consulate earlier.
It seems they found out somehow.
Oh, I've had some weirdos show up here too.
Huh?! Did they see it?
Don't you worry.
I hid it inside a birdhouse in Hyde Park.
Nicely done, Nao-chan!
Listen, you can't spill to anyone that you know me, all right?
Sure!
Good morning!
Hey, good morning.
Nao-chan, there's a letter for you from Japan.
Right, thanks.
Although it's just my dad's usual nagging, I imagine.
At the recent Todo Group conference for top executives,
it was decided to officially recognize Tanaka Kingo's underling,
Abe Naoya, as a member of the organization.
Wow! They did it!
May you safely carry out your duties in London, and upon your return to Japan,
dedicate yourself to the family
and work tirelessly for its success.
Come home soon, you dumbass!
Now I'm finally a full-fledged Todo Group member!
I can't wait to go home!
There you are, Nao-chan.
Whoa! Chief!
Come to my room for a moment.
Huh? Okay...
Excuse me.
This is Sasaki-san from the consulate.
Sir!
Did you sneak into the airbase
to steal the military's top secrets?
Military secrets?
Stop playing stupid.
I already know you did.
But why would I do that?
Aoki-kun already told me everything.
It's a false accusation.
I even have a good alibi.
Using a clueless boy like you was also part of Aoki-kun's plan.
He was working with a certain Japanese company
to steal the RAF's next-generation fighter aircraft development.
Not only that, you started
the prototype and destroyed it!
The damn thing did it itse—
Aw, damn!
By yourself, you've set the RAF's fighter program back by perhaps five years!
Fire!
But the British government's reputation is on the line if it's being pushed around
by a 16-year-old camera freak.
They've issued a notice for you
to leave the country within 24 hours.
Deportation?
Wow, jackpot!
Now I can go back to Japan!
Hey! Not so fast!
I did it, Boss!
Don't be sad
You were devastated
by today's happenings in the city
But brooding over it won't accomplish anything
You'll take it back tenfold tomorrow,
so don't be sad
If you can forgive, if only you can forgive
So that I can give you a special smile tomorrow
When we pass each other on the street
And then you realize I didn't intend to betray you
This town runs
At the drive-in, I heard the stories of the mailmen
I will continue to run today
For my loved ones whom I cannot replace
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad
Don't be sad
Don't let you down
Don't be sad, don't be sad