GAY BAR
Maurice
Wow!
President! You're actually prettier than us!
I'd bang you!
What do you think, Catherine?
You look gorgeous!
I thought so.
This is for you, Catherine.
President, I knew you were carrying a flame for me.
President, you can have all of Banana to yourself!
I don't want any of you to myself!
Banana-chan, hurry up.
Let me go!
Looks yummy.
Stop! I only want Catherine!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
It feels good!
This is Catherine, the main character.
Or rather, Okama Shinya, who was roped into this while drinking with his friends.
His friend Tanaka put him in makeup and women's clothes.
The female version of Shinya turned out to be beautiful.
The next day, Tanaka showed him a photo.
Shinya didn't realize he was the girl
in the photo and fell in love with her.
GAY BAR
Maurice
Shinya was desperate to meet the girl, so Tanaka decided to introduce him.
Tanaka took him to Maurice, a gay bar.
When Shinya realized that he was
the girl in the photo, he was incensed.
However, Tanaka sweet-talked him into working
at Maurice as an okama,
using the name Catherine.
Then, one day, he met Miki, a college girl who looked just like his female alter ego.
Shinya made every effort to nourish her friendship as Catherine.
Saint Anne Festival
Then at the school festival,
he met her as Okama Shinya.
Saint Anne Festival
As a man, he finally went on his first date with her.
The staff from Maurice
decided to go to the beach.
Tanaka arranged for Shinya to meet Miki
as both Shinya and Catherine.
On their last night, Shinya planned to pop Miki's cherry.
But Tarou had fallen for Catherine and butted in.
Instead of deflowering Miki,
Shinya lost his oral virginity to Tarou!
RAM
How unfortunate. The event brought Shinya to tears.
Okama Report 3
A Man's Resolve
It's my first date with Miki-chan
in a long time.
Second-year Student at Aoba College
Protagonist
Okama Shinya
We'll watch a movie, then dinner, then...
You're the best, Okama-san!
What's on your mind?
O-Oh, it's nothing.
First-year Student at Aoba College
Amamiya Miki
I know. You're worried about having enough time.
You've got work today.
Yeah. I'm sorry, Miki-chan.
I always have to leave early for work.
It's okay. I don't mind.
I just can't help admiring your spirit, Okama-san.
It must be hard to work part-time
as a security guard.
You have to study too.
Look after your health, okay?
You're so caring, Miki-chan.
But one of these days, we should have a proper feast!
I-I'd love that, Miki-chan.
GAY BAR
Maurice
To Catherine
What's this?
"I think about you every night. Tarou."
Former JSDF Soldier
Okama
Mimi
It's a love letter for Catherine from Tarou.
No way!
Former Pro Wrestler
Okama
Lily
Why are you fidgeting over there?!
Be upfront and tell her how you feel!
Yeah!
Lettering: I love you
Former Kickboxer
Banana
Former Figure Skater
Monroe
Tarou just confessed.
Her feelings are genuine.
You should go out on a date.
Yeah.
Maurice Bar Owner
Mama-rin
No self-respecting okama would go near a woman,
but they'd jump at this sort of chance!
I already have a girl I like!
I'm in love with that tenacity.
Okama at Maurice
Yamazaki Tarou
Real Estate
President Inoue
Oh, my! You're looking especially dangerous today, President!
That's right! I'm a treacherous and dangerous guy!
How was that?
I can't breathe!
Well, that was rude.
Welcome!
Mama-rin, long time no see.
Boss!
Here you go.
Thanks.
It's been a long time.
We haven't seen you
since that trip to the beach.
You're looking well.
Please let me work here, Mama-rin.
Boss!
Won't do. Call me Keiko, or no deal!
You've gotta be kidding me.
If I hire an okama this homely,
the bar's reputation will tank.
I'm sorry. At the moment, we're full up, Keiko-san.
Oh, dear. I really want to work here.
You're so mean, Mama-in.
Besides, don't you have a merry band of cute underlings?
I can't tell my underlings about this.
While I'm here, I'm an okama,
body and soul.
Right now, underlings are out of sight, out of mind!
Don't be so selfish.
No matter what?
No matter what!
If you're going to be so cold,
I'll resort to violence.
You'd use violence?!
That's right. I'll send in my underlings.
Anything but that.
Then listen to me.
Keiko's fire is burning hot.
Oh, my, Keiko-chan.
Dressing Room
Wh-What's going on in there?
Yes, yes! I'm gonna explode!
Maybe a wild boar broke in?
I can't believe it.
You're so dense, President.
That was wonderful, Mama-rin.
Was that Keiko-chan's voice?
Wanna have a drink?
No. If I don't return soon,
my underlings will worry. Later!
I'll see you off.
Hey, President, why don't we sneak out together too?
I'll only do it with Catherine.
Catherine.
Miki-chan!
Taxi
Take care.
Mama-rin, I enjoyed myself tonight.
Until next time. Kiss!
Taxi
What's wrong, Miki-chan?
I'm a little worried about Okama-san.
About me?
You see, he works part-time at night, so I don't get to see him often.
So I've been feeling kinda lonely.
I must be a monster.
I'm making the girl I like feel lonely.
What's wrong, Catherine?
Miki-chan, you'll have more fun if you have as many boyfriends as you can.
Tarou-chan!
Don't you agree, Catherine?
Your mouth today,
your bussy tomorrow.
You should have one for every eventuality.
But...
Well, you're still inexperienced,
so you don't understand that kind of fun.
But I have Catherine with me.
Catherine's an okama, not a real man.
But...
GAY BAR
Maurice
Here.
Thank you.
You haven't come here for a drink in a long time, Monroe-chan.
I guess not.
Who's that man?
He's a playboy who comes here to drink.
He's broken lots of women's hearts.
Unforgiveable.
Well then, this should be fun.
Whoa!
Hey, you alone?
My boyfriend dumped me recently.
Whoever'd dump a girl as pretty
as you can't call himself a real man.
Thank you.
Will you spend some time with me?
I'd love to.
Would you like to dine
at my favorite place?
All right.
Hotel Heaven
You're so beautiful. Turn around.
A guy?!
Help me!
Get back here!
You're every woman's worst nightmare!
Stop!
You'll enjoy it soon.
I... I... I...
I'm coming!
Hey, when can I see you again?
I can't live without you, Monroe.
Well, if you'll take me out for a drink, we can do it again.
Really?
I'll do it, even if I have to empty my account!
Damn it!
Miki-chan!
If... If you ask me, I'd gladly give it to you, Okama-san.
Incredible! You're incredible, Okama-san!
This feels great! Give me more!
More!
More. M-More.
More. More.
Hey! Shinya!
Open up!
Mo- Huh?
What is it at this hour?
I was having such a wonderful dream.
Listen, you!
You don't have to bang on the door. I'm coming.
Are you awake? It's me, Dan!
D-Dan-senpai?
Senpai!
Shinya's Senpai
Dan
Haven't lost your knack yet, Shinya.
Dan-senpai!
You look well, Okama.
Senpai! Long time no see!
Got yourself a pretty neat apartment, huh?
Yes. By the way, what are you up to now?
I'm traveling around Japan,
practicing martial arts.
That's awesome!
Anyway, I'd like exploit
your hospitality for a while.
I want to see if living in Tokyo
has changed you.
So... are you living your college life to the fullest?
Uh, yeah.
Doing some part-time job too?
Oh, no. Dan's a hard line macho man.
If he finds out I'm working as an okama,
I'll be dead before dawn!
Yeah, well, you see...
I work part-time at night.
At night?
A security guard,
or something like that?
Yeah, something like that.
Belt buckle: Man
That's a very manly part-time job.
Shinya's College Buddy
Tanaka Yasuyuki
Why do I have to show your senpai around Tokyo?
Well, because I'm asking, Tanaka.
I have to work at Maurice tonight.
Please. I'm begging you.
Why's your hand out?
Can't entertain in Tokyo
without appropriate funds.
Funds?
Well, if you don't want to,
then you don't...
All right. I'll pay!
Thanks.
Don't you dare tell him I work
as an okama at a gay bar.
Got it?
Signed and sealed!
I see. You're Shinya's college friend.
SAKE
Yuzuki
Look after him for me.
A Taste of Yuzuki
Leave it to me.
You're a strong drinker.
Another bottle over here, ma'am!
Coming!
Catherine.
Oh, Tarou-chan.
Here.
Please feel free to use this gesture of appreciation.
Thanks!
It looks great on you.
Really?
I bet it'd look great on Miki-chan.
Look here! I made it for you, Catherine!
I know.
But I think it'd look great
on Miki-chan too.
Right?
Look here!
I think it'd look great on Miki-chan.
Catherine?
You don't seem to grasp
a woman's feelings at all.
Tarou-chan's a guy.
Blockhead.
So many women. I think they're waiting for someone.
You've got sharp eyes, Dan-san.
They're street girls.
Look.
They're negotiating the price before they go to a hotel.
HOTEL
What's wrong?
Unforgivable! The moral decay! The corruption of the mind!
You're talking tough with your words,
but your body clearly
has a mind of its own.
Oh, no!
Disgraceful!
What's up with him?
I've still got lots of money.
Might as well give it a shot!
Hey, lady!
GAY BAR
Maurice
Hey, sis.
Wanna keep us company for a while?
P-Please, stop!
What's the big deal?
Maurice
Let me go, please!
She asked you to stop.
Let her go!
Who the hell are you?
GAY BAR
Maurice
Damn you!
GAY BAR
Maurice
The danger's gone, ma'am.
She's gone too.
VIDEO SHOP
She was particularly pretty.
You were attacked outside the bar?
But I'm perfectly fine.
Don't worry, Catherine.
Some guy came to my rescue.
Who was it?
I don't know.
I don't know him, but he was strong and very manly.
Very manly?
He beat them with karate.
Karate?
He was really strong.
And he wore a tank top too.
He had short hair and a square face.
Short hair? A square face?
His face looks like a sandal?
No way!
What is it, Catherine?
Oh, it's nothing.
Was he really as manly as you say?
Yes. He was really kind.
More so than Okama-san?
I guess so. Okama-san doesn't strike me as the manly type.
That's can't be true!
No, I... believe that his true manliness lies in his overflowing kindness. For sure!
But... aren't you just mistaking his cowardice for kindness?
Miki-chan, life means experiencing everything that's on offer.
You should go out with different kinds of men.
Tarou-chan!
What?
Do you think so too, Catherine?
Of course. She's had experience with all sorts of men.
Catherine belongs to me!
I won't let Miki-chan have her.
Welcome!
Mama-rin, I'm back.
Bathroom! I'm gonna barf!
Are you okay, Miki-chan?
That was rude. You're forcing Keiko to resort to violence.
See you, Catherine.
Bye-bye.
Dan-senpai.
GAY BAR
Maurice
I get it. The guy who saved Miki-chan was actually Dan-senpai.
He mistook me for Miki-chan.
It's here!
My eyes! I can't open my eyes!
It's a wonderful morning!
Aoba
College
Dan-senpai, please be reasonable and don't follow me to college.
You idiot! I want to be sure you're spending your college life as a true man!
Don't go breaking into the classrooms, okay?
I'm going to class.
Don't slack off, ya hear?
Eek!
Club
Warehouse
She's just my type.
Hey, Dan-san.
Tanaka-kun!
What's wrong? Those are some deep sighs.
W-Well...
Oh, Dan-san, she must've been Miki-chan.
Miki-chan?
That name's perfect for her.
Say, does she wear a blonde wig from time to time?
Oh, that must be Catherine. She works
at the place where you rescued Miki-chan.
She works at Maurice.
Catherine.
But they look so alike.
Are they sisters?
She's an okama.
What?! An okama?!
Because Catherine and Miki-chan are best buds, Miki-chan visits Maurice often.
I saved Miki-chan from some demons,
but she fell in with others!
Demons?
I must protect Miki-chan!
But why do you care about her so much, Dan-san?
W-Well...
No, instead, tell me everything you know about her!
You fell in love with a girl named Miki?!
A-And I'm going to save her from that den of demons!
Den of demons?
Yes. I'll save her from those okama,
who have betrayed the true path of men!
He means Maurice.
It must be my mission to rescue her from those abominations!
Miki-chan goes because she likes the place!
Among the monsters there,
one clings to her like a leech,
a guy using the name Catherine.
I bet this Catherine is the most rotten man who ever lived.
He's no longer a man. He poses as
a woman, and he talks like a woman,
He doesn't deserve to be called a man. He's subhuman. Decayed! Garbage!
I'm not garbage!
I-I wasn't talking about you.
Oh, right. I guess not.
GAY BAR
Maurice
Hey, listen to this.
On my way here, a five-year-old girl saw
my face, broke into tears, and ran away.
Wasn't that rude?
Even a bear would run away from you.
Shut up.
The President thinks I'm pretty,
so he wouldn't run away, would he?
As long as I can't see you, I'm fine.
Welcome, Miki-chan!
Catherine!
Stop!
Amazing!
What's wrong?
Spill it.
It's nothing.
The other day, Tarou-chan said
I should try dating different guys.
I think that's a good idea.
I want someone strong, like the guy who saved me the other day.
A guy who'd carry me
effortlessly in his arms.
Who'd say, "I'll protect you forever!"
What's that?! No way!
What do you mean?
I don't know why,
but it seems like a bad idea!
What's wrong, Catherine?
I'm already protecting you, aren't I, Miki-chan?!
Come what may, while I'm here,
no one will lay a finger on you.
I can carry you easily!
Uh-oh.
See?
Catherine's getting handsy with Miki-chan again.
Damn it!
Dummy!
Ow.
Oh, Catherine. Don't put your hand where it doesn't belong.
Move it away already!
Oh, you're awful, Catherine!
Welcome!
Senpai?
Oh, my. Welcome!
Y-You monsters!
Miki-san. I'm here to save you.
I'll protect Miki-chan!
Step aside.
Not going anywhere.
Who is that bugger?
He looks like a sandal.
Step aside!
Are you okay?
He sent you flying like a feather.
I'll protect you forever.
If I'm not mistaken,
you saved me the other night!
Yes. My name is Dan.
Let's go.
Wait!
You can't take Miki-chan away.
I'm going to protect her!
Your kind don't have
the right to promise that!
If you want to protect her,
then stand proudly as a man.
Men are supposed to protect women at all times!
Hold it!
Catherine couldn't discard her persona.
By the way, where are we going?
I'll take you home.
You idiot! Catherine, you idiot!
So that's why Dan-san's
becoming fixated on Miki-chan.
Can't you do something, Tanaka?
That's why I told you to hurry up
and bang her at least once!
Easier said than done.
Listen. Women are naturally predisposed to try dating multiple men.
They want to find out how different men make love.
Miki-chan's not like that.
You idiot.
Even Miki-chan needs some dick now and then.
One day, she'll try it "just once."
After that, she'll want it again and again! Like this, yeah!
Tanaka!
She's got a short skirt.
Pervert!
Medicine
GAY BAR
Maurice
Am I Okama Shinya or Catherine?
Am I a coward who can't be a man
in front of Miki-chan?
That's wrong! Wrong!
Nice throw.
Wrong! Wrong!
Dressing Room
It's me, Miki.
I'm coming in.
Dressing Room
Miki-chan!
Hi, Catherine!
M-Miki-chan!
Miki-chan, some brute took you away last night. I was worried about you.
Oh, that brute was Dan-san.
He's a real gentleman.
There's nothing to worry about.
But...
Thanks for your concern.
Really?
Hey, the bar's not open yet.
I wanted to tell you something.
What is it?
Tonight, I'm meeting Dan-san at the Opera Statue.
What the hell?!
I didn't think you were such an easy girl.
What about Okama-san?
Are you tired of him?!
No, it's not like that.
When I was thinking about dating different kinds of guys,
you said it was a good idea!
Shut the hell up!
Catherine, Catherine.
Don't pretend you've known each other forever!
Catherine, what's wrong with you?
I'm Okama Shinya.
You're not manly at all.
Wh-What was that for, Mama?
You couldn't be a proper man,
so you took it out on Miki-chan.
I misjudged you!
I don't care.
You're so pathetic.
Even I would make a better okama.
She's not wrong, you know.
But this doesn't feel right either.
If you're a true man,
you should go after Miki-chan
as Okama Shinya, before it's too late!
Well, you can't do it as you are now.
Nice.
Do it as a man!
They're meeting at the Opera Statue.
Good evening.
M-Miki-san!
G-Good evening.
Thank y-you for...
Wh-What's wrong?
Miki-chan's with senpai!
I didn't even get to hug her!
Sorry.
No, it's all right.
Let's go.
FIR TREE
FAMILY
GAY BAR
Maurice
Miki-chan hugged the guy who looked like a sandal?!
What should I do now?
Catherine, it's about time you
put Miki-chan behind you.
It's your duty to watch over them as Catherine.
Why do I have to be Catherine again?
To keep a close eye on them, you need to be Catherine.
Isn't that the course of action a real man would take?
A real man.
Mama's acting like a different person.
She just doesn't want Catherine to quit.
So that's what happened.
I was so sad, I ran away.
I won't forgive anyone
who makes you cry!
I'll kick the SOB.
You mustn't! Catherine only did it
because she's worried about me.
But I still like Catherine.
Catherine looks really down today.
President, Catherine's down in the dumps today. Just leave her alone over there.
I see.
Why did you start working as an okama, Tarou-chan?
I was a normal guy when I entered college. But then I fell in love with a woman!
When I was a sophomore...
I lost my head over a girl
who showed up at my regular pub.
She was beautiful, and her clothes accentuated her body perfectly.
At first glance, my dong went "bing bong!"
Let me guess! She turned out to be an okama?!
That's right! But I was dead sure she was a woman.
HOTEL ASS
One evening, we went to a hotel.
My flag was still flying high.
She was very assertive,
and her technique was unmatched.
She tickled me behind my balls.
I couldn't restrain myself,
so I unloaded without restraint!
But when it was my turn to do her,
I lifted her ass and...
Ding!
I saw a pair of precious things.
I thought, "What a stupid joke."
I broke up with her and
started dating real women.
I've actually banged a lot of women since then.
But they couldn't satisfy me.
For the life of me, I couldn't forget that okama's "behind the balls" technique.
So I ended up dating her again.
Since then, I've used makeup,
and as an okama, I proudly bring this blessing to other men.
Was it really that good? Do it to me.
No. I won't do it with anyone
but the one I love.
I'm still struggling to believe it.
Hey, okama are actually
superior to women.
Welcome!
Miki-chan.
Are you still mad at me, Catherine?
Watch over her as a man.
Not at all!
Sorry I yelled at you.
Oh, I'm glad.
A drink?
Sure!
I didn't think Miki-chan would come back.
She perked up as soon
as Miki-chan came back.
President, you have me, remember?
My perk just went down.
Cheers!
Are you still with Dan-san?
Yes.
I keep inviting him here
so he'll understand you,
but he said he wouldn't go
where "garbage" people go.
But I told him you're not like that.
Oh, Miki-chan.
So Catherine's not garbage, but I am?
Th-That's not what I meant.
Tarou-chan.
So have you arranged your next date, Miki-chan?
I wouldn't exactly call it a date, but yes.
Miki-chan, you-
Watch over her as a man.
I-I'm happy for you.
Catherine just won't give up on Miki-chan.
Say, does Dan-san live alone?
Yes. He said he lives alone
in an apartment.
Actually, he's freeloading at my place.
He said he does all the laundry and cleaning himself.
Actually, I do all of that.
Hey, Miki-chan, why don't you go to his apartment and make him some dinner?
No way!
Tarou-chan!
Miki-chan, you shouldn't go to a man's house alone.
Miki-chan, if you visit Dan-san's room, you'll find out what kind of life he leads, right?
You could learn a lot.
Miki-chan, don't.
Dan-san's a real gentleman, Catherine.
I'll go visit his apartment.
M-Miki-chan.
As a man... As a man...
A man and a woman, alone in a room.
Dan-san, it's too soon.
I can't take it anymore!
Dan-san, you're incredible!
Catherine will be mine.
GAY BAR
Maurice
I almost forgot, almost forgot.
Catherine.
Catherine?
Leave me alone!
Do you like Miki-chan that much?
I'm going on a date with Miki-san today.
Please don't make so much noise early in the morning.
Oh, my bad, by bad.
You're really grumpy today.
Miki-chan's so direct.
Well, she wouldn't cook for Dan-san after just a date or two,
no matter how much Tarou -chan insists.
You should just revert to being Okama Shinya and go out with her yourself.
Yeah.
However!
Even so, if Miki-chan ends up
choosing Dan-san over you,
you should give up on her.
Give up on her?
GAY BAR
Maurice
Oh, President!
It's true!
You're lying!
No, I'm not!
Miki-chan!
Here you are.
Thanks.
Your date ended quickly today.
Yeah. He left early, saying he needs to prepare for tomorrow.
"Prepare for tomorrow"?
What's that about?
I agreed to go to his apartment
to cook for him.
What's wrong?
Sorry. I just got a little dizzy.
You should get some rest, Catherine.
All right.
Catherine!
I'll keep you company until she feels better, Miki-chan.
She's just anemic.
A common thing for a girl.
Catherine's a woman, right.
Are you going out with Dan-san?
Yes.
Tomorrow evening, I promised to make dinner at his place.
So you know where Dan-san lives?
Shibuya. Oh, he drew me a map.
Here.
That's a nice neighborhood.
Oh, it's near the station.
Komei Apts,
2nd Floor, Room 2
Komei Apartments, second floor, room 2.
Miki-chan lives in the Aoba dormitories.
And Dan-san has never met me in person.
What's wrong?
Nothing at all.
Dan-san's apartment is close to mine.
You live in that area too?
You should watch over her as Catherine.
That's what a real man would do.
If that happens,
you should give up on her.
Shinya, breakfast is ready!
You made breakfast?
What's gotten into you?
I feel bad for making you
prepare it every day.
Oh, you have work tonight, don't you?
Yeah, I guess.
That's right. Miki-chan's coming tonight.
Why do you ask?
Well, you're always helping me out.
I think I should treat you to dinner
if you're not working.
I could always take the night off.
You idiot! Real men can't
afford to take time off!
Yeah, right. Just be honest.
You want to bring a woman home.
All right.
If a single woman visits
a man who is also single...
That can only mean one thing.
It's dinging!
Yes, coming!
Hi, Miki-san.
I'm Miki's college friend, Mako.
I see. So Miki-scan couldn't
make it tonight.
She didn't have your number,
so she asked me, very sincerely, to come in her place.
Shinya, you never told me your number!
She said she felt bad for letting down a gentleman as kind as you.
That's all right.
And so, although I'm not as gifted a chef,
I'll make you dinner instead.
You don't have to.
She's so sexy!
You can watch TV while you wait, okay?
All right.
I'd rather watch you than some TV.
There we go.
I can't reach it.
Let me help you.
Sorry to trouble you.
Can you get a plate from the top shelf?
Mako-san! I can't take it anymore! Can't!
What are you doing?!
Catherine.
Miki-chan.
I thought you were at Dan-san's house.
Didn't Tarou-chan tell you?
He's not here yet.
Really?
Tarou-chan called at four and said that she saw Dan-san at the station.
Dan-san said, "My grandfather had
an attack, so I have to go back home."
"Because Miki-chan lives in the women's dorm, it's hard to call her."
"Please give her this message."
Something's not right.
Senpai's grandfather is dead.
When he came to Maurice,
Tarou-chan wasn't here.
They couldn't have met.
What's wrong, Catherine?
It's nothing.
Senpai hates okama,
but he asked one to do him a favor.
Where did Tarou-chan see him?
Near Shibuya.
When she saw this map to Dan-san's, she said she also lives near there.
Tarou-chan lives in Nerima.
Is Tarou-chan there now?
If Dan-san finds out
Tarou-chan's an okama...
Tarou-chan's in trouble!
Catherine, I'll go with you!
Wh-What's going on?
Dan-san, stop! What about Miki?!
Right now, you're the only thing I see.
No.
You bastard. You're an okama?!
Unacceptable! You piece of shit!
As a man, a man...
Behind the balls...
Why does it feel so good?
Behind my balls. Behind my balls.
It feels so good!
Oh, no!
Dressing Room
I want you to understand.
I did this so Miki-chan wouldn't get hurt,
and so Catherine wouldn't get even more depressed.
That's why I did it.
Thanks, Tarou-chan.
Miki-chan, you should take better care of yourself.
I know. But it feels like I can't trust men anymore.
You shouldn't go that far!
Somewhere, there's a person
who truly loves you.
Right?
Right.
Still, I didn't anyone but the person I love to experience "behind the balls."
Tarou-chan.
Does it really feel that good, behind your balls?
I'd love to try it one day.
President, I'm quite good at it.
You're gonna crush them!
Behind the balls. Behind the balls.
Behind. Behind-hind-hind.
No!
No way.
That's not right. It's like my brain itches,
and I can't stop it!
I'm trying to scratch it,
but I can't do it.
Yes! That's what I must be searching for!
Huh?
Senpai moved out already?
TO SHINYA
It's from Dan-senpai!
Shinya, thanks for looking after me.
I've reached enlightenment as a man, so I bid you farewell.
Did you finally come to your senses, Senpai?
GAY BAR
Maurice
Please. Just once, Tarou-chan, come on! Let me feel "behind the balls" too!
Not happening. I won't do it again.
Unless it's for you, Catherine.
Oh, my! If I agree, I'll never be able to love a woman again!
Oh, we have a new employee with us today.
Come on, usher her in!
Tama the Geisha! Come on in!
I'm Tama the Geisha.
Dan-senpai!
Dan-san.
What a filthy geisha. She's so huge,
she can't even tie her sash properly.
Look closer, President.
Look at the loincloth.
I'm shocked!
Turns out his "enlightenment as a man" meant becoming an okama. Oh, my.
GAY BAR
Maurice
Should I stay as Catherine,
or should I be a man again?
I might have to make a decision soon.
The End
saa minna
Okay, everyone
ganbatte
Good luck
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
aaa...
Aaaah...
haran no toukyou janguru de (a sore)
In the wild Tokyo jungle (Oh, there!)
yamato nadeshiko hanazakari (a yada)
Proper maidens are blossoming (Oh, my!)
biiru nonde juusu nonde
Drink some beer, drink some juice
yopparapatte binkarakatte odamari yo
yopparapatte binkarakatte Oh, you hush!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song
saa minna
Okay, everyone
ganbatte
Good luck
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
aaa...
Aaaah...
kyou mo karorii yoku totte (ma nani)
You had a lot of calories today (No, what?)
haran no ten nai myouni chuui shite (a yada)
But the busy store grabbed your attention (Oh, my!)
dango kutte kyuuri kutte
Eat a dango, eat a cucumber
yopparapatte binkarakatte odamari yo
yopparapatte binkarakatte Oh, you hush!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song
Translation
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
Editing & Typesetting
Collectr
Song Translation,
Timing,
QC,
Encoding
anonymous
Presented by
Okizari Fansubs