LAKE
Minami St
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
EVE
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
Game Center
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KARAOKE
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
PUFFNON
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
KING
Game Center
LOVE
PUB
Okama-kun's here.
Hey, Shinya, over here.
Hi!
You're late!
Sorry about that.
I got held up at work.
Well, have a seat.
Okay.
Second-year Student at Aoba College
Protagonist
Okama Shinya
Today was "The End"
for my part-time job.
Gotta find a new one soon.
I see. Then we're gonna get boozed up tonight!
Shinya's College Buddy
Tanaka Yasuyuki
Yeah.
All right. Once again, cheers!
Okama Report
The Destined Transformation
Tanaka, willya lemme know
if you spot a good part-time gig?
Okay.
Why're you playing
Tamasaburo with me?
Note: A Kabuki actor
who specialized in female roles.
That's an old joke!
You'd make a nice girl
with makeup on, doncha think?
Don't be silly. I'm not like that.
Fortitude
He'd make a perfect night butterfly!
Do it!
I'm just messing with you.
Stop making fun of me.
Keiko! Put some on him.
Okay.
Look at me, Okama-kun.
For real?
More! More!
Shinya-chan.
I'll put some eyeshadow on.
Mister, lend us a woman's wig,
so we can take a pic.
Yes, sir.
All right. The transformation's complete.
Glasses away!
No way! He looks stunning!
He's prettier than me!
You're...
He's cute!
L-Looking good!
AOBA COLLEGE
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love. Yes. That's what love is.
Hey.
Why are you crying, Okama?
Stop calling me by my last name.
It annoys me.
Tanaka, I think...
I'll go look for true love.
If you want love...
you'll need a car first.
And you'll need money, right?
You're so pathetic.
That's why you have trouble getting girls.
You should read this book. Love is about sincerity.
Tch. What's next, "devotion"?
Thoughtless guys like you are so shallow.
That's why I drown my troubles.
Is he still intoxicated?
I drank too much last night.
I don't remember a thing.
Huh? You don't remember?
Did I do something bad?
Well...
What do you think about this girl?
BOWLING
She's my ideal woman!
She's perfect, Tanaka!
I've finally found her!
You idiot. That's you.
I-If I get to meet her,
I might at last find true love!
You'll introduce me to her, won't you?
I really can't tell him the truth, can I?
I-I'll introduce you.
Yes, you're truly my best friend, Tanaka!
GAY BAR
Maurice
Welcome, Tanaka-kun.
This is my buddy, Shinya.
Okama at Maurice
Yamazaki Tarou
Welcome.
You mentioned him on the phone.
Just wait here for a bit.
Hey, she's not the woman in the photo.
Well, he's a cross-dressing pro.
A cross-dresser?
What now? You're into that?
Thing is, if you want to meet the girl in the picture,
you'll have to do a few things.
First, you need to cross-dress.
Asshole! I know my name's "Okama,"
but any joke should have its limits! You...
Hold up there!
Chill, man.
Let... Let go!
Would you please calm down?
Have a seat.
Tanaka, what are you planning?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
What matters now is that Okama-kun has such lovely skin.
Your hands are so hairy.
You didn't have to point that out!
There. All done.
Dressing
Room
Wow. You're cute.
Really?
Nice!
Now you'll let me meet the lady in the photo, won't you?
L-Let's do it, face-to-face.
Here we go!
Nice to meet you.
I-I'm Okama.
Nice to-
T-Tanaka!
Defying his name, Okama-kun is a paragon of masculinity,
but just one drink, and voila! Look at this.
Isn't that scary?
This must be his latent desire.
Tanaka, you bastard! My latent desire?!
When did you take that photo?!
At the party last night.
You have to face the facts, Okama!
You said you wanted
a woman, didn't you?!
The key to that is money!
First, you need to make money.
To do that, you should leverage your special talent!
Now that you're dressed, you're ready to start!
He's right. Let's work together.
Work here? At a gay bar?
I'm Yamazaki Tarou.
Nice to meet you.
Give it a try, Okama.
You need a part-time job.
You'll rake in the dough here.
Damn you, Tanaka!
You tricked me!
Don't you care about me
as a friend at all?!
Then, tell me: what is love?
You read a book because you didn't know, did you?
You should know by now.
Love isn't about theory.
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
LOVE . . .
What is true love?
Love
It's about action!
Love isn't as simple as you think it is!
There are many forms of love!
If you don't even understand that,
you have no hope of finding a woman.
Tanaka, you really think so?
You moron!
Don't you trust me at all?
All right. I'll give it a try, Tanaka.
Lovely.
Maurice
Lucky me! I got 30,000 yen for referring him!
GAY BAR
Maurice
I'm saying, I pushed him and then grabbed his leg tight.
Former Pro Wrestler
Okama
Lily
We struggled, crotch against crotch.
It felt great like that, but then we fucked.
Former JSDF Soldier
Okama
Mimi
Yeah, yeah.
Once, a boy so cute I couldn't resist enlisted in my corps.
I tried sneaking into his room,
but they made a big fuss
over that and dismissed me!
You know, I've had enough of all of you.
Real Estate
President Inoue
Maurice Bar Owner
Mama-rin
Don't say that, President.
President! You reminded me.
We got a young cutie in today.
That sounds wonderful!
Send him in, now!
Come on in!
Welcome!
Okay!
I'm Catherine the Commando!
So cute!
You stink! Get out of the way!
Now, now, please sit next to me.
Yes, sir.
What's the big idea?!
You perverted old man!
O-Oh, my! You're so naughty, President!
So cute!
President, is Catherine
your favorite now?
GAY BAR
Maurice
Well, it's not so bad.
Shinya.
Hi, Tanaka.
Hop in.
That one's juicy!
She's not that nice.
Good for a side affair, maybe?
What's the big deal?
A "side affair"? I think your standards are too high.
Not really. I'm looking for a girl
who's like the image in my head.
Recently, I've set her up as my ideal.
What kind of girl is that?
A girl who resembles me, I guess.
Okama, shouldn't you consider
quitting that part-time job?
Well, it did get on my nerves at first.
But right now, I'm grateful to you.
When I'm Catherine,
something strange happens.
I feel that I'm beginning to understand how a woman feels.
A-Anyway, I'll take you to Maurice.
GAY BAR
Maurice
Getting you used to your job, Catherine?
A monster!
How cruel! Catherine, are you really that startled by my face?
I'm sorry. You just took me off guard.
More importantly, Catherine, look at my new panties.
See, see, it's a teddy-chan.
What're you looking at? Catherine, you pervert!
Catherine, would you like
to eat some sushi tonight?
President, I don't think that's what you mean.
You just want to eat me, don't you?
H-How can you say that?!
I'm hungry. I could go for some abalone now...
Liar. Your tuna is telling me
all about your real motives.
You noticed my tuna, huh?
Caught me red-handed...
You'd handle yourself here?!
Oh, you're so lewd, President!
Catherine, you're such a tease too!
Catherine, we'll entertain the President.
A bunch of college girls are here.
Go take care of them yourself.
Okay.
Me too!
I'm getting excited.
First-year Student at Aoba College
Amamiya Miki
Is this for real?
I'm not looking in a mirror, am I?
A drink!
Here you go.
Catherine is so lovely.
Welcome!
I'm Catherine!
No way!
Miki's spitting image!
We really are like twins!
Cheers!
But really, you are alike!
Your hairdo, your ribbons...
Even how our eyes look!
And maybe here too!
Oh, cut it out, you perv!
Big deal!
Cheer up, President.
They really do look like twins.
That's right. Catherine
and I are long-lost sisters!
But Catherine's an okama.
Just an okama?
How pitiful.
Hey, Catherine, no matter
what anyone says, we're siblings, okay?
We should get to know each other and be like real siblings.
Okay!
Catherine!
He's crying.
I see. You're gonna quit
your job as an okama.
Well, I've found someone I like.
I-It's not a guy, is it?
It's a girl, a girl!
That's a relief.
Where'd you meet her?
At Maurice.
So you've decided to bang her?
Don't be silly.
I don't want to fool around.
You might super serious, but girls only go to okama bars to fool around!
She's probably fucking lots of guys. Pow, pow, pow...
Tanaka!
Miki-chan's not that kind of girl!
Take it back!
All right.
Oh, Miki-chan!
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Catherine, well, we're siblings, aren't we?
Yeah.
I need some advice from you.
Can we meet somewhere this Sunday?
What's wrong, Miki?
Let's talk over there.
Nah, I can't do it here.
We have to be alone.
Here, I've drawn a map
to a coffee shop for you.
Hey, you'll be there, won't you?
Yeah! Of course I will!
That's wonderful. See you there.
Be careful, Miki-chan.
Bye-bye.
Catherine...
How cruel!
You see... I've met someone I like.
Well, if I tell you this, maybe you'll think I'm a slut, but I'll risk it anyway.
And well, I want the two of us
to stay in a hotel and watch
the night view of the Bay Bridge from the hotel lounge.
Catherine, wanna go there together?
Me?!
A girl who was with me at Maurice goes with her boyfriend to hot springs and all...
Is this a proposal?
If we're going there alone, it's a sure thing.
Make love to me, Catherine.
I can't wait!
You're incredible, Catherine!
Listen, Catherine.
Wh-What is it?
Come to the Bay Bridge with me.
Please!
Certainly! I'd follow you anywhere!
You sure you want to go with me?
Yeah!
I can't wait.
Sign: Chinatown
You're going beyond
The world of love
Your charmed heart
Sets out on a journey
We watched those mysterious
Ripples of life
The sun's setting already.
Sooner with each passing day.
Those circulating days have
Still, the night is young.
Wrapped around my neck
You have so much energy.
I won't let you sleep tonight.
Th-That too!
They will be erased
No way! He's hitting on
someone like that?
Like Catherine in the mirror
Love, love
begins...
Yokohama Bay Bridge
Wow, Catherine,
look, look!
Incredible!
It's so pretty!
I've never seen anything so pretty!
The Bay Bridge is irresistible at night!
Hey, Catherine, you think so too?
Hey, Catherine.
I've wanted to visit a place like this.
Thank you, Catherine!
I love you!
Catherine, should we have dinner soon?
Yeah.
Then, I'll take a refreshing shower first.
What's wrong, Catherine?
It's nothing.
Do I look pretty, Catherine?
Yeah, very pretty.
Then, come join me soon, okay?
Y-Yeah.
She said she loves me,
and that's something,
but she okay's with us being naked?
Apparently, women become very bold in front of men they like.
Quietly. Sneak, sneak.
Hey, Catherine.
Busted!
Catherine, hurry and join me in here.
Huh? Yeah, sure.
Seagull
Say, Catherine, have you ever met someone you like?
Well, I...
Wow, really? Me too.
How far have you gone?
How far? Well, we're going out,
starting today.
You got me wrong! I didn't mean that kind of "someone."
How far with your boyfriend?
Well, about that...
Say, doesn't your world have first, second, third, and home base?
Huh? Why, yes.
I see.
Damn it.
Why did she bring this up?
But doing it for the first time
must be scary.
Not at all. Everyone has
a first time, sooner or later.
You have to give it your all!
I see. Good advice.
You're blushing too, Catherine!
It hurts! It hurts so much!
Yes! Squeeze me harder! Harder!
It hurts.
Hey, wanna go back to our room?
Yeah.
I can't wait.
That felt great!
Oh, Catherine!
I can't wait!
What's wrong, Catherine?
Oh...
I'll get it.
Hello?
Yes, that's me.
Okay.
Okay, I've got it.
Room 709, right?
I need to go out for a while, Catherine.
Where are you going at this hour?
My boyfriend's just arrived here.
Boyfriend?!
You see, my parents would be worried if I wasn't with another girl.
That's why I asked you to tag along and be with me.
But you shouldn't go out at night!
Catherine, thanks for everything.
I'm glad I confided in you about this.
Today, I'm joining everyone else as an adult!
B-But that's...
I still need to refresh my makeup.
D-Damn it!
Fine!
Listen, Miki.
Yes?
I don't wanna be left all alone in the room.
I'll go out and play around too.
Sorry for bothering you, Catherine.
See you soon.
Damn it!
I won't let him take Miki away!
709. 709. 709.
709! 709! 709!
709! 709!
There, found it.
It's me.
Come on in. It's open.
Yo, you're early.
Miki's Boyfriend
Hashimoto Takayuki
Lose the clothes and c'mere.
Hurry up and get over here!
Hey, do you really love me?
Yeah.
Miki, you said you'd finally be ready today.
Well, I'm all ready to go, okay?
Wait. I need to get in the mood.
I can't let him add Miki
to his corrupt collection!
You're hesitating after coming this far?
Ow!
Hey! What the hell was that for?!
My dick!
Die!
Even so, I'm still angry.
I know.
Ha! Serves you right!
She's beautiful!
Huh?
Hey, Takayuki.
It's me, Miki.
Really, you fell asleep?
Hey, I'm sorry I'm late.
Wake up. C'mon.
How... How could you?
How could you?!
Red.
Shoe
I didn't ask for another one yet.
No, it's from the gentleman by the counter.
S-Spare me your conceited crap.
Allow me.
Are you alone?
Care to join me for a drink?
I'm glad I came to Yokohama.
I've met such a lovely woman.
The asshole's hitting on me.
Let's have a toast to our first meeting.
S-Sure.
This might be interesting. I'll play along.
It'll be a nice diversion.
Okay, then. Cheers!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I think I'm drunk already.
Whatever will I do?
Oh, that's all right.
It's cheap by English standards.
You must hate me now.
Of course not.
No. Not here.
Then if not here, let's do it in my room!
Of course.
I'm sorry, Catherine.
I'm going home without you.
A thousand pardons!
Mama, save me from his balls!
Stop fucking around!
Weren't you hitting on me?
I-I didn't know you were a man!
Mama! Help!
I'm too young to die here!
You rotten pervert!
I regret everything!
Playboys like you are a pain in the ass!
You'll make true love go extinct!
My youth is over!
H-Hey! He pierced me! Take it out!
For the next lecture on Japanese history from the Mirasaki Shibiku era, read...
Shinya. You've been
studying hard lately.
What'dya mean?
Last night, I stopped by Maurice.
I expected you'd be there.
I took the night off.
I was in my apartment.
I should've visited you at your apartment.
Sorry about that.
Miki-chan!
Th-That's all right.
We go to the same college!
She's one cute chick.
She's Miki-chan. She said she likes me.
Tanaka, clean this up for me.
H-Hey!
So she dumped you?
You shouldn't be chasing a girl
who can dump a guy so casually.
Something's been bothering me lately.
You were there as a man, right?
Hey, for this year's School Festival,
how about we visit the dorms instead?
The dorms?
You mean, the central dorms?
Yes. The girls' dorms, off limits for guys!
They'd never let a stray like you in.
Besides, I can go there anytime.
I'd rather hit on girls
at the School Festival.
Hit on girls? Now that's unusual.
You know, the last day of the festival will be open to the public,
so people from the town will be there.
For real?
Either way, the dorms'll be full of chicks desperate to hook up with a guy!
My senpai said that he was swarmed like hotcakes last year!
What?! Like hotcakes?! Really?!
Yeah! Count me in! I'm going too!
All right, my quest
for true love starts now.
You haven't changed one bit, after all.
GAY BAR
Maurice
You look dangerous again today, President.
What do you think? Am I cute?
Probably even cuter than Catherine.
But that look doesn't suit you at all!
Hey! Look who's talking!
Well, let's call it a draw.
I see.
Pardon me a moment, President.
Staff Room
What's wrong, Catherine?
You took a day off without calling us.
We were worried about you.
Sorry.
Did you find someone you like?
Miki-chan, right?
I've been through that too.
But once I chose this life, I didn't fall in love with a woman ever again.
You're standing at the fork
in that road now.
Mama.
It's all right. No need to say anything.
Think it over and choose for yourself.
Okay.
I won't let Miki-chan
have Catherine! I swear!
Saint Anne Festival
If you're one tile away from bingo, let us know with a "Riichi."
Shout out your "bingo" loudly!
Now, let's get started!
B-17.
Whoa!
G-31.
N-9.
Oh, Riichi!
Saint Anne Festival
Anyone other Riichi?
Also Riichi!
Saint Anne Festival
Quite a lot of you, apparently.
Then, let's keep going.
Next... I-30.
Here it comes!
Bingo!
Bingo.
Thank you.
I got a bingo too.
Miki-chan...
Congratulations.
What's your name?
Amamiya Miki.
All right.
And this young man?
Shinya.
What's your last name?
Huh?
Okama!
He's so okama!
Are you really?
No, nothing of the sort...
Well, let's leave this mystery unsolved.
Miki-san wins pair of tickets to fly
from Tokyo to Sapporo and back.
In addition, Okama Shinya-san wins a coupon
for two people to stay at Sapporo's Flower Hotel.
Wow.
Okama-san, who will you take with you?
Who?
I haven't decided yet.
How about your girlfriend?
As if he had one!
That was rude! Is he your friend?
Yeah. But what he said is true.
Miki-san, you'll bring your boyfriend, won't you?
It's so sudden.
I haven't thought about it.
Okay. Please collect your prizes from the reception desk on your way out.
Miki-san and Okama-san
are our winners!
Now it's time for your last chance.
Who will be the last winner?
Let's resume the game!
G-36.
Anyone get a bingo with that?
No one?
Tanaka. I'm going somewhere else.
Let's move on.
B-19!
Y-Yeah.
I-34!
Lovely...
I can't stop looking!
Miki-chan was so happy.
It boggles my mind.
Don't tell me...
He woke up before Miki-chan arrived?
Shit!
Oh, you again.
Miki-chan!
M-Me again. Are you alone?
I thought I'd help out
at the food booth, but...
Have we met before?
Huh? Oh, at the library!
Oh, of course.
Sorry about that.
Still, Shinya-san, are you really a cross-dresser?
No, it was a misunderstanding. My last name is "Okama."
No way!
Sorry. You're so honest, Shinya-san.
What do you mean?
You see, most guys, if they'd been asked about it, would've said,
"Of course I'm going
with my girlfriend!"
I guess so.
Then, are you going
with your boyfriend?
I don't have one.
To tell the truth, I had one until recently, but we broke up.
You broke up?
So my plan worked.
It's a long story.
Oh, what am I doing? I just unloaded my personal problems on you.
Huh? N-no, that's all right.
Well, then...
Love is about action!
Um... Miki-san?
Yes?
If it's all right with you...
Will you meet me this Sunday?
Yes, I'd be glad to.
How about the Bronze Dream Coffee Shop,
outside Shibuya Station, at 10?
The Bronze Dream at 10, right?
Yes.
See you.
Hooray!
This must be true love!
Love really is about sincerity. And action!
I can't let Tanaka
see me like this.
He'll laugh at me again.
I saw it.
You're so quick to lose your head!
He was right here.
Hamakura
I have something to tell you.
Back when I still had feelings for that guy,
I went on a trip with him.
Thinking about it now,
I don't know why I did it,
but back then, I promised him a night together.
When the time came, I saw what he was really like, and I got scared and left.
Why were you scared?
Because it was supposed to be
my first time, but what he... what he did...
Girls only have one first time, so when we yield to a guy,
we want him to be romantic and gentle.
When I went to see him, he had been fooling around with another woman.
How cruel!
That's really cruel!
What an asshole!
Doesn't he know what love is?!
Miki-chan, I'm glad you found out
sooner rather than later.
Really, Shinya-san?
Yeah. If I'm sure of anything,
it's that I'm not that kind of guy.
That's wonderful to know.
I feel a lot better now, somehow.
I'm glad you came out unscathed.
You believe me?
To the very last word.
My trick worked out perfectly.
Shinya-san.
I'm sure Catherine would agree with you too.
Catherine?
She's my best friend.
Next time, I'll introduce you to her.
She's a really nice girl.
She went with me on that trip.
But... after my boyfriend called me,
I didn't see her again.
Because of what happened, I couldn't meet Catherine, and I went home by myself.
She's probably mad at me for it.
No. I'm certain that girl, Catherine,
doesn't think you did anything wrong.
Oh, no. I forgot about Catherine.
Still, she's my best friend.
If we sit together, it's like we're siblings!
She means the world to me.
Anyhow, I should apologize the next time I see her.
I want to introduce you to her.
Hey, what will you do with the hotel stay you won at the School Festival?
Actually, I wanted to go with you.
I'm so happy!
What about you?
Who should I bring, I wonder?
Hey! That's not fair!
And so, Miki and I are getting along exceptionally well right now.
But how will I handle the double role of Catherine and me for Miki?
Either way, I'll move forward,
because love is about action!
Next Episode Preview
The glistening sea at the height of summer.
Strange okama dancing on the stage.
What exciting developments will happen next time?
Okama Report, Part 2.
We hope you enjoy it!
Episode 2
We hope you enjoy it  !!
Translation
Moho Kareshi
Perevodildo
saa minna
Okay, everyone
Song Translation
anonymous
ganbatte
Good luck
Timing
anonymous
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
Editing &
Typesetting
Collectr
aaa...
Aaaah...
haran no toukyou janguru de (a sore)
In the wild Tokyo jungle (Oh, there!)
QC
anonymous
yamato nadeshiko hanazakari (a yada)
Proper maidens are blossoming (Oh, my!)
Encoding
anonymous
biiru nonde juusu nonde
Drink some beer, drink some juice
Presented by
Okizari
Fansubs
yopparapatte binkarakatte odamari yo
yopparapatte binkarakatte Oh, you hush!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
aaa...
Aaaah...
kondo otoko ni umarete mo (e nani)
Even if I was born a man (Say what?)
onnagokoro no ohimesama (ma yada)
I'll still be a sentimental princess (Oh, my!)
hiiru haitte zouri haitte
Wear high heels, wear thong sandals
yopparapatte binkarakatte hottoite
yopparapatte binkarakatte Let me be!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song
saa minna
Okay, everyone
ganbatte
Good luck
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
aaa...
Aaaah...
kyou mo karorii yoku totte (ma nani)
You had a lot of calories today (No, what?)
haran no ten nai myouni chuui shite (a yada)
But the busy store grabbed your attention (Oh, my!)
dango kutte kyuuri kutte
Eat a dango, eat a cucumber
yopparapatte binkarakatte odamari yo
yopparapatte binkarakatte Oh, you hush!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song
kama kama kama kama kama kama kama kama
Crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing, crossing
aaa...
Aaaah...
koi no yamai wo naosu nara (e nani)
If you want to cure your lovesickness (Say what?)
minna kirei na hana ni nare (ma yada)
Everyone blossom into pretty flowers (Oh, my!)
paddo shite ruuju nutte
Wear some pads, put on lipstick
yopparapatte binkarakatte hottoite
yopparapatte binkarakatte Let me be!
okama ondo de shanshan no shan
Let's clap our hands to the okama song